[
    {
        "question": "687 × 2,395=？",
        "answer": 6.2162622548101325
    },
    {
        "question": "48,936,673 ÷ 3,452,615=？",
        "answer": 1.151486287141649
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 6,426=？",
        "answer": 4.506910725551518
    },
    {
        "question": "248,272,147 ÷ 877,103=？",
        "answer": 2.4518774034798234
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 26,047=？",
        "answer": 5.11472771437181
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 18,774,918=？",
        "answer": 7.75069930360624
    },
    {
        "question": "93,082,320 ÷ 1,046,944=？",
        "answer": 1.9489437468636888
    },
    {
        "question": "34,631,387 ÷ 27,074,663=？",
        "answer": 0.10690682591338717
    },
    {
        "question": "5,090,904 ÷ 1,214,957=？",
        "answer": 0.622233999983708
    },
    {
        "question": "314 × 396=？",
        "answer": 5.0946248339987275
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 33,972=？",
        "answer": 5.610302361460352
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 13,134,789=？",
        "answer": 7.595544355300319
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 697=？",
        "answer": 4.599107633770501
    },
    {
        "question": "82,108 ÷ 3,954=？",
        "answer": 1.31734880866544
    },
    {
        "question": "7,693 × 614=？",
        "answer": 6.674264103578915
    },
    {
        "question": "13,137,203 ÷ 380,764=？",
        "answer": 1.5378470302920544
    },
    {
        "question": "65,549,290 ÷ 339,513=？",
        "answer": 2.2857115838408912
    },
    {
        "question": "679 × 9,181=？",
        "answer": 6.794759761672293
    },
    {
        "question": "103,649 ÷ 2,067=？",
        "answer": 1.7002246397729057
    },
    {
        "question": "11,308,179 ÷ 74,403=？",
        "answer": 2.181802227361014
    },
    {
        "question": "1,220,208 ÷ 6,806=？",
        "answer": 2.253541923253131
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 998,021=？",
        "answer": 6.601199670980231
    },
    {
        "question": "399,436 ÷ 5,424=？",
        "answer": 1.8671275231328046
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 949,399=？",
        "answer": 6.676418774277122
    },
    {
        "question": "173 × 7,194=？",
        "answer": 6.095016536611288
    },
    {
        "question": "144,481,699 ÷ 24,226=？",
        "answer": 3.775531127102024
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 25,860=？",
        "answer": 5.889749775264038
    },
    {
        "question": "388,153,373 ÷ 4,041=？",
        "answer": 4.982514514033144
    },
    {
        "question": "321 × 505,554=？",
        "answer": 8.21027258332989
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 58,238=？",
        "answer": 4.765206452090041
    },
    {
        "question": "7,232 ÷ 1,749=？",
        "answer": 0.6164686079886303
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 306=？",
        "answer": 3.184691430817599
    },
    {
        "question": "688,554 ÷ 147,994=？",
        "answer": 0.6676938970645331
    },
    {
        "question": "140,945,923 ÷ 2,267=？",
        "answer": 4.793600997866056
    },
    {
        "question": "101,026,996 ÷ 13,042,726=？",
        "answer": 0.889069068827624
    },
    {
        "question": "305 × 849=？",
        "answer": 5.413207529590738
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 12,217,655=？",
        "answer": 8.23311589311593
    },
    {
        "question": "22,667,643 ÷ 2,437=？",
        "answer": 3.968550834995121
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 45,288,080=？",
        "answer": 7.957013904709037
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 2,424=？",
        "answer": 4.4984759678010855
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 82,840=？",
        "answer": 6.658602779715658
    },
    {
        "question": "129,337,469 ÷ 4,922,392=？",
        "answer": 1.4195481617482781
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 1,260=？",
        "answer": 4.562768543016519
    },
    {
        "question": "37,725 × 668=？",
        "answer": 7.401405710923173
    },
    {
        "question": "565 × 156,386=？",
        "answer": 7.946246319338082
    },
    {
        "question": "395,136 ÷ 272=？",
        "answer": 3.162177695095765
    },
    {
        "question": "26,060,387 ÷ 3,375=？",
        "answer": 3.887707083584677
    },
    {
        "question": "73,201,720 ÷ 1,068,764=？",
        "answer": 1.8356394689695221
    },
    {
        "question": "8,884 ÷ 5,695=？",
        "answer": 0.19311482146131717
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 111,244=？",
        "answer": 6.4776403605565696
    },
    {
        "question": "510 × 15,480=？",
        "answer": 6.89734113244481
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 19,950=？",
        "answer": 6.063370893585704
    },
    {
        "question": "6,573 ÷ 471=？",
        "answer": 1.1447427251514715
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 1,247,336=？",
        "answer": 7.326432378297253
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 44,965=？",
        "answer": 5.883323519127752
    },
    {
        "question": "68 × 491=？",
        "answer": 4.523590404829204
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,570,323=？",
        "answer": 6.711017698101624
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,416=？",
        "answer": 3.4520932490177314
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 22,345=？",
        "answer": 5.811578356895334
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 971,025=？",
        "answer": 6.7653816617770035
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 349=？",
        "answer": 4.275219186782149
    },
    {
        "question": "99 × 3,019,658=？",
        "answer": 8.475592953076715
    },
    {
        "question": "860 × 32,504=？",
        "answer": 7.446435260561923
    },
    {
        "question": "886,459,035 ÷ 3,195,289=？",
        "answer": 2.443148526487189
    },
    {
        "question": "2,537 × 3,835=？",
        "answer": 6.98808583550673
    },
    {
        "question": "16,430,040 ÷ 2,827,748=？",
        "answer": 0.7641979168622499
    },
    {
        "question": "473,331,942 ÷ 1,901=？",
        "answer": 5.396183696214971
    },
    {
        "question": "578,385,134 ÷ 598,497=？",
        "answer": 2.985155144111607
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 6,978,662=？",
        "answer": 7.922953410544962
    },
    {
        "question": "817,394,382 ÷ 42,139,816=？",
        "answer": 1.287739013488631
    },
    {
        "question": "4,205,472 ÷ 1,529,865=？",
        "answer": 0.4391616367663231
    },
    {
        "question": "178,696,618 ÷ 51,082=？",
        "answer": 3.543848440414748
    },
    {
        "question": "10,011,455 ÷ 284,631=？",
        "answer": 1.5462150009976818
    },
    {
        "question": "124,298,141 ÷ 255,151=？",
        "answer": 2.687667358613129
    },
    {
        "question": "139 × 11,669=？",
        "answer": 6.210048440096357
    },
    {
        "question": "11,688,031 ÷ 345,695=？",
        "answer": 1.5290482566820252
    },
    {
        "question": "7,254 × 121,833=？",
        "answer": 8.94634248959681
    },
    {
        "question": "45,316 × 2,172=？",
        "answer": 7.9931113890412036
    },
    {
        "question": "575,215 ÷ 486=？",
        "answer": 3.073193933446832
    },
    {
        "question": "382,933 ÷ 19,656=？",
        "answer": 1.2896276506645197
    },
    {
        "question": "6,235,962 ÷ 1,400=？",
        "answer": 3.6487754243920305
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 7,112,607=？",
        "answer": 8.29918684419491
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 17,326=？",
        "answer": 5.46914723144126
    },
    {
        "question": "479,349 ÷ 136,254=？",
        "answer": 0.5463025650080312
    },
    {
        "question": "536,168 × 639=？",
        "answer": 8.534801748674095
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,395=？",
        "answer": 4.078275522086601
    },
    {
        "question": "4,131 ÷ 237=？",
        "answer": 1.2413068489664822
    },
    {
        "question": "583 × 13,146=？",
        "answer": 6.884462182703363
    },
    {
        "question": "69,132 × 201=？",
        "answer": 7.1428751786946405
    },
    {
        "question": "3,717,182 ÷ 959=？",
        "answer": 3.588395218294356
    },
    {
        "question": "760,439,714 ÷ 113,223,715=？",
        "answer": 0.8271273893529191
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 4,085=？",
        "answer": 5.301388140896948
    },
    {
        "question": "268 × 1,157,777=？",
        "answer": 8.491759711800341
    },
    {
        "question": "5,697 × 101,225=？",
        "answer": 8.76093400489713
    },
    {
        "question": "63,204 ÷ 1,838=？",
        "answer": 1.5363990573550133
    },
    {
        "question": "26,927 ÷ 1,152=？",
        "answer": 1.3687354912563017
    },
    {
        "question": "495,170,586 ÷ 292,699,141=？",
        "answer": 0.22833339103728867
    },
    {
        "question": "2,499 × 6,969=？",
        "answer": 7.2409367206463475
    },
    {
        "question": "424 × 1,006,248=？",
        "answer": 8.6300708867738
    },
    {
        "question": "40,189,786 ÷ 6,771,795=？",
        "answer": 0.7734118912921484
    },
    {
        "question": "3,351,987 ÷ 330=？",
        "answer": 4.006788385760777
    },
    {
        "question": "110,332,540 ÷ 325,532=？",
        "answer": 2.5301099299002696
    },
    {
        "question": "789,709 ÷ 377,713=？",
        "answer": 0.32030515503576257
    },
    {
        "question": "7,920,065 ÷ 3,197=？",
        "answer": 3.3939861095887003
    },
    {
        "question": "13,399 × 3,198=？",
        "answer": 7.631950846529671
    },
    {
        "question": "12,618,095 ÷ 12,312,823=？",
        "answer": 0.0106361564074521
    },
    {
        "question": "15,490,375 ÷ 9,861=？",
        "answer": 3.1961409727383834
    },
    {
        "question": "330,230,771 ÷ 120,551,924=？",
        "answer": 0.437643392422012
    },
    {
        "question": "407,208 ÷ 4,384=？",
        "answer": 1.9679457560766687
    },
    {
        "question": "143,675 ÷ 53,583=？",
        "answer": 0.4283541806139451
    },
    {
        "question": "96,511,774 ÷ 140,668=？",
        "answer": 2.8363849857808647
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 13,962=？",
        "answer": 4.144947633670373
    },
    {
        "question": "73,813,136 ÷ 46,815,109=？",
        "answer": 0.19774761811448838
    },
    {
        "question": "6,287,200 ÷ 2,206,840=？",
        "answer": 0.45468642861906317
    },
    {
        "question": "601 ÷ 207=？",
        "answer": 0.46290412654582175
    },
    {
        "question": "1,964 × 2,751=？",
        "answer": 6.732632073840614
    },
    {
        "question": "1,149 × 2,297=？",
        "answer": 6.421481023883311
    },
    {
        "question": "1,969 × 14,699=？",
        "answer": 7.46153350603905
    },
    {
        "question": "40,992,736 ÷ 1,316,810=？",
        "answer": 1.4931837896708695
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 598=？",
        "answer": 3.077731179652392
    },
    {
        "question": "1,195,299 ÷ 3,393=？",
        "answer": 2.546892696523942
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 255=？",
        "answer": 2.406540180433955
    },
    {
        "question": "118,763,565 ÷ 5,217=？",
        "answer": 4.357262388885618
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 244=？",
        "answer": 2.9894498176666917
    },
    {
        "question": "654,596,585 ÷ 263,147,255=？",
        "answer": 0.39577489121572246
    },
    {
        "question": "23,688,226 ÷ 270,327=？",
        "answer": 1.942643113053958
    },
    {
        "question": "150,408 × 1,402=？",
        "answer": 8.324018950042216
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 969=？",
        "answer": 4.463445031770428
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 1,725,541=？",
        "answer": 8.007777294517528
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 291,461=？",
        "answer": 7.196974210451674
    },
    {
        "question": "33,990,387 ÷ 12,362,156=？",
        "answer": 0.43926188958124174
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 2,246,916=？",
        "answer": 8.320069785361857
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 27,190=？",
        "answer": 5.133379211923519
    },
    {
        "question": "24,146 × 34,353=？",
        "answer": 8.918809865684684
    },
    {
        "question": "315,252,759 ÷ 2,416=？",
        "answer": 5.11556196613102
    },
    {
        "question": "984,133,439 ÷ 645,097=？",
        "answer": 3.183428966337688
    },
    {
        "question": "10,933 × 58,686=？",
        "answer": 8.807273857394627
    },
    {
        "question": "25,837,120 ÷ 1,676=？",
        "answer": 4.187970087992593
    },
    {
        "question": "574,727 × 400=？",
        "answer": 8.361521591586023
    },
    {
        "question": "852,081 ÷ 4,945=？",
        "answer": 2.2363145854308653
    },
    {
        "question": "106,162 ÷ 732=？",
        "answer": 2.1614580106064087
    },
    {
        "question": "646,181 ÷ 291,492=？",
        "answer": 0.34572754403669187
    },
    {
        "question": "141 × 8,726=？",
        "answer": 6.090034321306181
    },
    {
        "question": "50,031 ÷ 22,095=？",
        "answer": 0.3549451775795727
    },
    {
        "question": "584 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 0.42202057342728877
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 23,421=？",
        "answer": 5.0685754384203685
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,571=？",
        "answer": 4.012162067970823
    },
    {
        "question": "10,343,423 ÷ 677,917=？",
        "answer": 1.1834877609911727
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 31,199,242=？",
        "answer": 8.096204034089475
    },
    {
        "question": "136,049 × 2,096=？",
        "answer": 8.455086632247546
    },
    {
        "question": "166,154,997 ÷ 643,968=？",
        "answer": 2.411649119952534
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 191,518,538=？",
        "answer": 8.58324081345399
    },
    {
        "question": "657 × 91,216=？",
        "answer": 7.777636393219837
    },
    {
        "question": "4,755,224 ÷ 711=？",
        "answer": 3.8253013789395918
    },
    {
        "question": "929,574 × 246=？",
        "answer": 8.359219075189177
    },
    {
        "question": "221 × 1,311=？",
        "answer": 5.461994965375195
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 743=？",
        "answer": 3.3481100684802376
    },
    {
        "question": "11,195,587 ÷ 10,416,652=？",
        "answer": 0.03131871369469977
    },
    {
        "question": "83 × 26,073=？",
        "answer": 6.335269097019161
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 3,346,758=？",
        "answer": 7.12668430151534
    },
    {
        "question": "18,711 × 397=？",
        "answer": 6.870887505533909
    },
    {
        "question": "884 × 282,835=？",
        "answer": 8.397985416129204
    },
    {
        "question": "38,112,643 ÷ 255=？",
        "answer": 5.174528886430972
    },
    {
        "question": "785,634,002 ÷ 12,232,284=？",
        "answer": 1.8077127156733446
    },
    {
        "question": "310,416 ÷ 162,142=？",
        "answer": 0.28204857264374783
    },
    {
        "question": "10,177,234 ÷ 32,687=？",
        "answer": 2.4932546971131146
    },
    {
        "question": "191,212,937 ÷ 23,186,177=？",
        "answer": 0.9162881253533672
    },
    {
        "question": "248,745,566 ÷ 488,690=？",
        "answer": 2.706721895787549
    },
    {
        "question": "63,439,108 ÷ 12,625=？",
        "answer": 3.7011256810654856
    },
    {
        "question": "162,833 ÷ 3,696=？",
        "answer": 1.6440104617493398
    },
    {
        "question": "205 × 7,181=？",
        "answer": 6.167938787782924
    },
    {
        "question": "2,108 ÷ 1,114=？",
        "answer": 0.2769854157027989
    },
    {
        "question": "1,028 × 9,951=？",
        "answer": 7.009859840898402
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 1,309,889=？",
        "answer": 7.807430575127063
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 169,861=？",
        "answer": 6.376221712198464
    },
    {
        "question": "36,095,631 ÷ 326,277=？",
        "answer": 2.043868177793766
    },
    {
        "question": "190,905,853 ÷ 107,775=？",
        "answer": 3.248301212146084
    },
    {
        "question": "422,266,654 ÷ 30,406=？",
        "answer": 4.1426274957855345
    },
    {
        "question": "2,296,154 ÷ 367=？",
        "answer": 3.7963349480049184
    },
    {
        "question": "605,827 ÷ 2,389=？",
        "answer": 2.4041324749579385
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,317=？",
        "answer": 3.596707029681446
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 46,861=？",
        "answer": 4.670811552076736
    },
    {
        "question": "18,515,969 ÷ 326,765=？",
        "answer": 1.7533109121997543
    },
    {
        "question": "124,233 ÷ 1,370=？",
        "answer": 1.9575164056106267
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,554,270=？",
        "answer": 6.191526464480762
    },
    {
        "question": "142,678 ÷ 114,937=？",
        "answer": 0.09389715563779834
    },
    {
        "question": "463,152 ÷ 10,340=？",
        "answer": 1.6512030050199262
    },
    {
        "question": "716,058,123 ÷ 2,431=？",
        "answer": 5.469163316919363
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 16,256,277=？",
        "answer": 8.114111077850847
    },
    {
        "question": "1,088,294 ÷ 537,178=？",
        "answer": 0.3066280168880414
    },
    {
        "question": "4,821 × 31,593=？",
        "answer": 8.182727998970439
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 7,032=？",
        "answer": 4.449138853393678
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 535=？",
        "answer": 4.205475036740891
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 1,249,396=？",
        "answer": 7.5280638753570255
    },
    {
        "question": "938,746 ÷ 17,508=？",
        "answer": 1.7293115615447796
    },
    {
        "question": "885,661,038 ÷ 615,349,725=？",
        "answer": 0.1581455287682713
    },
    {
        "question": "256,185 × 1,456=？",
        "answer": 8.57171507256391
    },
    {
        "question": "149,742,471 ÷ 24,780=？",
        "answer": 3.7812436933928892
    },
    {
        "question": "3,086,719 ÷ 26,304=？",
        "answer": 2.0694752993480656
    },
    {
        "question": "13,619 × 13,370=？",
        "answer": 8.260276627142279
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 67,428,229=？",
        "answer": 8.606993003481193
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 6,666,752=？",
        "answer": 8.079186804981417
    },
    {
        "question": "125 × 3,101,768=？",
        "answer": 8.588519324187835
    },
    {
        "question": "385,957,931 ÷ 2,062,307=？",
        "answer": 2.272186653734047
    },
    {
        "question": "87,169 × 216=？",
        "answer": 7.274815814952668
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 194,536=？",
        "answer": 6.8453024825453275
    },
    {
        "question": "6,491,506 ÷ 4,522=？",
        "answer": 3.1570149048335323
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 89,397=？",
        "answer": 5.428444199630718
    },
    {
        "question": "71,107,629 ÷ 7,283,532=？",
        "answer": 0.9895741652174436
    },
    {
        "question": "7,260,534 ÷ 405=？",
        "answer": 4.253513540284972
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 20,221=？",
        "answer": 4.907862620512867
    },
    {
        "question": "133,267,313 ÷ 114,145,868=？",
        "answer": 0.06726344639644455
    },
    {
        "question": "15,635 ÷ 5,187=？",
        "answer": 0.479181637585367
    },
    {
        "question": "44,940,206 ÷ 1,523,492=？",
        "answer": 1.4697948807930732
    },
    {
        "question": "1,057 × 156,381=？",
        "answer": 8.218258973266469
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 384=？",
        "answer": 3.86308482532036
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 958=？",
        "answer": 3.8264635490928014
    },
    {
        "question": "72,460,133 ÷ 19,889=？",
        "answer": 3.561486179083383
    },
    {
        "question": "16,804,063 ÷ 276,803=？",
        "answer": 1.783243508371461
    },
    {
        "question": "1,708 ÷ 916=？",
        "answer": 0.27059239268513585
    },
    {
        "question": "238,456 ÷ 9,718=？",
        "answer": 1.3898313598437295
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 14,499=？",
        "answer": 4.161338049858543
    },
    {
        "question": "45,107,684 ÷ 469,430=？",
        "answer": 1.9826796886065408
    },
    {
        "question": "292,531 ÷ 74,870=？",
        "answer": 0.5918640626424975
    },
    {
        "question": "4,641,842 ÷ 27,540=？",
        "answer": 2.226726417843123
    },
    {
        "question": "1,707,903 ÷ 224=？",
        "answer": 3.8822151830533627
    },
    {
        "question": "135,821,478 ÷ 675=？",
        "answer": 5.303664679288155
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 185,057=？",
        "answer": 6.221548026883833
    },
    {
        "question": "245,035,882 ÷ 862,613=？",
        "answer": 2.453413686346622
    },
    {
        "question": "1,286,573 ÷ 1,163,677=？",
        "answer": 0.043601982460625625
    },
    {
        "question": "329,047 ÷ 29,787=？",
        "answer": 1.0432311701723347
    },
    {
        "question": "20,223 ÷ 3,719=？",
        "answer": 0.7354194034994812
    },
    {
        "question": "16,011 ÷ 13,606=？",
        "answer": 0.0706879908987013
    },
    {
        "question": "68,678 ÷ 728=？",
        "answer": 1.9746862600935622
    },
    {
        "question": "109,232,170 ÷ 2,359=？",
        "answer": 4.665622620522883
    },
    {
        "question": "2,027 × 220=？",
        "answer": 5.649276429515215
    },
    {
        "question": "2,091,377 × 208=？",
        "answer": 8.638495662501413
    },
    {
        "question": "974,819 ÷ 175,541=？",
        "answer": 0.7445454172790316
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 305,416,371=？",
        "answer": 8.484892312499081
    },
    {
        "question": "4,401,561 ÷ 9,315=？",
        "answer": 2.67442386576722
    },
    {
        "question": "442,066 ÷ 80,690=？",
        "answer": 0.7386673984436061
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,049=？",
        "answer": 3.49789674291322
    },
    {
        "question": "121,728,341 ÷ 79,738,002=？",
        "answer": 0.1837263538653978
    },
    {
        "question": "530,400,671 ÷ 351,793,610=？",
        "answer": 0.17831611817256168
    },
    {
        "question": "199 × 17,706=？",
        "answer": 6.54697353629331
    },
    {
        "question": "62,951,138 ÷ 2,156=？",
        "answer": 4.46535482896418
    },
    {
        "question": "190 × 2,451,447=？",
        "answer": 8.668176109240163
    },
    {
        "question": "178 × 3,484=？",
        "answer": 5.79249814864452
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 82,336=？",
        "answer": 6.915589764530252
    },
    {
        "question": "116,821 ÷ 992=？",
        "answer": 2.071009247371677
    },
    {
        "question": "402 × 757=？",
        "answer": 5.483321932584543
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 481=？",
        "answer": 3.159266331093494
    },
    {
        "question": "5,834 × 6,364=？",
        "answer": 7.5696965957602576
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 9,685,872=？",
        "answer": 7.287168721156972
    },
    {
        "question": "38,048,939 ÷ 1,045,888=？",
        "answer": 1.560857370766224
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 8,138=？",
        "answer": 3.9105176855172665
    },
    {
        "question": "1,228,479 ÷ 564,342=？",
        "answer": 0.3378253639632742
    },
    {
        "question": "13,038 × 1,484=？",
        "answer": 7.286644877647176
    },
    {
        "question": "110,917 × 525=？",
        "answer": 7.765157417998535
    },
    {
        "question": "25,240,586 ÷ 978,312=？",
        "answer": 1.411622052894771
    },
    {
        "question": "19,433 ÷ 3,758=？",
        "answer": 0.7135830749059495
    },
    {
        "question": "46,279 ÷ 2,215=？",
        "answer": 1.320010235555239
    },
    {
        "question": "279,415,035 ÷ 5,805=？",
        "answer": 4.6824475472163005
    },
    {
        "question": "1,417,547 ÷ 43,964=？",
        "answer": 1.5084402680188138
    },
    {
        "question": "4,453,224 ÷ 51,700=？",
        "answer": 1.9351839978754195
    },
    {
        "question": "1,442 × 70,517=？",
        "answer": 8.007259088242693
    },
    {
        "question": "60,366,809 ÷ 2,368=？",
        "answer": 4.40641652152764
    },
    {
        "question": "2,035 × 8,626=？",
        "answer": 7.244373867371172
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 123,540=？",
        "answer": 5.392837592665656
    },
    {
        "question": "652 × 193,790=？",
        "answer": 8.101578958452498
    },
    {
        "question": "81,174,074 ÷ 54,682=？",
        "answer": 3.171572952522461
    },
    {
        "question": "4,543,082 ÷ 148,307=？",
        "answer": 1.486188925702367
    },
    {
        "question": "397,003,161 ÷ 1,052,228=？",
        "answer": 2.576684110417143
    },
    {
        "question": "662 ÷ 397=？",
        "answer": 0.22206748267658488
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 12,523=？",
        "answer": 5.211651732888466
    },
    {
        "question": "457 × 73,752=？",
        "answer": 7.527690002037835
    },
    {
        "question": "124,389 × 6,589=？",
        "answer": 8.913601483959203
    },
    {
        "question": "224,684,318 ÷ 11,203=？",
        "answer": 4.302238425615803
    },
    {
        "question": "607,668,599 ÷ 44,110,938=？",
        "answer": 1.139120501995477
    },
    {
        "question": "229 × 22,754=？",
        "answer": 6.716893236090232
    },
    {
        "question": "6,460 × 13,514=？",
        "answer": 7.94101643258404
    },
    {
        "question": "1,408,046 ÷ 4,516=？",
        "answer": 2.4938629099195246
    },
    {
        "question": "55,333,357 ÷ 32,335=？",
        "answer": 3.2333141537896766
    },
    {
        "question": "1,316 × 4,362=？",
        "answer": 6.7589415505206185
    },
    {
        "question": "237 × 312=？",
        "answer": 4.868902940028547
    },
    {
        "question": "627 × 81,221=？",
        "answer": 7.706935873088999
    },
    {
        "question": "259 × 344=？",
        "answer": 4.949858206652782
    },
    {
        "question": "226,005,062 ÷ 104,446=？",
        "answer": 3.335226354138301
    },
    {
        "question": "13,833,726 ÷ 4,359,263=？",
        "answer": 0.5015260981434024
    },
    {
        "question": "74,107,508 ÷ 86,981=？",
        "answer": 2.930437813229913
    },
    {
        "question": "255,345 ÷ 4,523=？",
        "answer": 1.7517007704563332
    },
    {
        "question": "227 × 586,983=？",
        "answer": 8.12465138073528
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 20,022,064=？",
        "answer": 8.748666876593742
    },
    {
        "question": "1,270,810 ÷ 46,173=？",
        "answer": 1.4396925307315478
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 15,212=？",
        "answer": 4.784246308067507
    },
    {
        "question": "500 × 1,893=？",
        "answer": 5.976120618299816
    },
    {
        "question": "29,787,810 ÷ 327,486=？",
        "answer": 1.958845836384674
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,983=？",
        "answer": 3.474653253362063
    },
    {
        "question": "73 × 11,580=？",
        "answer": 5.927031419511874
    },
    {
        "question": "29,234 × 1,364=？",
        "answer": 7.600702612946996
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 6,496,968=？",
        "answer": 7.2898319824273665
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 17,319,733=？",
        "answer": 7.238541192674373
    },
    {
        "question": "54,706 × 12,231=？",
        "answer": 8.825496927313104
    },
    {
        "question": "3,077 × 7,933=？",
        "answer": 7.387564950533636
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 21,663=？",
        "answer": 5.657937894448274
    },
    {
        "question": "710,246,808 ÷ 911=？",
        "answer": 5.891890913614723
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,702=？",
        "answer": 3.8262044234992527
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 217,374=？",
        "answer": 6.541327579757638
    },
    {
        "question": "23,060 ÷ 20,593=？",
        "answer": 0.049139683463587186
    },
    {
        "question": "68 × 75,544=？",
        "answer": 6.710708889384341
    },
    {
        "question": "30,044,800 ÷ 626=？",
        "answer": 4.6811949841691
    },
    {
        "question": "65,118,691 ÷ 2,273=？",
        "answer": 4.457106226162461
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 662=？",
        "answer": 3.2979792441593623
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 8,352=？",
        "answer": 4.699941736041831
    },
    {
        "question": "4,294 ÷ 3,800=？",
        "answer": 0.05307844348341968
    },
    {
        "question": "6,701 × 92,468=？",
        "answer": 8.792131082265714
    },
    {
        "question": "660 × 8,900=？",
        "answer": 6.768933942186782
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 31,050,181=？",
        "answer": 7.49206413614133
    },
    {
        "question": "401,470 × 869=？",
        "answer": 8.542672874453809
    },
    {
        "question": "2,423,854 ÷ 6,649=？",
        "answer": 2.561750123754092
    },
    {
        "question": "1,605,712 ÷ 3,415=？",
        "answer": 2.6722769449880084
    },
    {
        "question": "37,911 × 3,060=？",
        "answer": 8.064486666691556
    },
    {
        "question": "2,986,201 ÷ 9,576=？",
        "answer": 2.493934899163111
    },
    {
        "question": "23,599,711 ÷ 1,344=？",
        "answer": 4.244507415952564
    },
    {
        "question": "303,807,074 ÷ 962=？",
        "answer": 5.4994228099425335
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 253=？",
        "answer": 3.7041505168397992
    },
    {
        "question": "170 × 3,230=？",
        "answer": 5.739651443709377
    },
    {
        "question": "773 ÷ 384=？",
        "answer": 0.30384826955079414
    },
    {
        "question": "21,593,246 ÷ 5,039,526=？",
        "answer": 0.631928242302321
    },
    {
        "question": "119 × 774=？",
        "answer": 4.964287922075424
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 24,517=？",
        "answer": 5.292557314047313
    },
    {
        "question": "2,997 × 5,169=？",
        "answer": 7.190093275113336
    },
    {
        "question": "58,387,169 ÷ 1,235,781=？",
        "answer": 1.6743759045651248
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 8,152=？",
        "answer": 4.952656856156595
    },
    {
        "question": "1,765,950 ÷ 268=？",
        "answer": 3.8188436090454334
    },
    {
        "question": "544 ÷ 428=？",
        "answer": 0.10415513068500784
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 196,847=？",
        "answer": 6.993098804750691
    },
    {
        "question": "594,104,109 ÷ 260,535,876=？",
        "answer": 0.35799502164298996
    },
    {
        "question": "29,198,707 ÷ 268,782=？",
        "answer": 2.0359634389177734
    },
    {
        "question": "153,224,434 ÷ 158,555=？",
        "answer": 2.985148083806546
    },
    {
        "question": "837,420,395 ÷ 248,653=？",
        "answer": 3.5273498303668123
    },
    {
        "question": "21,591 ÷ 737=？",
        "answer": 1.466805269548104
    },
    {
        "question": "308,118,503 ÷ 1,002=？",
        "answer": 5.4878500576345095
    },
    {
        "question": "65,026 × 1,675=？",
        "answer": 8.037101851074185
    },
    {
        "question": "33,336,598 ÷ 26,469,698=？",
        "answer": 0.1001722916536183
    },
    {
        "question": "2,901 × 21,527=？",
        "answer": 7.7955312396188905
    },
    {
        "question": "60,978 × 830=？",
        "answer": 7.704251268338398
    },
    {
        "question": "782,782,811 ÷ 206=？",
        "answer": 6.5797740601198615
    },
    {
        "question": "2,756,141 ÷ 55,433=？",
        "answer": 1.6965330486721888
    },
    {
        "question": "75,090 × 3,023=？",
        "answer": 8.356020251505702
    },
    {
        "question": "131,997,087 ÷ 206=？",
        "answer": 5.806697126641354
    },
    {
        "question": "10,575 × 79,961=？",
        "answer": 8.927158592855918
    },
    {
        "question": "42,882,140 ÷ 9,189,556=？",
        "answer": 0.6689819217123264
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,457,466=？",
        "answer": 6.69151751357628
    },
    {
        "question": "51,532 ÷ 29,256=？",
        "answer": 0.24586205079008655
    },
    {
        "question": "7,028,010 ÷ 807=？",
        "answer": 3.93995883604964
    },
    {
        "question": "105,679,958 ÷ 509=？",
        "answer": 5.317274849669675
    },
    {
        "question": "16,791 ÷ 8,419=？",
        "answer": 0.29981605210695705
    },
    {
        "question": "16,633,955 ÷ 126,341=？",
        "answer": 2.11945121219734
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 12,897,486=？",
        "answer": 7.411535060790366
    },
    {
        "question": "19,484,232 ÷ 1,650=？",
        "answer": 4.072199347888861
    },
    {
        "question": "314 × 27,031=？",
        "answer": 6.928791760603184
    },
    {
        "question": "263,328 ÷ 2,109=？",
        "answer": 2.0964204609046115
    },
    {
        "question": "7,113 × 11,335=？",
        "answer": 7.906474333160387
    },
    {
        "question": "4,128 × 708=？",
        "answer": 6.465772946308924
    },
    {
        "question": "926,772,437 ÷ 215,685=？",
        "answer": 3.6331531662558465
    },
    {
        "question": "18,951,575 ÷ 5,244,854=？",
        "answer": 0.5579119051944532
    },
    {
        "question": "759,556,728 ÷ 13,814,736=？",
        "answer": 1.7402176250308063
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 88,323=？",
        "answer": 4.946073811985197
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 184,399=？",
        "answer": 5.265758561535075
    },
    {
        "question": "5,604 ÷ 1,284=？",
        "answer": 0.6399331028809025
    },
    {
        "question": "1,375 × 20,862=？",
        "answer": 7.457658639233183
    },
    {
        "question": "654,081,375 ÷ 1,107=？",
        "answer": 5.771484161872126
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 334,988=？",
        "answer": 7.148278540338847
    },
    {
        "question": "3,346,381 ÷ 102,889=？",
        "answer": 1.5122064395101353
    },
    {
        "question": "96,797,924 ÷ 149,465=？",
        "answer": 2.8113265367435294
    },
    {
        "question": "924,205 ÷ 7,093=？",
        "answer": 2.1149383538976
    },
    {
        "question": "57,055,786 ÷ 42,252=？",
        "answer": 3.1304524214656206
    },
    {
        "question": "48,143 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 2.3381408758777207
    },
    {
        "question": "124,743,449 ÷ 2,647,537=？",
        "answer": 1.6731757093818622
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 1,550=？",
        "answer": 4.946206553842783
    },
    {
        "question": "1,833,706 × 214=？",
        "answer": 8.593743479376283
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 610,185=？",
        "answer": 7.598374883945804
    },
    {
        "question": "179,083 ÷ 3,423=？",
        "answer": 1.7186474619394712
    },
    {
        "question": "170,403,728 ÷ 23,052,562=？",
        "answer": 0.8687598930593492
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 70,357,623=？",
        "answer": 8.888703843751758
    },
    {
        "question": "40,516 × 13,326=？",
        "answer": 8.732326371393373
    },
    {
        "question": "294,504,693 ÷ 94,435=？",
        "answer": 3.49395923510553
    },
    {
        "question": "23,616 × 1,053=？",
        "answer": 7.395634711328434
    },
    {
        "question": "922,638,843 ÷ 1,420=？",
        "answer": 5.812743390026909
    },
    {
        "question": "3,476,461 ÷ 850=？",
        "answer": 3.611718435986689
    },
    {
        "question": "48,056 × 1,182=？",
        "answer": 7.754365095484536
    },
    {
        "question": "5,051,543 ÷ 226=？",
        "answer": 4.349315615017046
    },
    {
        "question": "39,918 × 422=？",
        "answer": 7.226481224791367
    },
    {
        "question": "1,068 ÷ 315=？",
        "answer": 0.5302606989029371
    },
    {
        "question": "420,609 ÷ 6,857=？",
        "answer": 1.7877444118200656
    },
    {
        "question": "2,028,261 ÷ 322=？",
        "answer": 3.7992679682979995
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 138,976=？",
        "answer": 6.99419815640121
    },
    {
        "question": "1,066,195 ÷ 550,616=？",
        "answer": 0.286987814410063
    },
    {
        "question": "2,207,236 × 356=？",
        "answer": 8.895298768841
    },
    {
        "question": "817 × 10,619=？",
        "answer": 6.938305677333402
    },
    {
        "question": "18,511 × 355=？",
        "answer": 6.817658233869099
    },
    {
        "question": "2,280 × 221,216=？",
        "answer": 8.702751382202793
    },
    {
        "question": "99,893,871 ÷ 123,533=？",
        "answer": 2.9077558544621676
    },
    {
        "question": "96,321,132 ÷ 547,238=？",
        "answer": 2.2455453309221185
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 7,896=？",
        "answer": 4.9765883857092055
    },
    {
        "question": "81,081 ÷ 442=？",
        "answer": 2.2634968270088764
    },
    {
        "question": "9,731 × 781=？",
        "answer": 6.880808506434053
    },
    {
        "question": "575,320,580 ÷ 17,024=？",
        "answer": 4.528848298992984
    },
    {
        "question": "15,668,185 ÷ 4,000=？",
        "answer": 3.592958699452182
    },
    {
        "question": "590,009 ÷ 10,383=？",
        "answer": 1.754535782408906
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 1,326=？",
        "answer": 4.745792814466655
    },
    {
        "question": "1,245 × 18,802=？",
        "answer": 7.369373399778708
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 330,455=？",
        "answer": 5.519112327415351
    },
    {
        "question": "858,910 ÷ 102,891=？",
        "answer": 0.9215702709540757
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 2,788,726=？",
        "answer": 7.3996483551741
    },
    {
        "question": "9,599,260 ÷ 643,334=？",
        "answer": 1.1738012505489612
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 1,427,556=？",
        "answer": 7.476812448439167
    },
    {
        "question": "24,927 × 825=？",
        "answer": 7.313123962238436
    },
    {
        "question": "148,722 × 407=？",
        "answer": 7.7819696263812315
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 32,360=？",
        "answer": 5.957166544282454
    },
    {
        "question": "9,650,167 ÷ 139,705=？",
        "answer": 1.8393228793871186
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 26,662=？",
        "answer": 4.425892724087038
    },
    {
        "question": "104,769 × 2,857=？",
        "answer": 8.476143039055843
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 1,573=？",
        "answer": 4.776512319240097
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 8,718=？",
        "answer": 4.718568115065309
    },
    {
        "question": "12,506 ÷ 2,260=？",
        "answer": 0.7430099851972488
    },
    {
        "question": "5,664 × 408=？",
        "answer": 6.363783407771592
    },
    {
        "question": "241 × 22,431=？",
        "answer": 6.73286567794121
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 59,936=？",
        "answer": 6.056441356647972
    },
    {
        "question": "91,953,774 ÷ 33,939,935=？",
        "answer": 0.43285855216662206
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,831,501=？",
        "answer": 6.452016719342172
    },
    {
        "question": "270,439 ÷ 6,524=？",
        "answer": 1.6175553690117834
    },
    {
        "question": "497,390 × 1,818=？",
        "answer": 8.956290928439737
    },
    {
        "question": "437,427,045 ÷ 68,892,620=？",
        "answer": 0.8027329294818475
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 13,383,927=？",
        "answer": 8.55794732334587
    },
    {
        "question": "33,628,171 ÷ 2,180,174=？",
        "answer": 1.1882120910550775
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 195,928=？",
        "answer": 5.894156496626138
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 12,043=？",
        "answer": 5.671799293379642
    },
    {
        "question": "1,052,809 ÷ 392,032=？",
        "answer": 0.42902807069355364
    },
    {
        "question": "2,723 ÷ 1,123=？",
        "answer": 0.3846678850785068
    },
    {
        "question": "3,275 × 200=？",
        "answer": 5.816241299991783
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 37,469=？",
        "answer": 6.379852076464468
    },
    {
        "question": "694,795,536 ÷ 2,054=？",
        "answer": 5.529256580219047
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 66,366=？",
        "answer": 6.413010249735922
    },
    {
        "question": "2,105 × 52,549=？",
        "answer": 8.04381655605233
    },
    {
        "question": "59,416,716 ÷ 42,478,138=？",
        "answer": 0.14574317290607364
    },
    {
        "question": "143,809,018 ÷ 901,173=？",
        "answer": 2.2029779493408728
    },
    {
        "question": "754,925,575 ÷ 16,018,660=？",
        "answer": 1.6732779549626646
    },
    {
        "question": "180,014 ÷ 282=？",
        "answer": 2.80505717393011
    },
    {
        "question": "7,110 × 1,222=？",
        "answer": 6.938940806636301
    },
    {
        "question": "976,317,577 ÷ 420,146,467=？",
        "answer": 0.3661903922183707
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 26,922=？",
        "answer": 5.471500005074943
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 260=？",
        "answer": 3.0170333392987803
    },
    {
        "question": "11,969,449 ÷ 9,798,953=？",
        "answer": 0.0868944840035461
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 5,806=？",
        "answer": 4.462847035831674
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 13,976,014=？",
        "answer": 7.747443318342884
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 2,085,698=？",
        "answer": 7.699462666402044
    },
    {
        "question": "4,951 ÷ 1,269=？",
        "answer": 0.5912313042367793
    },
    {
        "question": "821,177,395 ÷ 224=？",
        "answer": 6.564188967466822
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,679=？",
        "answer": 3.565729787831127
    },
    {
        "question": "53,044,459 ÷ 8,814=？",
        "answer": 3.7794669782292103
    },
    {
        "question": "193,697,925 ÷ 196,091=？",
        "answer": 2.9946673070536027
    },
    {
        "question": "3,700 × 1,014=？",
        "answer": 6.574239679064312
    },
    {
        "question": "306,662,520 ÷ 13,287=？",
        "answer": 4.363233765165079
    },
    {
        "question": "2,561,533 ÷ 1,356,067=？",
        "answer": 0.276218807721185
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 113,085,399=？",
        "answer": 8.655466526022828
    },
    {
        "question": "2,258 × 1,883=？",
        "answer": 6.628574257605614
    },
    {
        "question": "2,107 × 4,311=？",
        "answer": 6.958242558461988
    },
    {
        "question": "7,631 ÷ 237=？",
        "answer": 1.5078331075443474
    },
    {
        "question": "4,968,296 ÷ 1,455,060=？",
        "answer": 0.5333265602329148
    },
    {
        "question": "7,209 ÷ 2,443=？",
        "answer": 0.4699515585501258
    },
    {
        "question": "453,136,054 ÷ 195,939=？",
        "answer": 3.364107731174175
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 10,502,754=？",
        "answer": 8.1674312290508
    },
    {
        "question": "105,334,052 ÷ 20,031=？",
        "answer": 3.720866160033282
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,670=？",
        "answer": 3.699837725867246
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 71,564=？",
        "answer": 6.058814589696282
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 3,773=？",
        "answer": 4.275656809537014
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 18,621=？",
        "answer": 5.5252755052083655
    },
    {
        "question": "79,265,154 ÷ 295,760=？",
        "answer": 2.4281428701629557
    },
    {
        "question": "111,343,062 ÷ 2,900,051=？",
        "answer": 1.5842575250656221
    },
    {
        "question": "2,124 × 537=？",
        "answer": 6.057128798108987
    },
    {
        "question": "2,182 × 604=？",
        "answer": 6.119891684873455
    },
    {
        "question": "291 × 81,592=？",
        "answer": 7.375540567762098
    },
    {
        "question": "359 × 211=？",
        "answer": 4.879376903876012
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 9,206=？",
        "answer": 4.441192225277618
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 2,243=？",
        "answer": 4.882308190625223
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 98,750,677=？",
        "answer": 8.772691332062966
    },
    {
        "question": "33,607 ÷ 2,369=？",
        "answer": 1.1518646852606576
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 381=？",
        "answer": 2.5809249756756194
    },
    {
        "question": "8,519,304 ÷ 4,568,067=？",
        "answer": 0.2706716506431347
    },
    {
        "question": "60,318 ÷ 227=？",
        "answer": 2.424421075745455
    },
    {
        "question": "2,522 × 557=？",
        "answer": 6.147600277410792
    },
    {
        "question": "1,639,664 ÷ 259=？",
        "answer": 3.8014550974443937
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,828=？",
        "answer": 3.4514794051248616
    },
    {
        "question": "139,515 × 639=？",
        "answer": 7.950121761588921
    },
    {
        "question": "101 × 74,091=？",
        "answer": 6.874086830240732
    },
    {
        "question": "48,391,320 ÷ 6,007=？",
        "answer": 3.9061098368423464
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 15,261,392=？",
        "answer": 8.817062603244834
    },
    {
        "question": "352,661 ÷ 6,892=？",
        "answer": 1.709012165880727
    },
    {
        "question": "342,692,387 ÷ 73,463=？",
        "answer": 3.668835796968069
    },
    {
        "question": "29,228,193 ÷ 744=？",
        "answer": 4.594229030875976
    },
    {
        "question": "60,102 ÷ 33,754=？",
        "answer": 0.25056367810198515
    },
    {
        "question": "1,530 × 55,152=？",
        "answer": 7.9262526968814715
    },
    {
        "question": "953,882 ÷ 624=？",
        "answer": 3.1843100639331237
    },
    {
        "question": "5,541 ÷ 3,646=？",
        "answer": 0.18177148584094638
    },
    {
        "question": "43,352,808 ÷ 3,822,115=？",
        "answer": 1.0547134823726763
    },
    {
        "question": "277,253,905 ÷ 17,584,319=？",
        "answer": 1.197752117954187
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 706,376=？",
        "answer": 6.326157189846604
    },
    {
        "question": "270 × 3,050,891=？",
        "answer": 8.915790455923274
    },
    {
        "question": "124,992 ÷ 2,685=？",
        "answer": 1.6679379272361672
    },
    {
        "question": "24,096,646 ÷ 22,357,612=？",
        "answer": 0.03253118253248812
    },
    {
        "question": "400,552,710 ÷ 324=？",
        "answer": 6.092114664160915
    },
    {
        "question": "26,566,071 ÷ 61,572=？",
        "answer": 2.6349440682954
    },
    {
        "question": "472,843 ÷ 22,364=？",
        "answer": 1.32516748050815
    },
    {
        "question": "138,147,277 ÷ 10,307=？",
        "answer": 4.127210052978304
    },
    {
        "question": "283,887,014 ÷ 978=？",
        "answer": 5.462806672020992
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 4,006=？",
        "answer": 5.460043441388826
    },
    {
        "question": "2,805,927 ÷ 244=？",
        "answer": 4.060686541740076
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 116,774=？",
        "answer": 5.067346156873189
    },
    {
        "question": "1,381,981 ÷ 824=？",
        "answer": 3.2245748605365203
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 648=？",
        "answer": 3.288696260590256
    },
    {
        "question": "5,430 × 101,251=？",
        "answer": 8.740199150782587
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 142,585,740=？",
        "answer": 8.15407609389604
    },
    {
        "question": "342,563,911 ÷ 3,207,452=？",
        "answer": 2.0285814424390534
    },
    {
        "question": "1,251 × 12,420=？",
        "answer": 7.191378905533981
    },
    {
        "question": "47,193 × 525=？",
        "answer": 7.394036889183607
    },
    {
        "question": "258,407 × 319=？",
        "answer": 7.916094957164271
    },
    {
        "question": "185 × 2,392,626=？",
        "answer": 8.646046546184742
    },
    {
        "question": "52,049,083 ÷ 33,958=？",
        "answer": 3.185470978525855
    },
    {
        "question": "1,667,851 ÷ 523=？",
        "answer": 3.5036555608108273
    },
    {
        "question": "17,262,674 ÷ 56,019=？",
        "answer": 2.4887727171735583
    },
    {
        "question": "614,710 ÷ 9,971=？",
        "answer": 1.789931561952877
    },
    {
        "question": "2,287,485 ÷ 717=？",
        "answer": 3.5038390992286805
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 366,405,586=？",
        "answer": 8.86499208170369
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 295,425=？",
        "answer": 5.771477239864823
    },
    {
        "question": "312,273 ÷ 4,790=？",
        "answer": 1.8141989221191062
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 437,629=？",
        "answer": 6.486204133327451
    },
    {
        "question": "1,887 × 2,622=？",
        "answer": 6.694404587518997
    },
    {
        "question": "1,081,518 × 420=？",
        "answer": 8.657283042315056
    },
    {
        "question": "368 ÷ 210=？",
        "answer": 0.24362852393959838
    },
    {
        "question": "218,745,940 ÷ 1,270=？",
        "answer": 5.236136280158007
    },
    {
        "question": "140,955 ÷ 25,428=？",
        "answer": 0.7437682831526107
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,343=？",
        "answer": 3.6051972673883776
    },
    {
        "question": "574 × 23,353=？",
        "answer": 7.127254571722197
    },
    {
        "question": "5,030,969 ÷ 574,740=？",
        "answer": 0.9421802176403778
    },
    {
        "question": "7,926 × 12,127=？",
        "answer": 7.982807445568182
    },
    {
        "question": "22,444,370 ÷ 127,177=？",
        "answer": 2.2466988434015853
    },
    {
        "question": "419,703 ÷ 259=？",
        "answer": 3.2096423094399578
    },
    {
        "question": "2,658,041 × 205=？",
        "answer": 8.736315536660372
    },
    {
        "question": "310 × 18,947=？",
        "answer": 6.768902148951703
    },
    {
        "question": "2,146 × 40,728=？",
        "answer": 7.9415228016592145
    },
    {
        "question": "814,800,744 ÷ 55,794=？",
        "answer": 4.16446391879015
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 9,040,490=？",
        "answer": 7.257221965799628
    },
    {
        "question": "4,674 × 591=？",
        "answer": 6.441276188937463
    },
    {
        "question": "129,638,024 ÷ 249,696=？",
        "answer": 2.7153208174669365
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 83,731,507=？",
        "answer": 7.922888907712467
    },
    {
        "question": "8,922,635 ÷ 2,179=？",
        "answer": 3.6122358973325794
    },
    {
        "question": "281,204,721 ÷ 396=？",
        "answer": 5.851327421627958
    },
    {
        "question": "60,290,375 ÷ 2,424=？",
        "answer": 4.395715369647007
    },
    {
        "question": "151,855 × 4,577=？",
        "answer": 8.842010008560807
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 33,012,266=？",
        "answer": 7.819705331491414
    },
    {
        "question": "141,787,514 ÷ 30,178,312=？",
        "answer": 0.6719430437714344
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 523=？",
        "answer": 4.496652939250918
    },
    {
        "question": "474 × 152,229=？",
        "answer": 7.858275736160239
    },
    {
        "question": "1,821 × 546=？",
        "answer": 5.997502588499657
    },
    {
        "question": "121,157,499 ÷ 40,914=？",
        "answer": 3.471478358978548
    },
    {
        "question": "930,756,040 ÷ 3,014=？",
        "answer": 5.48969261520906
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 683,385=？",
        "answer": 6.980793477672849
    },
    {
        "question": "2,285,103 ÷ 1,040,083=？",
        "answer": 0.34183778252124447
    },
    {
        "question": "395,961,038 ÷ 17,616=？",
        "answer": 4.351745152444106
    },
    {
        "question": "348,506,285 ÷ 9,665=？",
        "answer": 4.557008756253692
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 695=？",
        "answer": 3.143014800254095
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 63,185=？",
        "answer": 6.380397586443142
    },
    {
        "question": "467,535 ÷ 3,722=？",
        "answer": 2.0990377592221297
    },
    {
        "question": "16,588,119 ÷ 1,724=？",
        "answer": 3.983259880760193
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,354,096=？",
        "answer": 6.803053772020135
    },
    {
        "question": "121,211,563 ÷ 451=？",
        "answer": 5.429367509532846
    },
    {
        "question": "755 × 1,573=？",
        "answer": 6.074675674252475
    },
    {
        "question": "43,104,581 ÷ 8,448=？",
        "answer": 3.7077695226809535
    },
    {
        "question": "30,528,576 ÷ 5,043=？",
        "answer": 3.7820175790230723
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 36,462=？",
        "answer": 4.56184048673096
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 87,128=？",
        "answer": 5.6391277493705205
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 40,836=？",
        "answer": 5.95346587596564
    },
    {
        "question": "1,947 × 42,035=？",
        "answer": 7.912977003273213
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 9,276=？",
        "answer": 4.745511990349593
    },
    {
        "question": "372,964,714 ÷ 368=？",
        "answer": 6.0058199267008865
    },
    {
        "question": "663,712,157 ÷ 21,062=？",
        "answer": 4.498480164114109
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 4,043=？",
        "answer": 5.2087637326616365
    },
    {
        "question": "4,356,774 ÷ 34,261=？",
        "answer": 2.104364997382285
    },
    {
        "question": "391 × 95,463=？",
        "answer": 7.572011835686865
    },
    {
        "question": "48,890 ÷ 385=？",
        "answer": 2.1037593077553347
    },
    {
        "question": "392,403,977 ÷ 114,977,204=？",
        "answer": 0.5331216569646992
    },
    {
        "question": "4,847 × 36,475=？",
        "answer": 8.247468320288249
    },
    {
        "question": "218 × 57,664=？",
        "answer": 7.099361258567555
    },
    {
        "question": "2,001,136 ÷ 746=？",
        "answer": 3.428537777426639
    },
    {
        "question": "9,309 × 21,638=？",
        "answer": 8.304120146761262
    },
    {
        "question": "56,703,480 ÷ 40,419,636=？",
        "answer": 0.14701731503847315
    },
    {
        "question": "64,057 ÷ 931=？",
        "answer": 1.8376169143837007
    },
    {
        "question": "885,301,623 ÷ 538,035,063=？",
        "answer": 0.21628068144228482
    },
    {
        "question": "296 × 1,993,136=？",
        "answer": 8.770828644498211
    },
    {
        "question": "3,686 × 204,066=？",
        "answer": 8.876325982623039
    },
    {
        "question": "19,709 ÷ 605=？",
        "answer": 1.5129092148477057
    },
    {
        "question": "83,639 ÷ 761=？",
        "answer": 2.0410241749183644
    },
    {
        "question": "93,128,539 ÷ 1,477=？",
        "answer": 4.799702294487006
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 7,750=？",
        "answer": 5.168055303459139
    },
    {
        "question": "1,611 × 362,582=？",
        "answer": 8.766501780623518
    },
    {
        "question": "112,524,784 ÷ 3,094=？",
        "answer": 4.560727878586221
    },
    {
        "question": "104,690 × 2,643=？",
        "answer": 8.442002362936325
    },
    {
        "question": "95,710,853 ÷ 4,694,168=？",
        "answer": 1.3094025582472568
    },
    {
        "question": "909 × 473,682=？",
        "answer": 8.634050764996152
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 9,399=？",
        "answer": 4.876171636593311
    },
    {
        "question": "9,051,176 ÷ 1,033,144=？",
        "answer": 0.9425441519602941
    },
    {
        "question": "3,154 × 57,334=？",
        "answer": 8.257273931087246
    },
    {
        "question": "122 × 8,005=？",
        "answer": 5.9897211669300665
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,385=？",
        "answer": 3.7311857076340003
    },
    {
        "question": "653 × 34,061=？",
        "answer": 7.347170575580065
    },
    {
        "question": "993 × 7,610=？",
        "answer": 6.878333905265954
    },
    {
        "question": "2,557 × 1,169=？",
        "answer": 6.475545239188175
    },
    {
        "question": "1,625,659 ÷ 260,001=？",
        "answer": 0.7960544343972447
    },
    {
        "question": "440 × 4,447=？",
        "answer": 6.291519805935122
    },
    {
        "question": "12,855,465 ÷ 362,310=？",
        "answer": 1.550007469276645
    },
    {
        "question": "6,224,485 ÷ 110,534=？",
        "answer": 1.750607538159423
    },
    {
        "question": "175,531 ÷ 11,576=？",
        "answer": 1.1807953089018461
    },
    {
        "question": "87,475,023 ÷ 112,125=？",
        "answer": 2.892181609292813
    },
    {
        "question": "2,683,644 ÷ 28,636=？",
        "answer": 1.9718125500425305
    },
    {
        "question": "478,814,297 ÷ 28,472,682=？",
        "answer": 1.2257387319207527
    },
    {
        "question": "12,020,440 ÷ 2,978=？",
        "answer": 3.6059956715945436
    },
    {
        "question": "1,010 × 65,735=？",
        "answer": 7.822118041051952
    },
    {
        "question": "491 × 18,361=？",
        "answer": 6.954977822727579
    },
    {
        "question": "325 × 87,066=？",
        "answer": 7.451731953470635
    },
    {
        "question": "195,839 ÷ 369=？",
        "answer": 2.7248728167022875
    },
    {
        "question": "178,468,629 ÷ 34,900=？",
        "answer": 3.7087364604383377
    },
    {
        "question": "3,012,260 ÷ 6,720=？",
        "answer": 2.6515231817563842
    },
    {
        "question": "4,474 × 219,398=？",
        "answer": 8.991928644052527
    },
    {
        "question": "667 × 1,056,917=？",
        "answer": 8.848166717290834
    },
    {
        "question": "628,675,255 ÷ 43,942=？",
        "answer": 4.155546546870822
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 17,368=？",
        "answer": 6.2650556757111335
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,763=？",
        "answer": 3.8483123036272846
    },
    {
        "question": "5,634 × 2,562=？",
        "answer": 7.159395968058422
    },
    {
        "question": "1,648,897 ÷ 20,244=？",
        "answer": 1.9108971992159363
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 9,951=？",
        "answer": 4.9978667262391445
    },
    {
        "question": "6,858,749 ÷ 365=？",
        "answer": 4.273952045427885
    },
    {
        "question": "315 × 755=？",
        "answer": 5.376257505418788
    },
    {
        "question": "33,117,540 ÷ 249,511=？",
        "answer": 2.122968372745778
    },
    {
        "question": "5,303 × 281=？",
        "answer": 6.173227947023642
    },
    {
        "question": "1,307,066 ÷ 57,439=？",
        "answer": 1.3570906474038384
    },
    {
        "question": "166 × 253,847=？",
        "answer": 7.624680123256966
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 10,335=？",
        "answer": 4.0143104809633074
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 173,681,109=？",
        "answer": 8.239752583540806
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 550=？",
        "answer": 3.5185139398778875
    },
    {
        "question": "19,395 × 51,366=？",
        "answer": 8.998365531370261
    },
    {
        "question": "13,073,956 ÷ 1,196=？",
        "answer": 4.03867583937514
    },
    {
        "question": "8,485,233 ÷ 1,282=？",
        "answer": 3.8207757471308783
    },
    {
        "question": "269,083,337 ÷ 2,538=？",
        "answer": 5.025395187128769
    },
    {
        "question": "292,985,639 ÷ 7,106=？",
        "answer": 4.615221130320574
    },
    {
        "question": "2,519,955 × 284=？",
        "answer": 8.854711125500732
    },
    {
        "question": "349 × 43,062=？",
        "answer": 7.17691962357514
    },
    {
        "question": "65,989,523 ÷ 14,754,362=？",
        "answer": 0.6505545543914033
    },
    {
        "question": "94,531 × 1,244=？",
        "answer": 8.070394632474473
    },
    {
        "question": "112,520 × 312=？",
        "answer": 7.545384317511606
    },
    {
        "question": "10,350 ÷ 1,422=？",
        "answer": 0.8620407533991891
    },
    {
        "question": "19,920,270 ÷ 13,506=？",
        "answer": 3.168768475185215
    },
    {
        "question": "176 × 7,789=？",
        "answer": 6.13699437165367
    },
    {
        "question": "105 × 3,413,700=？",
        "answer": 8.554414651212053
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 619,605=？",
        "answer": 5.792114913708938
    },
    {
        "question": "629,715,228 ÷ 9,241,758=？",
        "answer": 1.833389603578358
    },
    {
        "question": "5,838,749 ÷ 463=？",
        "answer": 4.100738814896466
    },
    {
        "question": "501,555,681 ÷ 24,597,322=？",
        "answer": 1.3094313274684128
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 716=？",
        "answer": 3.1559430179718366
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 1,385,855=？",
        "answer": 7.849287969148521
    },
    {
        "question": "109 × 2,661,218=？",
        "answer": 8.46250695021435
    },
    {
        "question": "8,737,802 ÷ 1,832=？",
        "answer": 3.678476729970342
    },
    {
        "question": "978,390,802 ÷ 17,964,770=？",
        "answer": 1.7360906998039374
    },
    {
        "question": "11,782 ÷ 238=？",
        "answer": 1.6946420613434625
    },
    {
        "question": "2,614 × 30,665=？",
        "answer": 7.903948552268037
    },
    {
        "question": "1,811 ÷ 257=？",
        "answer": 0.8479853269827639
    },
    {
        "question": "1,944,090 ÷ 79,502=？",
        "answer": 1.3883383121844757
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 691=？",
        "answer": 3.1405080430381798
    },
    {
        "question": "86 × 4,195=？",
        "answer": 5.557230416408287
    },
    {
        "question": "927,830 × 297=？",
        "answer": 8.440224859991677
    },
    {
        "question": "756,587,202 ÷ 786,782=？",
        "answer": 2.983004575168697
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 7,937,117=？",
        "answer": 8.98244815254723
    },
    {
        "question": "5,630,405 ÷ 385=？",
        "answer": 4.165078905651741
    },
    {
        "question": "178,875 × 1,173=？",
        "answer": 8.321847658883362
    },
    {
        "question": "61,041 ÷ 59,984=？",
        "answer": 0.007586216727220178
    },
    {
        "question": "26,505,453 ÷ 17,031,242=？",
        "answer": 0.19208891111808704
    },
    {
        "question": "4,121 × 118,940=？",
        "answer": 8.690330548687847
    },
    {
        "question": "369,392,616 ÷ 319=？",
        "answer": 6.063697526773339
    },
    {
        "question": "172,153,838 ÷ 336=？",
        "answer": 5.709577431925848
    },
    {
        "question": "1,252 × 45,368=？",
        "answer": 7.7543539631523535
    },
    {
        "question": "24,974,843 ÷ 6,839,444=？",
        "answer": 0.5624819688047465
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 9,989,119=？",
        "answer": 8.113470539200433
    },
    {
        "question": "1,938 ÷ 669=？",
        "answer": 0.4619276549469234
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 167,275=？",
        "answer": 5.223431038551468
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 48,044,456=？",
        "answer": 7.6816432802975925
    },
    {
        "question": "759,603 ÷ 977=？",
        "answer": 2.8906921075658922
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 31,217,759=？",
        "answer": 8.773155324507346
    },
    {
        "question": "21,625 × 655=？",
        "answer": 7.1511974161286345
    },
    {
        "question": "6,978,781 ÷ 4,119=？",
        "answer": 3.228987778058298
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,149=？",
        "answer": 3.9342964068194055
    },
    {
        "question": "533 × 108,740=？",
        "answer": 7.763116537692264
    },
    {
        "question": "390,259,161 ÷ 12,929=？",
        "answer": 4.479788171091108
    },
    {
        "question": "314,002 ÷ 539=？",
        "answer": 2.7653436490845578
    },
    {
        "question": "2,294 × 325=？",
        "answer": 5.872476774544123
    },
    {
        "question": "31,484,808 ÷ 6,601,294=？",
        "answer": 0.6784719740053959
    },
    {
        "question": "20,536 × 1,712=？",
        "answer": 7.546019616004521
    },
    {
        "question": "57,004,930 ÷ 1,730,381=？",
        "answer": 1.5177706789120087
    },
    {
        "question": "1,478,911 ÷ 4,900=？",
        "answer": 2.4797459591665536
    },
    {
        "question": "367,384,943 ÷ 2,605=？",
        "answer": 5.149313625461046
    },
    {
        "question": "65,791,073 ÷ 279=？",
        "answer": 5.3725627661784445
    },
    {
        "question": "58,103 × 7,618=？",
        "answer": 8.646039524980484
    },
    {
        "question": "89,068,699 ÷ 70,674=？",
        "answer": 3.1004654365855915
    },
    {
        "question": "147,396,356 ÷ 65,683=？",
        "answer": 3.3510337663340763
    },
    {
        "question": "256,415 ÷ 420=？",
        "answer": 2.7856941369491977
    },
    {
        "question": "129,031,379 ÷ 33,400=？",
        "answer": 3.586948871932315
    },
    {
        "question": "310,073,482 ÷ 4,127=？",
        "answer": 4.875830157361467
    },
    {
        "question": "910,192 ÷ 7,811=？",
        "answer": 2.0664263762133968
    },
    {
        "question": "278,646 ÷ 175,985=？",
        "answer": 0.19957716058000763
    },
    {
        "question": "36,209,078 ÷ 969=？",
        "answer": 4.572493689367731
    },
    {
        "question": "227,949,622 ÷ 104,371,830=？",
        "answer": 0.3392555781430949
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 7,885=？",
        "answer": 5.771862961056621
    },
    {
        "question": "253 × 122,194=？",
        "answer": 7.490170402770857
    },
    {
        "question": "427,127 ÷ 10,464=？",
        "answer": 1.61085929439275
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 551,537=？",
        "answer": 5.741574652509347
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 24,617,488=？",
        "answer": 8.896393713211
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 4,308,856=？",
        "answer": 8.824693678577901
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 15,179,146=？",
        "answer": 8.02634537824561
    },
    {
        "question": "158 × 752=？",
        "answer": 5.074874927546065
    },
    {
        "question": "30,292 ÷ 7,310=？",
        "answer": 0.6174105711947148
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 103,403=？",
        "answer": 5.6165931303232695
    },
    {
        "question": "233 × 2,315=？",
        "answer": 5.731906916379991
    },
    {
        "question": "1,493,348 ÷ 1,479=？",
        "answer": 3.004192850652876
    },
    {
        "question": "48,872 × 1,230=？",
        "answer": 7.778965223563351
    },
    {
        "question": "51,300 × 1,461=？",
        "answer": 7.874767581046113
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 1,295=？",
        "answer": 4.43448906315119
    },
    {
        "question": "377,554,468 ÷ 751=？",
        "answer": 5.701339677094681
    },
    {
        "question": "4,752,877 ÷ 4,414,965=？",
        "answer": 0.03202931028440213
    },
    {
        "question": "4,036,508 ÷ 16,003=？",
        "answer": 2.401804412315189
    },
    {
        "question": "1,552 ÷ 214=？",
        "answer": 0.8604779435729788
    },
    {
        "question": "48,071,807 ÷ 9,789,640=？",
        "answer": 0.6911237258525972
    },
    {
        "question": "1,463 × 160,952=？",
        "answer": 8.371940703751896
    },
    {
        "question": "513,650 ÷ 18,338=？",
        "answer": 1.4473153240565957
    },
    {
        "question": "1,671 ÷ 939=？",
        "answer": 0.2503108576272804
    },
    {
        "question": "492,432,951 ÷ 3,823,742=？",
        "answer": 2.1098585245472536
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 859,789=？",
        "answer": 6.235421880187863
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 97,369,868=？",
        "answer": 8.590484572580948
    },
    {
        "question": "52,426,796 ÷ 1,336,739=？",
        "answer": 1.593506698158625
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 749=？",
        "answer": 3.4765418090274287
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 58,722=？",
        "answer": 5.768800838702498
    },
    {
        "question": "7,810 × 17,459=？",
        "answer": 8.134670398852853
    },
    {
        "question": "1,158,741 ÷ 10,365=？",
        "answer": 2.0484170675485496
    },
    {
        "question": "88 × 241=？",
        "answer": 4.326499714725037
    },
    {
        "question": "159 × 474,042=？",
        "answer": 7.877213946079284
    },
    {
        "question": "18,539,657 ÷ 87,322=？",
        "answer": 2.3269780209349915
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 13,350,747=？",
        "answer": 7.125505565992872
    },
    {
        "question": "229,456 ÷ 6,090=？",
        "answer": 1.5760821258276232
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 45,961=？",
        "answer": 4.662389469314709
    },
    {
        "question": "584,182 ÷ 2,152=？",
        "answer": 2.433705904230808
    },
    {
        "question": "96,076,009 ÷ 3,444,002=？",
        "answer": 1.4455515591799986
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 302,600=？",
        "answer": 5.480868923687168
    },
    {
        "question": "8,638,734 ÷ 14,610=？",
        "answer": 2.771799885676571
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 350=？",
        "answer": 3.3891660843645326
    },
    {
        "question": "178,840 × 940=？",
        "answer": 8.225592514795693
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 94,258=？",
        "answer": 5.275348216169513
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,993,861=？",
        "answer": 7.078736662930106
    },
    {
        "question": "660,767 ÷ 386,683=？",
        "answer": 0.23269326601792423
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 319,829=？",
        "answer": 6.9520758715184225
    },
    {
        "question": "771,156,134 ÷ 77,302,778=？",
        "answer": 0.9989472161695822
    },
    {
        "question": "277,972 × 920=？",
        "answer": 8.407788879170392
    },
    {
        "question": "251,883 × 312=？",
        "answer": 7.895353451253228
    },
    {
        "question": "39,477,781 ÷ 131,676=？",
        "answer": 2.4768461082502746
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,952=？",
        "answer": 3.470116353151004
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,954,807=？",
        "answer": 6.990073889867071
    },
    {
        "question": "51,538,559 ÷ 26,425,983=？",
        "answer": 0.2901011203941671
    },
    {
        "question": "3,074,560 ÷ 287=？",
        "answer": 4.029901075980764
    },
    {
        "question": "16,303 × 3,731=？",
        "answer": 7.784092777589767
    },
    {
        "question": "1,047,498 ÷ 685=？",
        "answer": 3.184462630943241
    },
    {
        "question": "3,363,539 ÷ 296=？",
        "answer": 4.055504756603289
    },
    {
        "question": "57,220 ÷ 20,614=？",
        "answer": 0.44338558175925935
    },
    {
        "question": "41,466,242 ÷ 4,229,302=？",
        "answer": 0.991425980195455
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 1,334=？",
        "answer": 5.137993054285702
    },
    {
        "question": "120,389 ÷ 36,924=？",
        "answer": 0.5132780647467923
    },
    {
        "question": "30,147,415 ÷ 44,066=？",
        "answer": 2.8351464492338407
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 19,872=？",
        "answer": 6.022517448097275
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,675=？",
        "answer": 3.427323786357247
    },
    {
        "question": "685,452 ÷ 65,656=？",
        "answer": 1.0187026275287103
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,687,803=？",
        "answer": 6.704443009209665
    },
    {
        "question": "6,283 ÷ 893=？",
        "answer": 0.8473156008273928
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 7,959,540=？",
        "answer": 8.363285967491612
    },
    {
        "question": "264,384,294 ÷ 431=？",
        "answer": 5.787758381743137
    },
    {
        "question": "1,255 × 7,916=？",
        "answer": 6.997149511351416
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,191=？",
        "answer": 3.9233476564978256
    },
    {
        "question": "2,984,336 ÷ 50,929=？",
        "answer": 1.7678825690289097
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 4,177=？",
        "answer": 5.459713566002376
    },
    {
        "question": "292 × 1,586=？",
        "answer": 5.665686034430003
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 85,324,681=？",
        "answer": 8.709225923657804
    },
    {
        "question": "6,833 × 545=？",
        "answer": 6.571007922999329
    },
    {
        "question": "871,278 × 795=？",
        "answer": 8.840523876778429
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 302=？",
        "answer": 2.4800069429571505
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 45,755,264=？",
        "answer": 7.961471061162445
    },
    {
        "question": "157,253,932 ÷ 15,735=？",
        "answer": 3.9997347661657052
    },
    {
        "question": "497 × 12,315=？",
        "answer": 6.786790804908454
    },
    {
        "question": "601,047,562 ÷ 211,907,761=？",
        "answer": 0.4527619770964065
    },
    {
        "question": "548,147 ÷ 326=？",
        "answer": 3.225679441496204
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 7,457,795=？",
        "answer": 7.571580445631029
    },
    {
        "question": "5,613,032 ÷ 13,297=？",
        "answer": 2.6254438493918206
    },
    {
        "question": "914 × 681,952=？",
        "answer": 8.794700003134073
    },
    {
        "question": "8,266 × 6,207=？",
        "answer": 7.710177146331087
    },
    {
        "question": "2,646 ÷ 486=？",
        "answer": 0.7359535705891888
    },
    {
        "question": "4,998,374 ÷ 607,279=？",
        "answer": 0.9154404855310209
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 2,778=？",
        "answer": 4.22188349178524
    },
    {
        "question": "11,794 × 17,057=？",
        "answer": 8.30356377289843
    },
    {
        "question": "1,401 × 27,866=？",
        "answer": 7.5915127680607055
    },
    {
        "question": "32,654,466 ÷ 72,714=？",
        "answer": 2.6523245502594692
    },
    {
        "question": "1,502 × 5,638=？",
        "answer": 6.927795004203733
    },
    {
        "question": "4,316,414 ÷ 2,994,876=？",
        "answer": 0.15874424692701408
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 3,103,013=？",
        "answer": 7.667874854110178
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 10,556,628=？",
        "answer": 7.9266152049194645
    },
    {
        "question": "4,943,759 ÷ 90,368=？",
        "answer": 1.738042620765954
    },
    {
        "question": "33,593 × 29,240=？",
        "answer": 8.992226158232501
    },
    {
        "question": "442,775 ÷ 6,356=？",
        "answer": 1.8429992031913152
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 19,309,794=？",
        "answer": 7.586807636344439
    },
    {
        "question": "2,850,396 ÷ 1,189=？",
        "answer": 3.379723345273262
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 123,950=？",
        "answer": 6.172427777151465
    },
    {
        "question": "67,351 ÷ 240=？",
        "answer": 2.448132806621456
    },
    {
        "question": "236,199,496 ÷ 33,325,091=？",
        "answer": 0.8505076225807942
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 9,809,325=？",
        "answer": 8.070820369751615
    },
    {
        "question": "11,198 × 633=？",
        "answer": 6.85054417317632
    },
    {
        "question": "4,941 × 11,421=？",
        "answer": 7.751518985423447
    },
    {
        "question": "1,904 ÷ 940=？",
        "answer": 0.3065390904487568
    },
    {
        "question": "648 × 123,379=？",
        "answer": 7.902816251789561
    },
    {
        "question": "59,743,014 ÷ 32,317,179=？",
        "answer": 0.26685368498029627
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,761=？",
        "answer": 3.575303333422399
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 5,163,729=？",
        "answer": 8.257031486137356
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 79,351=？",
        "answer": 5.501612395534713
    },
    {
        "question": "195,496 × 420=？",
        "answer": 7.91438716621828
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,325=？",
        "answer": 3.9684829485539352
    },
    {
        "question": "684,245 ÷ 10,796=？",
        "answer": 1.8019487566787296
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 591,807=？",
        "answer": 5.772180097768504
    },
    {
        "question": "169 × 1,247,778=？",
        "answer": 8.32402402878121
    },
    {
        "question": "31,104,242 ÷ 758,628=？",
        "answer": 1.6127907542733797
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 32,165=？",
        "answer": 5.6213269080432235
    },
    {
        "question": "393 × 379=？",
        "answer": 5.173031760343499
    },
    {
        "question": "103,122 ÷ 210=？",
        "answer": 2.6911320326189996
    },
    {
        "question": "2,559 ÷ 425=？",
        "answer": 0.7796813558368739
    },
    {
        "question": "131 × 244,387=？",
        "answer": 7.505349395841563
    },
    {
        "question": "27,124 ÷ 286=？",
        "answer": 1.976987702575929
    },
    {
        "question": "1,059,219 ÷ 1,608=？",
        "answer": 2.8186997180166027
    },
    {
        "question": "5,842,188 ÷ 202=？",
        "answer": 4.461224158892532
    },
    {
        "question": "212 × 2,396,329=？",
        "answer": 8.70588230447727
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 1,156=？",
        "answer": 4.104350519242735
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 265,980=？",
        "answer": 7.393331930236913
    },
    {
        "question": "23,857,526 ÷ 3,723,660=？",
        "answer": 0.8066553862418062
    },
    {
        "question": "1,968 × 11,894=？",
        "answer": 7.3693530282585815
    },
    {
        "question": "82,568,687 ÷ 16,415,622=？",
        "answer": 0.7015580354234594
    },
    {
        "question": "1,711,847 ÷ 431,786=？",
        "answer": 0.5981963891813515
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 15,830=？",
        "answer": 5.977632165246
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 208,104=？",
        "answer": 5.318280427934992
    },
    {
        "question": "1,795 × 1,236=？",
        "answer": 6.346082923667135
    },
    {
        "question": "53,427,559 ÷ 16,827=？",
        "answer": 3.5017586378470043
    },
    {
        "question": "271 × 1,383=？",
        "answer": 5.573791470983716
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 341,619=？",
        "answer": 6.895269853086332
    },
    {
        "question": "33,388 ÷ 24,154=？",
        "answer": 0.14060134286474507
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 995=？",
        "answer": 3.298853076409707
    },
    {
        "question": "12,579,282 ÷ 6,638,407=？",
        "answer": 0.2775919777295612
    },
    {
        "question": "3,466 ÷ 1,963=？",
        "answer": 0.24690825877789196
    },
    {
        "question": "455,094,705 ÷ 25,810,490=？",
        "answer": 1.2463055330467674
    },
    {
        "question": "13,502 × 12,996=？",
        "answer": 8.244207806325747
    },
    {
        "question": "237 × 401=？",
        "answer": 4.977892718630287
    },
    {
        "question": "111,294 ÷ 4,563=？",
        "answer": 1.3872212828295205
    },
    {
        "question": "20,119 × 13,424=？",
        "answer": 8.431488334119267
    },
    {
        "question": "346,937 ÷ 190,407=？",
        "answer": 0.26056770831434456
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,344=？",
        "answer": 3.6055205234374688
    },
    {
        "question": "88,616,327 ÷ 309=？",
        "answer": 5.457555265856743
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 41,146=？",
        "answer": 6.627164846456023
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,908=？",
        "answer": 3.979548374704095
    },
    {
        "question": "1,000 ÷ 496=？",
        "answer": 0.3045183235098025
    },
    {
        "question": "112,982,383 ÷ 1,416=？",
        "answer": 4.901947477188496
    },
    {
        "question": "713,049 ÷ 344=？",
        "answer": 3.316560932579651
    },
    {
        "question": "45,526 ÷ 6,122=？",
        "answer": 0.8713661687929483
    },
    {
        "question": "46,713 × 630=？",
        "answer": 7.468778308875981
    },
    {
        "question": "301,862 ÷ 97,159=？",
        "answer": 0.49232540893577237
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,750=？",
        "answer": 3.916453948549925
    },
    {
        "question": "140 × 212,843=？",
        "answer": 7.4741874073097225
    },
    {
        "question": "109,444,554 ÷ 94,554=？",
        "answer": 3.0635142498870445
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 28,171,708=？",
        "answer": 7.449813178277516
    },
    {
        "question": "431 × 1,123=？",
        "answer": 5.68485702642219
    },
    {
        "question": "138,031 × 6,448=？",
        "answer": 8.949401663147563
    },
    {
        "question": "52,729 × 573=？",
        "answer": 7.480204157027281
    },
    {
        "question": "32,181,588 ÷ 418=？",
        "answer": 4.886431188771734
    },
    {
        "question": "6,959,813 ÷ 1,356=？",
        "answer": 3.710337881378491
    },
    {
        "question": "133 × 884=？",
        "answer": 5.0703039059801585
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,027=？",
        "answer": 4.207041620935394
    },
    {
        "question": "7,712 ÷ 229=？",
        "answer": 1.5273315385548862
    },
    {
        "question": "593 × 305,329=？",
        "answer": 8.257822748700738
    },
    {
        "question": "927,546,683 ÷ 3,698=？",
        "answer": 5.399368869856485
    },
    {
        "question": "22,134 × 508=？",
        "answer": 7.050923617894366
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 294=？",
        "answer": 3.167317334748176
    },
    {
        "question": "864,374,873 ÷ 1,004,802=？",
        "answer": 2.9346216428118947
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 47,425,026=？",
        "answer": 7.6760075776556596
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 22,061,784=？",
        "answer": 8.848790606552319
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 261,885=？",
        "answer": 6.3723531334705585
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 11,904,076=？",
        "answer": 7.5528169456260414
    },
    {
        "question": "47,403 ÷ 10,062=？",
        "answer": 0.6731215148070764
    },
    {
        "question": "161 × 2,291,328=？",
        "answer": 8.566913138243478
    },
    {
        "question": "284,185,796 ÷ 28,080,494=？",
        "answer": 1.0051976237372597
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,021=？",
        "answer": 4.080698622871129
    },
    {
        "question": "478,841,845 ÷ 380,872=？",
        "answer": 3.099413049037309
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,558=？",
        "answer": 3.1925674533365456
    },
    {
        "question": "2,011,210 ÷ 249,798=？",
        "answer": 0.9058684628297646
    },
    {
        "question": "1,419,834 ÷ 106,338=？",
        "answer": 1.1255490839134854
    },
    {
        "question": "251,019,795 ÷ 564,158=？",
        "answer": 2.6483072195639576
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 432,386=？",
        "answer": 6.334841628051199
    },
    {
        "question": "308,949,504 ÷ 34,578=？",
        "answer": 3.9510876323522717
    },
    {
        "question": "171,745,860 ÷ 7,321,745=？",
        "answer": 1.3702716777186812
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 20,113,968=？",
        "answer": 7.303497754858911
    },
    {
        "question": "730,024,076 ÷ 205=？",
        "answer": 6.551583322217476
    },
    {
        "question": "10,576,028 ÷ 410,681=？",
        "answer": 1.4108179810866468
    },
    {
        "question": "1,512 ÷ 226=？",
        "answer": 0.8254433520177868
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 824,879=？",
        "answer": 6.51845023868234
    },
    {
        "question": "79,584,035 ÷ 159,817=？",
        "answer": 2.6972029805255744
    },
    {
        "question": "10,878 × 786=？",
        "answer": 6.93197160051856
    },
    {
        "question": "116,385 × 4,505=？",
        "answer": 8.71959180623885
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 6,689=？",
        "answer": 5.356840112994888
    },
    {
        "question": "118,952 × 1,061=？",
        "answer": 8.101087132348285
    },
    {
        "question": "2,876,679 ÷ 2,693,672=？",
        "answer": 0.02854669104453808
    },
    {
        "question": "60,521 ÷ 11,681=？",
        "answer": 0.7144260714093215
    },
    {
        "question": "55,554,011 ÷ 12,490,858=？",
        "answer": 0.6481231492838854
    },
    {
        "question": "545,332 ÷ 322,223=？",
        "answer": 0.2285044460142533
    },
    {
        "question": "86,913,651 ÷ 10,802,653=？",
        "answer": 0.9055575677851633
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 661,801=？",
        "answer": 6.297848673775219
    },
    {
        "question": "5,745 ÷ 3,705=？",
        "answer": 0.19050182070895705
    },
    {
        "question": "392,658,226 ÷ 616,892=？",
        "answer": 2.80380556189518
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 275=？",
        "answer": 4.210184705472407
    },
    {
        "question": "507 × 11,183=？",
        "answer": 6.753566284231818
    },
    {
        "question": "408,585 ÷ 139,951=？",
        "answer": 0.4653064127380322
    },
    {
        "question": "12,862,039 ÷ 1,534,835=？",
        "answer": 0.9232481279234064
    },
    {
        "question": "3,049 × 110,490=？",
        "answer": 8.527480397939955
    },
    {
        "question": "4,483,275 ÷ 2,350,476=？",
        "answer": 0.2804395578130832
    },
    {
        "question": "45,735 × 453=？",
        "answer": 7.3163468854338936
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 1,038,384=？",
        "answer": 7.688455845591891
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 84,171=？",
        "answer": 6.101253745931022
    },
    {
        "question": "1,657 ÷ 280=？",
        "answer": 0.7721644770771176
    },
    {
        "question": "2,278,996 ÷ 91,977=？",
        "answer": 1.3940643227741263
    },
    {
        "question": "1,153 ÷ 236=？",
        "answer": 0.6889173043245924
    },
    {
        "question": "7,151,423 ÷ 335=？",
        "answer": 4.329347659877287
    },
    {
        "question": "51,855,581 ÷ 120,767=？",
        "answer": 2.6328472265167404
    },
    {
        "question": "983,870,649 ÷ 50,457=？",
        "answer": 4.29001657952511
    },
    {
        "question": "126 × 5,640,675=？",
        "answer": 8.85170162272405
    },
    {
        "question": "292 × 74,045=？",
        "answer": 7.334878588907619
    },
    {
        "question": "142,527 ÷ 8,222=？",
        "answer": 1.238919671481055
    },
    {
        "question": "5,670,132 ÷ 1,014=？",
        "answer": 3.7475552143372695
    },
    {
        "question": "1,059,056 ÷ 2,213=？",
        "answer": 2.67993751109805
    },
    {
        "question": "629,121 ÷ 1,017=？",
        "answer": 2.7914132292133074
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 20,338=？",
        "answer": 6.308308242998225
    },
    {
        "question": "3,392 × 21,201=？",
        "answer": 7.8568121896190615
    },
    {
        "question": "347 × 29,424=？",
        "answer": 7.009031186684876
    },
    {
        "question": "1,150,563 ÷ 10,583=？",
        "answer": 2.0363016076719087
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 91,348=？",
        "answer": 6.0398802892690515
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 11,251=？",
        "answer": 4.750161129021717
    },
    {
        "question": "73,002,034 ÷ 28,330=？",
        "answer": 3.4110883861845385
    },
    {
        "question": "58,245,970 ÷ 105,566=？",
        "answer": 2.7417418161708453
    },
    {
        "question": "19,932 × 3,116=？",
        "answer": 7.793148327499546
    },
    {
        "question": "413,802,521 ÷ 27,170,267=？",
        "answer": 1.18269922596515
    },
    {
        "question": "423,557 ÷ 227,324=？",
        "answer": 0.27026657429285944
    },
    {
        "question": "208,618,704 ÷ 1,659,045=？",
        "answer": 2.099495077107533
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 802=？",
        "answer": 4.2659022043017565
    },
    {
        "question": "4,444,987 ÷ 91,978=？",
        "answer": 1.6841865332537005
    },
    {
        "question": "4,785,389 ÷ 12,799=？",
        "answer": 2.5727412078925416
    },
    {
        "question": "9,141 × 4,489=？",
        "answer": 7.613143314343989
    },
    {
        "question": "225,727 ÷ 4,487=？",
        "answer": 1.7016274401414637
    },
    {
        "question": "1,694 × 463,446=？",
        "answer": 8.894912544112186
    },
    {
        "question": "31,586 × 28,896=？",
        "answer": 8.960332359669309
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 30,825,747=？",
        "answer": 8.090973600976824
    },
    {
        "question": "3,726,567 ÷ 1,543=？",
        "answer": 3.3829430077598532
    },
    {
        "question": "92,841,152 ÷ 7,359=？",
        "answer": 4.100921717743432
    },
    {
        "question": "47,782 × 17,759=？",
        "answer": 8.928682831192864
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 11,838=？",
        "answer": 5.8861916922786905
    },
    {
        "question": "91,724,271 ÷ 2,716=？",
        "answer": 4.528554503176726
    },
    {
        "question": "85,365,422 ÷ 1,844=？",
        "answer": 4.665521074866309
    },
    {
        "question": "6,580 ÷ 509=？",
        "answer": 1.1115081112771967
    },
    {
        "question": "11,244,290 ÷ 1,307,303=？",
        "answer": 0.9345557801113512
    },
    {
        "question": "29,121,347 ÷ 47,298=？",
        "answer": 2.7893686823324364
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 179,192=？",
        "answer": 6.207561126186134
    },
    {
        "question": "448 × 537=？",
        "answer": 5.3812522996976995
    },
    {
        "question": "209,101,674 ÷ 29,966,372=？",
        "answer": 0.843723343141295
    },
    {
        "question": "46,973 × 886=？",
        "answer": 7.619282019814381
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 2,364=？",
        "answer": 4.695866766943137
    },
    {
        "question": "36,282,060 ÷ 461,671=？",
        "answer": 1.8953593421152684
    },
    {
        "question": "808,747,523 ÷ 93,786=？",
        "answer": 3.9356749500694534
    },
    {
        "question": "271,455,531 ÷ 849,712=？",
        "answer": 2.504426943390902
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 458,398=？",
        "answer": 7.229444438194612
    },
    {
        "question": "325,250,347 ÷ 1,294=？",
        "answer": 5.40028349223716
    },
    {
        "question": "6,076 ÷ 240=？",
        "answer": 1.4034065234791426
    },
    {
        "question": "14,340 ÷ 7,495=？",
        "answer": 0.28177751414748303
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,936,717=？",
        "answer": 7.142183972440368
    },
    {
        "question": "118 × 5,053,617=？",
        "answer": 8.775484332129942
    },
    {
        "question": "65,899 × 353=？",
        "answer": 7.366653529727249
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 990,481=？",
        "answer": 7.393786157729542
    },
    {
        "question": "178,722,098 ÷ 259,241=？",
        "answer": 2.83847456590073
    },
    {
        "question": "16,076,397 ÷ 1,187=？",
        "answer": 4.131738003421119
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 24,264=？",
        "answer": 5.929030441652882
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 967,239=？",
        "answer": 7.09947715168077
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 764,615=？",
        "answer": 6.997386165939269
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 201=？",
        "answer": 2.303196057420489
    },
    {
        "question": "120,635 ÷ 1,969=？",
        "answer": 1.7872276124090514
    },
    {
        "question": "58,115,334 ÷ 13,318,450=？",
        "answer": 0.6398370534979874
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,050=？",
        "answer": 3.975431808509263
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 1,217,235=？",
        "answer": 7.289494414091259
    },
    {
        "question": "27,244 ÷ 16,246=？",
        "answer": 0.22452442271224535
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 898,460=？",
        "answer": 7.275718041547892
    },
    {
        "question": "2,326 × 12,368=？",
        "answer": 7.45890918696668
    },
    {
        "question": "17,485,002 ÷ 575=？",
        "answer": 4.482997841631865
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 623,212=？",
        "answer": 7.703120826000809
    },
    {
        "question": "4,573,067 ÷ 1,347,063=？",
        "answer": 0.5308196568132404
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 1,463=？",
        "answer": 4.395693247503584
    },
    {
        "question": "302,661 ÷ 22,787=？",
        "answer": 1.1232693103288822
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 1,595,013=？",
        "answer": 7.406884209738941
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 21,829,450=？",
        "answer": 7.8161640483777655
    },
    {
        "question": "34,138 ÷ 1,413=？",
        "answer": 1.3830959122117388
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 20,539=？",
        "answer": 5.157677334920396
    },
    {
        "question": "792,049 ÷ 55,831=？",
        "answer": 1.1518766433338494
    },
    {
        "question": "82,444 ÷ 1,974=？",
        "answer": 1.6208119062896287
    },
    {
        "question": "993,307,365 ÷ 524=？",
        "answer": 6.277752368629956
    },
    {
        "question": "182,333,175 ÷ 99,506=？",
        "answer": 3.263016425915902
    },
    {
        "question": "130,029 ÷ 1,596=？",
        "answer": 1.911007335564499
    },
    {
        "question": "293 × 45,651=？",
        "answer": 7.1263179156904775
    },
    {
        "question": "4,558,932 ÷ 188,883=？",
        "answer": 1.3826702424531316
    },
    {
        "question": "3,482,285 ÷ 10,635=？",
        "answer": 2.5151268178792106
    },
    {
        "question": "35,232,972 ÷ 10,090,770=？",
        "answer": 0.5430249713180182
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 397,084=？",
        "answer": 5.5988823880668965
    },
    {
        "question": "2,745,687 ÷ 551=？",
        "answer": 3.697499428615381
    },
    {
        "question": "161,600,376 ÷ 848,179=？",
        "answer": 2.2799548513321306
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 1,217=？",
        "answer": 5.058418431829764
    },
    {
        "question": "265,463 ÷ 120,443=？",
        "answer": 0.34322243364856025
    },
    {
        "question": "3,558 × 33,792=？",
        "answer": 8.080019840265606
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 14,667,478=？",
        "answer": 7.643476700202832
    },
    {
        "question": "25,268,792 ÷ 10,119,427=？",
        "answer": 0.3974285587182221
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 17,897,122=？",
        "answer": 8.366726550883913
    },
    {
        "question": "628,627,659 ÷ 4,074,664=？",
        "answer": 2.188301683345175
    },
    {
        "question": "382,939,692 ÷ 44,004,314=？",
        "answer": 0.9396351286463049
    },
    {
        "question": "4,758 ÷ 1,172=？",
        "answer": 0.6084968260191757
    },
    {
        "question": "1,058 × 3,992=？",
        "answer": 6.6256762003145
    },
    {
        "question": "273 × 1,311,377=？",
        "answer": 8.55389020942701
    },
    {
        "question": "18,123 ÷ 4,386=？",
        "answer": 0.6161614631076248
    },
    {
        "question": "79 × 89,993=？",
        "answer": 6.851835820956388
    },
    {
        "question": "110 × 5,637=？",
        "answer": 5.792440719978413
    },
    {
        "question": "302,640,715 ÷ 2,073=？",
        "answer": 5.164328052228983
    },
    {
        "question": "99,907 ÷ 2,062=？",
        "answer": 1.6853072572571597
    },
    {
        "question": "1,499 × 428=？",
        "answer": 5.807245401861452
    },
    {
        "question": "621 × 542,036=？",
        "answer": 8.52711973188497
    },
    {
        "question": "3,899,311 ÷ 4,861=？",
        "answer": 2.9042622538152827
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 91,640=？",
        "answer": 6.848575805689841
    },
    {
        "question": "74,616 ÷ 201=？",
        "answer": 2.569635906334309
    },
    {
        "question": "15,639 × 1,572=？",
        "answer": 7.39066152135007
    },
    {
        "question": "37,208 × 11,620=？",
        "answer": 8.635842454557771
    },
    {
        "question": "124,384 ÷ 6,647=？",
        "answer": 1.2721388401770317
    },
    {
        "question": "778,925 ÷ 1,506=？",
        "answer": 2.7136706711041354
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 232=？",
        "answer": 3.4446692309385245
    },
    {
        "question": "399,972,465 ÷ 416,892=？",
        "answer": 2.982006533293338
    },
    {
        "question": "3,189,134 ÷ 3,348=？",
        "answer": 2.9788873183500653
    },
    {
        "question": "311,632,392 ÷ 28,776,853=？",
        "answer": 1.034599294904321
    },
    {
        "question": "244,066,092 ÷ 57,284,760=？",
        "answer": 0.6294683493430726
    },
    {
        "question": "236,115,009 ÷ 1,225=？",
        "answer": 5.284987505827142
    },
    {
        "question": "384,724,453 ÷ 545,561=？",
        "answer": 2.8483064740822854
    },
    {
        "question": "1,518,057 × 622=？",
        "answer": 8.975078463444428
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 13,440=？",
        "answer": 4.429429264381787
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,235=？",
        "answer": 3.5098742850047193
    },
    {
        "question": "2,804 × 47,509=？",
        "answer": 8.124553898500345
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 86,256=？",
        "answer": 4.935789314484561
    },
    {
        "question": "1,894,156 ÷ 286=？",
        "answer": 3.821049710888373
    },
    {
        "question": "246,935,458 ÷ 10,426,861=？",
        "answer": 1.3744298716798653
    },
    {
        "question": "115,866,292 ÷ 87,441,768=？",
        "answer": 0.12223817861474173
    },
    {
        "question": "39,061 ÷ 335=？",
        "answer": 2.0666985504229953
    },
    {
        "question": "3,555 × 28,219=？",
        "answer": 8.001381224612503
    },
    {
        "question": "351 × 885=？",
        "answer": 5.49225038716365
    },
    {
        "question": "1,493 × 128,555=？",
        "answer": 8.283148780420595
    },
    {
        "question": "126,379 ÷ 4,543=？",
        "answer": 1.444332177781945
    },
    {
        "question": "34,583 × 501=？",
        "answer": 7.238700390540631
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 54,661,162=？",
        "answer": 8.968127781168578
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,737,824=？",
        "answer": 7.240005790697662
    },
    {
        "question": "406,927 × 263=？",
        "answer": 8.029472255157957
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 545=？",
        "answer": 2.7363965022766426
    },
    {
        "question": "2,719,966 ÷ 36,939=？",
        "answer": 1.8670783411278649
    },
    {
        "question": "93,771,715 ÷ 706=？",
        "answer": 5.123267157882799
    },
    {
        "question": "6,275 ÷ 2,105=？",
        "answer": 0.47436162998138864
    },
    {
        "question": "348 × 1,074=？",
        "answer": 5.572583525310118
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 283=？",
        "answer": 3.296884475538547
    },
    {
        "question": "3,076,380 ÷ 15,875=？",
        "answer": 2.287326245315635
    },
    {
        "question": "205,077 × 3,251=？",
        "answer": 8.823933925168255
    },
    {
        "question": "742 × 145,642=？",
        "answer": 8.03369053944508
    },
    {
        "question": "366 × 2,331=？",
        "answer": 5.931023358914987
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,452,482=？",
        "answer": 7.276054111373258
    },
    {
        "question": "23,031 × 549=？",
        "answer": 7.101885139776602
    },
    {
        "question": "101,292 ÷ 23,240=？",
        "answer": 0.6393390225990139
    },
    {
        "question": "114,293,499 ÷ 19,855,022=？",
        "answer": 0.7601511558693531
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 88,675=？",
        "answer": 4.94780119714398
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 25,403,484=？",
        "answer": 7.882014537410988
    },
    {
        "question": "481,170 × 337=？",
        "answer": 8.209928442979276
    },
    {
        "question": "1,577,108 ÷ 5,204=？",
        "answer": 2.4815241468458398
    },
    {
        "question": "56,797,404 ÷ 773,028=？",
        "answer": 1.8661332612950374
    },
    {
        "question": "21,270,924 ÷ 371=？",
        "answer": 4.758412446267244
    },
    {
        "question": "26,775,008 ÷ 738,536=？",
        "answer": 1.5593579393797394
    },
    {
        "question": "1,099,297 ÷ 296=？",
        "answer": 3.569823331715219
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 610=？",
        "answer": 4.418798290590353
    },
    {
        "question": "21,982,935 ÷ 4,226,302=？",
        "answer": 0.7161251484447417
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 16,646,673=？",
        "answer": 7.920297452861833
    },
    {
        "question": "3,662 ÷ 542=？",
        "answer": 0.8297190534272908
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 288,846=？",
        "answer": 5.937787612437648
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 4,300,547=？",
        "answer": 7.7474670506708465
    },
    {
        "question": "395,756,704 ÷ 21,863=？",
        "answer": 4.257718525635285
    },
    {
        "question": "131,159 × 1,675=？",
        "answer": 8.341812908176706
    },
    {
        "question": "532 × 118,303=？",
        "answer": 7.7989073901683375
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 79,463=？",
        "answer": 5.201194952794743
    },
    {
        "question": "232,766 ÷ 329=？",
        "answer": 2.8497236455074133
    },
    {
        "question": "92,770 ÷ 8,584=？",
        "answer": 1.033717847639578
    },
    {
        "question": "760,833,122 ÷ 7,255,088=？",
        "answer": 2.0206467263092778
    },
    {
        "question": "24,295 × 977=？",
        "answer": 7.375411467117798
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 315,148,818=？",
        "answer": 8.799545678259868
    },
    {
        "question": "555,090,912 ÷ 7,159=？",
        "answer": 4.889511754662611
    },
    {
        "question": "7,664 × 20,792=？",
        "answer": 8.202351762563444
    },
    {
        "question": "26,766 ÷ 319=？",
        "answer": 1.9237927905680792
    },
    {
        "question": "73 × 4,411,416=？",
        "answer": 8.507900874141372
    },
    {
        "question": "189,825 ÷ 40,331=？",
        "answer": 0.6727144181540954
    },
    {
        "question": "141,544 ÷ 1,953=？",
        "answer": 1.8601892212142608
    },
    {
        "question": "122 × 1,800=？",
        "answer": 5.341632335778054
    },
    {
        "question": "338,938,381 ÷ 285,042,098=？",
        "answer": 0.07521174473992062
    },
    {
        "question": "656,801,785 ÷ 59,243=？",
        "answer": 4.044797281803301
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 90,130,744=？",
        "answer": 8.255902951705062
    },
    {
        "question": "252,567,368 ÷ 3,048,477=？",
        "answer": 1.9182943157611352
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,493,721=？",
        "answer": 6.776329478047132
    },
    {
        "question": "30,873,085 ÷ 753=？",
        "answer": 4.612785052424077
    },
    {
        "question": "721 × 1,135=？",
        "answer": 5.91293112624857
    },
    {
        "question": "11,931,839 ÷ 54,154=？",
        "answer": 2.3430768440349112
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 261,353=？",
        "answer": 6.894348744330275
    },
    {
        "question": "37,857,788 ÷ 302=？",
        "answer": 5.098148291935849
    },
    {
        "question": "4,171 × 101,988=？",
        "answer": 8.628789265133555
    },
    {
        "question": "244 × 36,235=？",
        "answer": 6.946518091993027
    },
    {
        "question": "10,644,601 ÷ 1,018,837=？",
        "answer": 1.0190246786954498
    },
    {
        "question": "23,825 × 4,849=？",
        "answer": 8.062685093425888
    },
    {
        "question": "8,630 × 4,295=？",
        "answer": 7.5689739638824705
    },
    {
        "question": "161,800 ÷ 242=？",
        "answer": 2.8251631512958224
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 16,126,483=？",
        "answer": 8.161782172535887
    },
    {
        "question": "8,668,940 ÷ 720=？",
        "answer": 4.080633500664943
    },
    {
        "question": "545,025,629 ÷ 318,288,497=？",
        "answer": 0.23359598136455095
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 40,059=？",
        "answer": 5.301670108057866
    },
    {
        "question": "506 × 278=？",
        "answer": 5.148195312757875
    },
    {
        "question": "238,308,941 ÷ 465=？",
        "answer": 5.709687383850623
    },
    {
        "question": "20,955 ÷ 582=？",
        "answer": 1.5563646805199747
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 1,735,583=？",
        "answer": 7.3855734232506745
    },
    {
        "question": "3,119 ÷ 2,449=？",
        "answer": 0.10502658963242964
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 77,958=？",
        "answer": 5.368981943552811
    },
    {
        "question": "27,155 ÷ 1,399=？",
        "answer": 1.2880320926368187
    },
    {
        "question": "10,275,282 ÷ 10,802=？",
        "answer": 2.9782895767623776
    },
    {
        "question": "7,285,262 ÷ 2,584=？",
        "answer": 3.450152665603581
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,289=？",
        "answer": 3.4112829130173843
    },
    {
        "question": "416,452,680 ÷ 48,992,316=？",
        "answer": 0.9294376910245318
    },
    {
        "question": "1,689,335 ÷ 54,881=？",
        "answer": 1.4882937638030693
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 205=？",
        "answer": 2.788875115775417
    },
    {
        "question": "21,552 ÷ 3,703=？",
        "answer": 0.7649338663294678
    },
    {
        "question": "281,077,510 ÷ 2,882,726=？",
        "answer": 1.9890227324415322
    },
    {
        "question": "2,835 × 45,052=？",
        "answer": 8.106267138670175
    },
    {
        "question": "32,696,793 ÷ 1,762,195=？",
        "answer": 1.2684511931836242
    },
    {
        "question": "2,834 × 60,337=？",
        "answer": 8.232983558846279
    },
    {
        "question": "2,919 × 86,633=？",
        "answer": 8.402917448760062
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 870,826=？",
        "answer": 8.02271675748381
    },
    {
        "question": "723,869,751 ÷ 8,638=？",
        "answer": 4.923247229039827
    },
    {
        "question": "4,292 × 7,034=？",
        "answer": 7.479862077274837
    },
    {
        "question": "7,298 × 10,062=？",
        "answer": 7.865888172018359
    },
    {
        "question": "11,293,377 ÷ 2,282=？",
        "answer": 3.694508186091378
    },
    {
        "question": "11,224 × 16,615=？",
        "answer": 8.270648003635033
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 10,653,866=？",
        "answer": 8.69026506178511
    },
    {
        "question": "617 × 492=？",
        "answer": 5.482250266800602
    },
    {
        "question": "56,139 × 405=？",
        "answer": 7.356719695525381
    },
    {
        "question": "157,023 × 6,233=？",
        "answer": 8.990660397399918
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,637=？",
        "answer": 3.691169934131604
    },
    {
        "question": "6,219,308 ÷ 629=？",
        "answer": 3.9950914195509517
    },
    {
        "question": "497,100,028 ÷ 1,897=？",
        "answer": 5.418376456712709
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 5,815=？",
        "answer": 5.454745799092981
    },
    {
        "question": "219,023 ÷ 1,611=？",
        "answer": 2.1333941828619776
    },
    {
        "question": "1,125,258 ÷ 193,935=？",
        "answer": 0.763595914719537
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 21,841=？",
        "answer": 5.418453764903565
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 7,875=？",
        "answer": 5.311223910432456
    },
    {
        "question": "630,847 ÷ 29,619=？",
        "answer": 1.328353650374433
    },
    {
        "question": "782,472,055 ÷ 390,478=？",
        "answer": 3.3018722659878748
    },
    {
        "question": "3,395,502 ÷ 1,954,731=？",
        "answer": 0.23981699013180435
    },
    {
        "question": "100,928 × 230=？",
        "answer": 7.365739503330383
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 1,412,117=？",
        "answer": 7.380319602760708
    },
    {
        "question": "969 × 103,085=？",
        "answer": 7.999519252313281
    },
    {
        "question": "23,718 ÷ 472=？",
        "answer": 1.7011360660925265
    },
    {
        "question": "650,677 ÷ 5,384=？",
        "answer": 2.082260404435067
    },
    {
        "question": "29,046,660 ÷ 59,931=？",
        "answer": 2.6854446768707803
    },
    {
        "question": "21,625 × 357=？",
        "answer": 6.887624332249045
    },
    {
        "question": "923,246,919 ÷ 302=？",
        "answer": 6.485310924068783
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 2,486=？",
        "answer": 4.939569168655901
    },
    {
        "question": "1,639,623 ÷ 762,887=？",
        "answer": 0.3322837874533315
    },
    {
        "question": "2,336,529 ÷ 36,141=？",
        "answer": 1.8105710106099229
    },
    {
        "question": "3,935,259 ÷ 235=？",
        "answer": 4.223905458557835
    },
    {
        "question": "12,325,146 ÷ 749,078=？",
        "answer": 1.2162650302291385
    },
    {
        "question": "120,505,889 ÷ 82,464=？",
        "answer": 3.1647438740874643
    },
    {
        "question": "207,769,878 ÷ 2,083,296=？",
        "answer": 1.9988316047701578
    },
    {
        "question": "372,868 ÷ 167,512=？",
        "answer": 0.34750918936982916
    },
    {
        "question": "2,165,007 ÷ 32,990=？",
        "answer": 1.817076989327162
    },
    {
        "question": "1,023 ÷ 277=？",
        "answer": 0.5673958646477116
    },
    {
        "question": "1,415 × 362,178=？",
        "answer": 8.709678506023929
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 247,987=？",
        "answer": 6.649701419896275
    },
    {
        "question": "91,749,228 ÷ 62,010,119=？",
        "answer": 0.17013985390467198
    },
    {
        "question": "11,780,083 ÷ 265,700=？",
        "answer": 1.6467567959996348
    },
    {
        "question": "3,446 × 26,298=？",
        "answer": 7.9572379941496125
    },
    {
        "question": "3,995,475 ÷ 54,952=？",
        "answer": 1.8615849142280871
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 557,531=？",
        "answer": 6.445239024495036
    },
    {
        "question": "102,168,716 ÷ 1,087,390=？",
        "answer": 1.9729326006745034
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,230,105=？",
        "answer": 6.993032170768195
    },
    {
        "question": "1,938 × 306=？",
        "answer": 5.7730751991963265
    },
    {
        "question": "1,440 × 220=？",
        "answer": 5.500785172917456
    },
    {
        "question": "3,040,908 ÷ 12,151=？",
        "answer": 2.3983912602796265
    },
    {
        "question": "123,032 ÷ 100,458=？",
        "answer": 0.08803355630674418
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 105,980=？",
        "answer": 5.803375165561954
    },
    {
        "question": "2,035,768 ÷ 6,704=？",
        "answer": 2.4823942778358337
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 206,434=？",
        "answer": 5.7919024825407535
    },
    {
        "question": "35,995,161 ÷ 543,981=？",
        "answer": 1.8206603893671087
    },
    {
        "question": "158,039 ÷ 53,694=？",
        "answer": 0.4688385145317904
    },
    {
        "question": "3,804 × 5,917=？",
        "answer": 7.352342077542388
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 3,051,549=？",
        "answer": 7.525913033155165
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 893,450=？",
        "answer": 7.127161512224493
    },
    {
        "question": "992,795,090 ÷ 70,275=？",
        "answer": 4.150058766355454
    },
    {
        "question": "299,773,378 ÷ 3,161,930=？",
        "answer": 1.9768408106701396
    },
    {
        "question": "44,261 ÷ 734=？",
        "answer": 1.7803251619114047
    },
    {
        "question": "870,413,110 ÷ 93,238=？",
        "answer": 3.9701324745432167
    },
    {
        "question": "8,747,365 ÷ 437=？",
        "answer": 4.301395811674379
    },
    {
        "question": "608,044 ÷ 17,541=？",
        "answer": 1.5398806587845297
    },
    {
        "question": "365 × 860=？",
        "answer": 5.496791315700042
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 15,058=？",
        "answer": 4.177767292804646
    },
    {
        "question": "6,571 × 109,723=？",
        "answer": 8.85792914058194
    },
    {
        "question": "41,624 ÷ 3,576=？",
        "answer": 1.0659463027641
    },
    {
        "question": "2,966,333 ÷ 106,990=？",
        "answer": 1.4428767157291094
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 2,053=？",
        "answer": 4.090540199754235
    },
    {
        "question": "587,272 ÷ 212=？",
        "answer": 3.442503434081791
    },
    {
        "question": "44,391,650 ÷ 52,936=？",
        "answer": 2.9235501660475776
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 13,180,985=？",
        "answer": 7.1199478658027955
    },
    {
        "question": "561,900 × 1,014=？",
        "answer": 8.755696987092216
    },
    {
        "question": "66,512,781 ÷ 60,676,923=？",
        "answer": 0.03988155764736402
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,683=？",
        "answer": 4.180326625415149
    },
    {
        "question": "914 × 763,953=？",
        "answer": 8.84401283641878
    },
    {
        "question": "1,396,005 × 617=？",
        "answer": 8.935172137813593
    },
    {
        "question": "76,496 × 4,502=？",
        "answer": 8.537044217016215
    },
    {
        "question": "9,718,384 ÷ 3,237=？",
        "answer": 3.477451355829277
    },
    {
        "question": "143,560,411 ÷ 4,288,318=？",
        "answer": 1.5247477100436244
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 86,855=？",
        "answer": 6.443944802944192
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,435=？",
        "answer": 3.646893624167745
    },
    {
        "question": "98 × 472,739=？",
        "answer": 7.665847507879312
    },
    {
        "question": "148,259,257 ÷ 6,953,979=？",
        "answer": 1.3287884444847178
    },
    {
        "question": "12,010,411 ÷ 35,848=？",
        "answer": 2.52509293844446
    },
    {
        "question": "1,568 × 2,882=？",
        "answer": 6.65504003482639
    },
    {
        "question": "2,187 ÷ 252=？",
        "answer": 0.938448242256093
    },
    {
        "question": "251,403,910 ÷ 26,974=？",
        "answer": 3.9694266746692812
    },
    {
        "question": "215,980 ÷ 207=？",
        "answer": 3.018443191380183
    },
    {
        "question": "13,598,029 ÷ 14,669=？",
        "answer": 2.9670754544673588
    },
    {
        "question": "4,097,776 ÷ 8,553=？",
        "answer": 2.680429742499012
    },
    {
        "question": "315,920,455 ÷ 533,160=？",
        "answer": 2.7727201869269726
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 726,406,582=？",
        "answer": 8.86117977069107
    },
    {
        "question": "23,677,993 ÷ 349,289=？",
        "answer": 1.8311599790188449
    },
    {
        "question": "270 × 2,804,731=？",
        "answer": 8.87925497883574
    },
    {
        "question": "599,095 ÷ 40,263=？",
        "answer": 1.1725895639358872
    },
    {
        "question": "1,713,920 ÷ 44,528=？",
        "answer": 1.5853573576699096
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,591=？",
        "answer": 4.201670179646581
    },
    {
        "question": "320,862,702 ÷ 1,722=？",
        "answer": 5.270286089276656
    },
    {
        "question": "112,715 ÷ 308=？",
        "answer": 2.5634309988690274
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 6,541=？",
        "answer": 4.857036834290191
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 459=？",
        "answer": 4.295281141116848
    },
    {
        "question": "233,008,631 ÷ 404,806=？",
        "answer": 2.760125067307929
    },
    {
        "question": "423,850,473 ÷ 1,861,972=？",
        "answer": 2.357239526296559
    },
    {
        "question": "1,159,436 ÷ 29,526=？",
        "answer": 1.5940421654873251
    },
    {
        "question": "9,856 × 2,577=？",
        "answer": 7.404815113371255
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 70,021,207=？",
        "answer": 8.447289584031209
    },
    {
        "question": "438 × 9,641=？",
        "answer": 6.62559619336521
    },
    {
        "question": "14,115,021 ÷ 571=？",
        "answer": 4.393045420370801
    },
    {
        "question": "31,722 × 942=？",
        "answer": 7.475411463581632
    },
    {
        "question": "48,200,297 ÷ 154,444=？",
        "answer": 2.4942786732328375
    },
    {
        "question": "25,372 ÷ 7,926=？",
        "answer": 0.5053006347272553
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 520=？",
        "answer": 4.90633504180509
    },
    {
        "question": "370,849 ÷ 352=？",
        "answer": 3.022654448789549
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 15,524=？",
        "answer": 5.492033629731958
    },
    {
        "question": "10,800 × 3,433=？",
        "answer": 7.569097558912699
    },
    {
        "question": "68 × 397=？",
        "answer": 4.431299419469352
    },
    {
        "question": "896,422,331 ÷ 162,774=？",
        "answer": 3.7409276308713086
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 210,250=？",
        "answer": 6.799857259189612
    },
    {
        "question": "295,000 ÷ 717=？",
        "answer": 2.614302860310363
    },
    {
        "question": "24,542 × 20,527=？",
        "answer": 8.702235434087164
    },
    {
        "question": "16,329 ÷ 426=？",
        "answer": 1.5835499899340173
    },
    {
        "question": "363,345 ÷ 587=？",
        "answer": 2.7916810869851174
    },
    {
        "question": "132,026 × 486=？",
        "answer": 7.80729573489707
    },
    {
        "question": "199 × 2,667,570=？",
        "answer": 8.724968901025374
    },
    {
        "question": "14,695 × 639=？",
        "answer": 6.972670448567031
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 35,170,432=？",
        "answer": 7.8472076984723635
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 16,983=？",
        "answer": 5.661378173763244
    },
    {
        "question": "234,757 ÷ 2,372=？",
        "answer": 1.9955038662610396
    },
    {
        "question": "963,821,146 ÷ 630=？",
        "answer": 6.184655900930752
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 7,874,394=？",
        "answer": 8.151489646284586
    },
    {
        "question": "11,569,143 ÷ 56,625=？",
        "answer": 2.3102929741680347
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 34,509,383=？",
        "answer": 8.969300958684007
    },
    {
        "question": "5,372,724 ÷ 15,901=？",
        "answer": 2.528770093598176
    },
    {
        "question": "46,192 ÷ 3,527=？",
        "answer": 1.1171613068691557
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 12,427=？",
        "answer": 5.685430905362634
    },
    {
        "question": "40,392,862 ÷ 11,085,203=？",
        "answer": 0.561560975178082
    },
    {
        "question": "456,775 ÷ 55,687=？",
        "answer": 0.9139485043075004
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 10,927,483=？",
        "answer": 7.339550135189713
    },
    {
        "question": "4,768,696 ÷ 36,201=？",
        "answer": 2.1196790699884684
    },
    {
        "question": "41,166,759 ÷ 444,858=？",
        "answer": 1.966325271952581
    },
    {
        "question": "138,020 × 673=？",
        "answer": 7.967957087293956
    },
    {
        "question": "266,557,510 ÷ 10,064,094=？",
        "answer": 1.4230162383709075
    },
    {
        "question": "1,981 ÷ 793=？",
        "answer": 0.39761128822094327
    },
    {
        "question": "19,040,349 ÷ 71,503=？",
        "answer": 2.425350640955459
    },
    {
        "question": "622,548,284 ÷ 546=？",
        "answer": 6.056980397659922
    },
    {
        "question": "41,912,131 ÷ 609,145=？",
        "answer": 1.8376190590941088
    },
    {
        "question": "9,406,139 ÷ 13,075=？",
        "answer": 2.856969694740932
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,401,367=？",
        "answer": 6.3804585381889645
    },
    {
        "question": "35,540 ÷ 2,530=？",
        "answer": 1.147596902293465
    },
    {
        "question": "232,095 ÷ 422=？",
        "answer": 2.740353333631257
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 414,155=？",
        "answer": 6.462260948880278
    },
    {
        "question": "170,931 × 652=？",
        "answer": 8.047068429125744
    },
    {
        "question": "256,232,765 ÷ 8,169=？",
        "answer": 4.496465767010529
    },
    {
        "question": "13,913 × 38,101=？",
        "answer": 8.724357159461267
    },
    {
        "question": "344,263 ÷ 127,476=？",
        "answer": 0.43146192146649687
    },
    {
        "question": "734,077 ÷ 186,207=？",
        "answer": 0.5957456138307486
    },
    {
        "question": "115 × 83,718=？",
        "answer": 6.983516684968434
    },
    {
        "question": "6,058,936 ÷ 8,648=？",
        "answer": 2.845480684161667
    },
    {
        "question": "4,570 ÷ 848=？",
        "answer": 0.7315203478131365
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 149,696=？",
        "answer": 7.17521019579304
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 1,446,219=？",
        "answer": 7.364354045524474
    },
    {
        "question": "2,786 × 12,271=？",
        "answer": 7.533861068195996
    },
    {
        "question": "609,463,271 ÷ 430=？",
        "answer": 6.151479082623113
    },
    {
        "question": "12,624 × 10,018=？",
        "answer": 8.10197801321884
    },
    {
        "question": "322,468,883 ÷ 3,521,248=？",
        "answer": 1.9617911999322089
    },
    {
        "question": "9,881,306 ÷ 41,283=？",
        "answer": 2.379043098974763
    },
    {
        "question": "12,916,111 ÷ 2,455,120=？",
        "answer": 0.7210590444686646
    },
    {
        "question": "1,594 × 170,270=？",
        "answer": 8.433626453089813
    },
    {
        "question": "331 × 11,203=？",
        "answer": 6.569162329748003
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,477,394=？",
        "answer": 6.541253900442168
    },
    {
        "question": "269 × 506=？",
        "answer": 5.133902796842207
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 15,771,381=？",
        "answer": 8.15211223285194
    },
    {
        "question": "1,216,466 × 631=？",
        "answer": 8.885129334230054
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 337=？",
        "answer": 2.5276299008713385
    },
    {
        "question": "350,640 ÷ 368=？",
        "answer": 2.9790136389723854
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 20,274=？",
        "answer": 5.930188732556441
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 7,640=？",
        "answer": 5.029221394253928
    },
    {
        "question": "1,889 × 5,659=？",
        "answer": 7.028971651857161
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 7,383=？",
        "answer": 5.4480164650392755
    },
    {
        "question": "7,615 × 12,560=？",
        "answer": 7.980659547073238
    },
    {
        "question": "73,746,831 ÷ 20,956,157=？",
        "answer": 0.5464317193869579
    },
    {
        "question": "34,321,997 ÷ 11,275,481=？",
        "answer": 0.48343747153009736
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 49,913,491=？",
        "answer": 8.953490451026642
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 15,466,480=？",
        "answer": 8.444663989421768
    },
    {
        "question": "86,587,631 ÷ 343=？",
        "answer": 5.402161737654633
    },
    {
        "question": "145,167 ÷ 1,247=？",
        "answer": 2.0660014483762077
    },
    {
        "question": "12,377,776 ÷ 36,379=？",
        "answer": 2.5317918621850373
    },
    {
        "question": "344 × 1,013,015=？",
        "answer": 8.54217431870081
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 193,598=？",
        "answer": 6.286900866435958
    },
    {
        "question": "2,721 × 461=？",
        "answer": 6.098429467169406
    },
    {
        "question": "23,348,979 ÷ 5,884,799=？",
        "answer": 0.5985362608068702
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 643=？",
        "answer": 3.5071809772602407
    },
    {
        "question": "584,535,880 ÷ 125,622=？",
        "answer": 3.667745470764549
    },
    {
        "question": "43,417,816 ÷ 891,334=？",
        "answer": 1.6876275007828434
    },
    {
        "question": "27,168 × 1,286=？",
        "answer": 7.543298637152062
    },
    {
        "question": "313 × 928,910=？",
        "answer": 8.463517975763112
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 4,929=？",
        "answer": 5.53160790889198
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 146,376,313=？",
        "answer": 8.165470803732664
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 4,602=？",
        "answer": 4.61718912377195
    },
    {
        "question": "64,307,083 ÷ 1,797,578=？",
        "answer": 1.5535710659763795
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 21,699=？",
        "answer": 4.336439719816778
    },
    {
        "question": "83 × 47,526=？",
        "answer": 6.596009356049543
    },
    {
        "question": "51,185 ÷ 1,214=？",
        "answer": 1.6249240208835587
    },
    {
        "question": "1,261,945 ÷ 195,748=？",
        "answer": 0.8093430937688857
    },
    {
        "question": "841,202,907 ÷ 39,743=？",
        "answer": 4.325640118110525
    },
    {
        "question": "860,017 ÷ 575=？",
        "answer": 3.174839191360009
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 242,383,521=？",
        "answer": 8.38450308999076
    },
    {
        "question": "20,389,596 ÷ 7,609=？",
        "answer": 3.4280810366403687
    },
    {
        "question": "489,101,429 ÷ 356,995,536=？",
        "answer": 0.136736146122085
    },
    {
        "question": "158,085 ÷ 14,093=？",
        "answer": 1.0498872116388218
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 55,342,769=？",
        "answer": 7.743060884680893
    },
    {
        "question": "11,120 × 4,834=？",
        "answer": 7.73041143331767
    },
    {
        "question": "352,993 ÷ 7,298=？",
        "answer": 1.684562234201924
    },
    {
        "question": "79 × 892,134=？",
        "answer": 7.848057182314355
    },
    {
        "question": "119,945,217 ÷ 92,335,643=？",
        "answer": 0.11361355664637411
    },
    {
        "question": "8,416,708 ÷ 74,499=？",
        "answer": 2.052991817249646
    },
    {
        "question": "225 × 8,515=？",
        "answer": 6.282367170409982
    },
    {
        "question": "78 × 211=？",
        "answer": 4.216377057988173
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 484,470=？",
        "answer": 6.287326880582975
    },
    {
        "question": "693,107,646 ÷ 1,813,800=？",
        "answer": 2.5822112922209857
    },
    {
        "question": "727,571,244 ÷ 7,072,665=？",
        "answer": 2.012292437975821
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 366=？",
        "answer": 3.4665710723863543
    },
    {
        "question": "753,463,906 ÷ 118,981,747=？",
        "answer": 0.8015821113197703
    },
    {
        "question": "878,600,134 ÷ 304,537=？",
        "answer": 3.4601511999879913
    },
    {
        "question": "10,286,647 ÷ 3,304,473=？",
        "answer": 0.49317162898411987
    },
    {
        "question": "381,221,962 ÷ 88,264=？",
        "answer": 3.6353943069968233
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 3,197,356=？",
        "answer": 7.618734346485315
    },
    {
        "question": "2,251,815 ÷ 99,900=？",
        "answer": 1.3529672195432685
    },
    {
        "question": "138,625 × 6,012=？",
        "answer": 8.920860531072087
    },
    {
        "question": "527,116,970 ÷ 42,020,349=？",
        "answer": 1.0984473429958572
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 112,482=？",
        "answer": 5.051083029770714
    },
    {
        "question": "174,807 × 3,560=？",
        "answer": 8.794008817578492
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 21,886,705=？",
        "answer": 7.641210379980675
    },
    {
        "question": "72,085 ÷ 203=？",
        "answer": 2.550348864878803
    },
    {
        "question": "33,670 ÷ 2,204=？",
        "answer": 1.1840315262083412
    },
    {
        "question": "560,390 ÷ 9,256=？",
        "answer": 1.7820670308778095
    },
    {
        "question": "7,529,536 ÷ 254=？",
        "answer": 4.47193449744949
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,350,400=？",
        "answer": 6.431492424945561
    },
    {
        "question": "67,693,430 ÷ 308=？",
        "answer": 5.3419958036883015
    },
    {
        "question": "383,644 ÷ 235,189=？",
        "answer": 0.21251140490416504
    },
    {
        "question": "340,935,651 ÷ 28,948=？",
        "answer": 4.07105385300685
    },
    {
        "question": "1,995 × 1,566=？",
        "answer": 6.494734657744692
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 151,160=？",
        "answer": 6.6108006474039644
    },
    {
        "question": "15,566 × 550=？",
        "answer": 6.932539715606996
    },
    {
        "question": "15,065,344 ÷ 371,188=？",
        "answer": 1.6083851251156873
    },
    {
        "question": "130 × 1,365=？",
        "answer": 5.249076003683611
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,375=？",
        "answer": 4.05595140532915
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 565,739=？",
        "answer": 5.752616118462835
    },
    {
        "question": "2,047 × 94,332=？",
        "answer": 8.285776884985845
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,322=？",
        "answer": 4.027104865879351
    },
    {
        "question": "6,529,114 ÷ 5,887=？",
        "answer": 3.0449602157512023
    },
    {
        "question": "18,859,036 ÷ 19,687=？",
        "answer": 2.981339948244534
    },
    {
        "question": "548,334,325 ÷ 1,166=？",
        "answer": 5.6723468825688155
    },
    {
        "question": "48,651 ÷ 1,778=？",
        "answer": 1.4371600147948111
    },
    {
        "question": "4,571 ÷ 1,127=？",
        "answer": 0.6080873052432242
    },
    {
        "question": "36,512 ÷ 290=？",
        "answer": 2.1000376248391643
    },
    {
        "question": "1,258 × 9,753=？",
        "answer": 7.088818865325039
    },
    {
        "question": "7,642,535 ÷ 205=？",
        "answer": 4.5714835752559555
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 72,093=？",
        "answer": 5.9718364504665065
    },
    {
        "question": "3,673 × 4,065=？",
        "answer": 7.17408147827538
    },
    {
        "question": "418,817 ÷ 1,011=？",
        "answer": 2.6172731460126286
    },
    {
        "question": "732,052 ÷ 1,001=？",
        "answer": 2.8641078540038785
    },
    {
        "question": "5,468,368 ÷ 1,317=？",
        "answer": 3.618271958255064
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 119,979,533=？",
        "answer": 8.079107167187052
    },
    {
        "question": "449,180 ÷ 9,488=？",
        "answer": 1.6752457347860463
    },
    {
        "question": "7,390,179 ÷ 283,345=？",
        "answer": 1.4163394043738549
    },
    {
        "question": "419,515,432 ÷ 803=？",
        "answer": 5.718032395831628
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 8,698=？",
        "answer": 5.687607430335517
    },
    {
        "question": "96 × 17,990=？",
        "answer": 6.23730239638512
    },
    {
        "question": "244 × 1,873=？",
        "answer": 5.6599276037139665
    },
    {
        "question": "634,817 ÷ 6,475=？",
        "answer": 1.9914087756183292
    },
    {
        "question": "123,904,936 ÷ 92,126,401=？",
        "answer": 0.1287045023137347
    },
    {
        "question": "416,015,239 ÷ 51,238=？",
        "answer": 3.9095170701458
    },
    {
        "question": "39,961,167 ÷ 3,643=？",
        "answer": 4.040178991351565
    },
    {
        "question": "55,537 × 526=？",
        "answer": 7.465568160464004
    },
    {
        "question": "1,541 × 557,787=？",
        "answer": 8.934271026930888
    },
    {
        "question": "780 × 101,173=？",
        "answer": 7.897159230653527
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 11,623=？",
        "answer": 5.99473716351803
    },
    {
        "question": "21,481,755 ÷ 1,193,002=？",
        "answer": 1.2554285873946038
    },
    {
        "question": "24,318,194 ÷ 2,089,282=？",
        "answer": 1.0659342560918954
    },
    {
        "question": "1,537,618 ÷ 782,524=？",
        "answer": 0.29335078815888177
    },
    {
        "question": "283,615,346 ÷ 26,491,752=？",
        "answer": 1.0296190453806533
    },
    {
        "question": "31,051,565 ÷ 1,569,304=？",
        "answer": 1.296376411799815
    },
    {
        "question": "9,332 × 1,212=？",
        "answer": 7.053477349951982
    },
    {
        "question": "1,344,904 ÷ 1,053,908=？",
        "answer": 0.10588858409691508
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 3,065,534=？",
        "answer": 8.394991156151722
    },
    {
        "question": "11,266 × 3,331=？",
        "answer": 7.574344379590509
    },
    {
        "question": "4,661 × 248=？",
        "answer": 6.062930783758802
    },
    {
        "question": "1,978 × 6,978=？",
        "answer": 7.139957252373253
    },
    {
        "question": "901,213,517 ÷ 53,779=？",
        "answer": 4.224214974516204
    },
    {
        "question": "87,440 ÷ 50,590=？",
        "answer": 0.23764546953307905
    },
    {
        "question": "5,416 × 1,382=？",
        "answer": 6.874186698715268
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 38,643,387=？",
        "answer": 7.587075184279311
    },
    {
        "question": "1,593 × 673=？",
        "answer": 6.030230840025109
    },
    {
        "question": "28,186,083 ÷ 13,764,125=？",
        "answer": 0.3112861184213638
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,861,577=？",
        "answer": 6.456605436501682
    },
    {
        "question": "2,786 ÷ 1,823=？",
        "answer": 0.18419444343296834
    },
    {
        "question": "23,891 × 402=？",
        "answer": 6.982460381377366
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 557=？",
        "answer": 4.126066436885335
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 22,166,654=？",
        "answer": 8.54982012507102
    },
    {
        "question": "357,223 × 709=？",
        "answer": 8.403585648589694
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 253=？",
        "answer": 3.5170638734826545
    },
    {
        "question": "140,857,594 ÷ 9,935,005=？",
        "answer": 1.151612175886648
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 1,035=？",
        "answer": 4.853789440530192
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 2,837,222=？",
        "answer": 8.086361774316195
    },
    {
        "question": "2,465,393 ÷ 520=？",
        "answer": 3.675882814918443
    },
    {
        "question": "571,435 ÷ 2,002=？",
        "answer": 2.4555027639558444
    },
    {
        "question": "352,596 ÷ 151,093=？",
        "answer": 0.36803303682829863
    },
    {
        "question": "5,162,196 ÷ 5,255=？",
        "answer": 2.992261769596101
    },
    {
        "question": "13,905,797 ÷ 188,968=？",
        "answer": 1.8668076185590396
    },
    {
        "question": "176 × 954=？",
        "answer": 5.225061042518245
    },
    {
        "question": "7,807 × 92,559=？",
        "answer": 8.858902833251035
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 3,156,239=？",
        "answer": 8.581955252195781
    },
    {
        "question": "114,359 ÷ 38,490=？",
        "answer": 0.4729224379664852
    },
    {
        "question": "7,758 × 1,912=？",
        "answer": 7.171237663204119
    },
    {
        "question": "230 × 16,260=？",
        "answer": 6.572848377275642
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 225,731=？",
        "answer": 5.654621201194734
    },
    {
        "question": "7,196,715 ÷ 203=？",
        "answer": 4.549638266444681
    },
    {
        "question": "31,343 × 2,023=？",
        "answer": 7.802136445455095
    },
    {
        "question": "653 × 6,704=？",
        "answer": 6.641247186897294
    },
    {
        "question": "572,259,675 ÷ 828=？",
        "answer": 5.839562807093099
    },
    {
        "question": "4,746,428 ÷ 2,137,004=？",
        "answer": 0.3465615622469629
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 1,317=？",
        "answer": 4.911977464460038
    },
    {
        "question": "49,098,703 ÷ 851=？",
        "answer": 4.7611404597902585
    },
    {
        "question": "188,817,826 ÷ 72,487,420=？",
        "answer": 0.4157803505185492
    },
    {
        "question": "167 × 168,660=？",
        "answer": 7.449728567138668
    },
    {
        "question": "11,325 ÷ 441=？",
        "answer": 1.409599621217031
    },
    {
        "question": "2,889,125 ÷ 1,969,573=？",
        "answer": 0.16639425022491297
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 244,234,778=？",
        "answer": 8.86492876043039
    },
    {
        "question": "1,874 ÷ 1,368=？",
        "answer": 0.13668348916766207
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 8,727,523=？",
        "answer": 7.940891002001819
    },
    {
        "question": "6,064,876 ÷ 395=？",
        "answer": 4.186224830257702
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 58,613=？",
        "answer": 5.06902394618913
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 7,039=？",
        "answer": 5.391579009553523
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 762,218=？",
        "answer": 6.183109196211872
    },
    {
        "question": "12,856 ÷ 296=？",
        "answer": 1.6378141526963497
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 721,595,450=？",
        "answer": 8.858293786110766
    },
    {
        "question": "5,092,331 ÷ 5,312=？",
        "answer": 2.9816585585512536
    },
    {
        "question": "39,057,842 ÷ 11,601=？",
        "answer": 3.527212817448855
    },
    {
        "question": "99 × 895=？",
        "answer": 4.947458229913462
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 346,070,670=？",
        "answer": 8.840194789419492
    },
    {
        "question": "784,963 ÷ 23,722=？",
        "answer": 1.5196978847615519
    },
    {
        "question": "108,457 × 226=？",
        "answer": 7.389366026509746
    },
    {
        "question": "6,160,442 ÷ 11,906=？",
        "answer": 2.7138459948698794
    },
    {
        "question": "6,277,301 ÷ 499,047=？",
        "answer": 1.0996315046174356
    },
    {
        "question": "122 × 469=？",
        "answer": 4.757532673389831
    },
    {
        "question": "20,413 ÷ 213=？",
        "answer": 1.981527232129943
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 33,574=？",
        "answer": 4.827033081756795
    },
    {
        "question": "156,981,900 ÷ 1,354,265=？",
        "answer": 2.0641459265950304
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 43,619=？",
        "answer": 6.445855678796946
    },
    {
        "question": "422 × 26,378=？",
        "answer": 7.046554314882729
    },
    {
        "question": "19,632,439 ÷ 1,047=？",
        "answer": 4.2730275750501505
    },
    {
        "question": "10,111,503 ÷ 1,599,314=？",
        "answer": 0.8008819760781377
    },
    {
        "question": "1,161 × 16,571=？",
        "answer": 7.284180937052152
    },
    {
        "question": "207 × 3,163=？",
        "answer": 5.81606953737264
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,009=？",
        "answer": 4.117834518543748
    },
    {
        "question": "6,026,869 ÷ 11,011=？",
        "answer": 2.7382649891098714
    },
    {
        "question": "45,720,627 ÷ 3,081=？",
        "answer": 4.171420479241234
    },
    {
        "question": "10,796 ÷ 2,542=？",
        "answer": 0.6280873296664896
    },
    {
        "question": "124,744 ÷ 1,018=？",
        "answer": 2.0882718878814037
    },
    {
        "question": "1,106 × 1,898=？",
        "answer": 6.322051335059953
    },
    {
        "question": "2,243 ÷ 616=？",
        "answer": 0.5612485614185423
    },
    {
        "question": "7,772 ÷ 2,173=？",
        "answer": 0.5534730656072203
    },
    {
        "question": "685,611,463 ÷ 371=？",
        "answer": 6.26670416049617
    },
    {
        "question": "841,786,834 ÷ 34,752=？",
        "answer": 4.384222325292508
    },
    {
        "question": "42,543,271 ÷ 388=？",
        "answer": 5.039999152606197
    },
    {
        "question": "6,523,573 ÷ 144,080=？",
        "answer": 1.6558818267730788
    },
    {
        "question": "689,232,483 ÷ 5,026,481=？",
        "answer": 2.1371016919558397
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 17,655,762=？",
        "answer": 8.02503771627901
    },
    {
        "question": "993,155,326 ÷ 584=？",
        "answer": 6.230604328824457
    },
    {
        "question": "8,208,679 ÷ 349=？",
        "answer": 4.3714478459738615
    },
    {
        "question": "570,306 ÷ 641=？",
        "answer": 2.9492499111583172
    },
    {
        "question": "704,216,597 ÷ 352=？",
        "answer": 6.301163592843334
    },
    {
        "question": "2,422 × 32,631=？",
        "answer": 7.897804522059426
    },
    {
        "question": "66,254,874 ÷ 45,496=？",
        "answer": 3.16324461715257
    },
    {
        "question": "14,900 ÷ 1,283=？",
        "answer": 1.0649596120373455
    },
    {
        "question": "441,179,090 ÷ 6,433=？",
        "answer": 4.836201369156507
    },
    {
        "question": "798,415,640 ÷ 447,233=？",
        "answer": 3.2516951943023384
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 281,397,333=？",
        "answer": 8.750349972668635
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 11,754=？",
        "answer": 4.915283726392637
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,152=？",
        "answer": 3.711975854351756
    },
    {
        "question": "58,322 × 6,611=？",
        "answer": 8.586099565716264
    },
    {
        "question": "22,510 ÷ 427=？",
        "answer": 1.7219476199754962
    },
    {
        "question": "774 × 217,020=？",
        "answer": 8.225240719828156
    },
    {
        "question": "2,636,446 ÷ 5,660=？",
        "answer": 2.6682024492991645
    },
    {
        "question": "3,268 × 16,084=？",
        "answer": 7.720676112291251
    },
    {
        "question": "969,689 ÷ 2,173=？",
        "answer": 2.649572742749053
    },
    {
        "question": "40,188 × 541=？",
        "answer": 7.337293658694061
    },
    {
        "question": "10,646 × 15,266=？",
        "answer": 8.210911719882315
    },
    {
        "question": "82,914,218 ÷ 603=？",
        "answer": 5.13831169693233
    },
    {
        "question": "128 × 16,269=？",
        "answer": 6.318570828802986
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 69,805,913=？",
        "answer": 8.798134721095527
    },
    {
        "question": "369 × 115,526=？",
        "answer": 7.629706102645213
    },
    {
        "question": "545 ÷ 323=？",
        "answer": 0.22719397994553953
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 1,411,017=？",
        "answer": 8.11332007353202
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 1,133,002=？",
        "answer": 7.74442675651874
    },
    {
        "question": "294 × 2,918,060=？",
        "answer": 8.933441547853421
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,019,878=？",
        "answer": 6.305325138987779
    },
    {
        "question": "310 × 37,019=？",
        "answer": 7.0597863767452775
    },
    {
        "question": "200 × 66,032=？",
        "answer": 7.120784447197322
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,487=？",
        "answer": 3.172310968521954
    },
    {
        "question": "355,982 × 1,004=？",
        "answer": 8.553161751516962
    },
    {
        "question": "15,312,768 ÷ 546=？",
        "answer": 4.447861059977103
    },
    {
        "question": "518,009 ÷ 227,100=？",
        "answer": 0.358120171116969
    },
    {
        "question": "86,559 ÷ 1,241=？",
        "answer": 1.8435404489695113
    },
    {
        "question": "99,444,684 ÷ 2,677=？",
        "answer": 4.569933200877113
    },
    {
        "question": "403,345 ÷ 469=？",
        "answer": 2.9345038349371024
    },
    {
        "question": "168 × 607=？",
        "answer": 5.008497972801121
    },
    {
        "question": "391 × 4,119=？",
        "answer": 6.206968549352284
    },
    {
        "question": "1,420,586 ÷ 4,010=？",
        "answer": 2.5493231577266195
    },
    {
        "question": "490,729 ÷ 62,145=？",
        "answer": 0.8974355313449474
    },
    {
        "question": "22,419,498 ÷ 19,882=？",
        "answer": 3.052165814521377
    },
    {
        "question": "29,677,627 ÷ 779=？",
        "answer": 4.5808917144732835
    },
    {
        "question": "15,502 × 268=？",
        "answer": 6.618522526581701
    },
    {
        "question": "171,352,205 ÷ 128,080,594=？",
        "answer": 0.12640636435861052
    },
    {
        "question": "8,062 × 224=？",
        "answer": 6.256690812151195
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,117,402=？",
        "answer": 7.046003309828028
    },
    {
        "question": "550,935 ÷ 152,589=？",
        "answer": 0.557577136408853
    },
    {
        "question": "70,287 ÷ 2,763=？",
        "answer": 1.405494122175185
    },
    {
        "question": "3,003,210 ÷ 1,512,616=？",
        "answer": 0.297857011458998
    },
    {
        "question": "6,137 × 216=？",
        "answer": 6.1224098744348625
    },
    {
        "question": "784,886,483 ÷ 31,148,363=？",
        "answer": 1.401371622623083
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 2,681,693=？",
        "answer": 7.428409058363691
    },
    {
        "question": "949,201 ÷ 253,100=？",
        "answer": 0.574066041924187
    },
    {
        "question": "573 × 215=？",
        "answer": 5.090593081882996
    },
    {
        "question": "5,842,415 ÷ 189,779=？",
        "answer": 1.4883442487729672
    },
    {
        "question": "2,885 × 65,085=？",
        "answer": 8.273626726676643
    },
    {
        "question": "73,132,829 ÷ 6,844=？",
        "answer": 4.028802372710055
    },
    {
        "question": "440,408,366 ÷ 100,633=？",
        "answer": 3.641115140475175
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 10,714=？",
        "answer": 5.071344327195066
    },
    {
        "question": "1,336,521 × 716=？",
        "answer": 8.980888809278055
    },
    {
        "question": "23,646,889 ÷ 246=？",
        "answer": 4.982838905665823
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,154=？",
        "answer": 3.0622058088197126
    },
    {
        "question": "3,525,303 ÷ 130,535=？",
        "answer": 1.4314694770631402
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,915=？",
        "answer": 3.765668554759014
    },
    {
        "question": "85,958,238 ÷ 62,121=？",
        "answer": 3.141049066382132
    },
    {
        "question": "217,435,944 ÷ 970=？",
        "answer": 5.350559603968533
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 5,093=？",
        "answer": 4.962246181279484
    },
    {
        "question": "46,119 ÷ 11,329=？",
        "answer": 0.6096883051048445
    },
    {
        "question": "115 × 54,004=？",
        "answer": 6.793123768946781
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,926=？",
        "answer": 3.2846562827885157
    },
    {
        "question": "211,558,702 ÷ 2,297=？",
        "answer": 4.9642698985841065
    },
    {
        "question": "259,973,142 ÷ 3,831=？",
        "answer": 4.831616331050446
    },
    {
        "question": "94,245,289 ÷ 3,444,527=？",
        "answer": 1.4371300571947678
    },
    {
        "question": "1,567,986 ÷ 17,830=？",
        "answer": 1.9441908375264514
    },
    {
        "question": "325,999 ÷ 8,932=？",
        "answer": 1.5622675534748331
    },
    {
        "question": "36,461 × 1,371=？",
        "answer": 7.698866030477813
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 16,445,101=？",
        "answer": 8.061134585124385
    },
    {
        "question": "113,761 ÷ 2,499=？",
        "answer": 1.6582271448803125
    },
    {
        "question": "118,896 × 3,078=？",
        "answer": 8.563435859456884
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 157,878=？",
        "answer": 5.800381607439675
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 4,019=？",
        "answer": 5.558360515631359
    },
    {
        "question": "9,798,569 ÷ 7,238=？",
        "answer": 3.1315440764323483
    },
    {
        "question": "329,266 ÷ 25,992=？",
        "answer": 1.1027071894514238
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 26,664=？",
        "answer": 6.312416025824955
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 552,062,341=？",
        "answer": 8.741988122699432
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 53,564,442=？",
        "answer": 8.029906580734657
    },
    {
        "question": "53,412 × 8,238=？",
        "answer": 8.643460627950546
    },
    {
        "question": "222 × 12,460=？",
        "answer": 6.441871016773789
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 10,612,545=？",
        "answer": 7.326849540443458
    },
    {
        "question": "644 × 889,116=？",
        "answer": 8.757844292979545
    },
    {
        "question": "110,652,589 ÷ 26,367,203=？",
        "answer": 0.6228975169911204
    },
    {
        "question": "269 × 1,860,168=？",
        "answer": 8.699304449047272
    },
    {
        "question": "42,228 × 2,219=？",
        "answer": 7.971757815114825
    },
    {
        "question": "3,895 × 128,106=？",
        "answer": 8.698076932938815
    },
    {
        "question": "231,034,874 ÷ 7,452,061=？",
        "answer": 1.4914011390262538
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 17,442,836=？",
        "answer": 7.843677088840715
    },
    {
        "question": "1,096,989 ÷ 503=？",
        "answer": 3.3386342876753448
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 70,066,672=？",
        "answer": 7.845511490030179
    },
    {
        "question": "16,543 ÷ 2,185=？",
        "answer": 0.8791628284386536
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 263,079=？",
        "answer": 6.4992674284240355
    },
    {
        "question": "331,012,099 ÷ 4,166=？",
        "answer": 4.900124602583643
    },
    {
        "question": "17,163,660 ÷ 1,265,160=？",
        "answer": 1.1324644503128236
    },
    {
        "question": "306 × 1,797,968=？",
        "answer": 8.740503384431019
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 18,236,166=？",
        "answer": 7.260933536839635
    },
    {
        "question": "2,382 × 120,322=？",
        "answer": 8.45728679932505
    },
    {
        "question": "966,869,118 ÷ 1,345,827=？",
        "answer": 2.856378452121817
    },
    {
        "question": "7,374,138 ÷ 7,203,745=？",
        "answer": 0.010152929602631816
    },
    {
        "question": "769,936,308 ÷ 836,024=？",
        "answer": 2.9642360551565368
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 298=？",
        "answer": 2.4742162640762553
    },
    {
        "question": "563,758,244 ÷ 354,359=？",
        "answer": 3.2016494383096314
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 5,373,127=？",
        "answer": 7.8763551414148765
    },
    {
        "question": "401,632,816 ÷ 871=？",
        "answer": 5.663811035248497
    },
    {
        "question": "247,651,772 ÷ 10,575,422=？",
        "answer": 1.369543733384514
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,790,538=？",
        "answer": 7.28244428079905
    },
    {
        "question": "241,621,171 ÷ 4,016,219=？",
        "answer": 1.7793175983912475
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 67,049=？",
        "answer": 6.59724431660798
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 69,762,336=？",
        "answer": 8.144651010233618
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 11,133=？",
        "answer": 5.192740244746684
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 107,178=？",
        "answer": 6.352324943344965
    },
    {
        "question": "104,395,443 ÷ 1,073,296=？",
        "answer": 1.9879620307295378
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 58,978,505=？",
        "answer": 8.071723755428094
    },
    {
        "question": "2,417 × 12,511=？",
        "answer": 7.480568674499547
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 19,481,325=？",
        "answer": 8.590648487252734
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 43,341=？",
        "answer": 4.937928923170892
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 735=？",
        "answer": 3.7693773260761385
    },
    {
        "question": "131,368 × 280=？",
        "answer": 7.565647619428052
    },
    {
        "question": "224,954,902 ÷ 130,403=？",
        "answer": 3.236807878612241
    },
    {
        "question": "32,467,653 ÷ 55,011=？",
        "answer": 2.7710013560655047
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 7,028,963=？",
        "answer": 8.587253946719231
    },
    {
        "question": "11,298,135 ÷ 97,652=？",
        "answer": 2.063325617308631
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 205,163,804=？",
        "answer": 8.312100742844942
    },
    {
        "question": "12,217 × 19,447=？",
        "answer": 8.375817188076798
    },
    {
        "question": "98,142,296 ÷ 4,678,271=？",
        "answer": 1.3217708381655247
    },
    {
        "question": "361 × 21,511=？",
        "answer": 6.890167802176293
    },
    {
        "question": "174,143,838 ÷ 32,161,580=？",
        "answer": 0.7335707355953578
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 7,767,134=？",
        "answer": 7.735358837760342
    },
    {
        "question": "1,894,147 ÷ 105,543=？",
        "answer": 1.2539842458899033
    },
    {
        "question": "178 × 1,585=？",
        "answer": 5.4504492688626645
    },
    {
        "question": "8,192 × 10,075=？",
        "answer": 7.916634998444903
    },
    {
        "question": "51,135,400 ÷ 5,909,495=？",
        "answer": 0.9371712879795195
    },
    {
        "question": "26,769 × 13,265=？",
        "answer": 8.550339402024006
    },
    {
        "question": "3,712 ÷ 2,356=？",
        "answer": 0.19743268143176043
    },
    {
        "question": "7,035 ÷ 3,526=？",
        "answer": 0.2999817938074613
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 18,143,913=？",
        "answer": 8.161820941769212
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 2,820=？",
        "answer": 4.72900270927219
    },
    {
        "question": "780 × 322=？",
        "answer": 5.399950474386311
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 200=？",
        "answer": 3.6434526764861874
    },
    {
        "question": "13,238 ÷ 6,238=？",
        "answer": 0.32677700633105994
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 12,229,293=？",
        "answer": 7.990491337317353
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 29,016=？",
        "answer": 4.939758797292041
    },
    {
        "question": "1,143 × 6,789=？",
        "answer": 6.889852039069673
    },
    {
        "question": "117,014 ÷ 40,081=？",
        "answer": 0.46529927708368163
    },
    {
        "question": "117,442 ÷ 5,248=？",
        "answer": 1.3498296121646083
    },
    {
        "question": "42,877,293 ÷ 526,854=？",
        "answer": 1.9105370772886274
    },
    {
        "question": "639 × 12,814=？",
        "answer": 6.913185577814242
    },
    {
        "question": "40,998 ÷ 4,070=？",
        "answer": 1.0031682618811106
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 10,238=？",
        "answer": 4.612275116542189
    },
    {
        "question": "422,999 × 1,795=？",
        "answer": 8.880403793587265
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 10,648=？",
        "answer": 4.726238046802638
    },
    {
        "question": "4,872,003 ÷ 4,140=？",
        "answer": 3.0707072059265483
    },
    {
        "question": "702 × 5,470=？",
        "answer": 6.584324438463236
    },
    {
        "question": "2,683,658 ÷ 978=？",
        "answer": 3.4383883146167635
    },
    {
        "question": "224,498 ÷ 79,685=？",
        "answer": 0.44983589935355284
    },
    {
        "question": "7,577 × 5,557=？",
        "answer": 7.624337684034808
    },
    {
        "question": "95,916 ÷ 3,596=？",
        "answer": 1.4260713759563106
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 317=？",
        "answer": 4.241421951711995
    },
    {
        "question": "662 × 245,692=？",
        "answer": 8.211249005047094
    },
    {
        "question": "1,524,248 ÷ 413,248=？",
        "answer": 0.5668448734570709
    },
    {
        "question": "56,119,426 ÷ 89,872=？",
        "answer": 2.7954888138016702
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 24,574=？",
        "answer": 5.168627104321459
    },
    {
        "question": "616,191,721 ÷ 10,905,448=？",
        "answer": 1.752072347680957
    },
    {
        "question": "444,269 ÷ 2,263=？",
        "answer": 2.2929614563407448
    },
    {
        "question": "667 × 334=？",
        "answer": 5.347872300728113
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 32,617,382=？",
        "answer": 8.29160035029508
    },
    {
        "question": "14,806,254 ÷ 9,545,445=？",
        "answer": 0.19064901577715046
    },
    {
        "question": "316,718 × 1,123=？",
        "answer": 8.551052502546316
    },
    {
        "question": "588,713 ÷ 177,931=？",
        "answer": 0.5196520064753193
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 63,243=？",
        "answer": 5.403072454304506
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 23,054,065=？",
        "answer": 8.53883877235694
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 2,828,882=？",
        "answer": 8.095067508772564
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 221,970=？",
        "answer": 5.346294282041345
    },
    {
        "question": "474,391,844 ÷ 873,680=？",
        "answer": 2.734784819699101
    },
    {
        "question": "2,127 ÷ 284=？",
        "answer": 0.8744491498556913
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 208=？",
        "answer": 3.640282629696681
    },
    {
        "question": "1,387,368 ÷ 111,745=？",
        "answer": 1.0939635733162232
    },
    {
        "question": "15,866,567 ÷ 273,942=？",
        "answer": 1.7628243478256276
    },
    {
        "question": "183 × 626=？",
        "answer": 5.059025422940859
    },
    {
        "question": "1,161 × 131,284=？",
        "answer": 8.183044020198777
    },
    {
        "question": "67 × 2,673=？",
        "answer": 5.2530737614573635
    },
    {
        "question": "47,716,306 ÷ 206=？",
        "answer": 5.364799594639354
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 400,998,775=？",
        "answer": 8.60314304590808
    },
    {
        "question": "1,306 ÷ 457=？",
        "answer": 0.4560269768692049
    },
    {
        "question": "334 × 2,109,290=？",
        "answer": 8.847882760510949
    },
    {
        "question": "4,087,487 ÷ 30,619=？",
        "answer": 2.1254653816530804
    },
    {
        "question": "16,506 × 7,369=？",
        "answer": 8.085050397296119
    },
    {
        "question": "1,038,279 ÷ 17,241=？",
        "answer": 1.779751618305715
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 350,377=？",
        "answer": 7.389633629802177
    },
    {
        "question": "25,577,299 ÷ 2,327=？",
        "answer": 4.041058297147921
    },
    {
        "question": "54,419,032 ÷ 678,347=？",
        "answer": 1.9042989036611915
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 1,128,530=？",
        "answer": 8.025640962127596
    },
    {
        "question": "1,593,318 ÷ 1,408=？",
        "answer": 3.053699807663289
    },
    {
        "question": "2,142,010 ÷ 185,001=？",
        "answer": 1.0636474180752846
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 501=？",
        "answer": 2.699837725867246
    },
    {
        "question": "16,991,089 ÷ 78,757=？",
        "answer": 2.3339320500451537
    },
    {
        "question": "619,993 ÷ 153,274=？",
        "answer": 0.6069182947890024
    },
    {
        "question": "478,543,556 ÷ 3,516=？",
        "answer": 5.133872606055068
    },
    {
        "question": "15,692,469 ÷ 46,789=？",
        "answer": 2.5255475160748384
    },
    {
        "question": "133,891,409 ÷ 618=？",
        "answer": 5.335764236773155
    },
    {
        "question": "1,901,764 ÷ 20,482=？",
        "answer": 1.9677842602316278
    },
    {
        "question": "929,020,050 ÷ 3,159,806=？",
        "answer": 2.468364667569349
    },
    {
        "question": "124 × 1,211,713=？",
        "answer": 8.17682145245436
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 10,516,984=？",
        "answer": 8.1358345655131
    },
    {
        "question": "109,201,869 ÷ 299,278=？",
        "answer": 2.5621552785037265
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,046,114=？",
        "answer": 6.71854901857396
    },
    {
        "question": "3,374,312 ÷ 1,195=？",
        "answer": 3.450817331123597
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 25,967=？",
        "answer": 5.317511764934505
    },
    {
        "question": "277 × 1,373=？",
        "answer": 5.580150306301204
    },
    {
        "question": "10,220,505 ÷ 3,291=？",
        "answer": 3.4921444727308324
    },
    {
        "question": "12,110,961 ÷ 11,081=？",
        "answer": 3.038599650730363
    },
    {
        "question": "20,843,773 ÷ 10,625=？",
        "answer": 3.2926473960955267
    },
    {
        "question": "3,563 ÷ 1,084=？",
        "answer": 0.5167865401486474
    },
    {
        "question": "124,937 ÷ 60,664=？",
        "answer": 0.3137600304332571
    },
    {
        "question": "170 × 570=？",
        "answer": 4.986323777050766
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 202=？",
        "answer": 3.5358002908248976
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 61,635=？",
        "answer": 5.692917387309496
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 224,412=？",
        "answer": 5.953106067594983
    },
    {
        "question": "4,593 × 105,375=？",
        "answer": 8.684834033050722
    },
    {
        "question": "911,217,530 ÷ 196,596,812=？",
        "answer": 0.6660455950426882
    },
    {
        "question": "1,575,357 ÷ 3,427=？",
        "answer": 2.66246488262346
    },
    {
        "question": "6,055 ÷ 635=？",
        "answer": 0.9793404221870954
    },
    {
        "question": "2,987 ÷ 207=？",
        "answer": 1.1592648771472105
    },
    {
        "question": "17,402 × 3,694=？",
        "answer": 7.808096055424105
    },
    {
        "question": "10,343,377 ÷ 286=？",
        "answer": 4.558296321201688
    },
    {
        "question": "188,848,304 ÷ 208,251=？",
        "answer": 2.957525993368013
    },
    {
        "question": "77,031 ÷ 8,035=？",
        "answer": 0.9816796547167004
    },
    {
        "question": "900,168,848 ÷ 1,901,582=？",
        "answer": 2.6752089215088213
    },
    {
        "question": "207,116,670 ÷ 14,515=？",
        "answer": 4.154398014774329
    },
    {
        "question": "315 × 312=？",
        "answer": 4.992465147808043
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 25,419=？",
        "answer": 5.8030984697985835
    },
    {
        "question": "3,593 × 90,395=？",
        "answer": 8.511601626303204
    },
    {
        "question": "41,526 × 512=？",
        "answer": 7.32759006060023
    },
    {
        "question": "212 × 1,056=？",
        "answer": 5.349999779126545
    },
    {
        "question": "375 × 1,946,247=？",
        "answer": 8.863229223870652
    },
    {
        "question": "18,299,830 ÷ 489=？",
        "answer": 4.573138196158457
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 763,926=？",
        "answer": 5.88305129136604
    },
    {
        "question": "67 × 40,495=？",
        "answer": 6.433476206002852
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 643,730=？",
        "answer": 7.188914990907157
    },
    {
        "question": "3,337,258 ÷ 15,073=？",
        "answer": 2.3451900836664756
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 487,376=？",
        "answer": 6.28992413061205
    },
    {
        "question": "345,519,768 ÷ 84,660=？",
        "answer": 3.6107946352935736
    },
    {
        "question": "6,640 ÷ 685=？",
        "answer": 0.986477507875592
    },
    {
        "question": "79,131,884 ÷ 1,582=？",
        "answer": 4.6991450265262165
    },
    {
        "question": "445,323,545 ÷ 892=？",
        "answer": 5.698310803237141
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 606,892=？",
        "answer": 6.260232667414027
    },
    {
        "question": "777,114,748 ÷ 58,818=？",
        "answer": 4.120974898010694
    },
    {
        "question": "109,375 × 572=？",
        "answer": 7.796314094823394
    },
    {
        "question": "16,312,425 ÷ 5,181,655=？",
        "answer": 0.4980500340891891
    },
    {
        "question": "10,722,603 ÷ 1,564=？",
        "answer": 3.8360634779864693
    },
    {
        "question": "87,050,693 ÷ 282=？",
        "answer": 5.489523124513402
    },
    {
        "question": "3,372,453 ÷ 45,288=？",
        "answer": 1.871962763989159
    },
    {
        "question": "196,409,109 ÷ 9,686=？",
        "answer": 4.307017160780632
    },
    {
        "question": "117,974 ÷ 4,585=？",
        "answer": 1.41044696475171
    },
    {
        "question": "383 × 25,375=？",
        "answer": 6.987604824889892
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 393=？",
        "answer": 3.071513805095089
    },
    {
        "question": "5,008,675 ÷ 152,330=？",
        "answer": 1.516937410270471
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,994,083=？",
        "answer": 7.379568335972774
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 5,603=？",
        "answer": 5.533750457478336
    },
    {
        "question": "272,266 × 436=？",
        "answer": 8.07447990022177
    },
    {
        "question": "10,895,181 ÷ 1,287,499=？",
        "answer": 0.9274875491139875
    },
    {
        "question": "18,087 × 334=？",
        "answer": 6.78111300539658
    },
    {
        "question": "947,119,598 ÷ 2,804,497=？",
        "answer": 2.528549843442171
    },
    {
        "question": "817,659 ÷ 1,145=？",
        "answer": 2.8537667347276887
    },
    {
        "question": "827,793,705 ÷ 384=？",
        "answer": 6.333590895094941
    },
    {
        "question": "646,855 ÷ 199=？",
        "answer": 3.5119538630574842
    },
    {
        "question": "103,291,513 ÷ 13,870=？",
        "answer": 3.8719881778840035
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 7,442,020=？",
        "answer": 8.710539923565738
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 22,227,093=？",
        "answer": 8.38827535178822
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,021,914=？",
        "answer": 6.905462775568474
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,035,364=？",
        "answer": 6.910702080100477
    },
    {
        "question": "791,201 ÷ 397=？",
        "answer": 3.29949632073173
    },
    {
        "question": "15,262 × 36,580=？",
        "answer": 8.746855150358831
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 335,259,376=？",
        "answer": 8.525380932349506
    },
    {
        "question": "169,974 × 269=？",
        "answer": 7.660134774791875
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 5,043=？",
        "answer": 4.957961473262439
    },
    {
        "question": "8,353 ÷ 586=？",
        "answer": 1.1539448653877673
    },
    {
        "question": "3,505 × 60,916=？",
        "answer": 8.329419400306119
    },
    {
        "question": "574 × 34,517=？",
        "answer": 7.296944934943368
    },
    {
        "question": "274 × 1,504,142=？",
        "answer": 8.615039401007753
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 2,076,044=？",
        "answer": 8.162334593793135
    },
    {
        "question": "2,667 × 1,374=？",
        "answer": 6.564009748413408
    },
    {
        "question": "2,693,938 ÷ 7,079=？",
        "answer": 2.5804156840441133
    },
    {
        "question": "3,338,607 ÷ 78,275=？",
        "answer": 1.6299422233354828
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 256,384=？",
        "answer": 6.7099209146054255
    },
    {
        "question": "36,347,961 ÷ 9,561,768=？",
        "answer": 0.5799418513266577
    },
    {
        "question": "430 × 58,798=？",
        "answer": 7.402831009483343
    },
    {
        "question": "678,711 ÷ 18,660=？",
        "answer": 1.5607732485324044
    },
    {
        "question": "265,805,248 ÷ 23,253,753=？",
        "answer": 1.0580704962018868
    },
    {
        "question": "3,001 × 22,292=？",
        "answer": 7.825415029809015
    },
    {
        "question": "114 × 7,363,933=？",
        "answer": 8.924014679801983
    },
    {
        "question": "9,544 × 1,446=？",
        "answer": 7.139898723620798
    },
    {
        "question": "32,707 × 7,417=？",
        "answer": 8.384868989960488
    },
    {
        "question": "4,674 × 2,499=？",
        "answer": 7.067454964182658
    },
    {
        "question": "29,592 × 926=？",
        "answer": 7.437785304989272
    },
    {
        "question": "1,467 ÷ 301=？",
        "answer": 0.6878636182494393
    },
    {
        "question": "14,386 ÷ 261=？",
        "answer": 1.7412995486264864
    },
    {
        "question": "9,977 ÷ 535=？",
        "answer": 1.2706461901970918
    },
    {
        "question": "552,179 ÷ 384,011=？",
        "answer": 0.15773622098390153
    },
    {
        "question": "42,206,449 ÷ 5,130,346=？",
        "answer": 0.9152321590118199
    },
    {
        "question": "7,345 × 836=？",
        "answer": 6.7881980775652915
    },
    {
        "question": "312,358 × 608=？",
        "answer": 8.278556212690242
    },
    {
        "question": "925,790 ÷ 571=？",
        "answer": 3.209876377157226
    },
    {
        "question": "3,149 ÷ 1,251=？",
        "answer": 0.40091535094312397
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 25,359=？",
        "answer": 5.851290155037533
    },
    {
        "question": "53,824 ÷ 691=？",
        "answer": 1.891497922407601
    },
    {
        "question": "576,604,215 ÷ 1,112,789=？",
        "answer": 2.7144649888011747
    },
    {
        "question": "33,988,458 ÷ 222=？",
        "answer": 5.184978487358604
    },
    {
        "question": "136,631 × 2,158=？",
        "answer": 8.46960068728764
    },
    {
        "question": "1,274,812 ÷ 594=？",
        "answer": 3.331659697920011
    },
    {
        "question": "26,631,675 ÷ 46,179=？",
        "answer": 2.760953958167755
    },
    {
        "question": "413,209,201 ÷ 265,308=？",
        "answer": 3.1924196377287215
    },
    {
        "question": "60,190 × 11,900=？",
        "answer": 8.85507130471732
    },
    {
        "question": "262,823,896 ÷ 76,481=？",
        "answer": 3.536111291054529
    },
    {
        "question": "233,780,835 ÷ 3,036=？",
        "answer": 4.886507138255499
    },
    {
        "question": "4,729,458 ÷ 398,277=？",
        "answer": 1.0746261458953241
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 348=？",
        "answer": 4.340919793400163
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 11,688=？",
        "answer": 5.06774020292624
    },
    {
        "question": "414,320 ÷ 4,889=？",
        "answer": 1.928115860746002
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 155,829=？",
        "answer": 5.192648283682961
    },
    {
        "question": "51,438,543 ÷ 8,448,718=？",
        "answer": 0.7844978441319659
    },
    {
        "question": "403,183 ÷ 108,112=？",
        "answer": 0.5716283104432742
    },
    {
        "question": "17,372,426 ÷ 5,393=？",
        "answer": 3.508030050136136
    },
    {
        "question": "32,049,525 ÷ 215=？",
        "answer": 5.173383137389852
    },
    {
        "question": "51,223,788 ÷ 6,004,576=？",
        "answer": 0.9309893453376069
    },
    {
        "question": "1,413 × 40,499=？",
        "answer": 7.757586461610297
    },
    {
        "question": "248 × 3,296=？",
        "answer": 5.912438883851294
    },
    {
        "question": "1,215 × 9,808=？",
        "answer": 7.076156735108671
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 6,970,018=？",
        "answer": 7.68833193967476
    },
    {
        "question": "32,655,773 ÷ 1,656=？",
        "answer": 4.29489963602339
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 987,466=？",
        "answer": 6.295552146781122
    },
    {
        "question": "1,116 × 1,149=？",
        "answer": 6.107984223289845
    },
    {
        "question": "30,897 ÷ 2,532=？",
        "answer": 1.0864526115197575
    },
    {
        "question": "98,287,772 ÷ 4,141,602=？",
        "answer": 1.375331128838755
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 13,412=？",
        "answer": 5.081736054196107
    },
    {
        "question": "2,445 × 1,340=？",
        "answer": 6.515383661824447
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 12,607=？",
        "answer": 4.799581757169809
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 15,744=？",
        "answer": 4.896085085423285
    },
    {
        "question": "46,535,382 ÷ 758=？",
        "answer": 4.788114077671324
    },
    {
        "question": "2,040 × 108,036=？",
        "answer": 8.343198663618038
    },
    {
        "question": "10,648 ÷ 6,672=？",
        "answer": 0.20301200483693643
    },
    {
        "question": "1,746,199 ÷ 7,111=？",
        "answer": 2.3901630565352168
    },
    {
        "question": "269 × 410=？",
        "answer": 5.042536136722143
    },
    {
        "question": "844,861,980 ÷ 10,100,711=？",
        "answer": 1.9224338213590595
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 721,181=？",
        "answer": 7.3631942547398594
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,649,402=？",
        "answer": 7.1204165038277845
    },
    {
        "question": "193,306,826 ÷ 76,931,270=？",
        "answer": 0.40014428805709434
    },
    {
        "question": "3,413 × 73,564=？",
        "answer": 8.399801623998265
    },
    {
        "question": "1,005 × 6,131=？",
        "answer": 6.7896973778837415
    },
    {
        "question": "31,006,710 ÷ 3,870=？",
        "answer": 3.9037447223842814
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 232,147,816=？",
        "answer": 8.365764602266204
    },
    {
        "question": "66,178 ÷ 27,810=？",
        "answer": 0.3765126491169924
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 705,869=？",
        "answer": 6.62687535957134
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 3,077=？",
        "answer": 4.333225536261716
    },
    {
        "question": "27,327,326 ÷ 6,010=？",
        "answer": 3.6577226657177304
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,245=？",
        "answer": 3.7197454925295768
    },
    {
        "question": "49,338 ÷ 1,813=？",
        "answer": 1.4347837365472957
    },
    {
        "question": "532,149,162 ÷ 330,375,727=？",
        "answer": 0.20702525076729042
    },
    {
        "question": "1,918 × 125,463=？",
        "answer": 8.381364270763115
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 377,438=？",
        "answer": 6.72297365794998
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 4,375=？",
        "answer": 4.720159303405957
    },
    {
        "question": "135,125,976 ÷ 670,972=？",
        "answer": 2.30403444661443
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 11,361,979=？",
        "answer": 8.745650062277221
    },
    {
        "question": "24,761 × 7,791=？",
        "answer": 8.285361384507711
    },
    {
        "question": "15,882 ÷ 4,656=？",
        "answer": 0.5328922200431597
    },
    {
        "question": "3,282,095 ÷ 205=？",
        "answer": 4.204397286465302
    },
    {
        "question": "2,049 ÷ 806=？",
        "answer": 0.40520691659610436
    },
    {
        "question": "37,309,154 ÷ 3,855,581=？",
        "answer": 0.9857255699159163
    },
    {
        "question": "5,526 × 3,004=？",
        "answer": 7.220110808912623
    },
    {
        "question": "650 × 244,411=？",
        "answer": 8.201034104579152
    },
    {
        "question": "390,904 ÷ 35,212=？",
        "answer": 1.0453794212721548
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 167,757=？",
        "answer": 5.224680651034449
    },
    {
        "question": "14,781 ÷ 12,906=？",
        "answer": 0.05891215622346538
    },
    {
        "question": "35,958 ÷ 1,032=？",
        "answer": 1.542115830788936
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 27,695=？",
        "answer": 4.4424013694827025
    },
    {
        "question": "32,294,656 ÷ 438,726=？",
        "answer": 1.8669372902902075
    },
    {
        "question": "778,650 × 271=？",
        "answer": 8.324311578808937
    },
    {
        "question": "1,514,436 ÷ 483=？",
        "answer": 3.4963037940390937
    },
    {
        "question": "10,196 × 12,721=？",
        "answer": 8.11295107941556
    },
    {
        "question": "1,041,660 ÷ 11,767=？",
        "answer": 1.9470602340131251
    },
    {
        "question": "608,636,017 ÷ 1,000=？",
        "answer": 5.784357648846213
    },
    {
        "question": "2,922,100 ÷ 118,693=？",
        "answer": 1.3912699673637192
    },
    {
        "question": "391,369,442 ÷ 158,151,966=？",
        "answer": 0.39351231803698905
    },
    {
        "question": "8,830 × 15,140=？",
        "answer": 8.126086578741623
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,131=？",
        "answer": 3.3544926005894364
    },
    {
        "question": "2,997 × 9,116=？",
        "answer": 7.436491059453982
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 25,474=？",
        "answer": 4.707127140138086
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 36,508=？",
        "answer": 6.106456086208381
    },
    {
        "question": "129,407 × 872=？",
        "answer": 8.052474254148935
    },
    {
        "question": "48,541 ÷ 4,971=？",
        "answer": 0.9896649559110657
    },
    {
        "question": "3,012 × 5,822=？",
        "answer": 7.243927168631455
    },
    {
        "question": "1,130 × 7,435=？",
        "answer": 6.924359416341392
    },
    {
        "question": "766,605,083 ÷ 39,801=？",
        "answer": 4.284677710673342
    },
    {
        "question": "1,646,266 × 434=？",
        "answer": 8.8539897383953
    },
    {
        "question": "1,553,300 ÷ 1,076=？",
        "answer": 3.159443070915895
    },
    {
        "question": "808 × 2,139=？",
        "answer": 6.237622145346114
    },
    {
        "question": "151,699 ÷ 24,384=？",
        "answer": 0.7938777682668856
    },
    {
        "question": "1,134 × 52,446=？",
        "answer": 7.7743254251766025
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 868,118=？",
        "answer": 5.93857876119702
    },
    {
        "question": "21,488 ÷ 965=？",
        "answer": 1.3476686819808477
    },
    {
        "question": "128,532,921 ÷ 333=？",
        "answer": 5.586570143791285
    },
    {
        "question": "224,030,497 ÷ 838,574=？",
        "answer": 2.426765749370809
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 1,537,064=？",
        "answer": 7.8942621270512765
    },
    {
        "question": "276,282,720 ÷ 6,347,664=？",
        "answer": 1.638739792736145
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 2,122,337=？",
        "answer": 7.171912385470227
    },
    {
        "question": "74,982,081 ÷ 1,452,055=？",
        "answer": 1.7129744227556676
    },
    {
        "question": "228 × 81,052=？",
        "answer": 7.266698582758057
    },
    {
        "question": "1,908 × 303,814=？",
        "answer": 8.76318615300431
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 2,435,178=？",
        "answer": 7.863651966304162
    },
    {
        "question": "223 × 17,572=？",
        "answer": 6.593126057641443
    },
    {
        "question": "503 × 211,665=？",
        "answer": 8.027217035973187
    },
    {
        "question": "356 × 409=？",
        "answer": 5.163173305980217
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 182,603,738=？",
        "answer": 8.738630918258345
    },
    {
        "question": "80,241,362 ÷ 5,860,556=？",
        "answer": 1.1364594715371215
    },
    {
        "question": "2,534,303 ÷ 293=？",
        "answer": 3.936990917328756
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 1,279=？",
        "answer": 4.282961803534335
    },
    {
        "question": "533 × 879=？",
        "answer": 5.670716084100344
    },
    {
        "question": "911,008,103 ÷ 2,794=？",
        "answer": 5.513295838062603
    },
    {
        "question": "96,023,597 ÷ 330=？",
        "answer": 5.463864030532516
    },
    {
        "question": "34,715 ÷ 9,436=？",
        "answer": 0.5657292373790143
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 16,625=？",
        "answer": 5.396852913030823
    },
    {
        "question": "852,650,187 ÷ 4,284,570=？",
        "answer": 2.298863649045973
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 13,703=？",
        "answer": 4.136815657726849
    },
    {
        "question": "7,365 ÷ 336=？",
        "answer": 1.3408334737888057
    },
    {
        "question": "87 × 177,622=？",
        "answer": 7.1890160084692845
    },
    {
        "question": "154 × 4,358=？",
        "answer": 5.8268079467467
    },
    {
        "question": "4,016 ÷ 275=？",
        "answer": 1.1644610103067004
    },
    {
        "question": "28,615,612 ÷ 24,332,792=？",
        "answer": 0.07041109483962807
    },
    {
        "question": "14,419 ÷ 2,434=？",
        "answer": 0.772614567935872
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 413,414=？",
        "answer": 5.91741517530841
    },
    {
        "question": "139 × 174,833=？",
        "answer": 7.385638210047048
    },
    {
        "question": "9,044,086 ÷ 3,539,359=？",
        "answer": 0.40744006768228636
    },
    {
        "question": "378 × 252,098=？",
        "answer": 7.97906120008563
    },
    {
        "question": "383,784 ÷ 3,396=？",
        "answer": 2.053119183417025
    },
    {
        "question": "79,514 ÷ 29,464=？",
        "answer": 0.4311518956077618
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 2,410,027=？",
        "answer": 7.724444588909659
    },
    {
        "question": "243 × 241,817=？",
        "answer": 7.769093102574138
    },
    {
        "question": "205,163 ÷ 13,947=？",
        "answer": 1.1676182400169945
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 564=？",
        "answer": 3.228400358703005
    },
    {
        "question": "53,734,669 ÷ 12,652=？",
        "answer": 3.628095394768508
    },
    {
        "question": "241,474 ÷ 978=？",
        "answer": 2.392531521441107
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 12,191,727=？",
        "answer": 8.165246475328502
    },
    {
        "question": "127 × 7,120,649=？",
        "answer": 8.95632329946271
    },
    {
        "question": "191 × 24,396=？",
        "answer": 6.668351991933391
    },
    {
        "question": "159,434,560 ÷ 3,657=？",
        "answer": 4.639457507226646
    },
    {
        "question": "233,637 × 1,370=？",
        "answer": 8.505262188231123
    },
    {
        "question": "128,675,990 ÷ 2,817=？",
        "answer": 4.659710671299426
    },
    {
        "question": "20,775 ÷ 1,153=？",
        "answer": 1.2557117251614496
    },
    {
        "question": "606,674,800 ÷ 455,196,550=？",
        "answer": 0.1247569938166578
    },
    {
        "question": "1,229 × 825=？",
        "answer": 6.006005831436379
    },
    {
        "question": "334,719 × 242=？",
        "answer": 7.90849573134375
    },
    {
        "question": "407,016,811 ÷ 991,515=？",
        "answer": 2.613313058488183
    },
    {
        "question": "3,888 × 19,702=？",
        "answer": 7.8842365709882145
    },
    {
        "question": "661,646 ÷ 1,595=？",
        "answer": 2.6178650039089932
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,160=？",
        "answer": 3.3654879848909
    },
    {
        "question": "162,559,591 ÷ 2,056,383=？",
        "answer": 1.8979085929977684
    },
    {
        "question": "1,564 ÷ 619=？",
        "answer": 0.4025460997037112
    },
    {
        "question": "18,677,368 ÷ 42,310=？",
        "answer": 2.644872650437921
    },
    {
        "question": "31,775,475 ÷ 2,917,088=？",
        "answer": 1.0371425206728653
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,286,773=？",
        "answer": 6.410531935309183
    },
    {
        "question": "21,922,846 ÷ 7,839,243=？",
        "answer": 0.4466228062403854
    },
    {
        "question": "17,505,188 ÷ 7,164=？",
        "answer": 3.3880112021299507
    },
    {
        "question": "13,924 × 14,400=？",
        "answer": 8.3021265067075
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 995=？",
        "answer": 3.298853076409707
    },
    {
        "question": "238 × 26,958=？",
        "answer": 6.807264626033181
    },
    {
        "question": "429,850,108 ÷ 13,297,442=？",
        "answer": 1.509548935474304
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 29,156,543=？",
        "answer": 8.640827288817325
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 637=？",
        "answer": 3.9502674680135885
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 69,351,693=？",
        "answer": 8.318178322170542
    },
    {
        "question": "40,184 × 204=？",
        "answer": 6.913683332577392
    },
    {
        "question": "291,326 ÷ 303=？",
        "answer": 2.9829366173771326
    },
    {
        "question": "399 × 249,762=？",
        "answer": 7.998499259085609
    },
    {
        "question": "5,393 ÷ 3,088=？",
        "answer": 0.24215312862446386
    },
    {
        "question": "102 × 415=？",
        "answer": 4.6266482684740105
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 74,188,988=？",
        "answer": 7.8703394469804975
    },
    {
        "question": "15,604,462 ÷ 743=？",
        "answer": 4.322259986189892
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 3,278,168=？",
        "answer": 7.770903711690854
    },
    {
        "question": "325 × 25,286=？",
        "answer": 6.914763494580981
    },
    {
        "question": "220,416 × 958=？",
        "answer": 8.324608625844048
    },
    {
        "question": "62,676 × 7,345=？",
        "answer": 8.663093072010893
    },
    {
        "question": "345 × 5,891=？",
        "answer": 6.308008117809267
    },
    {
        "question": "107,651,091 ÷ 13,738,259=？",
        "answer": 0.8940867359420239
    },
    {
        "question": "1,200,509 ÷ 60,819=？",
        "answer": 1.2953261451358897
    },
    {
        "question": "2,946,742 ÷ 666=？",
        "answer": 3.6458678839849075
    },
    {
        "question": "186,486,923 ÷ 305=？",
        "answer": 5.786348543886079
    },
    {
        "question": "595,520,446 ÷ 337,206=？",
        "answer": 3.2470013831609057
    },
    {
        "question": "204 × 7,555=？",
        "answer": 6.187864636100943
    },
    {
        "question": "136,716,713 ÷ 520,976=？",
        "answer": 2.419003891398997
    },
    {
        "question": "2,148 × 665=？",
        "answer": 6.154855922330623
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 83,791,946=？",
        "answer": 8.525262268002932
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 145,909=？",
        "answer": 6.669232059314025
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 5,432=？",
        "answer": 4.212081015992108
    },
    {
        "question": "31,119 × 2,666=？",
        "answer": 7.918885777693056
    },
    {
        "question": "405,804,131 ÷ 93,497,373=？",
        "answer": 0.6375170550937022
    },
    {
        "question": "537,403,162 ÷ 112,862,882=？",
        "answer": 0.6777490814651764
    },
    {
        "question": "543,095,277 ÷ 647=？",
        "answer": 5.92397174532084
    },
    {
        "question": "67,860,147 ÷ 147,409=？",
        "answer": 2.663090796071796
    },
    {
        "question": "631,932,316 ÷ 25,956,977=？",
        "answer": 1.386416452757869
    },
    {
        "question": "324,297 ÷ 17,816=？",
        "answer": 1.2601327271031364
    },
    {
        "question": "66,970 ÷ 19,161=？",
        "answer": 0.543462128058532
    },
    {
        "question": "151 × 11,674=？",
        "answer": 6.24619663626731
    },
    {
        "question": "3,139 × 15,518=？",
        "answer": 7.687627063232109
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 372,329=？",
        "answer": 5.8719568595736975
    },
    {
        "question": "2,821,628 ÷ 1,040=？",
        "answer": 3.433466417037842
    },
    {
        "question": "4,220 ÷ 593=？",
        "answer": 0.8522577575974113
    },
    {
        "question": "5,566,792 ÷ 435,676=？",
        "answer": 1.1064413577470058
    },
    {
        "question": "15,322 ÷ 1,536=？",
        "answer": 0.9989242423081632
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 4,669=？",
        "answer": 5.302692329510393
    },
    {
        "question": "34,062,960 ÷ 5,007=？",
        "answer": 3.832704793149889
    },
    {
        "question": "270,418,061 ÷ 9,898=？",
        "answer": 4.436488244934592
    },
    {
        "question": "43,448,519 ÷ 5,670,783=？",
        "answer": 0.8843319487854068
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 15,220,633=？",
        "answer": 7.483462710036149
    },
    {
        "question": "1,984 ÷ 1,168=？",
        "answer": 0.23009882504177914
    },
    {
        "question": "348 × 397,752=？",
        "answer": 8.141191616015748
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 65,300=？",
        "answer": 6.814913181275074
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 52,454,977=？",
        "answer": 7.719786700939318
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 20,348=？",
        "answer": 5.852589773309592
    },
    {
        "question": "1,170 × 850,739=？",
        "answer": 8.997982204150876
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,627=？",
        "answer": 3.882353746388714
    },
    {
        "question": "132,619,502 ÷ 679,226=？",
        "answer": 2.2905930909044816
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 637=？",
        "answer": 3.758381941774675
    },
    {
        "question": "281,933,287 ÷ 28,356,424=？",
        "answer": 0.9974948931931114
    },
    {
        "question": "28,033 ÷ 374=？",
        "answer": 1.8747979748223125
    },
    {
        "question": "6,714,809 ÷ 214=？",
        "answer": 4.49661989050204
    },
    {
        "question": "89,008 ÷ 12,120=？",
        "answer": 0.8659264227664853
    },
    {
        "question": "2,332 × 28,539=？",
        "answer": 7.82316729755339
    },
    {
        "question": "88,905,528 ÷ 208=？",
        "answer": 5.630865430566014
    },
    {
        "question": "415 × 4,205=？",
        "answer": 6.241814096846023
    },
    {
        "question": "19,385 × 259=？",
        "answer": 6.7007655694244805
    },
    {
        "question": "682,695 × 319=？",
        "answer": 8.338017405184731
    },
    {
        "question": "14,380,181 ÷ 1,181=？",
        "answer": 4.085514454831577
    },
    {
        "question": "555,076 ÷ 159,252=？",
        "answer": 0.542267554786294
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 140,642,567=？",
        "answer": 8.847086788855826
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,060=？",
        "answer": 3.6148972160331345
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 354,240=？",
        "answer": 5.549297599198629
    },
    {
        "question": "607 × 129,947=？",
        "answer": 7.896954948760039
    },
    {
        "question": "626 ÷ 302=？",
        "answer": 0.31656739025327907
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 87,797=？",
        "answer": 5.420600931153042
    },
    {
        "question": "12,897,852 ÷ 316=？",
        "answer": 4.610830306578353
    },
    {
        "question": "123 × 157,659=？",
        "answer": 7.287623879030597
    },
    {
        "question": "605,096 × 1,421=？",
        "answer": 8.934418359956462
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 211=？",
        "answer": 3.1024337056813365
    },
    {
        "question": "1,418,049 ÷ 24,944=？",
        "answer": 1.7547251400981498
    },
    {
        "question": "474,941,755 ÷ 166,569,528=？",
        "answer": 0.4550447976102896
    },
    {
        "question": "164 × 483=？",
        "answer": 4.89879097879921
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,006=？",
        "answer": 3.954531942626914
    },
    {
        "question": "52,900,707 ÷ 10,865,877=？",
        "answer": 0.6873966916913243
    },
    {
        "question": "4,086 × 107,794=？",
        "answer": 8.643892950239813
    },
    {
        "question": "3,752,740 ÷ 2,263=？",
        "answer": 3.2196639224016557
    },
    {
        "question": "23,413 × 4,483=？",
        "answer": 8.021025803992162
    },
    {
        "question": "268,811,862 ÷ 977,144=？",
        "answer": 2.4394898594894294
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 878,814=？",
        "answer": 7.462410906736188
    },
    {
        "question": "389,684,323 ÷ 2,798,811=？",
        "answer": 2.143739362352301
    },
    {
        "question": "9,532 ÷ 284=？",
        "answer": 1.525865693627381
    },
    {
        "question": "136,341 × 247=？",
        "answer": 7.527323428288755
    },
    {
        "question": "195,101,826 ÷ 816=？",
        "answer": 5.378571175315249
    },
    {
        "question": "391,205,116 ÷ 127,974,784=？",
        "answer": 0.4852801204489872
    },
    {
        "question": "1,959 × 1,387=？",
        "answer": 6.434110897068021
    },
    {
        "question": "6,532,641 ÷ 103,077=？",
        "answer": 1.8019270221196217
    },
    {
        "question": "167,534,297 ÷ 1,136,767=？",
        "answer": 2.1684322699644953
    },
    {
        "question": "44,171,817 ÷ 308=？",
        "answer": 5.1565945477532695
    },
    {
        "question": "378 × 261=？",
        "answer": 4.994132307175506
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 32,123,743=？",
        "answer": 7.506826142756649
    },
    {
        "question": "31,385 ÷ 774=？",
        "answer": 1.607981172303837
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 843,299=？",
        "answer": 7.10207284438843
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,292,328=？",
        "answer": 6.933722897016444
    },
    {
        "question": "15,818,128 ÷ 1,100=？",
        "answer": 4.157762400364019
    },
    {
        "question": "94,773,759 ÷ 78,582=？",
        "answer": 3.0813650284373786
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 406,993=？",
        "answer": 5.609586939722722
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 13,532=？",
        "answer": 4.131361989115943
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 938=？",
        "answer": 3.750354088762708
    },
    {
        "question": "1,003,685 × 947=？",
        "answer": 8.977947412701834
    },
    {
        "question": "7,535 ÷ 305=？",
        "answer": 1.3927834173038647
    },
    {
        "question": "3,751 × 292=？",
        "answer": 6.039529915599141
    },
    {
        "question": "41,226,443 ÷ 18,754=？",
        "answer": 3.342081954002216
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 370=？",
        "answer": 3.5224442335063197
    },
    {
        "question": "2,041 × 60,155=？",
        "answer": 8.089114735846001
    },
    {
        "question": "92,739,550 ÷ 3,255,671=？",
        "answer": 1.4546244731881828
    },
    {
        "question": "72,406,173 ÷ 13,335=？",
        "answer": 3.734782573596021
    },
    {
        "question": "55,068,998 ÷ 1,501=？",
        "answer": 4.564526482167378
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 96,217=？",
        "answer": 6.574316418710098
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 10,914=？",
        "answer": 5.079376634605352
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,181=？",
        "answer": 3.962889987391791
    },
    {
        "question": "2,250,659 ÷ 196,707=？",
        "answer": 1.0584898845515385
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 468,762=？",
        "answer": 7.434380392095142
    },
    {
        "question": "1,228,668 ÷ 317=？",
        "answer": 3.588375285236196
    },
    {
        "question": "20,560,942 ÷ 1,009,018=？",
        "answer": 1.309144094249751
    },
    {
        "question": "1,723 ÷ 366=？",
        "answer": 0.6728041920536179
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 138,541,477=？",
        "answer": 8.14157981336817
    },
    {
        "question": "400,385,693 ÷ 907,685=？",
        "answer": 2.6445433918736696
    },
    {
        "question": "5,863,195 ÷ 759,067=？",
        "answer": 0.8878542271946435
    },
    {
        "question": "2,568 × 7,828=？",
        "answer": 7.3032458363827795
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 7,942=？",
        "answer": 5.543382559214051
    },
    {
        "question": "645,177,770 ÷ 1,094,424=？",
        "answer": 2.7704937868157185
    },
    {
        "question": "189,443 ÷ 9,803=？",
        "answer": 1.2861195599023918
    },
    {
        "question": "484 × 630,429=？",
        "answer": 8.484481544314828
    },
    {
        "question": "205,117 ÷ 1,682=？",
        "answer": 2.08617566451951
    },
    {
        "question": "1,003 × 437=？",
        "answer": 5.64178236999084
    },
    {
        "question": "554,711 ÷ 7,177=？",
        "answer": 1.8881238318548013
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 158,856,212=？",
        "answer": 8.899974206719657
    },
    {
        "question": "120,619 × 5,605=？",
        "answer": 8.829991340532995
    },
    {
        "question": "49,469 × 2,415=？",
        "answer": 8.07725026641651
    },
    {
        "question": "43,486,708 ÷ 13,606=？",
        "answer": 3.5046260656315433
    },
    {
        "question": "816,196,000 ÷ 1,624,167=？",
        "answer": 2.701163779857434
    },
    {
        "question": "2,986,367 ÷ 1,879,807=？",
        "answer": 0.20102991540868448
    },
    {
        "question": "748,325,500 ÷ 25,712=？",
        "answer": 4.463954685109657
    },
    {
        "question": "239,682 ÷ 1,022=？",
        "answer": 2.370184524158178
    },
    {
        "question": "2,208 × 485=？",
        "answer": 6.029740807659425
    },
    {
        "question": "1,039,863 ÷ 65,224=？",
        "answer": 1.2025686962681463
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 12,471,334=？",
        "answer": 8.76801076833909
    },
    {
        "question": "109 × 1,525,312=？",
        "answer": 8.220785184914755
    },
    {
        "question": "491,874 ÷ 269,248=？",
        "answer": 0.2617013807646738
    },
    {
        "question": "11,812 × 6,671=？",
        "answer": 7.896514378945624
    },
    {
        "question": "9,000 × 1,598=？",
        "answer": 7.157819284417298
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 31,615=？",
        "answer": 5.2780444365328805
    },
    {
        "question": "374,746,508 ÷ 34,019=？",
        "answer": 4.042016051422211
    },
    {
        "question": "7,212,973 ÷ 52,987=？",
        "answer": 2.133944975045293
    },
    {
        "question": "326 × 751,929=？",
        "answer": 8.389394434856465
    },
    {
        "question": "41,044 × 13,482=？",
        "answer": 8.743004001740726
    },
    {
        "question": "335,466 ÷ 7,339=？",
        "answer": 1.6600116226156993
    },
    {
        "question": "292 × 749,978=？",
        "answer": 8.34043137534847
    },
    {
        "question": "727,210,705 ÷ 10,503=？",
        "answer": 4.840346897864817
    },
    {
        "question": "400,005,182 ÷ 5,860=？",
        "answer": 4.8341680015584405
    },
    {
        "question": "31,753 ÷ 460=？",
        "answer": 1.8390269317069254
    },
    {
        "question": "55,446 × 14,418=？",
        "answer": 8.902775241815409
    },
    {
        "question": "96 × 709,835=？",
        "answer": 7.83342864243846
    },
    {
        "question": "12,576 ÷ 400=？",
        "answer": 1.4974825373673704
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 3,910=？",
        "answer": 4.592176757395867
    },
    {
        "question": "17,027 × 3,943=？",
        "answer": 7.826964913102942
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 14,587=？",
        "answer": 5.6263639808538395
    },
    {
        "question": "16,415 ÷ 3,790=？",
        "answer": 0.6366016770972865
    },
    {
        "question": "623,569,441 ÷ 1,073,121=？",
        "answer": 2.7642361300559797
    },
    {
        "question": "315,116,587 ÷ 23,155,627=？",
        "answer": 1.1338147188574845
    },
    {
        "question": "328,850,639 ÷ 24,158,209=？",
        "answer": 1.1339339559266846
    },
    {
        "question": "22,646,707 ÷ 10,969=？",
        "answer": 3.314838024801996
    },
    {
        "question": "5,001,281 ÷ 983=？",
        "answer": 3.7065277384993744
    },
    {
        "question": "447,714,025 ÷ 18,627=？",
        "answer": 4.380857784652969
    },
    {
        "question": "4,535,855 ÷ 8,400=？",
        "answer": 2.7323798767307275
    },
    {
        "question": "640 × 328,498=？",
        "answer": 8.322712703765204
    },
    {
        "question": "1,311 × 118,957=？",
        "answer": 8.192992694784056
    },
    {
        "question": "3,282 ÷ 1,112=？",
        "answer": 0.47003378947103575
    },
    {
        "question": "15,223,430 ÷ 4,189,608=？",
        "answer": 0.5603391244320701
    },
    {
        "question": "1,614 × 377=？",
        "answer": 5.784244880591844
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 7,935,076=？",
        "answer": 8.330914854824217
    },
    {
        "question": "16,748,701 ÷ 330=？",
        "answer": 4.705467189679537
    },
    {
        "question": "1,678,688 ÷ 3,891=？",
        "answer": 2.6349087551082557
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,346=？",
        "answer": 3.6061663146076204
    },
    {
        "question": "16,075 × 2,349=？",
        "answer": 7.5770339983738655
    },
    {
        "question": "72,249,243 ÷ 2,205=？",
        "answer": 4.515424707276699
    },
    {
        "question": "2,113,788 ÷ 278,049=？",
        "answer": 0.8809400905962002
    },
    {
        "question": "264,718 ÷ 2,795=？",
        "answer": 1.9764016607558694
    },
    {
        "question": "1,067 × 10,841=？",
        "answer": 7.063233763845575
    },
    {
        "question": "5,174,875 ÷ 3,942,489=？",
        "answer": 0.11812937352655438
    },
    {
        "question": "80,618 × 7,075=？",
        "answer": 8.756158464015124
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 7,871=？",
        "answer": 5.804514931274877
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,301=？",
        "answer": 3.7243578042264267
    },
    {
        "question": "39,257,437 ÷ 476=？",
        "answer": 4.916314989688383
    },
    {
        "question": "655 × 584,653=？",
        "answer": 8.583139482488077
    },
    {
        "question": "718,005 ÷ 313=？",
        "answer": 3.360583131020154
    },
    {
        "question": "12,169,966 ÷ 511,487=？",
        "answer": 1.3764547647954384
    },
    {
        "question": "33,432 ÷ 7,329=？",
        "answer": 0.6591176364424703
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 79,935=？",
        "answer": 5.203766974960574
    },
    {
        "question": "17,372 × 44,189=？",
        "answer": 8.885163994250767
    },
    {
        "question": "19,892,810 ÷ 236=？",
        "answer": 4.925784131652435
    },
    {
        "question": "36,183 × 3,709=？",
        "answer": 8.127761405510558
    },
    {
        "question": "2,470 × 50,614=？",
        "answer": 8.096967614008122
    },
    {
        "question": "4,234 × 25,665=？",
        "answer": 8.036092122280175
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 32,499=？",
        "answer": 4.988991252585814
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,237,180=？",
        "answer": 6.092432890671713
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 8,257=？",
        "answer": 5.2390415793298315
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 47,432=？",
        "answer": 5.998290732070827
    },
    {
        "question": "57,654 × 1,011=？",
        "answer": 7.765580599358129
    },
    {
        "question": "12,792 ÷ 750=？",
        "answer": 1.2318771873464782
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 17,881=？",
        "answer": 5.155481790173188
    },
    {
        "question": "35,051 ÷ 1,583=？",
        "answer": 1.3452194979763177
    },
    {
        "question": "249,218,514 ÷ 258,987=？",
        "answer": 2.9833023371805054
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 65,472,589=？",
        "answer": 8.418119506011719
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 2,039=？",
        "answer": 4.827931165656027
    },
    {
        "question": "1,356 × 255,318=？",
        "answer": 8.539341123313386
    },
    {
        "question": "16,735,485 ÷ 2,502=？",
        "answer": 3.82535099751934
    },
    {
        "question": "176,741 ÷ 1,138=？",
        "answer": 2.1911950458421137
    },
    {
        "question": "445 × 1,897,761=？",
        "answer": 8.926601528388934
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 12,259,918=？",
        "answer": 8.468698807141424
    },
    {
        "question": "1,298,083 ÷ 80,686=？",
        "answer": 1.2065042764362952
    },
    {
        "question": "253,552 ÷ 3,792=？",
        "answer": 1.8251987119151147
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 15,381=？",
        "answer": 6.100798424543778
    },
    {
        "question": "129,120,310 ÷ 1,760,988=？",
        "answer": 1.865238163520271
    },
    {
        "question": "549 × 8,055=？",
        "answer": 6.645637889205329
    },
    {
        "question": "3,853,539 ÷ 586,573=？",
        "answer": 0.817537690154287
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,141,879=？",
        "answer": 6.358650081696016
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 232=？",
        "answer": 3.0644579892269186
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 311=？",
        "answer": 4.3440187377459125
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 350,383=？",
        "answer": 7.573926804446963
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 1,943=？",
        "answer": 4.951230632281357
    },
    {
        "question": "278 × 5,802=？",
        "answer": 6.207622520384722
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 12,086=？",
        "answer": 5.705531880310338
    },
    {
        "question": "17,386,567 ÷ 234=？",
        "answer": 4.870997981053754
    },
    {
        "question": "7,065 × 76,236=？",
        "answer": 8.731272267567464
    },
    {
        "question": "939,408 ÷ 40,717=？",
        "answer": 1.363078482320809
    },
    {
        "question": "4,710 × 2,751=？",
        "answer": 7.11251149751858
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 18,826=？",
        "answer": 5.654969296063615
    },
    {
        "question": "194,403 ÷ 11,588=？",
        "answer": 1.2246944760821565
    },
    {
        "question": "2,517,782 ÷ 2,484=？",
        "answer": 3.005866532879031
    },
    {
        "question": "534,392,458 ÷ 309,473=？",
        "answer": 3.2372375552684396
    },
    {
        "question": "33,611,994 ÷ 232=？",
        "answer": 5.1610062924553874
    },
    {
        "question": "197,177,159 ÷ 2,513,128=？",
        "answer": 1.8946419959723946
    },
    {
        "question": "303 × 196,940=？",
        "answer": 7.775776562085761
    },
    {
        "question": "587 × 6,132=？",
        "answer": 6.556240247429952
    },
    {
        "question": "93,082,009 ÷ 3,411=？",
        "answer": 4.435984028737575
    },
    {
        "question": "5,335 × 173,725=？",
        "answer": 8.966996744111977
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,775,613=？",
        "answer": 6.550378311679169
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 23,099=？",
        "answer": 4.965653170186233
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 374=？",
        "answer": 2.5728716022004803
    },
    {
        "question": "36,308 ÷ 3,508=？",
        "answer": 1.014942742079364
    },
    {
        "question": "740 × 1,641=？",
        "answer": 6.08434030078407
    },
    {
        "question": "632 ÷ 225=？",
        "answer": 0.4485345601710225
    },
    {
        "question": "151,535,134 ÷ 1,376=？",
        "answer": 5.04189490344919
    },
    {
        "question": "801,378 ÷ 299,143=？",
        "answer": 0.42795857097070816
    },
    {
        "question": "3,695,681 ÷ 10,251=？",
        "answer": 2.556928243662022
    },
    {
        "question": "226,183 ÷ 471=？",
        "answer": 2.6814390529493104
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,254,188=？",
        "answer": 6.70042263248208
    },
    {
        "question": "2,232,119 ÷ 78,502=？",
        "answer": 1.4538366228057615
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 476=？",
        "answer": 3.52270499273475
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 1,791=？",
        "answer": 4.39922362152727
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 47,551,484=？",
        "answer": 8.279224066396438
    },
    {
        "question": "3,563 ÷ 219=？",
        "answer": 1.2113717075108972
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 41,098,151=？",
        "answer": 7.613822283468273
    },
    {
        "question": "2,410 × 133,506=？",
        "answer": 8.507517826689968
    },
    {
        "question": "1,263,556 ÷ 3,049=？",
        "answer": 2.617437069972899
    },
    {
        "question": "133 × 232=？",
        "answer": 4.489339625857985
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 2,071,310=？",
        "answer": 7.939494392291921
    },
    {
        "question": "2,603 × 2,062=？",
        "answer": 6.7297628290567335
    },
    {
        "question": "63,961 ÷ 9,515=？",
        "answer": 0.8275064524931668
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 34,878=？",
        "answer": 5.583944258498256
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 72,556,243=？",
        "answer": 7.860674786640083
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 378=？",
        "answer": 2.8785217955012063
    },
    {
        "question": "2,227 × 1,866=？",
        "answer": 6.6186318564445195
    },
    {
        "question": "441,369,583 ÷ 23,796=？",
        "answer": 4.2682984401847905
    },
    {
        "question": "339,221,058 ÷ 689,474=？",
        "answer": 2.6919649107269303
    },
    {
        "question": "7,246,662 ÷ 5,456,516=？",
        "answer": 0.12322257234466165
    },
    {
        "question": "2,507,518 ÷ 40,050=？",
        "answer": 1.7966415388285766
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 7,984=？",
        "answer": 5.985005898595765
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 641,994=？",
        "answer": 6.585682219606596
    },
    {
        "question": "1,956 × 779=？",
        "answer": 6.182906308124147
    },
    {
        "question": "635,846 ÷ 60,719=？",
        "answer": 1.0200273331430096
    },
    {
        "question": "298,576,947 ÷ 4,089,245=？",
        "answer": 1.863413141657695
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 345,529=？",
        "answer": 6.316635753646495
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 343,303=？",
        "answer": 5.535677598583784
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 139,006=？",
        "answer": 5.143033546373904
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 1,319=？",
        "answer": 4.78300262722794
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 306,419=？",
        "answer": 5.486315690919196
    },
    {
        "question": "127,441,148 ÷ 120,837,616=？",
        "answer": 0.02310752646086893
    },
    {
        "question": "1,119,817 ÷ 62,548=？",
        "answer": 1.2529336287630204
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 90,023=？",
        "answer": 5.6533234859637655
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,749,433=？",
        "answer": 6.916364395691617
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 34,672=？",
        "answer": 6.071457811017998
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 12,870=？",
        "answer": 5.732827837302287
    },
    {
        "question": "527,790 ÷ 1,580=？",
        "answer": 2.523804070460564
    },
    {
        "question": "414 × 223=？",
        "answer": 4.965305204169059
    },
    {
        "question": "290,686,163 ÷ 929=？",
        "answer": 5.495408645345519
    },
    {
        "question": "1,591 × 4,146=？",
        "answer": 6.8192994774044235
    },
    {
        "question": "44,204,071 ÷ 2,635,119=？",
        "answer": 1.224662035392633
    },
    {
        "question": "2,232 ÷ 607=？",
        "answer": 0.5655054991902836
    },
    {
        "question": "44,985 × 1,377=？",
        "answer": 7.792001665072132
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 20,160,714=？",
        "answer": 8.735869672923005
    },
    {
        "question": "10,414,725 ÷ 6,382,005=？",
        "answer": 0.21269066681642082
    },
    {
        "question": "350,959,663 ÷ 9,857,732=？",
        "answer": 1.5514801974666927
    },
    {
        "question": "27,069,544 ÷ 839=？",
        "answer": 4.508718979095786
    },
    {
        "question": "18,793,044 ÷ 937,866=？",
        "answer": 1.3018563386923607
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,688,901=？",
        "answer": 6.5286341885068495
    },
    {
        "question": "611 × 56,672=？",
        "answer": 7.539409749752535
    },
    {
        "question": "336,326,975 ÷ 894=？",
        "answer": 5.575424182368953
    },
    {
        "question": "435 × 203=？",
        "answer": 4.94598529486785
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 520,985=？",
        "answer": 7.131798567410442
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 7,507,060=？",
        "answer": 8.273409895640699
    },
    {
        "question": "5,667 ÷ 944=？",
        "answer": 0.778381218343427
    },
    {
        "question": "439,603 × 417=？",
        "answer": 8.263196702508194
    },
    {
        "question": "1,936,987 ÷ 1,797=？",
        "answer": 3.0325786288722894
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 19,394=？",
        "answer": 5.719031155433123
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 82,464=？",
        "answer": 5.957657082029035
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 5,070=？",
        "answer": 4.5501059993475925
    },
    {
        "question": "308 × 1,739=？",
        "answer": 5.728850298503157
    },
    {
        "question": "274 × 694=？",
        "answer": 5.279110033275243
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 546,414=？",
        "answer": 7.281589862485053
    },
    {
        "question": "1,061,342 × 528=？",
        "answer": 8.74848927323984
    },
    {
        "question": "6,122,799 ÷ 409=？",
        "answer": 4.175226694589639
    },
    {
        "question": "82,424,108 ÷ 667=？",
        "answer": 5.091928421955978
    },
    {
        "question": "833,667,741 ÷ 4,851=？",
        "answer": 5.235161722052995
    },
    {
        "question": "58,497 × 1,121=？",
        "answer": 7.816739206594177
    },
    {
        "question": "545,188,067 ÷ 2,764=？",
        "answer": 5.295008302787752
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,114,729=？",
        "answer": 6.3252547209567185
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 2,158,691=？",
        "answer": 7.781348512213234
    },
    {
        "question": "2,745,784 ÷ 125,665=？",
        "answer": 1.3394520344359144
    },
    {
        "question": "1,833 × 276=？",
        "answer": 5.704071547027435
    },
    {
        "question": "31,369,501 ÷ 149,490=？",
        "answer": 2.3218954684656135
    },
    {
        "question": "33,014,169 ÷ 14,884=？",
        "answer": 3.3459807087660747
    },
    {
        "question": "3,495,890 ÷ 774,903=？",
        "answer": 0.654310416628635
    },
    {
        "question": "330 × 13,503=？",
        "answer": 6.6489442075360286
    },
    {
        "question": "14,780 × 290=？",
        "answer": 6.632072431957763
    },
    {
        "question": "780,588 ÷ 57,249=？",
        "answer": 1.1346539655601167
    },
    {
        "question": "40,494,835 ÷ 1,783=？",
        "answer": 4.356248290556711
    },
    {
        "question": "39,530 × 7,299=？",
        "answer": 8.460190177993452
    },
    {
        "question": "712,861 ÷ 370,607=？",
        "answer": 0.2840912375075508
    },
    {
        "question": "916 × 66,030=？",
        "answer": 7.781636770940861
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 1,223,779=？",
        "answer": 8.10054022115334
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 14,017=？",
        "answer": 5.40192757844428
    },
    {
        "question": "154,680 ÷ 57,469=？",
        "answer": 0.4300005232233141
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,686,237=？",
        "answer": 6.670824248663302
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 1,818,204=？",
        "answer": 7.975645952500915
    },
    {
        "question": "414,500 ÷ 6,444=？",
        "answer": 1.808369003139112
    },
    {
        "question": "89,897 × 517=？",
        "answer": 7.667235741999751
    },
    {
        "question": "1,024,636 ÷ 1,939=？",
        "answer": 2.7229918014179795
    },
    {
        "question": "1,226,413 ÷ 2,819=？",
        "answer": 2.638541669528485
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 562=？",
        "answer": 3.652826302561005
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 5,980=？",
        "answer": 5.239099181887367
    },
    {
        "question": "16,447,507 ÷ 5,478=？",
        "answer": 3.4774780519854938
    },
    {
        "question": "227,034 × 860=？",
        "answer": 8.29058935207841
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 359,350=？",
        "answer": 6.45860763618471
    },
    {
        "question": "409,274,934 ÷ 1,036=？",
        "answer": 5.596655391730965
    },
    {
        "question": "1,991,043 ÷ 60,535=？",
        "answer": 1.5170740927174293
    },
    {
        "question": "17,423,253 ÷ 3,269,899=？",
        "answer": 0.726594904518075
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 1,232=？",
        "answer": 4.903524064471262
    },
    {
        "question": "249,441,204 ÷ 1,925,986=？",
        "answer": 2.1123150681859006
    },
    {
        "question": "145,551,295 ÷ 1,767,553=？",
        "answer": 1.9156436288345506
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 601,565=？",
        "answer": 7.571674249879302
    },
    {
        "question": "17,324,208 ÷ 4,765=？",
        "answer": 3.560590484393662
    },
    {
        "question": "53,135 ÷ 7,341=？",
        "answer": 0.8596254608433412
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 3,671,497=？",
        "answer": 8.236941035615333
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 18,180=？",
        "answer": 5.490042800264223
    },
    {
        "question": "57,505,226 ÷ 44,120,731=？",
        "answer": 0.11506461530488735
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 167,120=？",
        "answer": 7.029208400956139
    },
    {
        "question": "3,127,392 ÷ 166,745=？",
        "answer": 1.2731295008169379
    },
    {
        "question": "4,155,501 ÷ 632,156=？",
        "answer": 0.8177991268320134
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 2,065=？",
        "answer": 5.06310808299862
    },
    {
        "question": "8,381 × 396=？",
        "answer": 6.520991026581016
    },
    {
        "question": "164,369,818 ÷ 24,716=？",
        "answer": 3.822843887735519
    },
    {
        "question": "3,820,978 ÷ 810,352=？",
        "answer": 0.6735008288394383
    },
    {
        "question": "424,932 ÷ 33,303=？",
        "answer": 1.1058360800006344
    },
    {
        "question": "39,001,438 ÷ 46,873=？",
        "answer": 2.920157869505774
    },
    {
        "question": "24,034 ÷ 3,242=？",
        "answer": 0.870013046323845
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 92,097=？",
        "answer": 6.627003315247959
    },
    {
        "question": "14,646 ÷ 247=？",
        "answer": 1.7730220765411664
    },
    {
        "question": "29,893,026 ÷ 1,071=？",
        "answer": 4.445780409031265
    },
    {
        "question": "20,993 ÷ 1,515=？",
        "answer": 1.1416618729354602
    },
    {
        "question": "13,297,575 ÷ 29,191=？",
        "answer": 2.658523475548037
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 292,889=？",
        "answer": 7.174273237335667
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 878=？",
        "answer": 4.972878293591312
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,069=？",
        "answer": 3.5060989599284405
    },
    {
        "question": "29,362,229 ÷ 757,663=？",
        "answer": 1.5883129421967623
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 213=？",
        "answer": 3.2314695904306814
    },
    {
        "question": "537,712,366 ÷ 3,087=？",
        "answer": 5.241013394764801
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 221=？",
        "answer": 3.79155030502733
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 1,918,364=？",
        "answer": 8.023293705359501
    },
    {
        "question": "1,163,386 ÷ 3,048=？",
        "answer": 2.58170887059629
    },
    {
        "question": "7,200,217 ÷ 422,664=？",
        "answer": 1.2313503265980306
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 36,534,480=？",
        "answer": 7.863732926019427
    },
    {
        "question": "200 × 1,556,091=？",
        "answer": 8.493064986545315
    },
    {
        "question": "5,955 ÷ 396=？",
        "answer": 1.177186579893284
    },
    {
        "question": "80,834 ÷ 5,582=？",
        "answer": 1.1608042378613976
    },
    {
        "question": "2,592 × 4,437=？",
        "answer": 7.060724425915111
    },
    {
        "question": "52,509 ÷ 38,230=？",
        "answer": 0.13782944948880002
    },
    {
        "question": "963,581,241 ÷ 8,854,534=？",
        "answer": 2.0367226266617466
    },
    {
        "question": "603 × 297=？",
        "answer": 5.2530737614573635
    },
    {
        "question": "52,402,309 ÷ 33,717,105=？",
        "answer": 0.191500145305314
    },
    {
        "question": "143,712 ÷ 7,974=？",
        "answer": 1.255816802056245
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 4,748=？",
        "answer": 4.375480714618573
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,167=？",
        "answer": 3.9701608430373136
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,501,017=？",
        "answer": 7.041472982732413
    },
    {
        "question": "97 × 2,209=？",
        "answer": 5.330967450137679
    },
    {
        "question": "45,489,218 ÷ 3,003,329=？",
        "answer": 1.1803055613458857
    },
    {
        "question": "18,932,115 ÷ 855,355=？",
        "answer": 1.3450527354498167
    },
    {
        "question": "3,381,603 ÷ 1,250=？",
        "answer": 3.432212607098826
    },
    {
        "question": "74,719,522 ÷ 3,666=？",
        "answer": 4.309241624311225
    },
    {
        "question": "4,520 × 466=？",
        "answer": 6.323524351501383
    },
    {
        "question": "150,426 ÷ 24,647=？",
        "answer": 0.7855588421860388
    },
    {
        "question": "36,238,575 ÷ 25,017,722=？",
        "answer": 0.16092334941522835
    },
    {
        "question": "2,209,975 ÷ 1,913,051=？",
        "answer": 0.06266081279163946
    },
    {
        "question": "28,405 × 497=？",
        "answer": 7.149751182346609
    },
    {
        "question": "1,274 × 81,593=？",
        "answer": 8.016822329501041
    },
    {
        "question": "32,321 × 20,424=？",
        "answer": 8.819625591020134
    },
    {
        "question": "3,652,470 ÷ 1,328,411=？",
        "answer": 0.43925419434421226
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 3,142=？",
        "answer": 5.099266172031917
    },
    {
        "question": "184 × 2,364=？",
        "answer": 5.638465295218754
    },
    {
        "question": "582,079,267 ÷ 2,752=？",
        "answer": 5.325333700922487
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 22,880=？",
        "answer": 6.323243847466542
    },
    {
        "question": "52,771,580 ÷ 986=？",
        "answer": 4.728523182362859
    },
    {
        "question": "32,389,184 ÷ 630,170=？",
        "answer": 1.7109422824890197
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 519=？",
        "answer": 2.7151673578484576
    },
    {
        "question": "202 × 15,009=？",
        "answer": 6.481703127049696
    },
    {
        "question": "75,971 ÷ 207=？",
        "answer": 2.5646774975673963
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 22,014=？",
        "answer": 5.986151638625779
    },
    {
        "question": "201,300,041 ÷ 36,622,477=？",
        "answer": 0.7400961484179397
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 828,286=？",
        "answer": 6.6963315711967155
    },
    {
        "question": "112,595 ÷ 5,587=？",
        "answer": 1.304340433892081
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 394=？",
        "answer": 3.595496221825574
    },
    {
        "question": "1,419 × 4,710=？",
        "answer": 6.82500330258637
    },
    {
        "question": "379 × 1,146=？",
        "answer": 5.637823827599443
    },
    {
        "question": "278,008 ÷ 63,700=？",
        "answer": 0.639917861085839
    },
    {
        "question": "940 × 2,675=？",
        "answer": 6.4004516399569455
    },
    {
        "question": "1,342,035 ÷ 476=？",
        "answer": 3.4501568895719843
    },
    {
        "question": "469,356,071 ÷ 61,089=？",
        "answer": 3.885539423744594
    },
    {
        "question": "30,997 × 5,451=？",
        "answer": 8.227795845329952
    },
    {
        "question": "585 × 1,548,901=？",
        "answer": 8.95717952623795
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 20,158=？",
        "answer": 4.304447440866175
    },
    {
        "question": "1,121,730 ÷ 39,809=？",
        "answer": 1.4499070667097411
    },
    {
        "question": "146,298 ÷ 6,914=？",
        "answer": 1.3255090138382604
    },
    {
        "question": "613,281,790 ÷ 63,922,224=？",
        "answer": 0.982008192833068
    },
    {
        "question": "99,591,060 ÷ 40,386,422=？",
        "answer": 0.39198497588838827
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 310,939=？",
        "answer": 7.256103191072661
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 659,147=？",
        "answer": 7.3241322581180315
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 18,930=？",
        "answer": 5.231393123403121
    },
    {
        "question": "645 × 319,650=？",
        "answer": 8.314234423405152
    },
    {
        "question": "167,886,846 ÷ 1,266,625=？",
        "answer": 2.122368614669124
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 8,667,880=？",
        "answer": 7.636882894558952
    },
    {
        "question": "267,306,651 ÷ 303=？",
        "answer": 5.9455671363023574
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 33,822=？",
        "answer": 5.80795288615666
    },
    {
        "question": "8,275 ÷ 334=？",
        "answer": 1.3940215356361918
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 17,300=？",
        "answer": 6.428377801299087
    },
    {
        "question": "304 × 74,032=？",
        "answer": 7.3522930657645755
    },
    {
        "question": "210 × 168,050=？",
        "answer": 7.547657811539415
    },
    {
        "question": "114 × 427=？",
        "answer": 4.687332726361497
    },
    {
        "question": "3,788,536 ÷ 1,542=？",
        "answer": 3.390387044708853
    },
    {
        "question": "197,314,845 ÷ 634,692=？",
        "answer": 2.492596736398773
    },
    {
        "question": "20,271 × 938=？",
        "answer": 7.279078012023702
    },
    {
        "question": "4,750,881 ÷ 2,258=？",
        "answer": 3.323050214764461
    },
    {
        "question": "1,057,056 ÷ 2,501=？",
        "answer": 2.6259843039466095
    },
    {
        "question": "9,553 × 337=？",
        "answer": 6.507769678617093
    },
    {
        "question": "9,925 × 81,885=？",
        "answer": 8.909934868796794
    },
    {
        "question": "3,466 × 3,781=？",
        "answer": 7.117435235740434
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 480=？",
        "answer": 3.936513742478893
    },
    {
        "question": "8,169,390 ÷ 227=？",
        "answer": 4.556163772224929
    },
    {
        "question": "30,161,219 ÷ 768,355=？",
        "answer": 1.5938869683090104
    },
    {
        "question": "500,561 × 1,905=？",
        "answer": 8.979351989597468
    },
    {
        "question": "272,433 ÷ 6,705=？",
        "answer": 1.608860930634122
    },
    {
        "question": "205 × 58,722=？",
        "answer": 7.0805546997582525
    },
    {
        "question": "3,125 × 4,551=？",
        "answer": 7.152956857186487
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 467,436,100=？",
        "answer": 8.669722249830652
    },
    {
        "question": "64,822 × 1,494=？",
        "answer": 7.986073023983717
    },
    {
        "question": "1,944 × 15,207=？",
        "answer": 7.47073980653332
    },
    {
        "question": "87,055 ÷ 49,793=？",
        "answer": 0.24262542679381185
    },
    {
        "question": "66,700,786 ÷ 9,636=？",
        "answer": 3.8402341603331442
    },
    {
        "question": "19,103,725 ÷ 12,326=？",
        "answer": 3.19029589438784
    },
    {
        "question": "491,296,824 ÷ 36,695=？",
        "answer": 4.126737064601245
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 951,474=？",
        "answer": 7.791310281887223
    },
    {
        "question": "266,443,854 ÷ 361=？",
        "answer": 5.868098505014413
    },
    {
        "question": "97 × 609=？",
        "answer": 4.77138902689912
    },
    {
        "question": "28,190,490 ÷ 137,557=？",
        "answer": 2.3116199290708623
    },
    {
        "question": "16,906 × 25,832=？",
        "answer": 8.640198896648737
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 162,594=？",
        "answer": 5.68822577005539
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 4,355=？",
        "answer": 4.869437080721956
    },
    {
        "question": "9,820,831 ÷ 28,645=？",
        "answer": 2.53509941104298
    },
    {
        "question": "208 × 375,107=？",
        "answer": 7.892218503706945
    },
    {
        "question": "50,385,107 ÷ 10,969=？",
        "answer": 3.6621351487020886
    },
    {
        "question": "2,477,475 ÷ 179,612=？",
        "answer": 1.1396739319383005
    },
    {
        "question": "1,363,447 ÷ 624=？",
        "answer": 3.339453671000134
    },
    {
        "question": "18,122,868 ÷ 489,160=？",
        "answer": 1.568775990901533
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 13,392=？",
        "answer": 5.357294362027459
    },
    {
        "question": "1,667 × 746=？",
        "answer": 6.094674427300674
    },
    {
        "question": "1,091,328 ÷ 204=？",
        "answer": 3.728325130533083
    },
    {
        "question": "3,276 × 2,449=？",
        "answer": 6.904332678213095
    },
    {
        "question": "3,206 × 8,222=？",
        "answer": 7.420940990462457
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 4,782=？",
        "answer": 5.351707429715473
    },
    {
        "question": "350,013,725 ÷ 155,128=？",
        "answer": 3.3533948812123664
    },
    {
        "question": "1,248 ÷ 387=？",
        "answer": 0.5085036203274937
    },
    {
        "question": "2,409 × 1,859=？",
        "answer": 6.651116189770242
    },
    {
        "question": "407 × 1,872=？",
        "answer": 5.881900253627307
    },
    {
        "question": "946,136,664 ÷ 154,259,081=？",
        "answer": 0.7877031325526149
    },
    {
        "question": "10,780,747 ÷ 57,477=？",
        "answer": 2.2731547620961234
    },
    {
        "question": "8,006 × 7,029=？",
        "answer": 7.750309129085712
    },
    {
        "question": "138 × 593=？",
        "answer": 4.912933779765499
    },
    {
        "question": "7,871 ÷ 7,124=？",
        "answer": 0.04330600160502115
    },
    {
        "question": "1,738,936 ÷ 2,234=？",
        "answer": 2.8912004296933245
    },
    {
        "question": "110,421 ÷ 20,640=？",
        "answer": 0.7283419829454442
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,617=？",
        "answer": 3.208710019906401
    },
    {
        "question": "10,899,136 ÷ 108,567=？",
        "answer": 2.001694234503985
    },
    {
        "question": "3,168 × 46,296=？",
        "answer": 8.166328642272946
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 34,401=？",
        "answer": 6.252574410862422
    },
    {
        "question": "30,083 × 5,196=？",
        "answer": 8.193990286105139
    },
    {
        "question": "925,625 ÷ 784=？",
        "answer": 3.072119013180845
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 80,137=？",
        "answer": 4.903833080200092
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 294,408,373=？",
        "answer": 8.468950157214332
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,753,190=？",
        "answer": 6.544858980485736
    },
    {
        "question": "195 × 430,365=？",
        "answer": 7.9238715558866915
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 523,715=？",
        "answer": 6.673337522378306
    },
    {
        "question": "327,465,694 ÷ 138,117,745=？",
        "answer": 0.3749163299391069
    },
    {
        "question": "591,120 ÷ 7,204=？",
        "answer": 1.9141019494032134
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 588=？",
        "answer": 2.7693773260761385
    },
    {
        "question": "431,434 ÷ 4,275=？",
        "answer": 2.0039782484768764
    },
    {
        "question": "180 × 68,446=？",
        "answer": 7.09062057804538
    },
    {
        "question": "7,894 ÷ 6,073=？",
        "answer": 0.11389384093693304
    },
    {
        "question": "2,960 × 177,356=？",
        "answer": 8.720137596411664
    },
    {
        "question": "720 × 58,453=？",
        "answer": 7.624139301920762
    },
    {
        "question": "62,005,817 ÷ 70,819=？",
        "answer": 2.9422826442076957
    },
    {
        "question": "64,735 × 475=？",
        "answer": 7.487832761962545
    },
    {
        "question": "1,013 × 4,564=？",
        "answer": 6.6649550811064575
    },
    {
        "question": "390 × 3,120=？",
        "answer": 6.085219201044942
    },
    {
        "question": "2,071 × 4,670=？",
        "answer": 6.9854969794595645
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 123,603=？",
        "answer": 5.092029011753074
    },
    {
        "question": "53,406 ÷ 34,053=？",
        "answer": 0.19543467302587156
    },
    {
        "question": "945 × 51,654=？",
        "answer": 7.688535766710765
    },
    {
        "question": "628,593 ÷ 17,483=？",
        "answer": 1.5557535828439213
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 96,632=？",
        "answer": 6.51659988530121
    },
    {
        "question": "56,280 ÷ 40,787=？",
        "answer": 0.1398323258667934
    },
    {
        "question": "200 × 18,783=？",
        "answer": 6.57479495416876
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 311=？",
        "answer": 3.1917303933628562
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 20,585,042=？",
        "answer": 8.091703007816232
    },
    {
        "question": "153,531,206 ÷ 30,737=？",
        "answer": 3.6985351842332714
    },
    {
        "question": "109,666 × 437=？",
        "answer": 7.680553440104673
    },
    {
        "question": "52,294,057 ÷ 90,339=？",
        "answer": 2.762577057061732
    },
    {
        "question": "146 × 3,457=？",
        "answer": 5.703052235326844
    },
    {
        "question": "1,151,871 ÷ 85,002=？",
        "answer": 1.1319747001421703
    },
    {
        "question": "14,018 × 8,506=？",
        "answer": 8.07641143402553
    },
    {
        "question": "41,326 × 22,440=？",
        "answer": 8.96724622394382
    },
    {
        "question": "213 × 694=？",
        "answer": 5.169739073893592
    },
    {
        "question": "13,598 ÷ 3,669=？",
        "answer": 0.5689273250821443
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 604=？",
        "answer": 4.521399628115375
    },
    {
        "question": "324 × 5,080=？",
        "answer": 6.216408722490532
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 296,845,602=？",
        "answer": 8.472530618896975
    },
    {
        "question": "188,540,610 ÷ 280,106=？",
        "answer": 2.828082496142402
    },
    {
        "question": "234,569 ÷ 3,518=？",
        "answer": 1.8239747812747558
    },
    {
        "question": "84,471 × 1,453=？",
        "answer": 8.088973249855252
    },
    {
        "question": "9,690 × 57,518=？",
        "answer": 8.74612755352043
    },
    {
        "question": "93,422,546 ÷ 6,790,962=？",
        "answer": 1.138520398429199
    },
    {
        "question": "49,440,063 ÷ 332=？",
        "answer": 5.172940931785601
    },
    {
        "question": "3,039 × 80,627=？",
        "answer": 8.389211200786098
    },
    {
        "question": "968,579 × 305=？",
        "answer": 8.470434888113688
    },
    {
        "question": "16,479,110 ÷ 18,778=？",
        "answer": 2.943284417993906
    },
    {
        "question": "4,094 × 1,154=？",
        "answer": 6.6743536471462
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 415,569=？",
        "answer": 6.521733130229639
    },
    {
        "question": "23,393,394 ÷ 1,072,094=？",
        "answer": 1.3388603699483215
    },
    {
        "question": "285 × 2,586=？",
        "answer": 5.867473380552886
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 223,221,890=？",
        "answer": 8.649766776610802
    },
    {
        "question": "111,455,015 ÷ 14,845=？",
        "answer": 3.875519412722021
    },
    {
        "question": "546 × 1,700,287=？",
        "answer": 8.96771487702195
    },
    {
        "question": "258 × 1,190,846=？",
        "answer": 8.487475308189442
    },
    {
        "question": "1,187 × 1,115=？",
        "answer": 6.121725586338771
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 872,506=？",
        "answer": 6.843858409165203
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,466=？",
        "answer": 3.3919930722597127
    },
    {
        "question": "2,018 × 153,969=？",
        "answer": 8.492354451021926
    },
    {
        "question": "498,766 ÷ 25,649=？",
        "answer": 1.2888264031663628
    },
    {
        "question": "24,222,372 ÷ 36,654=？",
        "answer": 2.8200952940952764
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 387=？",
        "answer": 2.5877109650189114
    },
    {
        "question": "798 × 1,522=？",
        "answer": 6.084417543785284
    },
    {
        "question": "4,449 × 3,285=？",
        "answer": 7.164797779643844
    },
    {
        "question": "22,015,764 ÷ 299=？",
        "answer": 4.867062572796437
    },
    {
        "question": "477,946,456 ÷ 24,215=？",
        "answer": 4.295294772254148
    },
    {
        "question": "126 × 203,970=？",
        "answer": 7.409936841011336
    },
    {
        "question": "311,624 × 2,626=？",
        "answer": 8.912925619618507
    },
    {
        "question": "10,088,748 ÷ 23,628=？",
        "answer": 2.6304103120364557
    },
    {
        "question": "266,745 ÷ 20,029=？",
        "answer": 1.124437020991056
    },
    {
        "question": "16,753 ÷ 291=？",
        "answer": 1.7601995995083604
    },
    {
        "question": "110,631,956 ÷ 81,795=？",
        "answer": 3.1311538341493024
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 813,158=？",
        "answer": 7.7614332877464465
    },
    {
        "question": "18,476 × 4,395=？",
        "answer": 7.9095668329843
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 643,251=？",
        "answer": 7.239744234197445
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 297,168=？",
        "answer": 7.4367898687340475
    },
    {
        "question": "3,851,224 ÷ 34,855=？",
        "answer": 2.043333692296705
    },
    {
        "question": "137,909,660 ÷ 455,198=？",
        "answer": 2.481394342534637
    },
    {
        "question": "1,033,683 ÷ 26,907=？",
        "answer": 1.584522095169909
    },
    {
        "question": "12,164,288 ÷ 2,395,230=？",
        "answer": 0.7057394713648389
    },
    {
        "question": "24,303,146 ÷ 47,811=？",
        "answer": 2.706134668543974
    },
    {
        "question": "1,873,786 ÷ 51,762=？",
        "answer": 1.5587089413713873
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,594=？",
        "answer": 3.4139699717480614
    },
    {
        "question": "22,416,302 ÷ 391=？",
        "answer": 4.758387211547351
    },
    {
        "question": "692,131,804 ÷ 552,984,030=？",
        "answer": 0.09747621667023428
    },
    {
        "question": "350,805,266 ÷ 13,976,574=？",
        "answer": 1.399665375754867
    },
    {
        "question": "7,817,308 ÷ 361=？",
        "answer": 4.335550021483631
    },
    {
        "question": "441,237,139 ÷ 1,510=？",
        "answer": 5.465695112648925
    },
    {
        "question": "739,597,544 ÷ 100,272=？",
        "answer": 3.867815782961123
    },
    {
        "question": "339,332 ÷ 528=？",
        "answer": 2.807990894282294
    },
    {
        "question": "252,566,480 ÷ 3,409=？",
        "answer": 4.869748710322916
    },
    {
        "question": "178,870,868 ÷ 14,317,126=？",
        "answer": 1.0966837674304117
    },
    {
        "question": "431,735 ÷ 6,916=？",
        "answer": 1.795362272974278
    },
    {
        "question": "240 × 4,112=？",
        "answer": 5.9942643476988255
    },
    {
        "question": "6,425 × 779=？",
        "answer": 6.699410589675897
    },
    {
        "question": "2,618,179 ÷ 17,135=？",
        "answer": 2.1841152263651136
    },
    {
        "question": "534 × 6,155=？",
        "answer": 6.516769314295892
    },
    {
        "question": "4,679 × 1,842=？",
        "answer": 6.935442671053011
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 1,521,443=？",
        "answer": 7.504474981136173
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 676,328=？",
        "answer": 5.8301573676024425
    },
    {
        "question": "317 × 474=？",
        "answer": 5.176837603891837
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,898=？",
        "answer": 4.075473964588946
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 6,274=？",
        "answer": 5.052817019465032
    },
    {
        "question": "2,408,351 ÷ 7,008=？",
        "answer": 2.536125689365247
    },
    {
        "question": "1,131 × 5,029=？",
        "answer": 6.754944240546382
    },
    {
        "question": "25,667 ÷ 1,864=？",
        "answer": 1.1389292025863094
    },
    {
        "question": "3,612 × 2,252=？",
        "answer": 6.910316127820777
    },
    {
        "question": "313,927,613 ÷ 1,263,483=？",
        "answer": 2.3952601149027717
    },
    {
        "question": "266,640 ÷ 539=？",
        "answer": 2.694336535465735
    },
    {
        "question": "429 × 1,604,419=？",
        "answer": 8.837775088567318
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 590,680=？",
        "answer": 6.771352266207899
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 411=？",
        "answer": 3.0909630765957314
    },
    {
        "question": "1,736,499 ÷ 587,477=？",
        "answer": 0.4706836691051037
    },
    {
        "question": "435,945,207 ÷ 1,535,533=？",
        "answer": 2.4531727529121157
    },
    {
        "question": "4,371 × 12,254=？",
        "answer": 7.728858682485588
    },
    {
        "question": "542,745,597 ÷ 38,254=？",
        "answer": 4.151919455414197
    },
    {
        "question": "19,489,409 ÷ 420,950=？",
        "answer": 1.6655681558455235
    },
    {
        "question": "823,583,582 ÷ 622,980,878=？",
        "answer": 0.12123296397281567
    },
    {
        "question": "70,745,473 ÷ 7,522,743=？",
        "answer": 0.97332242935926
    },
    {
        "question": "1,111 ÷ 242=？",
        "answer": 0.6618986929604364
    },
    {
        "question": "341,602 ÷ 99,871=？",
        "answer": 0.5340810062647083
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 258=？",
        "answer": 2.7126497016272113
    },
    {
        "question": "192,397,938 ÷ 655,267=？",
        "answer": 2.4677821162947358
    },
    {
        "question": "1,343,186 ÷ 456,640=？",
        "answer": 0.46856220507659413
    },
    {
        "question": "124,633 ÷ 250=？",
        "answer": 2.6976930402352055
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 90,219=？",
        "answer": 5.654268013343678
    },
    {
        "question": "474,783 ÷ 968=？",
        "answer": 2.6906198029775967
    },
    {
        "question": "147 × 409=？",
        "answer": 4.779040642755518
    },
    {
        "question": "68,334 × 5,903=？",
        "answer": 8.605709626555955
    },
    {
        "question": "162,628 ÷ 1,109=？",
        "answer": 2.1662637749281135
    },
    {
        "question": "146,822 ÷ 2,236=？",
        "answer": 1.8173193364933116
    },
    {
        "question": "28,644,366 ÷ 25,939,741=？",
        "answer": 0.04307357875772596
    },
    {
        "question": "337,484 × 915=？",
        "answer": 8.489674281970007
    },
    {
        "question": "498,304,260 ÷ 4,096,893=？",
        "answer": 2.085039978488693
    },
    {
        "question": "64,371 × 1,026=？",
        "answer": 7.819837616698436
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 63,235,523=？",
        "answer": 8.579112365198176
    },
    {
        "question": "1,587,330 ÷ 1,890=？",
        "answer": 2.924205420174825
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 65,106=？",
        "answer": 6.228594361835744
    },
    {
        "question": "28,484,406 ÷ 1,332,524=？",
        "answer": 1.3299321275027394
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 5,534=？",
        "answer": 5.174402918963921
    },
    {
        "question": "411,030 ÷ 2,592=？",
        "answer": 2.2002385238477697
    },
    {
        "question": "46,394 ÷ 1,628=？",
        "answer": 1.454807417601219
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 430,829=？",
        "answer": 7.139454907198597
    },
    {
        "question": "2,414 × 218,976=？",
        "answer": 8.723133784077547
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 245=？",
        "answer": 2.8662873390841948
    },
    {
        "question": "549 ÷ 217=？",
        "answer": 0.4031126106015624
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 181,905=？",
        "answer": 6.037995887009336
    },
    {
        "question": "43,052,348 ÷ 14,118,018=？",
        "answer": 0.4842231108285201
    },
    {
        "question": "104,193,958 ÷ 269=？",
        "answer": 5.588090255819652
    },
    {
        "question": "3,378,995 ÷ 6,875=？",
        "answer": 2.691514846634533
    },
    {
        "question": "264,970 ÷ 38,411=？",
        "answer": 0.8387410919149595
    },
    {
        "question": "216,707 ÷ 16,651=？",
        "answer": 1.1144326191756968
    },
    {
        "question": "6,204 × 9,324=？",
        "answer": 7.762274053990106
    },
    {
        "question": "5,320 × 4,715=？",
        "answer": 7.3993933293683956
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 93,217=？",
        "answer": 5.668465126270809
    },
    {
        "question": "214,251,114 ÷ 439,513=？",
        "answer": 2.687951363472528
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 2,343,057=？",
        "answer": 8.189326789433052
    },
    {
        "question": "73,790,759 ÷ 46,836=？",
        "answer": 3.197422180122955
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,412=？",
        "answer": 3.7333577879255855
    },
    {
        "question": "1,302,192 ÷ 534=？",
        "answer": 3.3871337659078877
    },
    {
        "question": "2,247,108 ÷ 187,397=？",
        "answer": 1.0788613118081463
    },
    {
        "question": "167,071,131 ÷ 1,193,712=？",
        "answer": 2.146001852897286
    },
    {
        "question": "291 × 35,098=？",
        "answer": 7.009175358622362
    },
    {
        "question": "31,301,495 ÷ 335,316=？",
        "answer": 1.970110803710842
    },
    {
        "question": "45,442 ÷ 573=？",
        "answer": 1.899302815388946
    },
    {
        "question": "122 × 443,482=？",
        "answer": 7.7332358281022096
    },
    {
        "question": "409,461,585 ÷ 3,700=？",
        "answer": 5.044011439159838
    },
    {
        "question": "780 ÷ 613=？",
        "answer": 0.1046341281720654
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 49,841=？",
        "answer": 6.059314583355004
    },
    {
        "question": "452,893,250 ÷ 2,279,845=？",
        "answer": 2.298090526339207
    },
    {
        "question": "68,541 ÷ 421=？",
        "answer": 2.2116683405773183
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 49,106=？",
        "answer": 6.447009415161907
    },
    {
        "question": "4,683,332 ÷ 42,001=？",
        "answer": 2.0472953152592512
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 1,019,526=？",
        "answer": 7.976881254207621
    },
    {
        "question": "122 × 338,748=？",
        "answer": 7.616236570449379
    },
    {
        "question": "5,213 × 444=？",
        "answer": 6.364470695041639
    },
    {
        "question": "20,958 ÷ 236=？",
        "answer": 1.9484378330511838
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 2,959,357=？",
        "answer": 8.062261966164119
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 10,432,119=？",
        "answer": 8.57467503321462
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 2,839,122=？",
        "answer": 8.366997907392275
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 343=？",
        "answer": 3.7113853790984517
    },
    {
        "question": "17,585,330 ÷ 100,560=？",
        "answer": 2.2427252578661205
    },
    {
        "question": "26,909,501 ÷ 21,438=？",
        "answer": 3.098721377853413
    },
    {
        "question": "602,982,946 ÷ 24,923,612=？",
        "answer": 1.3836940475561534
    },
    {
        "question": "47,437 × 5,191=？",
        "answer": 8.391368244550334
    },
    {
        "question": "330,129 ÷ 226=？",
        "answer": 3.164575237217987
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 10,363=？",
        "answer": 4.0154854981544545
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 315,232=？",
        "answer": 6.799660293053884
    },
    {
        "question": "56,733,464 ÷ 189,253=？",
        "answer": 2.4767965287086406
    },
    {
        "question": "664,043 ÷ 6,234=？",
        "answer": 2.027429405008629
    },
    {
        "question": "322,977,722 ÷ 493=？",
        "answer": 5.816325647802655
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 11,317,391=？",
        "answer": 8.839076155423342
    },
    {
        "question": "32,500 ÷ 5,473=？",
        "answer": 0.7736579128363693
    },
    {
        "question": "48,245,219 ÷ 532=？",
        "answer": 4.957542649844947
    },
    {
        "question": "69,747 ÷ 1,349=？",
        "answer": 1.7135135825394583
    },
    {
        "question": "688,076,857 ÷ 87,907,574=？",
        "answer": 0.8936106559682361
    },
    {
        "question": "788 × 393=？",
        "answer": 5.490918767864982
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,612=？",
        "answer": 3.508395033133053
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 160,069,919=？",
        "answer": 8.505339720839029
    },
    {
        "question": "4,772 × 2,589=？",
        "answer": 7.0918324854331765
    },
    {
        "question": "24,954,772 ÷ 574,571=？",
        "answer": 1.637809903968956
    },
    {
        "question": "512 × 214=？",
        "answer": 5.039683734325021
    },
    {
        "question": "4,690 × 39,606=？",
        "answer": 8.268933825850311
    },
    {
        "question": "11,210 × 21,660=？",
        "answer": 8.385264064884275
    },
    {
        "question": "4,320,181 ÷ 5,344=？",
        "answer": 2.907635493100784
    },
    {
        "question": "2,274,080 ÷ 177,736=？",
        "answer": 1.1070303366731935
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 9,669=？",
        "answer": 4.763532810615641
    },
    {
        "question": "680,407 ÷ 38,815=？",
        "answer": 1.2437691824683375
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 30,101,314=？",
        "answer": 8.893558802052821
    },
    {
        "question": "4,456 × 598=？",
        "answer": 6.4256463661540835
    },
    {
        "question": "5,072 × 210=？",
        "answer": 6.027398539607596
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 262,176=？",
        "answer": 6.321682920171245
    },
    {
        "question": "19,969 × 3,552=？",
        "answer": 7.850829274087634
    },
    {
        "question": "54,663,386 ÷ 1,476,568=？",
        "answer": 1.5684430773689062
    },
    {
        "question": "5,882,085 ÷ 31,589=？",
        "answer": 2.269995418216825
    },
    {
        "question": "583,337,706 ÷ 114,851,817=？",
        "answer": 0.7057821791344254
    },
    {
        "question": "70,083 × 328=？",
        "answer": 7.361486527847152
    },
    {
        "question": "8,920 × 1,316=？",
        "answer": 7.06962074365406
    },
    {
        "question": "985,769,113 ÷ 255,041=？",
        "answer": 3.587165203767352
    },
    {
        "question": "425,715,418 ÷ 5,298=？",
        "answer": 4.905007425205983
    },
    {
        "question": "180,931,725 ÷ 1,167,690=？",
        "answer": 2.1901871628042975
    },
    {
        "question": "446,583 ÷ 36,764=？",
        "answer": 1.08447942940333
    },
    {
        "question": "483,727 × 1,555=？",
        "answer": 8.876330722272407
    },
    {
        "question": "738,672 ÷ 459,161=？",
        "answer": 0.2064866439686668
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 58,576,110=？",
        "answer": 8.721963036538583
    },
    {
        "question": "48,866,976 ÷ 22,080=？",
        "answer": 3.3450163956688286
    },
    {
        "question": "2,210,961 ÷ 1,544=？",
        "answer": 3.1559337859574783
    },
    {
        "question": "7,701,207 ÷ 22,373=？",
        "answer": 2.536834574273077
    },
    {
        "question": "60,935,743 ÷ 851,300=？",
        "answer": 1.8547894775348697
    },
    {
        "question": "420,727,188 ÷ 1,081=？",
        "answer": 5.590174883708691
    },
    {
        "question": "418,832 ÷ 6,785=？",
        "answer": 1.7904900036579097
    },
    {
        "question": "11,411 × 306=？",
        "answer": 6.543045131850865
    },
    {
        "question": "1,311,336 × 633=？",
        "answer": 8.919117694041235
    },
    {
        "question": "843,277,269 ÷ 42,084,390=？",
        "answer": 1.3018493572440077
    },
    {
        "question": "181 × 1,935,870=？",
        "answer": 8.54455476452633
    },
    {
        "question": "909 × 3,758=？",
        "answer": 6.5335206589864745
    },
    {
        "question": "19,558 × 11,430=？",
        "answer": 8.349370672187701
    },
    {
        "question": "622,134 × 321=？",
        "answer": 8.300388968852657
    },
    {
        "question": "179 × 164,151=？",
        "answer": 7.468096563754415
    },
    {
        "question": "380,123,321 ÷ 70,397=？",
        "answer": 3.7323703630024263
    },
    {
        "question": "120 × 31,413=？",
        "answer": 6.5762906603585725
    },
    {
        "question": "4,494 × 80,848=？",
        "answer": 8.560302348977265
    },
    {
        "question": "853,265 ÷ 464=？",
        "answer": 3.2645659511569654
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 1,561,613=？",
        "answer": 7.917849285320924
    },
    {
        "question": "6,866 ÷ 326=？",
        "answer": 1.3234861990217923
    },
    {
        "question": "5,290,889 ÷ 315,619=？",
        "answer": 1.2243655108742757
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 373=？",
        "answer": 4.090222771686575
    },
    {
        "question": "4,219 × 300=？",
        "answer": 6.102330780101544
    },
    {
        "question": "106,113,262 ÷ 1,515=？",
        "answer": 4.845357032434239
    },
    {
        "question": "475,624,296 ÷ 7,913=？",
        "answer": 4.778922865562347
    },
    {
        "question": "583,604,233 ÷ 41,381=？",
        "answer": 4.149317451780936
    },
    {
        "question": "480 × 425=？",
        "answer": 5.309630167425898
    },
    {
        "question": "4,667,751 ÷ 794,676=？",
        "answer": 0.768917583568921
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 86,331=？",
        "answer": 5.714318021897912
    },
    {
        "question": "177 × 558,500=？",
        "answer": 7.994996443813434
    },
    {
        "question": "554,009 × 651=？",
        "answer": 8.557097808564832
    },
    {
        "question": "16,596,802 ÷ 578,416=？",
        "answer": 1.4577841150872726
    },
    {
        "question": "64,049 × 4,502=？",
        "answer": 8.459917844138301
    },
    {
        "question": "13,353,002 ÷ 3,199=？",
        "answer": 3.620564673966299
    },
    {
        "question": "25,499,590 ÷ 723,236=？",
        "answer": 1.5472531620333005
    },
    {
        "question": "996 ÷ 236=？",
        "answer": 0.6253473354535922
    },
    {
        "question": "9,277 × 11,572=？",
        "answer": 8.030815981573419
    },
    {
        "question": "96 × 9,206,500=？",
        "answer": 8.946365790534768
    },
    {
        "question": "6,389,006 ÷ 336,644=？",
        "answer": 1.278262417533874
    },
    {
        "question": "34,944 ÷ 2,069=？",
        "answer": 1.2276121260228898
    },
    {
        "question": "9,768 × 568=？",
        "answer": 6.744153986647845
    },
    {
        "question": "1,873,818 ÷ 531=？",
        "answer": 3.5476328854093757
    },
    {
        "question": "136 × 9,011=？",
        "answer": 6.088311898059935
    },
    {
        "question": "336,760,550 ÷ 326,067,141=？",
        "answer": 0.01401417460231136
    },
    {
        "question": "14,247,848 ÷ 220=？",
        "answer": 4.811326592483531
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 525,776=？",
        "answer": 5.720800758062752
    },
    {
        "question": "1,407 × 676=？",
        "answer": 5.978240793376382
    },
    {
        "question": "730,276 ÷ 2,532=？",
        "answer": 2.4600233267521956
    },
    {
        "question": "3,684,532 ÷ 66,560=？",
        "answer": 1.7431690194211884
    },
    {
        "question": "100,208,905 ÷ 596=？",
        "answer": 5.225660056806156
    },
    {
        "question": "10,286,076 ÷ 304=？",
        "answer": 4.529376145229
    },
    {
        "question": "112,791,001 ÷ 21,800=？",
        "answer": 3.71381795735525
    },
    {
        "question": "6,830 × 1,089=？",
        "answer": 6.871448583437307
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 10,238=？",
        "answer": 5.2406640465925
    },
    {
        "question": "9,934,583 ÷ 1,544=？",
        "answer": 3.808502346497982
    },
    {
        "question": "13,891 × 504=？",
        "answer": 6.845164047759044
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,699,636=？",
        "answer": 6.973094217575603
    },
    {
        "question": "6,011 ÷ 1,086=？",
        "answer": 0.7431169027157887
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 89,422=？",
        "answer": 6.707319234683037
    },
    {
        "question": "481,195,839 ÷ 1,294,583=？",
        "answer": 2.5701919635299215
    },
    {
        "question": "636,391,281 ÷ 896=？",
        "answer": 5.851416211218881
    },
    {
        "question": "203 × 219,547=？",
        "answer": 7.64902354497718
    },
    {
        "question": "164,895,218 ÷ 99,731=？",
        "answer": 3.218377887464326
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 35,434,768=？",
        "answer": 8.804702098779094
    },
    {
        "question": "2,085,234 ÷ 792=？",
        "answer": 3.4204296159488194
    },
    {
        "question": "12,199 ÷ 11,554=？",
        "answer": 0.023591868101991206
    },
    {
        "question": "811 × 655,387=？",
        "answer": 8.725518676847598
    },
    {
        "question": "1,270,964 ÷ 10,448=？",
        "answer": 2.0851000854249206
    },
    {
        "question": "4,816 ÷ 454=？",
        "answer": 1.0256306253926644
    },
    {
        "question": "438,146 ÷ 51,564=？",
        "answer": 0.9292722514777617
    },
    {
        "question": "14,708 × 3,281=？",
        "answer": 7.6835598515828725
    },
    {
        "question": "2,026,540 ÷ 908=？",
        "answer": 3.3486693317786016
    },
    {
        "question": "645 × 371,308=？",
        "answer": 8.379294021034674
    },
    {
        "question": "2,106 ÷ 558=？",
        "answer": 0.576824167911889
    },
    {
        "question": "106,588 ÷ 85,512=？",
        "answer": 0.09568124919137502
    },
    {
        "question": "29,083 × 3,556=？",
        "answer": 8.014600955594021
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 189,072=？",
        "answer": 6.723785249526948
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 221,120=？",
        "answer": 5.946688017022066
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 459,857=？",
        "answer": 6.9848420964892926
    },
    {
        "question": "726 × 899=？",
        "answer": 5.814696312433322
    },
    {
        "question": "115,455,840 ÷ 139,437=？",
        "answer": 2.9180378750237
    },
    {
        "question": "781,199,943 ÷ 54,143,528=？",
        "answer": 1.1592156518808328
    },
    {
        "question": "3,717 × 173,712=？",
        "answer": 8.810022381579513
    },
    {
        "question": "927,871,801 ÷ 10,350=？",
        "answer": 4.952547626464351
    },
    {
        "question": "19,184,627 ÷ 1,719=？",
        "answer": 4.04767748309349
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 274=？",
        "answer": 3.693023067923694
    },
    {
        "question": "3,516 × 8,362=？",
        "answer": 7.46835902961613
    },
    {
        "question": "12,125 ÷ 707=？",
        "answer": 1.2342623334774019
    },
    {
        "question": "622,381,206 ÷ 227=？",
        "answer": 6.438030612627637
    },
    {
        "question": "137,366,310 ÷ 62,357,685=？",
        "answer": 0.34299024834064523
    },
    {
        "question": "666,619,741 ÷ 15,122=？",
        "answer": 4.644268936805063
    },
    {
        "question": "487,568 × 214=？",
        "answer": 8.018448967671524
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 46,118=？",
        "answer": 6.588149751037587
    },
    {
        "question": "337 × 255=？",
        "answer": 4.934170081305294
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,288=？",
        "answer": 3.933284772348695
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 1,526,375=？",
        "answer": 8.070151969422595
    },
    {
        "question": "316,523 × 314=？",
        "answer": 7.997334921384441
    },
    {
        "question": "333 × 216=？",
        "answer": 4.856897984657251
    },
    {
        "question": "372,756,355 ÷ 115,206=？",
        "answer": 3.509949958328922
    },
    {
        "question": "613 × 10,771=？",
        "answer": 6.819716500408868
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 47,651=？",
        "answer": 5.377042023474579
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,332,006=？",
        "answer": 6.8652228116865
    },
    {
        "question": "578,345 × 305=？",
        "answer": 8.246486824649434
    },
    {
        "question": "4,926 × 11,962=？",
        "answer": 7.770298205579173
    },
    {
        "question": "105,920,888 ÷ 56,695=？",
        "answer": 3.271436853438002
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 11,133=？",
        "answer": 4.7455822134044645
    },
    {
        "question": "11,560 ÷ 584=？",
        "answer": 1.2965449869721106
    },
    {
        "question": "1,433 × 40,436=？",
        "answer": 7.763014378269643
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 904,442=？",
        "answer": 6.257410717343402
    },
    {
        "question": "418,556 ÷ 4,671=？",
        "answer": 1.9523437046327847
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 237,547=？",
        "answer": 6.074719554386243
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 57,890=？",
        "answer": 5.364663540894766
    },
    {
        "question": "4,606 ÷ 647=？",
        "answer": 0.8524196529595119
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 63,856=？",
        "answer": 6.0604742155432545
    },
    {
        "question": "166 × 904,193=？",
        "answer": 8.176369228569406
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 565=？",
        "answer": 3.4510184521554574
    },
    {
        "question": "145,090,534 ÷ 1,840=？",
        "answer": 4.8968212561017435
    },
    {
        "question": "676,448,770 ÷ 216,246,674=？",
        "answer": 0.4952854749449064
    },
    {
        "question": "38,041,616 ÷ 7,269=？",
        "answer": 3.7187842885400677
    },
    {
        "question": "116 × 343,461=？",
        "answer": 7.600335419279304
    },
    {
        "question": "243,969 ÷ 88,943=？",
        "answer": 0.4382228721939633
    },
    {
        "question": "198,841 ÷ 4,047=？",
        "answer": 1.6913727342103266
    },
    {
        "question": "222,187 ÷ 175,570=？",
        "answer": 0.1022683359580415
    },
    {
        "question": "26,315 × 239=？",
        "answer": 6.798601275301434
    },
    {
        "question": "9,352 ÷ 202=？",
        "answer": 1.6655531287071599
    },
    {
        "question": "46,005,201 ÷ 1,723=？",
        "answer": 4.426521655057808
    },
    {
        "question": "4,554,865 ÷ 288=？",
        "answer": 4.199083021843112
    },
    {
        "question": "92,210,846 ÷ 12,193,307=？",
        "answer": 0.8786604980343715
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 233,904=？",
        "answer": 6.900516565799137
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 1,471,707=？",
        "answer": 8.04863494783309
    },
    {
        "question": "3,622 × 9,140=？",
        "answer": 7.519894641711871
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 516,752=？",
        "answer": 5.713282166164896
    },
    {
        "question": "15,639,306 ÷ 2,174=？",
        "answer": 3.8569579374225484
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,686=？",
        "answer": 3.527887565952705
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 11,882=？",
        "answer": 5.765085628069182
    },
    {
        "question": "464,343,810 ÷ 181,838,341=？",
        "answer": 0.4071542000450953
    },
    {
        "question": "1,881 × 532=？",
        "answer": 6.000300427845427
    },
    {
        "question": "145,336 × 239=？",
        "answer": 7.5407711041300445
    },
    {
        "question": "197,673,482 ÷ 592=？",
        "answer": 5.523626705668563
    },
    {
        "question": "486 × 1,488,773=？",
        "answer": 8.85946475320463
    },
    {
        "question": "63,465 × 14,287=？",
        "answer": 8.957475329117303
    },
    {
        "question": "31,048 ÷ 3,490=？",
        "answer": 0.9492082027727786
    },
    {
        "question": "20,271,017 ÷ 204=？",
        "answer": 4.99724537043378
    },
    {
        "question": "1,421,555 ÷ 4,174=？",
        "answer": 2.5322112224869096
    },
    {
        "question": "125,806,842 ÷ 9,510=？",
        "answer": 4.121523743901906
    },
    {
        "question": "19,294,261 ÷ 84,775=？",
        "answer": 2.357160350626332
    },
    {
        "question": "768,830,363 ÷ 21,604,533=？",
        "answer": 1.5512856432440358
    },
    {
        "question": "1,085,749 ÷ 31,821=？",
        "answer": 1.5330156144678286
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 586,395=？",
        "answer": 6.245311513280313
    },
    {
        "question": "258,170,867 ÷ 12,769,111=？",
        "answer": 1.3057465709836447
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 1,028=？",
        "answer": 4.614053105987219
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 271,289=？",
        "answer": 7.290764681139597
    },
    {
        "question": "335,493 ÷ 124,945=？",
        "answer": 0.4289645817407406
    },
    {
        "question": "12,520 ÷ 251=？",
        "answer": 1.6979306073933726
    },
    {
        "question": "59,112 ÷ 9,507=？",
        "answer": 0.7936321596407463
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 407,580=？",
        "answer": 7.072610862873327
    },
    {
        "question": "21,441 ÷ 400=？",
        "answer": 1.7291850454928672
    },
    {
        "question": "14,069 × 262=？",
        "answer": 6.566564520956624
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 101,688,859=？",
        "answer": 8.706243378695694
    },
    {
        "question": "3,271,944 ÷ 553=？",
        "answer": 3.7720807307180864
    },
    {
        "question": "8,654 ÷ 530=？",
        "answer": 1.2129410212619165
    },
    {
        "question": "131,781 ÷ 46,849=？",
        "answer": 0.4491524735694216
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 2,299,187=？",
        "answer": 8.44435966553761
    },
    {
        "question": "4,809 × 7,795=？",
        "answer": 7.573870896598668
    },
    {
        "question": "759,079,345 ÷ 2,649=？",
        "answer": 5.457205215878401
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 20,803,365=？",
        "answer": 7.3181335889402845
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 81,982,361=？",
        "answer": 8.515780412682279
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 14,872,954=？",
        "answer": 8.835155066409888
    },
    {
        "question": "38,392,904 ÷ 1,162=？",
        "answer": 4.519044834896035
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 33,143=？",
        "answer": 4.520391816831582
    },
    {
        "question": "126,904,131 ÷ 4,638,036=？",
        "answer": 1.4371416442679819
    },
    {
        "question": "896,778,149 ÷ 53,190,195=？",
        "answer": 1.2268534351604954
    },
    {
        "question": "334,713,761 ÷ 3,985=？",
        "answer": 4.924245242029029
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,707=？",
        "answer": 3.672744198306599
    },
    {
        "question": "488,097,722 ÷ 60,243,738=？",
        "answer": 0.9085948696584688
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,018=？",
        "answer": 3.782042416620554
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 7,633,781=？",
        "answer": 8.41421861367501
    },
    {
        "question": "458,012 ÷ 249,715=？",
        "answer": 0.2634322262060711
    },
    {
        "question": "34,958 × 1,087=？",
        "answer": 7.57977612211588
    },
    {
        "question": "617 × 55,329=？",
        "answer": 7.533237985008165
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 1,162=？",
        "answer": 4.79759988787728
    },
    {
        "question": "151 × 1,239,570=？",
        "answer": 8.272248004218177
    },
    {
        "question": "460 × 1,258,690=？",
        "answer": 8.762676613523311
    },
    {
        "question": "7,620 × 2,110=？",
        "answer": 7.206237426637293
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,004,574=？",
        "answer": 6.001981933725331
    },
    {
        "question": "7,895,758 ÷ 332,788=？",
        "answer": 1.3752261713342018
    },
    {
        "question": "54,784 × 1,526=？",
        "answer": 7.922208272279902
    },
    {
        "question": "412,775 ÷ 6,602=？",
        "answer": 1.7960378660792402
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 402,869=？",
        "answer": 5.605163850543239
    },
    {
        "question": "6,326,534 ÷ 15,034=？",
        "answer": 2.6240913004533106
    },
    {
        "question": "333 × 4,822=？",
        "answer": 6.205671439547754
    },
    {
        "question": "782 × 177,460=？",
        "answer": 8.14230723024277
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 42,593,682=？",
        "answer": 7.930375179836455
    },
    {
        "question": "204,770,210 ÷ 869,015=？",
        "answer": 2.372239502838145
    },
    {
        "question": "237,178,296 ÷ 1,221,131=？",
        "answer": 2.2883126880500377
    },
    {
        "question": "6,470 × 1,105=？",
        "answer": 6.8542665586898295
    },
    {
        "question": "1,081,299 × 406=？",
        "answer": 8.642471834926306
    },
    {
        "question": "1,995 × 400=？",
        "answer": 5.90200289135073
    },
    {
        "question": "486,569,587 ÷ 16,843,055=？",
        "answer": 1.4607240930812675
    },
    {
        "question": "73,336,667 ÷ 2,426=？",
        "answer": 4.480430371755596
    },
    {
        "question": "468,122,926 ÷ 18,105,325=？",
        "answer": 1.4125535858885603
    },
    {
        "question": "8,757 ÷ 1,466=？",
        "answer": 0.7762213794025676
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 489,159=？",
        "answer": 6.8355780841652045
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 4,943,323=？",
        "answer": 8.108992336447912
    },
    {
        "question": "743,784,863 ÷ 8,118=？",
        "answer": 4.961998288667842
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 9,837=？",
        "answer": 5.511376611266916
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 174,277,875=？",
        "answer": 8.940212260204966
    },
    {
        "question": "653 × 115,082=？",
        "answer": 7.875920582124716
    },
    {
        "question": "5,469,600 ÷ 1,613=？",
        "answer": 3.53032119950302
    },
    {
        "question": "153,624 × 240=？",
        "answer": 7.566670310619003
    },
    {
        "question": "113,022,776 ÷ 326=？",
        "answer": 5.539948369914609
    },
    {
        "question": "860,912 ÷ 121,185=？",
        "answer": 0.8515098941766674
    },
    {
        "question": "389,409 ÷ 1,502=？",
        "answer": 2.413736052022716
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 5,591,716=？",
        "answer": 7.349605097061835
    },
    {
        "question": "551,003,080 ÷ 1,160,899=？",
        "answer": 2.676359589386538
    },
    {
        "question": "326,121,121 ÷ 109,109=？",
        "answer": 3.4755183510668277
    },
    {
        "question": "5,682 × 606=？",
        "answer": 6.536973853553203
    },
    {
        "question": "103,429 × 2,857=？",
        "answer": 8.470552566124676
    },
    {
        "question": "4,828 × 1,240=？",
        "answer": 6.777188946587547
    },
    {
        "question": "117,968 ÷ 34,760=？",
        "answer": 0.5306844487823944
    },
    {
        "question": "6,492 × 1,320=？",
        "answer": 6.932952442360044
    },
    {
        "question": "21,832,374 ÷ 533,661=？",
        "answer": 1.6118354967390052
    },
    {
        "question": "522,509,337 ÷ 6,041,784=？",
        "answer": 1.9369288607539812
    },
    {
        "question": "78,263 × 9,636=？",
        "answer": 8.877453282712
    },
    {
        "question": "989,983,734 ÷ 8,112=？",
        "answer": 5.086500116959726
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 197,642,535=？",
        "answer": 8.295880415595093
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,890=？",
        "answer": 3.7535830588929064
    },
    {
        "question": "17,968,473 ÷ 70,720=？",
        "answer": 2.40496891938043
    },
    {
        "question": "1,831 × 854=？",
        "answer": 6.194146214990702
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 19,341,584=？",
        "answer": 8.976688118249617
    },
    {
        "question": "36,743,574 ÷ 1,734,921=？",
        "answer": 1.3259016934031909
    },
    {
        "question": "120,741,419 ÷ 205,462=？",
        "answer": 2.769124764253979
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 3,989=？",
        "answer": 4.680045282357464
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 759=？",
        "answer": 3.9216344610537055
    },
    {
        "question": "14,828 ÷ 798=？",
        "answer": 1.2690796860067968
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 8,431=？",
        "answer": 5.839692941685217
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 5,027=？",
        "answer": 5.219822825105963
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 127,502=？",
        "answer": 6.992007722351486
    },
    {
        "question": "5,378 × 100,956=？",
        "answer": 8.734752932850519
    },
    {
        "question": "109,983 × 2,877=？",
        "answer": 8.500265423623494
    },
    {
        "question": "1,848,722 ÷ 543,529=？",
        "answer": 0.531648888574439
    },
    {
        "question": "27,070,814 ÷ 21,489,560=？",
        "answer": 0.1002737915135389
    },
    {
        "question": "968,287,972 ÷ 8,963,601=？",
        "answer": 2.0335220207269704
    },
    {
        "question": "12,049,096 ÷ 4,586=？",
        "answer": 3.419520414198375
    },
    {
        "question": "40,935,063 ÷ 40,813,367=？",
        "answer": 0.001293038662928359
    },
    {
        "question": "372 ÷ 246=？",
        "answer": 0.17960783277851838
    },
    {
        "question": "4,633 × 742=？",
        "answer": 6.536266205482182
    },
    {
        "question": "18,846,133 ÷ 235,737=？",
        "answer": 1.902794499295665
    },
    {
        "question": "54,766,058 ÷ 4,861=？",
        "answer": 4.0517858609449915
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 46,015,987=？",
        "answer": 7.662908741674031
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 112,934=？",
        "answer": 5.353854706317274
    },
    {
        "question": "569,025,093 ÷ 186,363=？",
        "answer": 3.484771725497518
    },
    {
        "question": "17,786,816 ÷ 444,248=？",
        "answer": 1.6024727311316684
    },
    {
        "question": "385,562 ÷ 5,005=？",
        "answer": 1.8866901425763956
    },
    {
        "question": "239,207 ÷ 121,693=？",
        "answer": 0.2935082868674413
    },
    {
        "question": "20,815 ÷ 11,669=？",
        "answer": 0.251342775380534
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 188,555=？",
        "answer": 5.877498044609609
    },
    {
        "question": "275,361 ÷ 46,166=？",
        "answer": 0.7755801829335373
    },
    {
        "question": "407,551 × 1,036=？",
        "answer": 8.625541718504058
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 7,692,848=？",
        "answer": 7.187117147130273
    },
    {
        "question": "10,922,847 ÷ 2,091=？",
        "answer": 3.7179818175693318
    },
    {
        "question": "2,175,602 ÷ 1,882,315=？",
        "answer": 0.06288714627880361
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 681=？",
        "answer": 3.678245151927042
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 38,636=？",
        "answer": 5.189052148723337
    },
    {
        "question": "111 × 108,937=？",
        "answer": 7.082498389916671
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 1,539,072=？",
        "answer": 7.877455017255234
    },
    {
        "question": "397,249,197 ÷ 5,873,586=？",
        "answer": 1.8301596959994302
    },
    {
        "question": "2,043,490 × 462=？",
        "answer": 8.975014492350278
    },
    {
        "question": "2,469 × 59,855=？",
        "answer": 8.169621525070514
    },
    {
        "question": "454,220 ÷ 4,105=？",
        "answer": 2.0439530914982895
    },
    {
        "question": "5,844 × 266=？",
        "answer": 6.191591843893326
    },
    {
        "question": "286 × 2,598=？",
        "answer": 5.871005179866052
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,629,336=？",
        "answer": 6.720876083338185
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 20,198,874=？",
        "answer": 8.34671984523769
    },
    {
        "question": "163,928 ÷ 1,327=？",
        "answer": 2.0917822174474208
    },
    {
        "question": "101,904 ÷ 2,816=？",
        "answer": 1.5585585810715115
    },
    {
        "question": "655 × 232,841=？",
        "answer": 8.183300755806263
    },
    {
        "question": "152,368 × 1,990=？",
        "answer": 8.481746843395754
    },
    {
        "question": "102 × 10,225=？",
        "answer": 6.018263488441297
    },
    {
        "question": "27,472 ÷ 222=？",
        "answer": 2.0925373033662025
    },
    {
        "question": "181,505,897 ÷ 18,530=？",
        "answer": 3.9910153202072625
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 1,997,942=？",
        "answer": 8.349800899230033
    },
    {
        "question": "273,447,581 ÷ 217,562,615=？",
        "answer": 0.099289815638016
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 3,005,044=？",
        "answer": 7.591794187653018
    },
    {
        "question": "81,066,021 ÷ 2,653,601=？",
        "answer": 1.485003234695086
    },
    {
        "question": "19,857 ÷ 1,531=？",
        "answer": 1.1129384451096052
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 906,696=？",
        "answer": 6.73561295017472
    },
    {
        "question": "2,561 × 4,503=？",
        "answer": 7.061911525431363
    },
    {
        "question": "11,664 × 393=？",
        "answer": 6.661240061349326
    },
    {
        "question": "2,866 × 67,894=？",
        "answer": 8.289107582108723
    },
    {
        "question": "62,635,139 ÷ 2,453=？",
        "answer": 4.407120497341044
    },
    {
        "question": "446,338 ÷ 407,806=？",
        "answer": 0.03921025185136047
    },
    {
        "question": "23,230,526 ÷ 2,620=？",
        "answer": 3.9477577521572544
    },
    {
        "question": "655,392,202 ÷ 568,937,422=？",
        "answer": 0.06143676921170328
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 108,693,008=？",
        "answer": 8.337231603368638
    },
    {
        "question": "299,865,761 ÷ 436,654=？",
        "answer": 2.83678943747402
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 20,209,754=？",
        "answer": 7.305561027167319
    },
    {
        "question": "51,603 ÷ 809=？",
        "answer": 1.8047264289601457
    },
    {
        "question": "6,611 × 1,311=？",
        "answer": 6.937869848851049
    },
    {
        "question": "15,107 × 1,946=？",
        "answer": 7.468321065142127
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,562,458=？",
        "answer": 6.7452667448092845
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 5,439=？",
        "answer": 5.036549054479153
    },
    {
        "question": "166,063 ÷ 81,723=？",
        "answer": 0.30792857844527394
    },
    {
        "question": "675,255,561 ÷ 1,342,997=？",
        "answer": 2.7013931269247355
    },
    {
        "question": "7,681 ÷ 294=？",
        "answer": 1.4170704346987788
    },
    {
        "question": "115,404,831 ÷ 32,130,255=？",
        "answer": 0.5553098170265031
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 123,977,767=？",
        "answer": 8.570465064600102
    },
    {
        "question": "150 × 545,107=？",
        "answer": 7.912573018118516
    },
    {
        "question": "97,470,168 ÷ 268,626=？",
        "answer": 2.559723669389198
    },
    {
        "question": "121,539,730 ÷ 512,865=？",
        "answer": 2.374715205179274
    },
    {
        "question": "1,514,720 ÷ 1,164=？",
        "answer": 3.1143793794594323
    },
    {
        "question": "399,757 × 304=？",
        "answer": 8.084669660866941
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 12,511=？",
        "answer": 4.398322019755877
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 14,428,119=？",
        "answer": 7.761269706955867
    },
    {
        "question": "109,925 × 3,166=？",
        "answer": 8.54160738481808
    },
    {
        "question": "6,289,870 ÷ 108,749=？",
        "answer": 1.7622163973770815
    },
    {
        "question": "12,209,935 ÷ 372=？",
        "answer": 4.5161704120878445
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,474=？",
        "answer": 4.216799061647666
    },
    {
        "question": "640,294,691 ÷ 344,206=？",
        "answer": 3.269561464460868
    },
    {
        "question": "512,573,581 ÷ 488,976=？",
        "answer": 3.020468674542149
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 25,097,667=？",
        "answer": 7.3996333527114295
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 212,214=？",
        "answer": 7.178032380132587
    },
    {
        "question": "30,928,986 ÷ 988,505=？",
        "answer": 1.4953868116085556
    },
    {
        "question": "77,818,619 ÷ 1,171,108=？",
        "answer": 1.822486571662226
    },
    {
        "question": "698,499,621 ÷ 989,974=？",
        "answer": 2.8485423860716343
    },
    {
        "question": "809,699 ÷ 87,845=？",
        "answer": 0.9646065557390082
    },
    {
        "question": "2,759 × 50,828=？",
        "answer": 8.146854721729158
    },
    {
        "question": "133,358,606 ÷ 128,118,324=？",
        "answer": 0.017409798417949256
    },
    {
        "question": "223 × 38,236=？",
        "answer": 6.930777315983015
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 228=？",
        "answer": 3.5620548296563785
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,199=？",
        "answer": 3.9819091700907925
    },
    {
        "question": "734,776,483 ÷ 22,075,973=？",
        "answer": 1.52223539374834
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 64,301=？",
        "answer": 4.808217727062711
    },
    {
        "question": "75,822,390 ÷ 76,372=？",
        "answer": 2.996863305831362
    },
    {
        "question": "2,285 × 247,061=？",
        "answer": 8.751690399336223
    },
    {
        "question": "129 × 110,214=？",
        "answer": 7.152826474838288
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 1,039,900=？",
        "answer": 7.732994921841004
    },
    {
        "question": "5,748 × 801=？",
        "answer": 6.663149275546425
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 29,547,921=？",
        "answer": 7.470526929210803
    },
    {
        "question": "28,028 ÷ 26,157=？",
        "answer": 0.030004176438346474
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 7,407=？",
        "answer": 5.073762327307519
    },
    {
        "question": "48,855 ÷ 497=？",
        "answer": 1.9925526288872222
    },
    {
        "question": "1,745,303 ÷ 812,549=？",
        "answer": 0.3320212750355544
    },
    {
        "question": "15,311,745 ÷ 1,475=？",
        "answer": 4.016232667489599
    },
    {
        "question": "1,312,564 ÷ 639=？",
        "answer": 3.3126196304294604
    },
    {
        "question": "121,199 ÷ 48,364=？",
        "answer": 0.39897682403108853
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 52,046=？",
        "answer": 6.51572790684132
    },
    {
        "question": "315 × 763,261=？",
        "answer": 8.3809836257906
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 430,300=？",
        "answer": 6.71295259213018
    },
    {
        "question": "3,985 × 1,749=？",
        "answer": 6.843218135210807
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 8,802=？",
        "answer": 5.0907093999051645
    },
    {
        "question": "29,330,627 ÷ 97,397=？",
        "answer": 2.478775766935027
    },
    {
        "question": "890,879,730 ÷ 280,553=？",
        "answer": 3.5018041605886934
    },
    {
        "question": "3,009,291 ÷ 294,459=？",
        "answer": 1.0094393534084483
    },
    {
        "question": "848,366,945 ÷ 2,124,275=？",
        "answer": 2.6013730006721656
    },
    {
        "question": "215 ÷ 211=？",
        "answer": 0.008156004617912655
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 1,425=？",
        "answer": 4.5517548730165664
    },
    {
        "question": "12,412,038 ÷ 1,080,913=？",
        "answer": 1.0600523564489495
    },
    {
        "question": "183,621,790 ÷ 18,936,912=？",
        "answer": 0.9866150557002424
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,599,035=？",
        "answer": 6.9636967103584855
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,928,142=？",
        "answer": 6.7676221296354
    },
    {
        "question": "115,867,250 ÷ 560,707=？",
        "answer": 2.3152247215484825
    },
    {
        "question": "19,832,356 ÷ 211,109=？",
        "answer": 1.9728675610703936
    },
    {
        "question": "1,586,590 ÷ 154,710=？",
        "answer": 1.010946326550048
    },
    {
        "question": "739,412,411 ÷ 403,808,739=？",
        "answer": 0.26271102244472305
    },
    {
        "question": "105,317 × 1,348=？",
        "answer": 8.152188371744591
    },
    {
        "question": "9,859,073 ÷ 9,559,730=？",
        "answer": 0.013390455829285221
    },
    {
        "question": "14,469 × 15,109=？",
        "answer": 8.339674237840025
    },
    {
        "question": "1,355 ÷ 379=？",
        "answer": 0.5533000852423522
    },
    {
        "question": "73 × 8,299=？",
        "answer": 5.782348624707816
    },
    {
        "question": "1,485 × 97,044=？",
        "answer": 8.158695142811473
    },
    {
        "question": "121,214,983 ÷ 468=？",
        "answer": 5.413310451839054
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 278=？",
        "answer": 3.6201360549737576
    },
    {
        "question": "1,128 ÷ 230=？",
        "answer": 0.6905812636297306
    },
    {
        "question": "29,612,327 ÷ 9,166,363=？",
        "answer": 0.509275484639135
    },
    {
        "question": "12,032,012 ÷ 699=？",
        "answer": 4.235861080641113
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,304,474=？",
        "answer": 7.212306792557352
    },
    {
        "question": "469 × 10,153=？",
        "answer": 6.677767228899221
    },
    {
        "question": "2,130,160 ÷ 907,557=？",
        "answer": 0.3705383144211556
    },
    {
        "question": "130,327,008 ÷ 64,345,073=？",
        "answer": 0.30651912707305407
    },
    {
        "question": "3,709,263 ÷ 2,457,209=？",
        "answer": 0.17884553011343476
    },
    {
        "question": "25,271 × 3,835=？",
        "answer": 7.986387796033528
    },
    {
        "question": "29,322 ÷ 886=？",
        "answer": 1.5197598675247648
    },
    {
        "question": "130,456 ÷ 1,297=？",
        "answer": 2.002524082108523
    },
    {
        "question": "2,121,855 ÷ 933=？",
        "answer": 3.356834058697478
    },
    {
        "question": "45,606,377 ÷ 336,125=？",
        "answer": 2.132524757746169
    },
    {
        "question": "90,246 ÷ 2,960=？",
        "answer": 1.4841362505832913
    },
    {
        "question": "252,204,328 ÷ 693=？",
        "answer": 5.561019300481679
    },
    {
        "question": "444 × 1,096=？",
        "answer": 5.6871935242629705
    },
    {
        "question": "229,384,137 ÷ 522=？",
        "answer": 5.642892878080111
    },
    {
        "question": "1,515 × 3,640=？",
        "answer": 6.74151401648738
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 26,216=？",
        "answer": 4.418566428374319
    },
    {
        "question": "2,229 × 8,035=？",
        "answer": 7.253095949579601
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 236=？",
        "answer": 2.974971994298069
    },
    {
        "question": "223,527 × 411=？",
        "answer": 7.963171811280443
    },
    {
        "question": "175 × 1,676=？",
        "answer": 5.467312062980552
    },
    {
        "question": "197 × 3,305,872=？",
        "answer": 8.813752260282122
    },
    {
        "question": "55,930 × 7,191=？",
        "answer": 8.604434108081565
    },
    {
        "question": "263,152,481 ÷ 8,673=？",
        "answer": 4.482038122508028
    },
    {
        "question": "240,852,789 ÷ 426=？",
        "answer": 5.7523420805711805
    },
    {
        "question": "8,552,109 ÷ 2,134=？",
        "answer": 3.6028788124018933
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 159,148=？",
        "answer": 5.502831180911788
    },
    {
        "question": "58,161,684 ÷ 52,192,015=？",
        "answer": 0.04703290831884815
    },
    {
        "question": "2,936 ÷ 514=？",
        "answer": 0.7567929322487572
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 1,674=？",
        "answer": 4.7289054319771475
    },
    {
        "question": "61,704 × 1,477=？",
        "answer": 7.959693813666416
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 312,446=？",
        "answer": 6.193744973444911
    },
    {
        "question": "654 × 76,464=？",
        "answer": 7.699034761500986
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,330,265=？",
        "answer": 6.822908169042721
    },
    {
        "question": "10,098 × 3,130=？",
        "answer": 7.499779703905916
    },
    {
        "question": "1,874 × 1,549=？",
        "answer": 6.462821004310966
    },
    {
        "question": "4,593 × 789=？",
        "answer": 6.559173448627344
    },
    {
        "question": "204,255,588 ÷ 594,788=？",
        "answer": 2.535811748807514
    },
    {
        "question": "194 × 12,981=？",
        "answer": 6.401109879848613
    },
    {
        "question": "6,403 × 154,901=？",
        "answer": 8.996437723283051
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 7,345,735=？",
        "answer": 7.644186507347778
    },
    {
        "question": "1,006,010 ÷ 8,721=？",
        "answer": 2.062036011250926
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 2,761=？",
        "answer": 5.240406956092845
    },
    {
        "question": "89,700,110 ÷ 500=？",
        "answer": 5.253822971287379
    },
    {
        "question": "6,233,099 ÷ 759,025=？",
        "answer": 0.9144479443396055
    },
    {
        "question": "2,578,048 ÷ 27,327=？",
        "answer": 1.9746990423130204
    },
    {
        "question": "284,387 × 234=？",
        "answer": 7.82312559729732
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 5,043=？",
        "answer": 5.666476795504689
    },
    {
        "question": "69,668 × 3,228=？",
        "answer": 8.351966869218
    },
    {
        "question": "783,773,500 ÷ 292=？",
        "answer": 6.428807724103044
    },
    {
        "question": "690 × 58,511=？",
        "answer": 7.606086611353027
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 9,966,583=？",
        "answer": 7.299576283503781
    },
    {
        "question": "3,703 × 6,429=？",
        "answer": 7.376697137810933
    },
    {
        "question": "5,236 × 3,768=？",
        "answer": 7.295110531999558
    },
    {
        "question": "136,472,170 ÷ 2,337,659=？",
        "answer": 1.7662629373267635
    },
    {
        "question": "337,713 × 567=？",
        "answer": 8.282130837679333
    },
    {
        "question": "3,251,694 ÷ 79,822=？",
        "answer": 1.6099870644934717
    },
    {
        "question": "135,852 ÷ 2,783=？",
        "answer": 1.688552830108274
    },
    {
        "question": "2,223 ÷ 1,423=？",
        "answer": 0.19373456261470628
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 5,349=？",
        "answer": 4.330332589222979
    },
    {
        "question": "437,701 ÷ 4,706=？",
        "answer": 1.9685256159914934
    },
    {
        "question": "26,528 ÷ 1,154=？",
        "answer": 1.361498700050467
    },
    {
        "question": "36,961 × 415=？",
        "answer": 7.18579180949303
    },
    {
        "question": "1,337 × 3,454=？",
        "answer": 6.664453740493425
    },
    {
        "question": "22,905 × 1,633=？",
        "answer": 7.572916480848771
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 34,060=？",
        "answer": 4.532244643626583
    },
    {
        "question": "404 × 1,599,719=？",
        "answer": 8.810425068099642
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 119,321=？",
        "answer": 5.8548681348043266
    },
    {
        "question": "2,130 × 5,673=？",
        "answer": 7.08219238700344
    },
    {
        "question": "212,263,830 ÷ 13,225,347=？",
        "answer": 1.205468920536035
    },
    {
        "question": "87,591,820 ÷ 5,368,438=？",
        "answer": 1.2126156084770803
    },
    {
        "question": "983 × 2,064=？",
        "answer": 6.307263210787309
    },
    {
        "question": "2,554 × 1,178=？",
        "answer": 6.478366183378479
    },
    {
        "question": "424,544,974 ÷ 2,882,269=？",
        "answer": 2.1681891930799955
    },
    {
        "question": "18,495 × 26,059=？",
        "answer": 8.683012081532404
    },
    {
        "question": "438,498 ÷ 25,135=？",
        "answer": 1.2416887273148305
    },
    {
        "question": "212,411,832 ÷ 4,108=？",
        "answer": 4.713548269712016
    },
    {
        "question": "22,274,395 ÷ 12,763=？",
        "answer": 3.241853147659147
    },
    {
        "question": "91,874 ÷ 624=？",
        "answer": 2.1680080353693327
    },
    {
        "question": "726,349,274 ÷ 19,897,472=？",
        "answer": 1.5623476045515428
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 1,694,186=？",
        "answer": 7.60917233031505
    },
    {
        "question": "5,594 ÷ 2,946=？",
        "answer": 0.27848971952889634
    },
    {
        "question": "4,968 × 1,308=？",
        "answer": 6.812789331156773
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 706,561=？",
        "answer": 6.694247702051332
    },
    {
        "question": "216,104 × 311=？",
        "answer": 7.827423194604434
    },
    {
        "question": "3,000,727 ÷ 495,737=？",
        "answer": 0.7819751517295095
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,416,048=？",
        "answer": 6.834553960136649
    },
    {
        "question": "104,142,451 ÷ 1,068,073=？",
        "answer": 1.9890268580109864
    },
    {
        "question": "973,211,567 ÷ 51,281=？",
        "answer": 4.278250776539837
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 1,310=？",
        "answer": 4.45969397647797
    },
    {
        "question": "363,292 × 942=？",
        "answer": 8.53430673722562
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 588=？",
        "answer": 3.371437317404101
    },
    {
        "question": "101,545 ÷ 963=？",
        "answer": 2.023032256806646
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 853=？",
        "answer": 3.4080702858871854
    },
    {
        "question": "451,945,946 ÷ 29,215,609=？",
        "answer": 1.1894715514634082
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 551,910=？",
        "answer": 7.189026294415409
    },
    {
        "question": "114,450 × 2,855=？",
        "answer": 8.514221909592429
    },
    {
        "question": "885,189,110 ÷ 503,296,643=？",
        "answer": 0.24521202874659237
    },
    {
        "question": "157 × 133,199=？",
        "answer": 7.320400616762194
    },
    {
        "question": "25,166 ÷ 7,012=？",
        "answer": 0.5549722848458016
    },
    {
        "question": "1,847 ÷ 970=？",
        "answer": 0.2796951611739965
    },
    {
        "question": "211,234 ÷ 3,937=？",
        "answer": 1.7295984082759017
    },
    {
        "question": "577,400,896 ÷ 21,025=？",
        "answer": 4.438741449005396
    },
    {
        "question": "81,174 × 774=？",
        "answer": 7.798157907846568
    },
    {
        "question": "12,704,850 ÷ 223,759=？",
        "answer": 1.7541890294474607
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 41,497=？",
        "answer": 6.667234723465644
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 20,976=？",
        "answer": 4.321722674346009
    },
    {
        "question": "29,137 × 877=？",
        "answer": 7.407444427329969
    },
    {
        "question": "1,696,851 ÷ 527,844=？",
        "answer": 0.5071381194220973
    },
    {
        "question": "43,091,175 ÷ 271=？",
        "answer": 5.201419045614957
    },
    {
        "question": "439,338,529 ÷ 17,678,201=？",
        "answer": 1.3953612240926698
    },
    {
        "question": "61,666 ÷ 543=？",
        "answer": 2.0552459489936457
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 836=？",
        "answer": 3.9222062774390163
    },
    {
        "question": "43,576,938 ÷ 1,075,378=？",
        "answer": 1.6076955631492498
    },
    {
        "question": "5,400,068 ÷ 4,252,949=？",
        "answer": 0.10370905385686091
    },
    {
        "question": "956 ÷ 812=？",
        "answer": 0.07090186303492477
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 262,906=？",
        "answer": 6.5337438499276805
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 6,861=？",
        "answer": 5.15860671406033
    },
    {
        "question": "1,339,377 ÷ 189,987=？",
        "answer": 0.8481789518379956
    },
    {
        "question": "1,496,820 × 355=？",
        "answer": 8.725397930481046
    },
    {
        "question": "20,143 × 1,019=？",
        "answer": 7.312298336739335
    },
    {
        "question": "187,346 ÷ 1,055=？",
        "answer": 2.2493919653302785
    },
    {
        "question": "5,634 × 642=？",
        "answer": 6.5583518707186075
    },
    {
        "question": "67,906,177 ÷ 47,551=？",
        "answer": 3.1547496265238193
    },
    {
        "question": "867 × 4,524=？",
        "answer": 6.593541693729628
    },
    {
        "question": "27,791 × 881=？",
        "answer": 7.388880082633401
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,147=？",
        "answer": 3.63286204010023
    },
    {
        "question": "27,253 × 29,410=？",
        "answer": 8.903909340724597
    },
    {
        "question": "4,404 × 91,811=？",
        "answer": 8.606742028027163
    },
    {
        "question": "5,842,799 ÷ 16,774=？",
        "answer": 2.5419843075822164
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 12,522=？",
        "answer": 5.176854945496722
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 1,057,504=？",
        "answer": 7.988069846110973
    },
    {
        "question": "5,625 ÷ 481=？",
        "answer": 1.0679774504095683
    },
    {
        "question": "4,718,124 ÷ 117,613=？",
        "answer": 1.6033140228369225
    },
    {
        "question": "5,133 × 4,029=？",
        "answer": 7.315568531649141
    },
    {
        "question": "583 × 1,148,371=？",
        "answer": 8.825750771412636
    },
    {
        "question": "9,829,181 ÷ 200=？",
        "answer": 4.691487336817311
    },
    {
        "question": "65,822,305 ÷ 5,752,367=？",
        "answer": 1.0585265004065123
    },
    {
        "question": "4,551 × 408=？",
        "answer": 6.268766998596273
    },
    {
        "question": "336,187 ÷ 536=？",
        "answer": 2.7974161260215613
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 26,006=？",
        "answer": 5.4942548042596835
    },
    {
        "question": "242,556,838 ÷ 1,170=？",
        "answer": 5.316627660727803
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 232,257=？",
        "answer": 6.978752668795794
    },
    {
        "question": "26,350,810 ÷ 1,249,744=？",
        "answer": 1.3239729091831283
    },
    {
        "question": "79,355,951 ÷ 1,363,950=？",
        "answer": 1.7647810504444668
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 14,737=？",
        "answer": 5.071499070511569
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 179,616=？",
        "answer": 5.555375016203559
    },
    {
        "question": "3,491,764 ÷ 1,158,679=？",
        "answer": 0.4790817472525651
    },
    {
        "question": "44,937 ÷ 11,916=？",
        "answer": 0.5764735809514286
    },
    {
        "question": "64,829,749 ÷ 869,490=？",
        "answer": 1.8725097486083244
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 112,890,705=？",
        "answer": 8.0526581852076
    },
    {
        "question": "56,339,019 ÷ 8,886,976=？",
        "answer": 0.802055273264993
    },
    {
        "question": "213,009 ÷ 479=？",
        "answer": 2.648062440107566
    },
    {
        "question": "41,806 ÷ 1,843=？",
        "answer": 1.3557132810031516
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 2,279=？",
        "answer": 5.12859633682252
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 126,463=？",
        "answer": 5.880114730470299
    },
    {
        "question": "59,237,869 ÷ 364,041=？",
        "answer": 2.2114491283105053
    },
    {
        "question": "354,010,460 ÷ 2,427,139=？",
        "answer": 2.1639214456929343
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 184,746,227=？",
        "answer": 8.56760557339492
    },
    {
        "question": "34,592 ÷ 6,952=？",
        "answer": 0.6968659088326062
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,707=？",
        "answer": 3.8868853589860084
    },
    {
        "question": "1,048 × 343,397=？",
        "answer": 8.556157779386593
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 453=？",
        "answer": 3.501196242027089
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 2,899,149=？",
        "answer": 7.784489830963326
    },
    {
        "question": "102,414,778 ÷ 15,192,556=？",
        "answer": 0.8287317820979703
    },
    {
        "question": "1,160 × 55,917=？",
        "answer": 7.812001852279359
    },
    {
        "question": "10,612 ÷ 301=？",
        "answer": 1.5472307457164483
    },
    {
        "question": "42,713 × 10,802=？",
        "answer": 8.664064248649447
    },
    {
        "question": "208,688 × 281=？",
        "answer": 7.768203796840122
    },
    {
        "question": "32,346 ÷ 280=？",
        "answer": 2.0626625508700607
    },
    {
        "question": "1,192,001 ÷ 85,202=？",
        "answer": 1.1458268303918793
    },
    {
        "question": "751,013 ÷ 576,064=？",
        "answer": 0.1151767190014444
    },
    {
        "question": "418 × 1,082=？",
        "answer": 5.655403542545586
    },
    {
        "question": "126,553 × 1,233=？",
        "answer": 8.193235521372523
    },
    {
        "question": "90,925 × 8,039=？",
        "answer": 8.863885338389068
    },
    {
        "question": "92,254 ÷ 45,069=？",
        "answer": 0.31110728365497176
    },
    {
        "question": "20,172 × 730=？",
        "answer": 7.168071819607552
    },
    {
        "question": "402,096,256 ÷ 1,269,695=？",
        "answer": 2.500630619956147
    },
    {
        "question": "677,827 ÷ 552=？",
        "answer": 3.0891797864438444
    },
    {
        "question": "898,894 × 200=？",
        "answer": 8.25473847724229
    },
    {
        "question": "1,221 × 334=？",
        "answer": 5.610462130756447
    },
    {
        "question": "17,377,019 ÷ 1,444,573=？",
        "answer": 1.0802357826174898
    },
    {
        "question": "24,303,072 ÷ 571=？",
        "answer": 4.629025065283488
    },
    {
        "question": "165,320,560 ÷ 49,537,805=？",
        "answer": 0.5233901084590478
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,529,712=？",
        "answer": 6.880192335606814
    },
    {
        "question": "20,860,072 ÷ 6,091,948=？",
        "answer": 0.5345596154869131
    },
    {
        "question": "99 × 68,075=？",
        "answer": 6.828622844609552
    },
    {
        "question": "2,630,808 ÷ 833=？",
        "answer": 3.499444152424559
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 5,568,572=？",
        "answer": 8.046773834997202
    },
    {
        "question": "62,628 × 3,061=？",
        "answer": 8.28263187250042
    },
    {
        "question": "52,294 × 301=？",
        "answer": 7.19701835814423
    },
    {
        "question": "225 × 76,908=？",
        "answer": 7.2381540357430545
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 2,778=？",
        "answer": 4.288830281415853
    },
    {
        "question": "79,903,796 ÷ 2,099,642=？",
        "answer": 1.5804221603347512
    },
    {
        "question": "10,407 ÷ 2,797=？",
        "answer": 0.570633088190195
    },
    {
        "question": "180,421,077 ÷ 5,601=？",
        "answer": 4.508021698287214
    },
    {
        "question": "71,517 × 381=？",
        "answer": 7.435334264030986
    },
    {
        "question": "1,696 × 222,948=？",
        "answer": 8.577629428697554
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 15,584=？",
        "answer": 5.234071624692765
    },
    {
        "question": "6,690 ÷ 3,184=？",
        "answer": 0.32245305870219165
    },
    {
        "question": "1,401 × 49,727=？",
        "answer": 7.843030394583432
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 9,324,843=？",
        "answer": 8.173761511092934
    },
    {
        "question": "180,403,306 ÷ 2,164,031=？",
        "answer": 1.9209810141897283
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 173,432=？",
        "answer": 5.540159228026968
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 1,105=？",
        "answer": 4.611564002088125
    },
    {
        "question": "14,132 ÷ 2,178=？",
        "answer": 0.8121457533430517
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 218=？",
        "answer": 3.29269900304393
    },
    {
        "question": "168,313 ÷ 2,229=？",
        "answer": 1.8780075924167123
    },
    {
        "question": "11,530,477 ÷ 2,719=？",
        "answer": 3.627438066245176
    },
    {
        "question": "339 ÷ 313=？",
        "answer": 0.03465536065663366
    },
    {
        "question": "523,545,255 ÷ 6,345,522=？",
        "answer": 1.9164868736910277
    },
    {
        "question": "101,111,623 ÷ 10,559,249=？",
        "answer": 0.981168050357111
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 85,822,837=？",
        "answer": 8.535662858004232
    },
    {
        "question": "65,790 ÷ 6,169=？",
        "answer": 1.027945116153206
    },
    {
        "question": "19,270 × 3,492=？",
        "answer": 7.8279559496889854
    },
    {
        "question": "2,368,035 ÷ 2,638=？",
        "answer": 2.953113325841606
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 16,629=？",
        "answer": 4.521896128976105
    },
    {
        "question": "15,148 ÷ 7,656=？",
        "answer": 0.2963533716800015
    },
    {
        "question": "640,840,237 ÷ 48,034,309=？",
        "answer": 1.1251982248449461
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 84,347=？",
        "answer": 4.92606964049224
    },
    {
        "question": "567,950,564 ÷ 1,182=？",
        "answer": 5.681693058608784
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 6,105,644=？",
        "answer": 8.41919993399902
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 664,343=？",
        "answer": 6.725482350314638
    },
    {
        "question": "35,216,797 ÷ 13,985=？",
        "answer": 3.401087383238248
    },
    {
        "question": "609,679,815 ÷ 3,688=？",
        "answer": 5.218310904455598
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 227=？",
        "answer": 3.861175835513029
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 17,681,281=？",
        "answer": 7.247513726235757
    },
    {
        "question": "2,299 ÷ 1,623=？",
        "answer": 0.1512204514430472
    },
    {
        "question": "219,704 ÷ 44,657=？",
        "answer": 0.6919484195252508
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 2,628=？",
        "answer": 4.650074282266017
    },
    {
        "question": "1,025 × 121,416=？",
        "answer": 8.094999786511947
    },
    {
        "question": "8,559 × 113,223=？",
        "answer": 8.9863576843108
    },
    {
        "question": "690,575,379 ÷ 367,465,581=？",
        "answer": 0.2739944237060869
    },
    {
        "question": "792,788 × 653=？",
        "answer": 8.714070249123099
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 360=？",
        "answer": 2.5563025007672873
    },
    {
        "question": "3,790 ÷ 2,751=？",
        "answer": 0.1391486195783888
    },
    {
        "question": "5,072 × 2,122=？",
        "answer": 7.031924624438998
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 3,363=？",
        "answer": 5.371824907328892
    },
    {
        "question": "195 × 17,044=？",
        "answer": 6.5216061368909335
    },
    {
        "question": "37,312,645 ÷ 227=？",
        "answer": 5.215830178987591
    },
    {
        "question": "130,669 ÷ 2,574=？",
        "answer": 1.7055640249217898
    },
    {
        "question": "21,236 × 1,248=？",
        "answer": 7.423287302015525
    },
    {
        "question": "954,825,792 ÷ 64,269,576=？",
        "answer": 1.1719187069802615
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,395=？",
        "answer": 3.144574207609616
    },
    {
        "question": "96 × 4,299,967=？",
        "answer": 8.615736355648714
    },
    {
        "question": "115 × 92,448=？",
        "answer": 7.026595360517715
    },
    {
        "question": "4,345 ÷ 237=？",
        "answer": 1.2632414347745813
    },
    {
        "question": "853 × 6,975=？",
        "answer": 6.774493243113159
    },
    {
        "question": "1,492 × 12,186=？",
        "answer": 7.2596299969251
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 425,536=？",
        "answer": 6.859385228313552
    },
    {
        "question": "111 × 24,141=？",
        "answer": 6.428078234833275
    },
    {
        "question": "7,278 × 5,719=？",
        "answer": 7.6193321477968885
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 23,574=？",
        "answer": 5.413825964353674
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 551,478=？",
        "answer": 6.519679442283739
    },
    {
        "question": "12,294 × 66,926=？",
        "answer": 8.91528807786663
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 7,821,295=？",
        "answer": 8.671429917099662
    },
    {
        "question": "102,390 ÷ 355=？",
        "answer": 2.460029189943207
    },
    {
        "question": "342 × 65,029=？",
        "answer": 7.347133181641442
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 579=？",
        "answer": 3.4616485680634552
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 3,531,808=？",
        "answer": 7.3930951259710325
    },
    {
        "question": "6,458,271 ÷ 3,137=？",
        "answer": 3.313601746098487
    },
    {
        "question": "76,517,838 ÷ 42,744=？",
        "answer": 3.2528875294285187
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 561=？",
        "answer": 3.4479328655921804
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 6,496,704=？",
        "answer": 7.854085765238186
    },
    {
        "question": "4,424 × 59,900=？",
        "answer": 8.423241940685953
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 7,623=？",
        "answer": 5.02825395544827
    },
    {
        "question": "9,473,968 ÷ 1,061,176=？",
        "answer": 0.9507444942522889
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 6,430=？",
        "answer": 4.95433900860246
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 8,839=？",
        "answer": 4.90064564333838
    },
    {
        "question": "908,481,457 ÷ 273,786=？",
        "answer": 3.5209048305648882
    },
    {
        "question": "536,397,652 ÷ 512,161=？",
        "answer": 3.0200803633593343
    },
    {
        "question": "10,500,747 ÷ 5,843=？",
        "answer": 3.254584308610958
    },
    {
        "question": "451,191,898 ÷ 412=？",
        "answer": 6.039464076437088
    },
    {
        "question": "921 ÷ 380=？",
        "answer": 0.38447603358003873
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 5,759,908=？",
        "answer": 8.316718047487127
    },
    {
        "question": "514,363,483 ÷ 101,222,641=？",
        "answer": 0.7059924641744264
    },
    {
        "question": "52,559,321 ÷ 14,316,930=？",
        "answer": 0.5647998444907982
    },
    {
        "question": "4,321 × 201,704=？",
        "answer": 8.940298777120438
    },
    {
        "question": "203 × 4,579,992=？",
        "answer": 8.968360757323438
    },
    {
        "question": "714,867,699 ÷ 15,304,654=？",
        "answer": 1.6694021583628469
    },
    {
        "question": "268,092,718 ÷ 6,373,426=？",
        "answer": 1.6239120700228573
    },
    {
        "question": "484 × 1,556=？",
        "answer": 5.876854954298083
    },
    {
        "question": "3,368,307 ÷ 83,660=？",
        "answer": 1.604893807597768
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 154,373=？",
        "answer": 6.229964029238304
    },
    {
        "question": "9,242,778 ÷ 1,469,432=？",
        "answer": 0.7986530286547933
    },
    {
        "question": "3,889 × 30,456=？",
        "answer": 8.07351080695377
    },
    {
        "question": "8,903,028 ÷ 3,252,861=？",
        "answer": 0.43727223365903645
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 6,670=？",
        "answer": 4.669223873930806
    },
    {
        "question": "835,455 × 270=？",
        "answer": 8.353286826673251
    },
    {
        "question": "25,526,245 ÷ 1,015,153=？",
        "answer": 1.4004554308689003
    },
    {
        "question": "2,594,545 ÷ 264,045=？",
        "answer": 0.9923832595052734
    },
    {
        "question": "3,910,877 ÷ 6,918=？",
        "answer": 2.752293599603042
    },
    {
        "question": "27,624,374 ÷ 1,580=？",
        "answer": 4.242635358239158
    },
    {
        "question": "291 × 45,471=？",
        "answer": 7.121627494317172
    },
    {
        "question": "38,963 × 3,270=？",
        "answer": 8.105200141146277
    },
    {
        "question": "252,560,209 ÷ 18,315=？",
        "answer": 4.139558005273481
    },
    {
        "question": "1,545,987 ÷ 4,216=？",
        "answer": 2.5643052354683706
    },
    {
        "question": "1,779,089 ÷ 18,033=？",
        "answer": 1.9941296917824212
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 240=？",
        "answer": 3.526339277389844
    },
    {
        "question": "222,029,452 ÷ 518,299=？",
        "answer": 2.631830216112685
    },
    {
        "question": "120,143,793 ÷ 59,742,307=？",
        "answer": 0.3034193494803545
    },
    {
        "question": "385,839 × 218=？",
        "answer": 7.924862616935172
    },
    {
        "question": "3,795 × 923=？",
        "answer": 6.544413481257411
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 3,226,721=？",
        "answer": 8.272189409106684
    },
    {
        "question": "11,786 × 543=？",
        "answer": 6.806166266347978
    },
    {
        "question": "25,722 × 4,179=？",
        "answer": 8.031377105037903
    },
    {
        "question": "261,101,235 ÷ 4,059,936=？",
        "answer": 1.8082897385241505
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 57,995,157=？",
        "answer": 8.842572974507235
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 474,297=？",
        "answer": 5.676050377682514
    },
    {
        "question": "11,348,380 ÷ 10,308,772=？",
        "answer": 0.041726935296599245
    },
    {
        "question": "211,935,136 ÷ 518,459=？",
        "answer": 2.611488545018192
    },
    {
        "question": "14,613,684 ÷ 83,033=？",
        "answer": 2.2455089827551817
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,837,199=？",
        "answer": 7.3780995526633255
    },
    {
        "question": "47,983 ÷ 780=？",
        "answer": 1.7889927948120135
    },
    {
        "question": "1,140,806 ÷ 776,175=？",
        "answer": 0.16725214632139143
    },
    {
        "question": "2,890 ÷ 624=？",
        "answer": 0.6657132530741239
    },
    {
        "question": "622 × 75,101=？",
        "answer": 7.669436104539068
    },
    {
        "question": "4,300,000 ÷ 2,001=？",
        "answer": 3.332221366943375
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 929=？",
        "answer": 3.5700757053216043
    },
    {
        "question": "397,752 × 1,511=？",
        "answer": 8.778876836408191
    },
    {
        "question": "499,569 ÷ 16,213=？",
        "answer": 1.4887320983483343
    },
    {
        "question": "2,861,859 ÷ 1,319=？",
        "answer": 3.3364034372909424
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 64,971,006=？",
        "answer": 8.11374958702326
    },
    {
        "question": "2,753,749 ÷ 12,300=？",
        "answer": 2.3500192410091905
    },
    {
        "question": "1,571 ÷ 1,355=？",
        "answer": 0.06423688982954882
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,567=？",
        "answer": 3.1950689964685903
    },
    {
        "question": "286,331,668 ÷ 10,092,267=？",
        "answer": 1.452880651570588
    },
    {
        "question": "421,096,364 ÷ 847=？",
        "answer": 5.696498081145237
    },
    {
        "question": "68,907,062 ÷ 400,434=？",
        "answer": 2.2357327878406976
    },
    {
        "question": "278 × 1,510,522=？",
        "answer": 8.62317185085609
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 171,900=？",
        "answer": 6.9756385661812965
    },
    {
        "question": "43,766,801 ÷ 449=？",
        "answer": 4.988898463347511
    },
    {
        "question": "24,304 × 30,936=？",
        "answer": 8.87614191558372
    },
    {
        "question": "1,699 × 569=？",
        "answer": 5.985305645264117
    },
    {
        "question": "170,195 ÷ 13,037=？",
        "answer": 1.1157691316776308
    },
    {
        "question": "639,939,697 ÷ 6,114,724=？",
        "answer": 2.019762192251176
    },
    {
        "question": "5,594 × 30,168=？",
        "answer": 8.227268981433072
    },
    {
        "question": "464,445 ÷ 23,602=？",
        "answer": 1.2939854857986193
    },
    {
        "question": "31,966 ÷ 913=？",
        "answer": 1.5442175175859287
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 235,976=？",
        "answer": 5.372867835183716
    },
    {
        "question": "955,430,083 ÷ 203=？",
        "answer": 6.67270287359474
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 644,183=？",
        "answer": 6.286130514316017
    },
    {
        "question": "235 × 2,722,129=？",
        "answer": 8.80597656457207
    },
    {
        "question": "120,136,144 ÷ 10,025=？",
        "answer": 4.078589307028311
    },
    {
        "question": "475,174,555 ÷ 848,722=？",
        "answer": 2.7480877168607076
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 684,333=？",
        "answer": 5.835267483109484
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,015,868=？",
        "answer": 6.7058072845320265
    },
    {
        "question": "113,968 × 1,217=？",
        "answer": 8.14207350523056
    },
    {
        "question": "5,217 ÷ 338=？",
        "answer": 1.1885041364447202
    },
    {
        "question": "35,301 × 15,927=？",
        "answer": 8.74992098823421
    },
    {
        "question": "105,015 ÷ 15,068=？",
        "answer": 0.843195725176397
    },
    {
        "question": "301,920 ÷ 147,436=？",
        "answer": 0.31128834303992947
    },
    {
        "question": "6,455,291 ÷ 1,124,356=？",
        "answer": 0.7590119829357509
    },
    {
        "question": "13,644 × 47,431=？",
        "answer": 8.811003991826272
    },
    {
        "question": "44,238,405 ÷ 6,735=？",
        "answer": 3.8174618601864165
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 5,153=？",
        "answer": 5.189181397180737
    },
    {
        "question": "351,803 ÷ 268,673=？",
        "answer": 0.11707551390745154
    },
    {
        "question": "87,791,824 ÷ 1,187,625=？",
        "answer": 1.8687747411046443
    },
    {
        "question": "6,693,496 ÷ 623,264=？",
        "answer": 1.030980965614087
    },
    {
        "question": "517 × 57,602=？",
        "answer": 7.4739281059248714
    },
    {
        "question": "137 × 1,171=？",
        "answer": 5.20527746222877
    },
    {
        "question": "483,877 ÷ 51,165=？",
        "answer": 0.9757620009291229
    },
    {
        "question": "842 × 662,444=？",
        "answer": 8.746461262381809
    },
    {
        "question": "157,255 × 995=？",
        "answer": 8.194427543689027
    },
    {
        "question": "4,088 × 776=？",
        "answer": 6.501372608384845
    },
    {
        "question": "25,846 ÷ 283=？",
        "answer": 1.9606069044648216
    },
    {
        "question": "36,954,193 ÷ 11,187,056=？",
        "answer": 0.5189479105904848
    },
    {
        "question": "6,696,241 ÷ 179,148=？",
        "answer": 1.572619111587524
    },
    {
        "question": "61,441,355 ÷ 689=？",
        "answer": 4.950241562956553
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 3,210=？",
        "answer": 5.2468677218991155
    },
    {
        "question": "6,545 ÷ 653=？",
        "answer": 1.0009964696117006
    },
    {
        "question": "1,851 × 155,232=？",
        "answer": 8.458387671698874
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 31,396,778=？",
        "answer": 7.496885082193675
    },
    {
        "question": "636,844,986 ÷ 617=？",
        "answer": 6.013748569844463
    },
    {
        "question": "1,448,007 ÷ 16,231=？",
        "answer": 1.9504253835959322
    },
    {
        "question": "158,627,930 ÷ 66,296,080=？",
        "answer": 0.37889180708254255
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,110=？",
        "answer": 3.9995654882259823
    },
    {
        "question": "38,067 × 209=？",
        "answer": 6.900694938213484
    },
    {
        "question": "4,106,286 ÷ 284=？",
        "answer": 4.160130854353394
    },
    {
        "question": "4,832 × 2,155=？",
        "answer": 7.017574200109826
    },
    {
        "question": "137,855 ÷ 288=？",
        "answer": 2.6800300348264092
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 727=？",
        "answer": 4.393013327901293
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 41,649=？",
        "answer": 6.124754556699072
    },
    {
        "question": "16,965,744 ÷ 776,772=？",
        "answer": 1.339279347209308
    },
    {
        "question": "11,955 ÷ 10,111=？",
        "answer": 0.07275547006308151
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 2,023,919=？",
        "answer": 7.151291167472059
    },
    {
        "question": "11,262 ÷ 1,123=？",
        "answer": 1.001235766743532
    },
    {
        "question": "1,521 × 554=？",
        "answer": 5.9256389787814285
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 1,721,325=？",
        "answer": 7.667226640518539
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 12,192,298=？",
        "answer": 7.688145560331196
    },
    {
        "question": "812 × 459=？",
        "answer": 5.571368714778437
    },
    {
        "question": "316,989,968 ÷ 23,035,366=？",
        "answer": 1.138650401038261
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 8,221,379=？",
        "answer": 8.517004660675875
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 40,775,248=？",
        "answer": 7.6103966111520185
    },
    {
        "question": "7,005 ÷ 6,539=？",
        "answer": 0.02989680225902924
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 13,543=？",
        "answer": 5.131714878465068
    },
    {
        "question": "76,254 × 1,755=？",
        "answer": 8.126539750884454
    },
    {
        "question": "9,810 × 63,793=？",
        "answer": 8.796442033622114
    },
    {
        "question": "90,207 ÷ 11,060=？",
        "answer": 0.9114851128284391
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 482=？",
        "answer": 4.316515493818436
    },
    {
        "question": "145 × 5,254,538=？",
        "answer": 8.881902539369722
    },
    {
        "question": "31,339 ÷ 13,781=？",
        "answer": 0.35680440167917765
    },
    {
        "question": "9,804 ÷ 7,214=？",
        "answer": 0.13322716459769604
    },
    {
        "question": "133,632,393 ÷ 378=？",
        "answer": 5.548419945697017
    },
    {
        "question": "59,485 × 7,550=？",
        "answer": 8.65235441755082
    },
    {
        "question": "42,027 × 1,552=？",
        "answer": 7.8144201069288854
    },
    {
        "question": "2,795,697 ÷ 675=？",
        "answer": 3.6171863275907077
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 181,838,515=？",
        "answer": 8.736807130747515
    },
    {
        "question": "33,768 ÷ 546=？",
        "answer": 1.7913126964416144
    },
    {
        "question": "42,427 ÷ 6,128=？",
        "answer": 0.8403235673997194
    },
    {
        "question": "3,859,445 ÷ 158,607=？",
        "answer": 1.386202505623353
    },
    {
        "question": "161,815 ÷ 116,565=？",
        "answer": 0.14245060955262043
    },
    {
        "question": "422,281 × 1,705=？",
        "answer": 8.857325924661573
    },
    {
        "question": "10,554 × 6,366=？",
        "answer": 7.827283724126089
    },
    {
        "question": "337,426,719 ÷ 1,195=？",
        "answer": 5.450811563765702
    },
    {
        "question": "322,376 × 587=？",
        "answer": 8.277000803563235
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 4,396=？",
        "answer": 5.28651036023764
    },
    {
        "question": "1,038,538 ÷ 306=？",
        "answer": 3.530700965471275
    },
    {
        "question": "13,849 × 201=？",
        "answer": 6.444614472686577
    },
    {
        "question": "188 × 29,719=？",
        "answer": 6.747192041236858
    },
    {
        "question": "2,571 × 76,193=？",
        "answer": 8.292017150331317
    },
    {
        "question": "29,732,454 ÷ 2,739,002=？",
        "answer": 1.0356384062725685
    },
    {
        "question": "203 × 4,104=？",
        "answer": 5.920703390016973
    },
    {
        "question": "12,220 ÷ 1,292=？",
        "answer": 0.9758086922474701
    },
    {
        "question": "5,544,021 ÷ 33,698=？",
        "answer": 2.2162207407022225
    },
    {
        "question": "22,377 ÷ 6,156=？",
        "answer": 0.560503250712151
    },
    {
        "question": "21,355 ÷ 1,263=？",
        "answer": 1.228096225207512
    },
    {
        "question": "643,160 ÷ 522=？",
        "answer": 3.090648523534983
    },
    {
        "question": "93,556,345 ÷ 884=？",
        "answer": 5.024620981713849
    },
    {
        "question": "6,719,933 ÷ 125,294=？",
        "answer": 1.729434668740825
    },
    {
        "question": "19,764 ÷ 1,019=？",
        "answer": 1.2877006612109527
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 5,332,180=？",
        "answer": 8.656323727312692
    },
    {
        "question": "133,910,835 ÷ 2,450,859=？",
        "answer": 1.737497391449621
    },
    {
        "question": "340 × 1,215=？",
        "answer": 5.616055194976586
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 6,090,684=？",
        "answer": 8.216029831955217
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,069,946=？",
        "answer": 6.315959015887873
    },
    {
        "question": "405 × 3,608=？",
        "answer": 6.164721552084573
    },
    {
        "question": "444 × 305=？",
        "answer": 5.131682809461406
    },
    {
        "question": "2,317 ÷ 2,020=？",
        "answer": 0.05957466434335176
    },
    {
        "question": "1,769 ÷ 1,237=？",
        "answer": 0.15535813328060247
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 10,178=？",
        "answer": 4.706632450873295
    },
    {
        "question": "117,109,071 ÷ 313=？",
        "answer": 5.573046198283127
    },
    {
        "question": "37,072,707 ÷ 1,279,408=？",
        "answer": 1.4620452368091672
    },
    {
        "question": "48,316,217 ÷ 13,802,177=？",
        "answer": 0.5441453305966776
    },
    {
        "question": "143,617,565 ÷ 1,185=？",
        "answer": 5.083489208752811
    },
    {
        "question": "2,437,656 ÷ 5,046=？",
        "answer": 2.6840251721464634
    },
    {
        "question": "1,088,027 ÷ 226=？",
        "answer": 3.682531233609537
    },
    {
        "question": "298,436 ÷ 11,163=？",
        "answer": 1.427070285675783
    },
    {
        "question": "48,693,456 ÷ 3,207=？",
        "answer": 4.181371639601322
    },
    {
        "question": "4,566,819 ÷ 5,849=？",
        "answer": 2.8925321778813062
    },
    {
        "question": "1,445,805 × 671=？",
        "answer": 8.986832242494906
    },
    {
        "question": "234,628,245 ÷ 547=？",
        "answer": 5.632392965799321
    },
    {
        "question": "45,792,239 ÷ 226=？",
        "answer": 5.306683439618827
    },
    {
        "question": "166,353,228 ÷ 715,292=？",
        "answer": 2.366547864734417
    },
    {
        "question": "10,158,550 ÷ 32,935=？",
        "answer": 2.489174054743275
    },
    {
        "question": "163,468 ÷ 65,462=？",
        "answer": 0.39744347937289143
    },
    {
        "question": "288 × 1,035=？",
        "answer": 5.474332837552168
    },
    {
        "question": "99,878 ÷ 2,078=？",
        "answer": 1.6818242940458543
    },
    {
        "question": "107,414,371 ÷ 679=？",
        "answer": 5.199192615355584
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,918,996=？",
        "answer": 6.94235475457951
    },
    {
        "question": "27,222 × 3,934=？",
        "answer": 8.029754385232978
    },
    {
        "question": "111,852,877 ÷ 6,179=？",
        "answer": 4.257728963974936
    },
    {
        "question": "4,899,384 ÷ 1,113=？",
        "answer": 3.643646315241123
    },
    {
        "question": "315,611,891 ÷ 638,361=？",
        "answer": 2.694087010948944
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 122,037=？",
        "answer": 6.316940444345204
    },
    {
        "question": "572 × 46,369=？",
        "answer": 7.423623758737461
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 59,871=？",
        "answer": 5.078246507707361
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 3,422,164=？",
        "answer": 7.136360809679849
    },
    {
        "question": "639 × 24,280=？",
        "answer": 7.19074954056162
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 5,716=？",
        "answer": 5.497454909613176
    },
    {
        "question": "74 × 255=？",
        "answer": 4.275771900164932
    },
    {
        "question": "333,942 ÷ 50,515=？",
        "answer": 0.8202506865303949
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 817,854=？",
        "answer": 5.912675782089903
    },
    {
        "question": "56,393,428 ÷ 1,019=？",
        "answer": 4.743054310940753
    },
    {
        "question": "7,110 × 25,661=？",
        "answer": 8.261143177399216
    },
    {
        "question": "156,156 ÷ 269=？",
        "answer": 2.7638063958313723
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 6,969=？",
        "answer": 5.649350438503785
    },
    {
        "question": "995 ÷ 935=？",
        "answer": 0.027011469873207693
    },
    {
        "question": "539,178,636 ÷ 73,589=？",
        "answer": 3.8649197743734436
    },
    {
        "question": "757,042,305 ÷ 3,671=？",
        "answer": 5.3143357648966045
    },
    {
        "question": "155,365,729 ÷ 5,071,767=？",
        "answer": 1.4861959335727033
    },
    {
        "question": "435 × 33,099=？",
        "answer": 7.158304129852943
    },
    {
        "question": "39,458,952 ÷ 409=？",
        "answer": 4.984422238528165
    },
    {
        "question": "857 × 3,338=？",
        "answer": 6.456467154266426
    },
    {
        "question": "6,801,815 ÷ 605=？",
        "answer": 4.0508694408931065
    },
    {
        "question": "115,885,018 ÷ 6,007=？",
        "answer": 4.285369660612383
    },
    {
        "question": "453,072,825 ÷ 331,253=？",
        "answer": 3.1360081941125
    },
    {
        "question": "188,636 ÷ 43,567=？",
        "answer": 0.6364669230121297
    },
    {
        "question": "575,297,253 ÷ 871,504=？",
        "answer": 2.8196229155468857
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 150,049=？",
        "answer": 6.799482395817359
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 112,559=？",
        "answer": 6.864293582714791
    },
    {
        "question": "67,524 ÷ 673=？",
        "answer": 2.0014430969776407
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 227=？",
        "answer": 2.3560258571931225
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 151,771=？",
        "answer": 5.658310050368951
    },
    {
        "question": "44,854,430 ÷ 6,388,312=？",
        "answer": 0.8464192235540151
    },
    {
        "question": "238 × 1,874=？",
        "answer": 5.649346543608272
    },
    {
        "question": "649,723,849 ÷ 227,423,814=？",
        "answer": 0.4558928698572204
    },
    {
        "question": "680 × 1,426,876=？",
        "answer": 8.986895145908013
    },
    {
        "question": "215,421,158 ÷ 1,661,209=？",
        "answer": 2.1128640807786776
    },
    {
        "question": "347,697,862 ÷ 8,936,897=？",
        "answer": 1.5900152675976782
    },
    {
        "question": "23,238,355 ÷ 20,597=？",
        "answer": 3.05240141291226
    },
    {
        "question": "5,935,848 ÷ 3,407,602=？",
        "answer": 0.2410339069106171
    },
    {
        "question": "462,289,781 ÷ 2,239=？",
        "answer": 5.314860199806354
    },
    {
        "question": "274,642 ÷ 87,510=？",
        "answer": 0.49670926921029646
    },
    {
        "question": "565,598,060 ÷ 320=？",
        "answer": 6.247357932842452
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 485,965=？",
        "answer": 6.288664983112418
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 152,491=？",
        "answer": 6.46199781338528
    },
    {
        "question": "350,477 ÷ 186,945=？",
        "answer": 0.27294566865095893
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 4,401=？",
        "answer": 4.546641355554889
    },
    {
        "question": "1,174 × 14,205=？",
        "answer": 7.2221093349705505
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 494=？",
        "answer": 2.693726948923647
    },
    {
        "question": "181,906 ÷ 47,406=？",
        "answer": 0.5840137119186951
    },
    {
        "question": "71,479,857 ÷ 21,287=？",
        "answer": 3.5260692148423547
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 49,972=？",
        "answer": 4.999756726967326
    },
    {
        "question": "2,167 × 282,231=？",
        "answer": 8.786463625874656
    },
    {
        "question": "4,617 × 45,256=？",
        "answer": 8.320036040283494
    },
    {
        "question": "12,757 × 4,110=？",
        "answer": 7.719590377403062
    },
    {
        "question": "9,068,460 ÷ 1,933,787=？",
        "answer": 0.6711249053792726
    },
    {
        "question": "5,844 ÷ 3,033=？",
        "answer": 0.28483779695159567
    },
    {
        "question": "13,418 × 351=？",
        "answer": 6.672994904005675
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,551=？",
        "answer": 3.190611797813605
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 52,709=？",
        "answer": 5.19900603153789
    },
    {
        "question": "7,586 ÷ 4,794=？",
        "answer": 0.19931480866913673
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 11,129,587=？",
        "answer": 8.1256602947535
    },
    {
        "question": "40,407,667 ÷ 24,869,853=？",
        "answer": 0.2107905582313451
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,092=？",
        "answer": 3.0382226383687185
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 6,064=？",
        "answer": 5.737001702063322
    },
    {
        "question": "11,919 ÷ 1,083=？",
        "answer": 1.0416113631497048
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 836=？",
        "answer": 2.9222062774390163
    },
    {
        "question": "976,022 × 263=？",
        "answer": 8.409415355470916
    },
    {
        "question": "268,573,788 ÷ 6,570,520=？",
        "answer": 1.6114638829726713
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 128,712,845=？",
        "answer": 8.41065188549187
    },
    {
        "question": "23,453 × 210=？",
        "answer": 6.692417698293027
    },
    {
        "question": "88 × 5,855,880=？",
        "answer": 8.712074840632232
    },
    {
        "question": "228 × 41,765=？",
        "answer": 6.978747332742331
    },
    {
        "question": "34,072,933 ÷ 5,570=？",
        "answer": 3.7865543240968216
    },
    {
        "question": "10,275,927 ÷ 763=？",
        "answer": 4.129296472430223
    },
    {
        "question": "958,604,159 ÷ 1,958=？",
        "answer": 5.689826621422775
    },
    {
        "question": "40,082,418 ÷ 1,327,897=？",
        "answer": 1.47978952302792
    },
    {
        "question": "1,384 × 733=？",
        "answer": 6.006240064761867
    },
    {
        "question": "180,934,515 ÷ 622=？",
        "answer": 5.463731035923775
    },
    {
        "question": "47,545 ÷ 4,358=？",
        "answer": 1.0378176258240714
    },
    {
        "question": "400,404 ÷ 154,657=？",
        "answer": 0.41312882580998994
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 472=？",
        "answer": 3.3729120029701067
    },
    {
        "question": "1,031 × 4,104=？",
        "answer": 6.626466017387276
    },
    {
        "question": "266 × 2,560=？",
        "answer": 5.833121601942916
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,218=？",
        "answer": 3.6469915374771222
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 29,892=？",
        "answer": 5.475554973584131
    },
    {
        "question": "344,032 ÷ 53,076=？",
        "answer": 0.8117006547620608
    },
    {
        "question": "1,550 × 3,802=？",
        "answer": 6.770343810699716
    },
    {
        "question": "729,248,467 ÷ 110,423=？",
        "answer": 3.819815982849671
    },
    {
        "question": "103,556,027 ÷ 92,406,496=？",
        "answer": 0.049472877703378486
    },
    {
        "question": "42,419 ÷ 2,855=？",
        "answer": 1.1719543135128447
    },
    {
        "question": "1,017,217 ÷ 3,532=？",
        "answer": 2.459392914703231
    },
    {
        "question": "512 × 12,210=？",
        "answer": 6.795985624920713
    },
    {
        "question": "621 × 141,248=？",
        "answer": 7.943073907322122
    },
    {
        "question": "301 × 7,568=？",
        "answer": 6.35754761898758
    },
    {
        "question": "2,021,053 ÷ 931=？",
        "answer": 3.336628021601617
    },
    {
        "question": "2,656,751 ÷ 179,450=？",
        "answer": 1.1704073900498508
    },
    {
        "question": "185,489,358 ÷ 158,279=？",
        "answer": 3.0688957003294264
    },
    {
        "question": "47,550,874 ÷ 1,392=？",
        "answer": 4.533519268541241
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 8,979,594=？",
        "answer": 7.555316692411113
    },
    {
        "question": "2,170 ÷ 961=？",
        "answer": 0.3537363461799842
    },
    {
        "question": "14,075,551 ÷ 2,824=？",
        "answer": 3.69760071232129
    },
    {
        "question": "45,337 × 3,170=？",
        "answer": 8.157512041207381
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 748=？",
        "answer": 4.049992856920142
    },
    {
        "question": "715 × 10,633=？",
        "answer": 6.880961855678124
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 2,328=？",
        "answer": 4.728710811995444
    },
    {
        "question": "26,920 × 3,597=？",
        "answer": 7.98601549337045
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 23,799=？",
        "answer": 6.335600101326934
    },
    {
        "question": "4,612,479 ÷ 140,967=？",
        "answer": 1.5148169445172228
    },
    {
        "question": "19,812,860 ÷ 16,050=？",
        "answer": 3.0914721340306808
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 157,079=？",
        "answer": 6.196118127791503
    },
    {
        "question": "116 × 598,311=？",
        "answer": 7.841384976684352
    },
    {
        "question": "3,459,284 ÷ 9,780=？",
        "answer": 2.548647363361411
    },
    {
        "question": "62,731 ÷ 548=？",
        "answer": 2.0587016522319916
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 2,093=？",
        "answer": 5.250188154052979
    },
    {
        "question": "877,868 ÷ 291=？",
        "answer": 3.479536229447129
    },
    {
        "question": "448,986,846 ÷ 162,958=？",
        "answer": 3.4401579317481947
    },
    {
        "question": "3,793 × 240,461=？",
        "answer": 8.960027491569596
    },
    {
        "question": "30,341,279 ÷ 1,584,643=？",
        "answer": 1.282102447469936
    },
    {
        "question": "109,843 × 7,801=？",
        "answer": 8.932922663616347
    },
    {
        "question": "3,522 × 3,362=？",
        "answer": 7.07338706073471
    },
    {
        "question": "725,043 ÷ 8,579=？",
        "answer": 1.9269270961363594
    },
    {
        "question": "3,377 × 61,205=？",
        "answer": 8.31531796290696
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 126,019=？",
        "answer": 6.763193860712428
    },
    {
        "question": "9,143 × 356=？",
        "answer": 6.512538717740771
    },
    {
        "question": "93,328 ÷ 10,119=？",
        "answer": 0.9648743631770763
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,145=？",
        "answer": 3.9618954736678504
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 68,427=？",
        "answer": 4.835227499926078
    },
    {
        "question": "216,776 ÷ 21,053=？",
        "answer": 1.0126972078630894
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 97,406=？",
        "answer": 5.289615704972114
    },
    {
        "question": "743,738,378 ÷ 292,106,127=？",
        "answer": 0.4058795257972749
    },
    {
        "question": "232,662,878 ÷ 1,483=？",
        "answer": 5.195585944910545
    },
    {
        "question": "14,373,378 ÷ 99,469=？",
        "answer": 2.1598710952386457
    },
    {
        "question": "513,790,521 ÷ 590=？",
        "answer": 5.939934075996692
    },
    {
        "question": "1,228 × 461,719=？",
        "answer": 8.75357611318946
    },
    {
        "question": "11,121,267 ÷ 6,264,556=？",
        "answer": 0.24926397161291516
    },
    {
        "question": "133,955,847 ÷ 2,498=？",
        "answer": 4.729369240713994
    },
    {
        "question": "239 × 2,039,870=？",
        "answer": 8.68800039186343
    },
    {
        "question": "4,603,943 ÷ 591=？",
        "answer": 3.891542457243591
    },
    {
        "question": "3,806,894 ÷ 25,740=？",
        "answer": 2.169962241822573
    },
    {
        "question": "48,485 × 547=？",
        "answer": 7.423594726279603
    },
    {
        "question": "684,403 ÷ 101,881=？",
        "answer": 0.8272187054772234
    },
    {
        "question": "32,921 ÷ 748=？",
        "answer": 1.643571420895875
    },
    {
        "question": "2,755,289 ÷ 98,197=？",
        "answer": 1.448068938436357
    },
    {
        "question": "17,009 × 7,524=？",
        "answer": 8.107127568024817
    },
    {
        "question": "378 × 563,746=？",
        "answer": 8.328575273243702
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 8,084=？",
        "answer": 5.4639288056105535
    },
    {
        "question": "7,003,851 ÷ 78,130=？",
        "answer": 1.9525190740147222
    },
    {
        "question": "887,443,962 ÷ 15,398=？",
        "answer": 4.7606766236031755
    },
    {
        "question": "1,106 ÷ 209=？",
        "answer": 0.7236088408576254
    },
    {
        "question": "240,454,012 ÷ 17,377=？",
        "answer": 4.141057226601582
    },
    {
        "question": "5,040 × 257=？",
        "answer": 6.11236365977682
    },
    {
        "question": "166,995,436 ÷ 64,807=？",
        "answer": 3.411082684139088
    },
    {
        "question": "23,356 × 1,212=？",
        "answer": 7.451901086409517
    },
    {
        "question": "3,715 × 3,378=？",
        "answer": 7.098618463331584
    },
    {
        "question": "75,731 ÷ 3,584=？",
        "answer": 1.3249056905712813
    },
    {
        "question": "35,974,081 ÷ 146,130=？",
        "answer": 2.39125032389812
    },
    {
        "question": "21,689 ÷ 761=？",
        "answer": 1.4548548719843484
    },
    {
        "question": "895 ÷ 209=？",
        "answer": 0.631676749204858
    },
    {
        "question": "48,450 ÷ 1,050=？",
        "answer": 1.664104482316846
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 677,152=？",
        "answer": 5.83068616551198
    },
    {
        "question": "10,008 × 36,325=？",
        "answer": 8.560552919655423
    },
    {
        "question": "170,110 ÷ 3,500=？",
        "answer": 1.6866618002274048
    },
    {
        "question": "198 × 234=？",
        "answer": 4.665881047671674
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 34,689=？",
        "answer": 6.397524276793892
    },
    {
        "question": "315 × 228,405=？",
        "answer": 7.857016160581631
    },
    {
        "question": "17,862,052 ÷ 1,735,477=？",
        "answer": 1.0125124869401247
    },
    {
        "question": "166 × 22,652=？",
        "answer": 6.575214640994546
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 29,935,670=？",
        "answer": 7.476188982677014
    },
    {
        "question": "133,368,339 ÷ 3,467,218=？",
        "answer": 1.5850715937886857
    },
    {
        "question": "93,811 ÷ 51,529=？",
        "answer": 0.26020205106326166
    },
    {
        "question": "3,571 × 7,436=？",
        "answer": 7.424129231292643
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 465,616=？",
        "answer": 5.969057891258389
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,942=？",
        "answer": 3.5957166199434245
    },
    {
        "question": "77,121 × 6,965=？",
        "answer": 8.730093773030097
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,122=？",
        "answer": 3.527114111639805
    },
    {
        "question": "1,062 × 817,406=？",
        "answer": 8.938562337981715
    },
    {
        "question": "1,061,051 ÷ 4,018=？",
        "answer": 2.4217263265939795
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 19,618,795=？",
        "answer": 7.292672329194702
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 3,180=？",
        "answer": 5.5277329852492025
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 572=？",
        "answer": 4.643886753965506
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 19,015=？",
        "answer": 6.034971185420092
    },
    {
        "question": "882 ÷ 606=？",
        "answer": 0.1629959609655335
    },
    {
        "question": "1,224 × 68,359=？",
        "answer": 7.922577118762009
    },
    {
        "question": "64,938,196 ÷ 421,713=？",
        "answer": 2.1874832305775427
    },
    {
        "question": "816,716,364 ÷ 1,170=？",
        "answer": 5.843885395597825
    },
    {
        "question": "2,751 × 1,249=？",
        "answer": 6.536053028763819
    },
    {
        "question": "249,110,628 ÷ 39,528,708=？",
        "answer": 0.7994796369603141
    },
    {
        "question": "83 × 74,514=？",
        "answer": 6.791315969842911
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 360,496,492=？",
        "answer": 8.857931038609983
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 281,008,441=？",
        "answer": 8.44871936554445
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 305,265=？",
        "answer": 6.262828263728408
    },
    {
        "question": "932,931,430 ÷ 9,730=？",
        "answer": 4.981736884220925
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 64,665=？",
        "answer": 6.242033046068556
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 477=？",
        "answer": 3.6327608884794387
    },
    {
        "question": "59,675 × 14,361=？",
        "answer": 8.932977109880403
    },
    {
        "question": "1,760,991 ÷ 690,400=？",
        "answer": 0.40665635369151204
    },
    {
        "question": "1,045 × 205,165=？",
        "answer": 8.331219564999246
    },
    {
        "question": "61,517,332 ÷ 178,219=？",
        "answer": 2.538043489417099
    },
    {
        "question": "89,719 × 960=？",
        "answer": 7.935155657369778
    },
    {
        "question": "711,663,412 ÷ 61,329,557=？",
        "answer": 1.0646048108048085
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 2,267,168=？",
        "answer": 8.323966651640145
    },
    {
        "question": "157 × 32,326=？",
        "answer": 6.705451621004648
    },
    {
        "question": "14,936 ÷ 6,036=？",
        "answer": 0.3934850738374696
    },
    {
        "question": "695 × 72,448=？",
        "answer": 7.7020112054262535
    },
    {
        "question": "45,328,705 ÷ 99,546=？",
        "answer": 2.658349498129184
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,878,511=？",
        "answer": 6.896444145714439
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 580=？",
        "answer": 3.7634279935629373
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 84,871=？",
        "answer": 6.360123083478604
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 228,662=？",
        "answer": 5.660223993407937
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 14,186,474=？",
        "answer": 8.193267151607248
    },
    {
        "question": "737,788,958 ÷ 1,475,854=？",
        "answer": 2.6988887544468096
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 79,576=？",
        "answer": 5.678933355317314
    },
    {
        "question": "2,039,223 ÷ 161,706=？",
        "answer": 1.1007385863814054
    },
    {
        "question": "13,054,925 ÷ 801=？",
        "answer": 4.212141865078195
    },
    {
        "question": "25,417 × 21,994=？",
        "answer": 8.74742850964536
    },
    {
        "question": "524,779,988 ÷ 58,162,907=？",
        "answer": 0.9553311606991856
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 216,250=？",
        "answer": 7.113107366520495
    },
    {
        "question": "23,577 × 415=？",
        "answer": 6.990536640205117
    },
    {
        "question": "115,751,092 ÷ 1,662=？",
        "answer": 4.842894077411119
    },
    {
        "question": "70,722 ÷ 50,912=？",
        "answer": 0.1427343759486247
    },
    {
        "question": "518,820,170 ÷ 67,456=？",
        "answer": 3.8859962668026364
    },
    {
        "question": "2,485,115 ÷ 102,222=？",
        "answer": 1.38580211695253
    },
    {
        "question": "1,133,439 ÷ 155,177=？",
        "answer": 0.8635708005074482
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 2,727=？",
        "answer": 4.736715133605611
    },
    {
        "question": "2,049,801 ÷ 164,744=？",
        "answer": 1.0949020941799736
    },
    {
        "question": "19,434 ÷ 2,803=？",
        "answer": 0.8409391006335344
    },
    {
        "question": "931,546 ÷ 29,586=？",
        "answer": 1.4981180524290325
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 28,389,108=？",
        "answer": 8.152121751325991
    },
    {
        "question": "30,834,805 ÷ 976=？",
        "answer": 4.499591388616249
    },
    {
        "question": "62,043,085 ÷ 308,095=？",
        "answer": 2.304008734011828
    },
    {
        "question": "18,997,908 ÷ 1,167=？",
        "answer": 4.2116349241665345
    },
    {
        "question": "12,485 × 203=？",
        "answer": 6.403884584600579
    },
    {
        "question": "192,308,031 ÷ 349,028=？",
        "answer": 2.741137152572136
    },
    {
        "question": "58,917,841 ÷ 74,155=？",
        "answer": 2.900106384829664
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,513,231=？",
        "answer": 6.741406189454343
    },
    {
        "question": "72,243,945 ÷ 3,274=？",
        "answer": 4.343722778244915
    },
    {
        "question": "22,681 ÷ 17,509=？",
        "answer": 0.1124008558648253
    },
    {
        "question": "74,603 ÷ 2,622=？",
        "answer": 1.454123604692987
    },
    {
        "question": "62,525,558 ÷ 10,736,473=？",
        "answer": 0.765195939936873
    },
    {
        "question": "26,020 × 3,181=？",
        "answer": 7.917870961332931
    },
    {
        "question": "3,315,673 ÷ 54,152=？",
        "answer": 1.786957191688233
    },
    {
        "question": "310,612,534 ÷ 18,080=？",
        "answer": 4.235020550485669
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 376,106=？",
        "answer": 5.876340257419554
    },
    {
        "question": "8,692 × 3,561=？",
        "answer": 7.49069169132274
    },
    {
        "question": "2,195,183 ÷ 55,258=？",
        "answer": 1.599075568689976
    },
    {
        "question": "696,076,367 ÷ 2,157,341=？",
        "answer": 2.5087380916956015
    },
    {
        "question": "485,797 × 1,336=？",
        "answer": 8.812261286666546
    },
    {
        "question": "20,643,661 ÷ 255,245=？",
        "answer": 1.9078294752491163
    },
    {
        "question": "1,700,378 ÷ 7,787=？",
        "answer": 2.3391753026031648
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 17,741=？",
        "answer": 5.395106131570891
    },
    {
        "question": "120 × 5,084=？",
        "answer": 5.785386787929595
    },
    {
        "question": "3,338 ÷ 1,401=？",
        "answer": 0.3770481970574533
    },
    {
        "question": "77,777 ÷ 7,783=？",
        "answer": 0.999704157159627
    },
    {
        "question": "1,207,183 × 617=？",
        "answer": 8.872058274947415
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 863,245=？",
        "answer": 6.2371640672163755
    },
    {
        "question": "144,920 ÷ 127,126=？",
        "answer": 0.05689394316602452
    },
    {
        "question": "2,539,778 ÷ 321,681=？",
        "answer": 0.8973703467643194
    },
    {
        "question": "7,292 × 20,710=？",
        "answer": 8.179026758876391
    },
    {
        "question": "701 × 1,756=？",
        "answer": 6.090242529536742
    },
    {
        "question": "40,733,591 ÷ 16,890=？",
        "answer": 3.3823230488218603
    },
    {
        "question": "609,396 ÷ 8,430=？",
        "answer": 1.8590720246159838
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 1,454=？",
        "answer": 4.241745652570644
    },
    {
        "question": "5,322 × 113,029=？",
        "answer": 8.779264755505322
    },
    {
        "question": "236 × 49,362=？",
        "answer": 7.066304750659945
    },
    {
        "question": "35,398,088 ÷ 95,555=？",
        "answer": 2.5687263877540087
    },
    {
        "question": "733,039,966 ÷ 216=？",
        "answer": 6.530673902262496
    },
    {
        "question": "78,560 × 369=？",
        "answer": 7.462227840937953
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 277,514,597=？",
        "answer": 8.443285831530142
    },
    {
        "question": "240,074,463 ÷ 9,269,831=？",
        "answer": 1.4132741495906063
    },
    {
        "question": "4,715 ÷ 248=？",
        "answer": 1.2790300162471309
    },
    {
        "question": "22,516,819 ÷ 37,840=？",
        "answer": 2.774555909056772
    },
    {
        "question": "357,581 ÷ 3,574=？",
        "answer": 2.000219886410698
    },
    {
        "question": "23,824 ÷ 2,189=？",
        "answer": 1.0367689188401692
    },
    {
        "question": "550,221,813 ÷ 89,425=？",
        "answer": 3.7890788547494734
    },
    {
        "question": "4,025 ÷ 1,013=？",
        "answer": 0.5991564393436069
    },
    {
        "question": "25,325,429 ÷ 3,434=？",
        "answer": 3.8677565199993142
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 36,085,418=？",
        "answer": 8.03445299508761
    },
    {
        "question": "85,474 × 256=？",
        "answer": 7.340073993797477
    },
    {
        "question": "5,737,430 ÷ 77,013=？",
        "answer": 1.8721533585024626
    },
    {
        "question": "627,660,800 ÷ 11,740,960=？",
        "answer": 1.7280213975532628
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,765=？",
        "answer": 4.061829307294699
    },
    {
        "question": "1,422,293 ÷ 5,763=？",
        "answer": 2.3923404530257404
    },
    {
        "question": "1,485,337 ÷ 113,947=？",
        "answer": 1.1151221039871984
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 31,325=？",
        "answer": 4.796921075330169
    },
    {
        "question": "178,074 × 3,235=？",
        "answer": 8.760474799185435
    },
    {
        "question": "309,931 ÷ 157,324=？",
        "answer": 0.2944700376105101
    },
    {
        "question": "369 × 2,335=？",
        "answer": 5.935313251061191
    },
    {
        "question": "179,893,580 ÷ 79,505=？",
        "answer": 3.354621222706302
    },
    {
        "question": "7,391,942 ÷ 462=？",
        "answer": 4.204116575028927
    },
    {
        "question": "138,935 ÷ 443=？",
        "answer": 2.4964079391841127
    },
    {
        "question": "240,591 ÷ 10,786=？",
        "answer": 1.348418961318335
    },
    {
        "question": "27,198,696 ÷ 1,783,698=？",
        "answer": 1.1832267575904984
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 5,594,460=？",
        "answer": 8.706799565341274
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 47,030=？",
        "answer": 4.973404974410061
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 3,108,773=？",
        "answer": 8.44683152082102
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 4,595=？",
        "answer": 5.077258863692948
    },
    {
        "question": "3,786,644 ÷ 3,187=？",
        "answer": 3.0748724135237566
    },
    {
        "question": "120,414 ÷ 316=？",
        "answer": 2.580989900725981
    },
    {
        "question": "125,022,352 ÷ 21,955,875=？",
        "answer": 0.7554369152924411
    },
    {
        "question": "6,233 × 290=？",
        "answer": 6.257095124790955
    },
    {
        "question": "878,341,395 ÷ 197,775,773=？",
        "answer": 0.6474902603113162
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 113,212,746=？",
        "answer": 8.655955315758376
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 35,170=？",
        "answer": 5.546172368316943
    },
    {
        "question": "449,934,763 ÷ 8,497,128=？",
        "answer": 1.7238773885808205
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,346=？",
        "answer": 3.430075055551939
    },
    {
        "question": "4,368,477 ÷ 1,460=？",
        "answer": 3.4759771977120373
    },
    {
        "question": "220 × 1,172,241=？",
        "answer": 8.411439587905653
    },
    {
        "question": "876 × 405,655=？",
        "answer": 8.550660939517886
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 6,072,145=？",
        "answer": 7.561493384145242
    },
    {
        "question": "13,327 × 8,001=？",
        "answer": 8.027876668129569
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 1,013,845=？",
        "answer": 7.30700155934951
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 18,426,034=？",
        "answer": 8.043583118577923
    },
    {
        "question": "3,756 ÷ 447=？",
        "answer": 0.9244180604621369
    },
    {
        "question": "58,420 ÷ 20,837=？",
        "answer": 0.447726360909867
    },
    {
        "question": "243,722,286 ÷ 7,701=？",
        "answer": 4.500348119557673
    },
    {
        "question": "217,799 ÷ 1,860=？",
        "answer": 2.0685429371913764
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 151,224,136=？",
        "answer": 8.17962111189981
    },
    {
        "question": "139 × 63,693=？",
        "answer": 6.947106505298678
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 1,778=？",
        "answer": 5.069475692176064
    },
    {
        "question": "326 × 554,712=？",
        "answer": 8.257285161074613
    },
    {
        "question": "12,334 × 7,041=？",
        "answer": 7.938738288408541
    },
    {
        "question": "77,937,921 ÷ 156,837=？",
        "answer": 2.696300290310455
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 842=？",
        "answer": 4.101403350555331
    },
    {
        "question": "34,962,933 ÷ 525,614=？",
        "answer": 1.8229409335889162
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 14,491,250=？",
        "answer": 8.652467542706972
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 161,578=？",
        "answer": 5.208382228164881
    },
    {
        "question": "1,632 × 2,214=？",
        "answer": 6.557897770960547
    },
    {
        "question": "2,182,045 ÷ 555,168=？",
        "answer": 0.5944392773941122
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 261,902=？",
        "answer": 6.372381324342783
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 292,420=？",
        "answer": 6.913165104117087
    },
    {
        "question": "13,259 ÷ 349=？",
        "answer": 1.5796853436511402
    },
    {
        "question": "6,227 × 7,155=？",
        "answer": 7.648888503817195
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 10,485,337=？",
        "answer": 8.798733643686523
    },
    {
        "question": "857 × 3,744=？",
        "answer": 6.506316661989266
    },
    {
        "question": "24,023 × 870=？",
        "answer": 7.320146493907407
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 87,471,481=？",
        "answer": 8.543926471056523
    },
    {
        "question": "41,681 ÷ 12,176=？",
        "answer": 0.5344334904732266
    },
    {
        "question": "379,206,293 ÷ 69,269,806=？",
        "answer": 0.738331564589999
    },
    {
        "question": "28,636,468 ÷ 360=？",
        "answer": 4.9006169506233155
    },
    {
        "question": "203,517 × 485=？",
        "answer": 7.99434243077691
    },
    {
        "question": "23,403,625 ÷ 208,277=？",
        "answer": 2.050641817208308
    },
    {
        "question": "42,972 × 417=？",
        "answer": 7.253321622033285
    },
    {
        "question": "1,245,356 ÷ 20,757=？",
        "answer": 1.7781289321608504
    },
    {
        "question": "14,637,889 ÷ 1,908,440=？",
        "answer": 0.8847999389639878
    },
    {
        "question": "728 × 646,952=？",
        "answer": 8.673003439103157
    },
    {
        "question": "923 × 244,001=？",
        "answer": 8.352593307256411
    },
    {
        "question": "23,367 × 3,006=？",
        "answer": 7.846591934810072
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 610=？",
        "answer": 4.353531559077762
    },
    {
        "question": "14,005 × 1,392=？",
        "answer": 7.28992234843413
    },
    {
        "question": "7,087 ÷ 483=？",
        "answer": 1.1665153020100043
    },
    {
        "question": "522,206 ÷ 14,769=？",
        "answer": 1.548490766944568
    },
    {
        "question": "162 × 11,691=？",
        "answer": 6.277366675054984
    },
    {
        "question": "234,180 ÷ 215=？",
        "answer": 3.037111341749287
    },
    {
        "question": "223,636,510 ÷ 2,143=？",
        "answer": 5.018520535136613
    },
    {
        "question": "14,807,706 ÷ 807,466=？",
        "answer": 1.263363538584177
    },
    {
        "question": "23,256 × 41,341=？",
        "answer": 8.98291599635672
    },
    {
        "question": "16,583,934 ÷ 304,276=？",
        "answer": 1.7364198623006586
    },
    {
        "question": "1,494 × 3,481=？",
        "answer": 6.716054620763669
    },
    {
        "question": "486,048,460 ÷ 1,267=？",
        "answer": 5.5839029565628
    },
    {
        "question": "28,830,611 ÷ 675,570=？",
        "answer": 1.6301834907452648
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 13,050,747=？",
        "answer": 8.229578722884835
    },
    {
        "question": "1,789 × 634=？",
        "answer": 6.054699598449106
    },
    {
        "question": "59,634 ÷ 9,738=？",
        "answer": 0.7870241707753906
    },
    {
        "question": "88 × 195,591=？",
        "answer": 7.235831539267075
    },
    {
        "question": "4,736 ÷ 593=？",
        "answer": 0.9023570003506007
    },
    {
        "question": "10,839 × 3,920=？",
        "answer": 7.628275283308142
    },
    {
        "question": "24,444 ÷ 241=？",
        "answer": 2.0061552324729206
    },
    {
        "question": "138 × 1,933,130=？",
        "answer": 8.426140147043467
    },
    {
        "question": "170,776 ÷ 2,037=？",
        "answer": 1.9234358080792031
    },
    {
        "question": "12,910,419 ÷ 55,419=？",
        "answer": 2.367281652311292
    },
    {
        "question": "89 × 689=？",
        "answer": 4.7876092285525385
    },
    {
        "question": "290 × 15,953=？",
        "answer": 6.665240363093589
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 1,228,017=？",
        "answer": 7.9922943659755035
    },
    {
        "question": "365,285 ÷ 1,828=？",
        "answer": 2.3006556473868383
    },
    {
        "question": "258,413 ÷ 3,175=？",
        "answer": 1.9105706283260497
    },
    {
        "question": "53,285 ÷ 756=？",
        "answer": 1.8480831746123563
    },
    {
        "question": "2,977 ÷ 2,369=？",
        "answer": 0.0992137739239597
    },
    {
        "question": "652 × 313=？",
        "answer": 5.309791933278369
    },
    {
        "question": "1,116,101 ÷ 1,848=？",
        "answer": 2.7810015303679365
    },
    {
        "question": "15,454 ÷ 518=？",
        "answer": 1.474711148163777
    },
    {
        "question": "762,978,122 ÷ 170,895=？",
        "answer": 3.649782728530164
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 145,206,032=？",
        "answer": 8.63910591247425
    },
    {
        "question": "29,660 ÷ 357=？",
        "answer": 1.91950293058017
    },
    {
        "question": "4,304 × 720=？",
        "answer": 6.491204759089602
    },
    {
        "question": "8,399,882 ÷ 505=？",
        "answer": 4.2209818070969325
    },
    {
        "question": "1,755,804 ÷ 1,623,004=？",
        "answer": 0.03415644390701431
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 505=？",
        "answer": 2.7032913781186614
    },
    {
        "question": "65,563 × 2,185=？",
        "answer": 8.15611025889613
    },
    {
        "question": "65,543 × 3,910=？",
        "answer": 8.408703073197607
    },
    {
        "question": "512,093 × 1,540=？",
        "answer": 8.89686956016988
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 6,015=？",
        "answer": 5.451333489611581
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,382,010=？",
        "answer": 6.529174887394898
    },
    {
        "question": "2,929 × 224=？",
        "answer": 5.816967390015762
    },
    {
        "question": "49,958 × 15,107=？",
        "answer": 8.877783272876064
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 1,334=？",
        "answer": 5.15453960726574
    },
    {
        "question": "3,120,550 ÷ 4,117=？",
        "answer": 2.879650278595951
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 313=？",
        "answer": 2.4955443375464483
    },
    {
        "question": "1,842 × 317=？",
        "answer": 5.766348888078582
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 12,203=？",
        "answer": 4.563587865991245
    },
    {
        "question": "193,863,612 ÷ 17,104,737=？",
        "answer": 1.0543798991794497
    },
    {
        "question": "35,272,191 ÷ 68,577=？",
        "answer": 2.7112539551880697
    },
    {
        "question": "2,751,511 ÷ 114,421=？",
        "answer": 1.3810655143446675
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 5,144,946=？",
        "answer": 7.188502075601381
    },
    {
        "question": "228 × 2,045=？",
        "answer": 5.668628159343815
    },
    {
        "question": "190,457,200 ÷ 78,242=？",
        "answer": 3.386357452040749
    },
    {
        "question": "53,623,699 ÷ 83,594=？",
        "answer": 2.80718166175514
    },
    {
        "question": "697,518,501 ÷ 104,060,451=？",
        "answer": 0.8262700275324976
    },
    {
        "question": "10,375,060 ÷ 9,076=？",
        "answer": 3.0580961297465157
    },
    {
        "question": "334,662,209 ÷ 7,622=？",
        "answer": 4.642537728933283
    },
    {
        "question": "304 × 55,680=？",
        "answer": 7.22857281021126
    },
    {
        "question": "22,370,822 ÷ 11,268=？",
        "answer": 3.2978351039190303
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,022=？",
        "answer": 3.3104808914626753
    },
    {
        "question": "677 × 8,541=？",
        "answer": 6.762097390551762
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,424,798=？",
        "answer": 6.384675565148859
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 768=？",
        "answer": 4.283301228703549
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 3,836=？",
        "answer": 5.6091844637633965
    },
    {
        "question": "20,135,427 ÷ 2,137=？",
        "answer": 3.974156321701281
    },
    {
        "question": "182,443 × 2,341=？",
        "answer": 8.630528618642053
    },
    {
        "question": "418,275,257 ÷ 828=？",
        "answer": 5.703431837941122
    },
    {
        "question": "43,688 × 10,425=？",
        "answer": 8.658438227173281
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 69,669,535=？",
        "answer": 7.843042911903766
    },
    {
        "question": "212 × 731=？",
        "answer": 5.190253237886612
    },
    {
        "question": "18,656 ÷ 12,657=？",
        "answer": 0.16848775297737667
    },
    {
        "question": "59,959 × 16,125=？",
        "answer": 8.98535410435307
    },
    {
        "question": "4,127 × 106,496=？",
        "answer": 8.642967764816008
    },
    {
        "question": "183 × 621,107=？",
        "answer": 8.055617513589153
    },
    {
        "question": "450 ÷ 247=？",
        "answer": 0.260515560515678
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 131,546=？",
        "answer": 6.022167633755443
    },
    {
        "question": "216,202,841 ÷ 89,427,678=？",
        "answer": 0.3833894420821973
    },
    {
        "question": "499,170,424 ÷ 665,384=？",
        "answer": 2.8751764918578724
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 13,433=？",
        "answer": 5.4503923094836475
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 22,755=？",
        "answer": 6.243567565014893
    },
    {
        "question": "83,078,522 ÷ 528=？",
        "answer": 5.196854839126145
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 652,421=？",
        "answer": 6.291649186299027
    },
    {
        "question": "36,665 ÷ 991=？",
        "answer": 1.568178034846354
    },
    {
        "question": "903,379,173 ÷ 11,790,285=？",
        "answer": 1.8843457706962214
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 74,120,773=？",
        "answer": 8.347061194614822
    },
    {
        "question": "22,223 × 4,893=？",
        "answer": 8.036377902025462
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,845,498=？",
        "answer": 6.584952589819404
    },
    {
        "question": "116 × 1,901,324=？",
        "answer": 8.343514119465487
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,476,476=？",
        "answer": 6.947377642319839
    },
    {
        "question": "30,102 × 24,797=？",
        "answer": 8.872994493436986
    },
    {
        "question": "7,191,134 ÷ 52,865=？",
        "answer": 2.133629144953909
    },
    {
        "question": "84,193 × 3,762=？",
        "answer": 8.500694775971152
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 916=？",
        "answer": 2.9618954736678504
    },
    {
        "question": "258,314,278 ÷ 11,444,029=？",
        "answer": 1.35356946225501
    },
    {
        "question": "23,972 × 5,350=？",
        "answer": 8.108058051045676
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 870=？",
        "answer": 4.956552591917399
    },
    {
        "question": "92,342 ÷ 6,757=？",
        "answer": 1.1356453576098084
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 18,659,980=？",
        "answer": 8.049062424312115
    },
    {
        "question": "443 × 555=？",
        "answer": 5.390696709345746
    },
    {
        "question": "9,521,397 ÷ 3,189,584=？",
        "answer": 0.47496662959084657
    },
    {
        "question": "168 × 71,775=？",
        "answer": 7.081282482894406
    },
    {
        "question": "11,204,362 ÷ 1,281,424=？",
        "answer": 0.9416942782269888
    },
    {
        "question": "3,146 × 1,013=？",
        "answer": 6.503368163647549
    },
    {
        "question": "4,693 × 202=？",
        "answer": 5.976801923659118
    },
    {
        "question": "45,704,665 ÷ 814,036=？",
        "answer": 1.749316918464399
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 57,030=？",
        "answer": 5.455073375921124
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 444,069,381=？",
        "answer": 8.647450829194451
    },
    {
        "question": "65,094 × 7,059=？",
        "answer": 8.662284141478004
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,180,794=？",
        "answer": 6.373204133356437
    },
    {
        "question": "4,070 × 4,968=？",
        "answer": 7.305775996393744
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 3,530=？",
        "answer": 5.564808044686603
    },
    {
        "question": "113 × 2,375=？",
        "answer": 5.428742057444305
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 1,618=？",
        "answer": 4.288159763323878
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 113,020=？",
        "answer": 6.665939159681615
    },
    {
        "question": "248,492 ÷ 87,660=？",
        "answer": 0.45251094521506574
    },
    {
        "question": "3,314,618 ÷ 449=？",
        "answer": 3.8681871434564754
    },
    {
        "question": "2,451,923 ÷ 155,056=？",
        "answer": 1.199018251284052
    },
    {
        "question": "655 × 1,177=？",
        "answer": 5.887017762835217
    },
    {
        "question": "250,403 ÷ 630=？",
        "answer": 2.5992989782622904
    },
    {
        "question": "26,142,298 ÷ 8,073=？",
        "answer": 3.510308808452535
    },
    {
        "question": "42,177,740 ÷ 209=？",
        "answer": 5.304937019215967
    },
    {
        "question": "23,963,316 ÷ 118,833=？",
        "answer": 2.3046098535055286
    },
    {
        "question": "147,571,725 ÷ 32,682,255=？",
        "answer": 0.654691139668327
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 3,387=？",
        "answer": 4.852034491378549
    },
    {
        "question": "1,685 × 4,251=？",
        "answer": 6.855091010174481
    },
    {
        "question": "10,097 × 79,524=？",
        "answer": 8.904690572898437
    },
    {
        "question": "21,104,491 ÷ 12,417,135=？",
        "answer": 0.2303534794361446
    },
    {
        "question": "32,009 × 5,898=？",
        "answer": 8.275976874685254
    },
    {
        "question": "440,863 ÷ 77,262=？",
        "answer": 0.756337705549112
    },
    {
        "question": "328,711,922 ÷ 822=？",
        "answer": 5.601943638184161
    },
    {
        "question": "397 × 6,970=？",
        "answer": 6.442023284861125
    },
    {
        "question": "27,134,426 ÷ 408,647=？",
        "answer": 1.8221723239928878
    },
    {
        "question": "61,371 × 5,887=？",
        "answer": 8.557857235696128
    },
    {
        "question": "2,258,279 ÷ 64,878=？",
        "answer": 1.5416801426185134
    },
    {
        "question": "16,671 × 3,348=？",
        "answer": 7.746747100826264
    },
    {
        "question": "2,465,842 ÷ 3,339=？",
        "answer": 2.8683488264711667
    },
    {
        "question": "156,074 × 385=？",
        "answer": 7.778791290501716
    },
    {
        "question": "4,494,819 ÷ 989,076=？",
        "answer": 0.6574825441932376
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,028,850=？",
        "answer": 6.313382057578149
    },
    {
        "question": "35,071,320 ÷ 352,435=？",
        "answer": 1.9978730807146476
    },
    {
        "question": "237 × 417=？",
        "answer": 4.994884400983861
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 7,681,771=？",
        "answer": 7.48752134766939
    },
    {
        "question": "1,287,766 ÷ 791,574=？",
        "answer": 0.21134543357516478
    },
    {
        "question": "4,817 × 25,742=？",
        "answer": 8.093418932286875
    },
    {
        "question": "107,974 ÷ 99,608=？",
        "answer": 0.0350249704108861
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 12,845,853=？",
        "answer": 8.011852934900904
    },
    {
        "question": "14,313 × 956=？",
        "answer": 7.136188563554689
    },
    {
        "question": "1,105 × 236=？",
        "answer": 5.416274280991236
    },
    {
        "question": "96 × 187,735=？",
        "answer": 7.255816480034166
    },
    {
        "question": "859,002 ÷ 41,366=？",
        "answer": 1.3173506473756038
    },
    {
        "question": "220 × 450=？",
        "answer": 4.99563519459755
    },
    {
        "question": "133 × 38,180=？",
        "answer": 6.705687565024734
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 8,110=？",
        "answer": 4.210050849875137
    },
    {
        "question": "811,892,965 ÷ 26,615=？",
        "answer": 4.484372307779365
    },
    {
        "question": "298,607 ÷ 17,300=？",
        "answer": 1.2370538811903526
    },
    {
        "question": "4,428 × 58,625=？",
        "answer": 8.414290467929824
    },
    {
        "question": "18,036 ÷ 2,276=？",
        "answer": 0.8989679689114994
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 2,267,264=？",
        "answer": 8.230563355669885
    },
    {
        "question": "96,605 × 3,239=？",
        "answer": 8.495410552854386
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 15,224=？",
        "answer": 4.483558770942945
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 3,716,447=？",
        "answer": 8.032525941637772
    },
    {
        "question": "21,598,865 ÷ 3,742,083=？",
        "answer": 0.7613175139928618
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 54,398=？",
        "answer": 5.513734183079417
    },
    {
        "question": "251 × 2,357=？",
        "answer": 5.772033304005362
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 65,121=？",
        "answer": 5.114751056635227
    },
    {
        "question": "2,704 × 1,583=？",
        "answer": 6.631487602131954
    },
    {
        "question": "30,674 ÷ 6,437=？",
        "answer": 0.6780869041099741
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 5,503=？",
        "answer": 5.694842022250481
    },
    {
        "question": "41,724,984 ÷ 498,998=？",
        "answer": 1.9222973738546663
    },
    {
        "question": "10,618,772 ÷ 105,463=？",
        "answer": 2.0029741748765724
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,048=？",
        "answer": 3.6072405038317426
    },
    {
        "question": "5,906 ÷ 826=？",
        "answer": 0.8543133953086774
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 667=？",
        "answer": 3.12515582958053
    },
    {
        "question": "55,623,492 ÷ 65,568=？",
        "answer": 2.9285663133360886
    },
    {
        "question": "11,068,212 ÷ 2,182,279=？",
        "answer": 0.7051671955224567
    },
    {
        "question": "477,025 ÷ 163,854=？",
        "answer": 0.4640840923744538
    },
    {
        "question": "54,588 ÷ 5,376=？",
        "answer": 1.0066379228318112
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,101=？",
        "answer": 3.799547307125615
    },
    {
        "question": "32,915,589 ÷ 4,466,450=？",
        "answer": 0.8674391542637748
    },
    {
        "question": "7,958 × 29,179=？",
        "answer": 8.36587433882004
    },
    {
        "question": "88 × 2,494=？",
        "answer": 5.341379121292692
    },
    {
        "question": "15,133,657 ÷ 4,442,038=？",
        "answer": 0.5323616171253114
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 856=？",
        "answer": 2.932473764677153
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 3,798,056=？",
        "answer": 8.202810654251161
    },
    {
        "question": "96,322 × 329=？",
        "answer": 7.5009213895126665
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,257=？",
        "answer": 3.0993352776859577
    },
    {
        "question": "81,794 ÷ 53,350=？",
        "answer": 0.1855870234015175
    },
    {
        "question": "189,314,845 ÷ 525,279=？",
        "answer": 2.5567946316195407
    },
    {
        "question": "1,859 ÷ 1,267=？",
        "answer": 0.16650277488845724
    },
    {
        "question": "457,536,485 ÷ 411,534,217=？",
        "answer": 0.046019780962086074
    },
    {
        "question": "3,654 × 2,395=？",
        "answer": 6.942074060767101
    },
    {
        "question": "6,426 × 107,938=？",
        "answer": 8.841115087909204
    },
    {
        "question": "1,697 × 281=？",
        "answer": 5.678388162222756
    },
    {
        "question": "27,959 ÷ 448=？",
        "answer": 1.7952436200909347
    },
    {
        "question": "1,463,488 × 272=？",
        "answer": 8.599958069782383
    },
    {
        "question": "61,833,899 ÷ 6,414=？",
        "answer": 3.984097676654424
    },
    {
        "question": "48 × 65,117=？",
        "answer": 6.494935621371939
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 25,257,094=？",
        "answer": 8.101353384903474
    },
    {
        "question": "65,120 × 369=？",
        "answer": 7.380740758040205
    },
    {
        "question": "88,733,875 ÷ 898=？",
        "answer": 4.994813110865059
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 42,404=？",
        "answer": 5.405558076221433
    },
    {
        "question": "18,454 ÷ 11,905=？",
        "answer": 0.19036111653428112
    },
    {
        "question": "116,312 ÷ 2,096=？",
        "answer": 1.7442332452296105
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,255=？",
        "answer": 3.399673721481038
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 198,263=？",
        "answer": 6.075392923766293
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 197,038=？",
        "answer": 5.595579986286684
    },
    {
        "question": "61,192 × 9,785=？",
        "answer": 8.777255477908255
    },
    {
        "question": "6,872,024 ÷ 1,131,897=？",
        "answer": 0.783277758704603
    },
    {
        "question": "262 × 4,471=？",
        "answer": 6.068705961187777
    },
    {
        "question": "6,139 ÷ 840=？",
        "answer": 0.8638183473184157
    },
    {
        "question": "13,234 × 66,447=？",
        "answer": 8.944166508169367
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 577=？",
        "answer": 4.669660832034381
    },
    {
        "question": "493 × 207=？",
        "answer": 5.008817264734148
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 85,289=？",
        "answer": 6.044836374712863
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 16,376=？",
        "answer": 5.469480334757756
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 15,392,046=？",
        "answer": 8.228689037767523
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 6,206,329=？",
        "answer": 8.023283715362053
    },
    {
        "question": "1,572 × 238=？",
        "answer": 5.573029498759901
    },
    {
        "question": "98,226,730 ÷ 1,092,004=？",
        "answer": 1.9540054572938503
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 34,035=？",
        "answer": 4.531925754940617
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 267=？",
        "answer": 4.307324853645366
    },
    {
        "question": "44,536 ÷ 912=？",
        "answer": 1.688716369970466
    },
    {
        "question": "33,837,523 ÷ 11,986=？",
        "answer": 3.4507242906163142
    },
    {
        "question": "1,604 × 761=？",
        "answer": 6.086589020718717
    },
    {
        "question": "216 × 4,104=？",
        "answer": 5.947661103254691
    },
    {
        "question": "2,491,838 × 367=？",
        "answer": 8.961185868694674
    },
    {
        "question": "73,334 ÷ 1,796=？",
        "answer": 1.610999041884966
    },
    {
        "question": "28,327 × 27,507=？",
        "answer": 8.89164381000234
    },
    {
        "question": "97,106,806 ÷ 4,323,229=？",
        "answer": 1.3514414291318337
    },
    {
        "question": "3,558,571 ÷ 2,345,842=？",
        "answer": 0.1809768775835758
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 10,066=？",
        "answer": 4.479978180780783
    },
    {
        "question": "48 × 8,937,886=？",
        "answer": 8.632476048442076
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 6,625,315=？",
        "answer": 8.143425826325348
    },
    {
        "question": "87,395,496 ÷ 32,406,412=？",
        "answer": 0.4308581023643463
    },
    {
        "question": "6,061 × 14,214=？",
        "answer": 7.935260595116419
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 48,796=？",
        "answer": 6.494564196619234
    },
    {
        "question": "15,907,061 ÷ 8,894,832=？",
        "answer": 0.2524521966823267
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 1,379,628=？",
        "answer": 7.952675356575737
    },
    {
        "question": "63,341,107 ÷ 23,485=？",
        "answer": 3.4308950846617208
    },
    {
        "question": "662 × 1,462=？",
        "answer": 5.985805362061542
    },
    {
        "question": "833 × 20,331=？",
        "answer": 7.228803741766476
    },
    {
        "question": "96,166 ÷ 461=？",
        "answer": 2.3193206266650237
    },
    {
        "question": "303 × 359,729=？",
        "answer": 8.037418078921037
    },
    {
        "question": "1,656 ÷ 1,100=？",
        "answer": 0.17766764729063628
    },
    {
        "question": "569,733,000 ÷ 221,394,360=？",
        "answer": 0.4105048222596461
    },
    {
        "question": "4,373 × 1,961=？",
        "answer": 6.933257071012641
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 15,643=？",
        "answer": 6.0974100322953655
    },
    {
        "question": "10,602 × 12,937=？",
        "answer": 8.137221378039255
    },
    {
        "question": "804 ÷ 207=？",
        "answer": 0.5892857032915335
    },
    {
        "question": "1,803 × 9,013=？",
        "answer": 7.21086509778888
    },
    {
        "question": "150,291 ÷ 64,707=？",
        "answer": 0.365981708985357
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,617=？",
        "answer": 4.035469763481282
    },
    {
        "question": "58,189,085 ÷ 30,301,530=？",
        "answer": 0.28337697047071847
    },
    {
        "question": "32,779 × 627=？",
        "answer": 7.312863241099168
    },
    {
        "question": "542,678,953 ÷ 824=？",
        "answer": 5.818615766740273
    },
    {
        "question": "281 × 26,765=？",
        "answer": 6.87627356762453
    },
    {
        "question": "9,133 ÷ 865=？",
        "answer": 1.0235973501830946
    },
    {
        "question": "476,617,734 ÷ 31,972,047=？",
        "answer": 1.1733997548208388
    },
    {
        "question": "646,372 ÷ 174,235=？",
        "answer": 0.5693471354020028
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 347,115,723=？",
        "answer": 8.540474285977623
    },
    {
        "question": "27,644,723 ÷ 14,375=？",
        "answer": 3.2840043893061353
    },
    {
        "question": "168,121,533 ÷ 1,190,316=？",
        "answer": 2.1499610700833154
    },
    {
        "question": "10,643 × 1,746=？",
        "answer": 7.269108301520596
    },
    {
        "question": "3,112 × 1,933=？",
        "answer": 6.779271442346205
    },
    {
        "question": "6,226 × 414=？",
        "answer": 6.411209457467395
    },
    {
        "question": "463,228 ÷ 10,223=？",
        "answer": 1.6562164418202834
    },
    {
        "question": "251,203 × 631=？",
        "answer": 8.200054180916243
    },
    {
        "question": "230,468,235 ÷ 4,125,188=？",
        "answer": 1.7471673301301325
    },
    {
        "question": "92,114 ÷ 7,965=？",
        "answer": 1.0631398615762864
    },
    {
        "question": "169,281 × 617=？",
        "answer": 8.018893379919993
    },
    {
        "question": "299,041 ÷ 15,423=？",
        "answer": 1.2875618777412512
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 2,530=？",
        "answer": 4.4031205211758175
    },
    {
        "question": "19,089 ÷ 7,969=？",
        "answer": 0.3793793511306349
    },
    {
        "question": "787 × 3,017=？",
        "answer": 6.375550042534053
    },
    {
        "question": "10,383,194 ÷ 378,305=？",
        "answer": 1.4384888871293688
    },
    {
        "question": "43,679 ÷ 829=？",
        "answer": 1.7217181563933555
    },
    {
        "question": "316,770,284 ÷ 2,675,238=？",
        "answer": 2.0733820092941975
    },
    {
        "question": "6,115,433 ÷ 738,882=？",
        "answer": 0.9178521256685607
    },
    {
        "question": "2,095 ÷ 1,755=？",
        "answer": 0.07690690650047119
    },
    {
        "question": "16,849 ÷ 6,451=？",
        "answer": 0.4169470883952371
    },
    {
        "question": "13,592 ÷ 5,614=？",
        "answer": 0.38401095756256887
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 634=？",
        "answer": 2.802089257881733
    },
    {
        "question": "211,016,253 ÷ 218=？",
        "answer": 5.985859413429449
    },
    {
        "question": "433 ÷ 316=？",
        "answer": 0.1368008137349616
    },
    {
        "question": "80,953,253 ÷ 653=？",
        "answer": 5.093321123717522
    },
    {
        "question": "20,558,703 ÷ 875=？",
        "answer": 4.370987659552352
    },
    {
        "question": "812,682,625 ÷ 86,406=？",
        "answer": 3.973377073947876
    },
    {
        "question": "1,773,658 ÷ 978=？",
        "answer": 3.258531027319335
    },
    {
        "question": "214,989,924 ÷ 5,827,845=？",
        "answer": 1.5669101136180705
    },
    {
        "question": "227,768,115 ÷ 1,174,607=？",
        "answer": 2.2876003429397294
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 2,318,272=？",
        "answer": 7.726892225871613
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 2,466=？",
        "answer": 4.839151103601932
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,272,910=？",
        "answer": 7.104797698323626
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,009=？",
        "answer": 3.7028611705729295
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 25,028=？",
        "answer": 5.699456141969465
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 45,075,731=？",
        "answer": 8.131064033191018
    },
    {
        "question": "396,192 ÷ 36,987=？",
        "answer": 1.0298565946157143
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 986,715=？",
        "answer": 6.295221726042961
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 1,641,580=？",
        "answer": 7.746740969329637
    },
    {
        "question": "22,385 ÷ 15,426=？",
        "answer": 0.16170377169295966
    },
    {
        "question": "927,370,033 ÷ 6,809=？",
        "answer": 5.134169723832799
    },
    {
        "question": "3,451 × 2,018=？",
        "answer": 6.842866121192379
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 473=？",
        "answer": 3.276921132065774
    },
    {
        "question": "3,215 × 136,149=？",
        "answer": 8.641195433100918
    },
    {
        "question": "9,863,888 ÷ 540=？",
        "answer": 4.261654372574711
    },
    {
        "question": "25,898,308 ÷ 10,694,000=？",
        "answer": 0.384131211719754
    },
    {
        "question": "1,636,608 ÷ 946=？",
        "answer": 3.2380535333439213
    },
    {
        "question": "46,798 × 313=？",
        "answer": 7.165771630630745
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,383=？",
        "answer": 3.8303319934519617
    },
    {
        "question": "44,246,303 ÷ 6,862,903=？",
        "answer": 0.8093691284398319
    },
    {
        "question": "6,038 × 676=？",
        "answer": 6.610839804628715
    },
    {
        "question": "864,347,040 ÷ 63,713,165=？",
        "answer": 1.1324589695443896
    },
    {
        "question": "55,590 ÷ 40,789=？",
        "answer": 0.13445361593415314
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 418,680=？",
        "answer": 6.400033465879379
    },
    {
        "question": "22,039,685 ÷ 3,346=？",
        "answer": 3.818679446487155
    },
    {
        "question": "395,378,241 ÷ 63,872,871=？",
        "answer": 0.7916963273911348
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 38,081,384=？",
        "answer": 8.960923965369435
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 54,355=？",
        "answer": 5.212360754798497
    },
    {
        "question": "4,360 ÷ 2,491=？",
        "answer": 0.24311276173207952
    },
    {
        "question": "979 × 64,417=？",
        "answer": 7.799783186987464
    },
    {
        "question": "117,171 × 480=？",
        "answer": 7.750061373815078
    },
    {
        "question": "318 × 9,068=？",
        "answer": 6.459938631438913
    },
    {
        "question": "39,711,915 ÷ 31,950=？",
        "answer": 3.0944499677545534
    },
    {
        "question": "185 × 3,069=？",
        "answer": 5.7541686168348365
    },
    {
        "question": "148 × 113,093=？",
        "answer": 7.223697440077662
    },
    {
        "question": "117,071,577 ÷ 1,373=？",
        "answer": 4.9307809312737865
    },
    {
        "question": "162,256,148 ÷ 1,455,595=？",
        "answer": 2.047160606402791
    },
    {
        "question": "119,592 ÷ 5,101=？",
        "answer": 1.370046805351476
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 947,720=？",
        "answer": 6.879770032751278
    },
    {
        "question": "132,117,838 ÷ 252=？",
        "answer": 5.719560917423176
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 1,536,458=？",
        "answer": 7.81998914863437
    },
    {
        "question": "651,228,345 ÷ 1,363=？",
        "answer": 5.679237439316104
    },
    {
        "question": "204,752,786 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 5.9668375460816305
    },
    {
        "question": "206 × 9,837=？",
        "answer": 6.306729891758181
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 21,903,141=？",
        "answer": 7.641536394575007
    },
    {
        "question": "6,320,868 ÷ 12,800=？",
        "answer": 2.6935667513126753
    },
    {
        "question": "371,322,370 ÷ 189,505=？",
        "answer": 3.29213044060533
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 34,953,902=？",
        "answer": 7.84452565993674
    },
    {
        "question": "68,580,973 ÷ 10,859,644=？",
        "answer": 0.8003880539442939
    },
    {
        "question": "22,496 × 572=？",
        "answer": 7.109501332132754
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 5,665=？",
        "answer": 4.53135116458306
    },
    {
        "question": "449 × 78,155=？",
        "answer": 7.545203108425037
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 10,036,047=？",
        "answer": 8.14769072217821
    },
    {
        "question": "10,509,314 ÷ 36,240=？",
        "answer": 2.4623861791892137
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 271=？",
        "answer": 3.9381192691943117
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 13,675=？",
        "answer": 4.135927335005468
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,465=？",
        "answer": 3.9439888750737717
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 957=？",
        "answer": 2.9809119377768436
    },
    {
        "question": "1,391 × 9,687=？",
        "answer": 7.129516429728871
    },
    {
        "question": "11,936,816 ÷ 1,646=？",
        "answer": 3.860458668610931
    },
    {
        "question": "6,389 × 59,115=？",
        "answer": 8.577130582053424
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 5,014,088=？",
        "answer": 7.399161956131937
    },
    {
        "question": "2,228,542 ÷ 57,752=？",
        "answer": 1.5864537945827428
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,600,086=？",
        "answer": 6.505173321020979
    },
    {
        "question": "712 × 378,036=？",
        "answer": 8.430013152883847
    },
    {
        "question": "127 × 91,779=？",
        "answer": 7.066547042381193
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 680=？",
        "answer": 3.3096301674258988
    },
    {
        "question": "1,797,683 ÷ 1,161=？",
        "answer": 3.1898808917474004
    },
    {
        "question": "6,520,325 ÷ 1,209,808=？",
        "answer": 0.7315527913019105
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,546=？",
        "answer": 4.327889981648543
    },
    {
        "question": "3,571 × 2,906=？",
        "answer": 7.016085460154785
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 58,247=？",
        "answer": 6.309341606374555
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 182,185=？",
        "answer": 7.2147551263935386
    },
    {
        "question": "3,604,528 ÷ 60,006=？",
        "answer": 1.778653725814906
    },
    {
        "question": "358,910,065 ÷ 707,850=？",
        "answer": 2.7050444011284482
    },
    {
        "question": "6,557,140 ÷ 3,003,020=？",
        "answer": 0.3391562316944035
    },
    {
        "question": "3,194 × 2,253=？",
        "answer": 6.857096103526295
    },
    {
        "question": "275,608,060 ÷ 3,682,886=？",
        "answer": 1.8741036381970515
    },
    {
        "question": "36,434,887 ÷ 560,164=？",
        "answer": 1.8132022323046995
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,016=？",
        "answer": 3.8519917479621575
    },
    {
        "question": "194 × 17,102=？",
        "answer": 6.520848632028408
    },
    {
        "question": "2,310 ÷ 201=？",
        "answer": 1.0604159224716554
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 203,164=？",
        "answer": 7.0321226244603725
    },
    {
        "question": "10,982,645 ÷ 125,409=？",
        "answer": 1.9423782409758852
    },
    {
        "question": "87,381 × 557=？",
        "answer": 7.687272205700595
    },
    {
        "question": "70,929 ÷ 16,319=？",
        "answer": 0.6381302945240314
    },
    {
        "question": "2,332,088 ÷ 5,994=？",
        "answer": 2.590028195639157
    },
    {
        "question": "35,240 ÷ 257=？",
        "answer": 2.1371027764087156
    },
    {
        "question": "123,531 × 512=？",
        "answer": 7.801045918081776
    },
    {
        "question": "8,117,873 ÷ 38,393=？",
        "answer": 2.3251902038319567
    },
    {
        "question": "923,465,734 ÷ 20,264=？",
        "answer": 4.658695608417905
    },
    {
        "question": "20,683,904 ÷ 5,885=？",
        "answer": 3.5458860462385533
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 83,662=？",
        "answer": 6.77986073892046
    },
    {
        "question": "9,700 × 1,597=？",
        "answer": 7.190076650404728
    },
    {
        "question": "172,939 ÷ 8,432=？",
        "answer": 1.3119623455201925
    },
    {
        "question": "293,593,230 ÷ 7,497=？",
        "answer": 4.592858526067058
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 20,927,551=？",
        "answer": 7.922778400296572
    },
    {
        "question": "163 × 2,773,123=？",
        "answer": 8.65515673724781
    },
    {
        "question": "80,026,601 ÷ 2,629,234=？",
        "answer": 1.483405131598655
    },
    {
        "question": "147,547,065 ÷ 68,916=？",
        "answer": 3.330610512625574
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 31,827=？",
        "answer": 4.502795704130007
    },
    {
        "question": "297,080 ÷ 6,267=？",
        "answer": 1.6758137205435888
    },
    {
        "question": "57,804 ÷ 6,545=？",
        "answer": 0.9460482414752842
    },
    {
        "question": "153 × 3,009,939=？",
        "answer": 8.663249125005516
    },
    {
        "question": "2,130 ÷ 474=？",
        "answer": 0.6526012617646526
    },
    {
        "question": "127,828 × 1,430=？",
        "answer": 8.261962031456298
    },
    {
        "question": "179,636 ÷ 479=？",
        "answer": 2.574057862539304
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 4,940,959=？",
        "answer": 7.170932504855257
    },
    {
        "question": "598,038 ÷ 21,255=？",
        "answer": 1.4492676711166834
    },
    {
        "question": "13,579,640 ÷ 3,126=？",
        "answer": 3.6378992831474815
    },
    {
        "question": "46,992 ÷ 8,283=？",
        "answer": 0.7538362678197994
    },
    {
        "question": "252,074,685 ÷ 2,578,193=？",
        "answer": 1.990213808229328
    },
    {
        "question": "3,029 × 401=？",
        "answer": 6.084443645953038
    },
    {
        "question": "22,360,084 ÷ 11,380,554=？",
        "answer": 0.29331002690490793
    },
    {
        "question": "483 × 6,311=？",
        "answer": 6.484045310926287
    },
    {
        "question": "229,997,081 ÷ 803=？",
        "answer": 5.45700677894049
    },
    {
        "question": "246,364,067 ÷ 539=？",
        "answer": 5.659988599662713
    },
    {
        "question": "692,904 ÷ 288,697=？",
        "answer": 0.3802307975128544
    },
    {
        "question": "8,386,112 ÷ 820,733=？",
        "answer": 1.0093587624193459
    },
    {
        "question": "144,310,940 ÷ 8,911=？",
        "answer": 4.2093728118991605
    },
    {
        "question": "902 × 533,966=？",
        "answer": 8.682720141981576
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 7,653,124=？",
        "answer": 7.184868745721446
    },
    {
        "question": "4,055,498 ÷ 1,500=？",
        "answer": 3.431952932505634
    },
    {
        "question": "42,349,479 ÷ 7,395,574=？",
        "answer": 0.7578761848692656
    },
    {
        "question": "29,660,817 ÷ 27,580,863=？",
        "answer": 0.03157525834829703
    },
    {
        "question": "32,171 × 5,337=？",
        "answer": 8.234761763479634
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,545,185=？",
        "answer": 7.092070470538731
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,304=？",
        "answer": 3.1152775913959014
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,037=？",
        "answer": 3.4929000111087034
    },
    {
        "question": "13,100,512 ÷ 794=？",
        "answer": 4.217467766849242
    },
    {
        "question": "19,802,133 ÷ 283,773=？",
        "answer": 1.8437409016027162
    },
    {
        "question": "987,406,921 ÷ 4,620=？",
        "answer": 5.3298541914245865
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 43,800=？",
        "answer": 6.172953027546354
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 9,854,808=？",
        "answer": 8.778978002403214
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,038,469=？",
        "answer": 6.493514791382899
    },
    {
        "question": "4,296 × 7,369=？",
        "answer": 7.50047282921429
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 1,266=？",
        "answer": 5.016247558065053
    },
    {
        "question": "16,636,959 ÷ 2,815,006=？",
        "answer": 0.7715946214824435
    },
    {
        "question": "1,637,038 ÷ 2,876=？",
        "answer": 2.755269878946527
    },
    {
        "question": "81,921,025 ÷ 449,433=？",
        "answer": 2.2607304198849025
    },
    {
        "question": "1,387 × 3,628=？",
        "answer": 6.701743739461342
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 54,434,466=？",
        "answer": 8.337933958193076
    },
    {
        "question": "8,298,079 ÷ 1,361,756=？",
        "answer": 0.7848782676321037
    },
    {
        "question": "92,394,300 ÷ 114,113=？",
        "answer": 2.9083100564961737
    },
    {
        "question": "348,035 ÷ 585=？",
        "answer": 2.7744670547107644
    },
    {
        "question": "264,164,311 ÷ 516,439=？",
        "answer": 2.708855111883759
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 156,168,447=？",
        "answer": 8.193593291525707
    },
    {
        "question": "23,715 ÷ 18,162=？",
        "answer": 0.11585945764767366
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,645,075=？",
        "answer": 6.72346798644893
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 48,282=？",
        "answer": 5.160906506430261
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,013,371=？",
        "answer": 6.005768471772114
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 17,469=？",
        "answer": 4.84432803615565
    },
    {
        "question": "300,511,826 ÷ 1,084=？",
        "answer": 5.442832285202893
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 1,244=？",
        "answer": 4.475031622066406
    },
    {
        "question": "86,603,653 ÷ 1,252,286=？",
        "answer": 1.839832685845594
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,148=？",
        "answer": 3.7589118923979736
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,802,487=？",
        "answer": 6.892233053744552
    },
    {
        "question": "6,149 × 8,353=？",
        "answer": 7.710646974450507
    },
    {
        "question": "2,894,507 ÷ 304=？",
        "answer": 3.978701020581751
    },
    {
        "question": "420,871,148 ÷ 2,623,456=？",
        "answer": 2.205275369849629
    },
    {
        "question": "84,937,980 ÷ 350=？",
        "answer": 5.385033884010471
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 97,525=？",
        "answer": 4.989115958983829
    },
    {
        "question": "529,103,035 ÷ 489=？",
        "answer": 6.0342313935820755
    },
    {
        "question": "126,676 ÷ 52,187=？",
        "answer": 0.3851320094617406
    },
    {
        "question": "6,457,596 ÷ 3,721=？",
        "answer": 3.2394112011862455
    },
    {
        "question": "887 × 272,094=？",
        "answer": 8.382642585001335
    },
    {
        "question": "779,914,920 ÷ 52,744=？",
        "answer": 4.169874165865282
    },
    {
        "question": "150,449,714 ÷ 75,129,181=？",
        "answer": 0.30158271197292413
    },
    {
        "question": "10,321 ÷ 990=？",
        "answer": 1.018086583453513
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 98,958,516=？",
        "answer": 8.296483169574419
    },
    {
        "question": "6,129 × 1,765=？",
        "answer": 7.034134331075951
    },
    {
        "question": "166,175 × 634=？",
        "answer": 8.022654945327911
    },
    {
        "question": "1,860,462 × 409=？",
        "answer": 8.881344111975832
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 3,785=？",
        "answer": 4.754157142891772
    },
    {
        "question": "24,770 ÷ 16,655=？",
        "answer": 0.17238136955864136
    },
    {
        "question": "18,874,158 ÷ 910,933=？",
        "answer": 1.3163811509386427
    },
    {
        "question": "468 ÷ 256=？",
        "answer": 0.26200588776227446
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 2,835,796=？",
        "answer": 8.020876709653862
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,053=？",
        "answer": 3.7035492982382303
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 28,746,251=？",
        "answer": 7.759611208996463
    },
    {
        "question": "146,738 ÷ 222=？",
        "answer": 2.8201896210099164
    },
    {
        "question": "1,542,819 ÷ 13,132=？",
        "answer": 2.069984104557979
    },
    {
        "question": "28,523 ÷ 6,711=？",
        "answer": 0.6284079631112844
    },
    {
        "question": "35,029,660 ÷ 7,978,891=？",
        "answer": 0.6424933898530745
    },
    {
        "question": "160,292 × 2,514=？",
        "answer": 8.605277121078043
    },
    {
        "question": "86,891,501 ÷ 461=？",
        "answer": 5.275276374081912
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,058,425=？",
        "answer": 6.723630093672891
    },
    {
        "question": "44,227,499 ÷ 20,564=？",
        "answer": 3.332584786154953
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,120=？",
        "answer": 3.959994838328416
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,263,329=？",
        "answer": 6.402546461245387
    },
    {
        "question": "2,320,286 ÷ 61,416=？",
        "answer": 1.5772599920190546
    },
    {
        "question": "541,370,458 ÷ 2,450,827=？",
        "answer": 2.3441818969274952
    },
    {
        "question": "59,618,082 ÷ 717,739=？",
        "answer": 1.9194114547757837
    },
    {
        "question": "29,095,889 ÷ 356,329=？",
        "answer": 1.9119804621824652
    },
    {
        "question": "40,798 ÷ 344=？",
        "answer": 2.0740804310513536
    },
    {
        "question": "1,714 × 338=？",
        "answer": 5.762927517864834
    },
    {
        "question": "565,928 × 650=？",
        "answer": 8.565674538375792
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 15,242=？",
        "answer": 4.961193207674284
    },
    {
        "question": "2,934,058 ÷ 361=？",
        "answer": 3.9099614927519064
    },
    {
        "question": "10,737,906 ÷ 8,016=？",
        "answer": 3.1269618892917945
    },
    {
        "question": "391,291 ÷ 7,198=？",
        "answer": 1.735288016584841
    },
    {
        "question": "3,825 ÷ 3,015=？",
        "answer": 0.10334412301346634
    },
    {
        "question": "21,883,141 ÷ 4,125=？",
        "answer": 3.7246857057746934
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 1,901=？",
        "answer": 4.601201411599362
    },
    {
        "question": "235 × 38,645=？",
        "answer": 6.958161173905664
    },
    {
        "question": "56,680,331 ÷ 476=？",
        "answer": 5.075825425041482
    },
    {
        "question": "546,929 × 449=？",
        "answer": 8.390177292730616
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,341=？",
        "answer": 3.9725268178658557
    },
    {
        "question": "70,034,500 ÷ 427=？",
        "answer": 5.21488415739723
    },
    {
        "question": "117,282,765 ÷ 40,829,506=？",
        "answer": 0.45826007074259256
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 4,404=？",
        "answer": 4.874296231677988
    },
    {
        "question": "73,606 ÷ 3,404=？",
        "answer": 1.3349236659233708
    },
    {
        "question": "13,174 × 5,365=？",
        "answer": 7.8492873854074645
    },
    {
        "question": "78,637,379 ÷ 21,155=？",
        "answer": 3.5702160002736716
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 317,231=？",
        "answer": 5.97849687495131
    },
    {
        "question": "27,233 ÷ 2,094=？",
        "answer": 1.1141188087154645
    },
    {
        "question": "1,321 × 15,210=？",
        "answer": 7.3030320316675255
    },
    {
        "question": "18,364 × 3,506=？",
        "answer": 7.808779195851759
    },
    {
        "question": "735,632,775 ÷ 409,643=？",
        "answer": 3.2542555323144606
    },
    {
        "question": "1,830 × 1,559=？",
        "answer": 6.455297204919271
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 12,126,869=？",
        "answer": 8.426171366969408
    },
    {
        "question": "273,678,578 ÷ 4,650,397=？",
        "answer": 1.7697507748601686
    },
    {
        "question": "77,455 ÷ 7,942=？",
        "answer": 0.9891195755496694
    },
    {
        "question": "184,409 ÷ 16,300=？",
        "answer": 1.0535945083817417
    },
    {
        "question": "312 × 43,449=？",
        "answer": 7.132134379418097
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 12,486=？",
        "answer": 4.096423330595271
    },
    {
        "question": "6,983 × 1,338=？",
        "answer": 6.9704981554728205
    },
    {
        "question": "1,042 × 183,279=？",
        "answer": 8.28098042557006
    },
    {
        "question": "728,182 × 725=？",
        "answer": 8.722577945935067
    },
    {
        "question": "163,925,510 ÷ 685=？",
        "answer": 5.378955972011851
    },
    {
        "question": "2,324 × 2,321=？",
        "answer": 6.731911264174211
    },
    {
        "question": "333 × 2,697,872=？",
        "answer": 8.953465574315747
    },
    {
        "question": "2,548,272 ÷ 671=？",
        "answer": 3.579523262126352
    },
    {
        "question": "3,350 ÷ 251=？",
        "answer": 1.1253710855558072
    },
    {
        "question": "3,436,189 ÷ 48,399=？",
        "answer": 1.8512406547014022
    },
    {
        "question": "1,261,963 ÷ 742=？",
        "answer": 3.2306427165614235
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 318,088=？",
        "answer": 7.426826571541187
    },
    {
        "question": "4,150 × 527=？",
        "answer": 6.33985871192464
    },
    {
        "question": "1,091 × 618,732=？",
        "answer": 8.829327328324904
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 5,508,032=？",
        "answer": 7.971445376090076
    },
    {
        "question": "149,937,301 ÷ 2,491=？",
        "answer": 4.7795359613708355
    },
    {
        "question": "178 × 861=？",
        "answer": 5.185423153762549
    },
    {
        "question": "121,001,095 ÷ 57,092,009=？",
        "answer": 0.3262139749016014
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,030,616=？",
        "answer": 6.307627803833903
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 4,417,652=？",
        "answer": 8.335387581416274
    },
    {
        "question": "46,633,791 ÷ 971,012=？",
        "answer": 1.6814761249268253
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 1,093,016=？",
        "answer": 7.640686510698389
    },
    {
        "question": "3,972 × 16,740=？",
        "answer": 7.822764693480584
    },
    {
        "question": "747,839,345 ÷ 280,798,922=？",
        "answer": 0.42541287414818535
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 7,373=？",
        "answer": 4.946825479950723
    },
    {
        "question": "24,574 × 582=？",
        "answer": 7.155398838587704
    },
    {
        "question": "3,206 × 265,953=？",
        "answer": 8.93076841162602
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 29,709=？",
        "answer": 5.074948025097599
    },
    {
        "question": "153,719,495 ÷ 24,670,355=？",
        "answer": 0.7945535501289218
    },
    {
        "question": "710,006,170 ÷ 8,926,166=？",
        "answer": 1.9005971636243786
    },
    {
        "question": "943,412,040 ÷ 50,074=？",
        "answer": 4.275089129493344
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 284=？",
        "answer": 2.4533183400470375
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 2,521=？",
        "answer": 5.100542850012465
    },
    {
        "question": "1,533 × 404=？",
        "answer": 5.79192351996498
    },
    {
        "question": "164,392,330 ÷ 3,046=？",
        "answer": 4.732151651938907
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 13,116=？",
        "answer": 5.923981381981215
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 54,410=？",
        "answer": 6.303880449972899
    },
    {
        "question": "1,058 ÷ 348=？",
        "answer": 0.4829064237525861
    },
    {
        "question": "7,601 × 39,832=？",
        "answer": 8.481102845799827
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,948=？",
        "answer": 3.694429690957083
    },
    {
        "question": "5,203 × 930=？",
        "answer": 6.684736774449972
    },
    {
        "question": "4,166,073 ÷ 94,336=？",
        "answer": 1.6450494180950652
    },
    {
        "question": "875,198,290 ÷ 104,020,551=？",
        "answer": 0.924987310531085
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 908=？",
        "answer": 2.958085848521085
    },
    {
        "question": "840 × 373,027=？",
        "answer": 8.496019553598812
    },
    {
        "question": "274,113,075 ÷ 1,741,305=？",
        "answer": 2.1970549045137613
    },
    {
        "question": "264,628 ÷ 32,403=？",
        "answer": 0.9120505737110263
    },
    {
        "question": "4,383 × 2,634=？",
        "answer": 7.062387241279724
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 1,056=？",
        "answer": 4.2541128395760675
    },
    {
        "question": "577,427,478 ÷ 16,829,431=？",
        "answer": 1.5354280139702
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 59,235,384=？",
        "answer": 8.617679248178145
    },
    {
        "question": "429,284,680 ÷ 36,403=？",
        "answer": 4.071608214294428
    },
    {
        "question": "214 × 880,872=？",
        "answer": 8.275326578773301
    },
    {
        "question": "1,836 × 552=？",
        "answer": 6.005811754594423
    },
    {
        "question": "74,119 ÷ 2,021=？",
        "answer": 1.5643632377493164
    },
    {
        "question": "1,999 ÷ 1,327=？",
        "answer": 0.17794187125368147
    },
    {
        "question": "111,953,296 ÷ 2,235=？",
        "answer": 4.699759356633256
    },
    {
        "question": "86,795,392 ÷ 790,144=？",
        "answer": 2.0407904223161837
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 17,059=？",
        "answer": 5.462402490577255
    },
    {
        "question": "161,597,004 ÷ 88,653=？",
        "answer": 3.2607398680911874
    },
    {
        "question": "6,831,727 ÷ 53,258=？",
        "answer": 2.1081456500243974
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 34,508=？",
        "answer": 5.860139084099762
    },
    {
        "question": "424 × 86,756=？",
        "answer": 7.565665376675616
    },
    {
        "question": "8,133 × 1,841=？",
        "answer": 7.175304560804163
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 13,860=？",
        "answer": 5.604161228174744
    },
    {
        "question": "164,771 ÷ 271=？",
        "answer": 2.7839114865823142
    },
    {
        "question": "163 × 2,677=？",
        "answer": 5.6398359755908904
    },
    {
        "question": "14,890,436 ÷ 2,697,021=？",
        "answer": 0.7420230862720651
    },
    {
        "question": "298,730,935 ÷ 248,662,194=？",
        "answer": 0.0796704369750629
    },
    {
        "question": "8,230,884 ÷ 23,419=？",
        "answer": 2.54587813450939
    },
    {
        "question": "586,011 ÷ 4,950=？",
        "answer": 2.073300569293505
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 455=？",
        "answer": 4.3014640731433
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 251,356=？",
        "answer": 6.178440506909308
    },
    {
        "question": "56,749,715 ÷ 16,373=？",
        "answer": 3.5398354229979065
    },
    {
        "question": "83 × 631,524=？",
        "answer": 7.719467952207261
    },
    {
        "question": "2,073 × 2,145=？",
        "answer": 6.648026598614604
    },
    {
        "question": "217 × 381,732=？",
        "answer": 7.918218301554781
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 162,442,911=？",
        "answer": 8.511730759170414
    },
    {
        "question": "13,301,967 ÷ 360,470=？",
        "answer": 1.5670467395454366
    },
    {
        "question": "9,248,193 ÷ 604=？",
        "answer": 4.185019945816092
    },
    {
        "question": "184 × 4,761=？",
        "answer": 5.942516004484047
    },
    {
        "question": "465,402 ÷ 6,223=？",
        "answer": 1.8738284442900428
    },
    {
        "question": "115,698,201 ÷ 948=？",
        "answer": 5.08651826878873
    },
    {
        "question": "36,203,411 ÷ 662=？",
        "answer": 4.737891501223013
    },
    {
        "question": "365,894 ÷ 2,066=？",
        "answer": 2.248224970717173
    },
    {
        "question": "1,769,293 ÷ 18,685=？",
        "answer": 1.9763066570927923
    },
    {
        "question": "445,565 ÷ 2,368=？",
        "answer": 2.2745293707757916
    },
    {
        "question": "8,513 ÷ 4,436=？",
        "answer": 0.2830910959152487
    },
    {
        "question": "29,516 ÷ 353=？",
        "answer": 1.922282796285091
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 47,641=？",
        "answer": 5.523078908902324
    },
    {
        "question": "3,244 × 8,225=？",
        "answer": 7.42621675216113
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 951,786=？",
        "answer": 7.937580704711271
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,494=？",
        "answer": 3.475380593143361
    },
    {
        "question": "30,493 ÷ 4,481=？",
        "answer": 0.8328252098505882
    },
    {
        "question": "3,449,586 ÷ 276,886=？",
        "answer": 1.0954659792464372
    },
    {
        "question": "10,783,163 ÷ 4,445=？",
        "answer": 3.3848744048170616
    },
    {
        "question": "657 × 3,795=？",
        "answer": 6.39677714979128
    },
    {
        "question": "101,579 × 4,817=？",
        "answer": 8.689580579392368
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 6,864=？",
        "answer": 5.809705128440347
    },
    {
        "question": "161 × 1,807=？",
        "answer": 5.463784028592782
    },
    {
        "question": "5,196 × 387=？",
        "answer": 6.303380107419902
    },
    {
        "question": "549,004,436 ÷ 168,692=？",
        "answer": 3.512481366375448
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 21,610,228=？",
        "answer": 8.413840595004883
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 22,388,858=？",
        "answer": 7.350031941861877
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 7,711,440=？",
        "answer": 7.928528169001606
    },
    {
        "question": "132,067,895 ÷ 397=？",
        "answer": 5.522006749012339
    },
    {
        "question": "11,772 × 35,858=？",
        "answer": 8.625436316311674
    },
    {
        "question": "50,514,054 ÷ 858,530=？",
        "answer": 1.7696567486586863
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 6,172,023=？",
        "answer": 7.693517522781381
    },
    {
        "question": "219,023,224 ÷ 9,373,629=？",
        "answer": 1.3685824069138728
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 1,110=？",
        "answer": 4.425534220498263
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 29,831,801=？",
        "answer": 7.474679473300081
    },
    {
        "question": "201 × 820=？",
        "answer": 5.217009909804205
    },
    {
        "question": "31,022 × 207=？",
        "answer": 6.807640138965583
    },
    {
        "question": "813,619,295 ÷ 7,305,318=？",
        "answer": 2.046782113848978
    },
    {
        "question": "32,663,371 ÷ 7,246=？",
        "answer": 3.653962674068635
    },
    {
        "question": "499 × 1,114=？",
        "answer": 5.7449857364611
    },
    {
        "question": "1,224,173 ÷ 6,516=？",
        "answer": 2.2738617209608396
    },
    {
        "question": "4,557 × 8,526=？",
        "answer": 7.589424356893562
    },
    {
        "question": "29,786 ÷ 11,629=？",
        "answer": 0.40846981465071175
    },
    {
        "question": "1,817,384 ÷ 25,369=？",
        "answer": 1.8551433518063674
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 120,763=？",
        "answer": 5.780903897584581
    },
    {
        "question": "6,249,350 ÷ 577,246=？",
        "answer": 1.034473916193422
    },
    {
        "question": "2,341 × 130,871=？",
        "answer": 8.48624483461485
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 8,103=？",
        "answer": 5.385767093626776
    },
    {
        "question": "3,796,430 × 217=？",
        "answer": 8.915835130451772
    },
    {
        "question": "107,160,383 ÷ 22,803=？",
        "answer": 3.672042269890966
    },
    {
        "question": "136,033,783 ÷ 156,490=？",
        "answer": 2.9391601850890234
    },
    {
        "question": "2,873 × 218=？",
        "answer": 5.796792119596552
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 120,641=？",
        "answer": 6.51285869259087
    },
    {
        "question": "376,644,011 ÷ 94,707=？",
        "answer": 3.5995489862881653
    },
    {
        "question": "573,459,732 ÷ 24,899=？",
        "answer": 4.3623210222086755
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 27,340=？",
        "answer": 6.090011024007147
    },
    {
        "question": "113,274 ÷ 604=？",
        "answer": 2.27309329822966
    },
    {
        "question": "242,718,647 ÷ 18,267,116=？",
        "answer": 1.1234331558940496
    },
    {
        "question": "1,074 × 371=？",
        "answer": 5.600378190978582
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,496=？",
        "answer": 3.652052848248105
    },
    {
        "question": "399 × 474,097=？",
        "answer": 8.276840102877529
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 206=？",
        "answer": 2.3138672203691533
    },
    {
        "question": "426,721,249 ÷ 8,332,936=？",
        "answer": 1.709346223216478
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 256,389=？",
        "answer": 6.9002610823028165
    },
    {
        "question": "665,890,569 ÷ 592,659,556=？",
        "answer": 0.050597572702123804
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 346,065=？",
        "answer": 5.84018767390784
    },
    {
        "question": "564,919 ÷ 13,046=？",
        "answer": 1.6365088074827512
    },
    {
        "question": "83,675,992 ÷ 212,745=？",
        "answer": 2.5947415077801477
    },
    {
        "question": "341,621 ÷ 202=？",
        "answer": 3.2281931901809933
    },
    {
        "question": "2,742,575 ÷ 25,247=？",
        "answer": 2.0359487328258035
    },
    {
        "question": "3,547 ÷ 2,559=？",
        "answer": 0.1417909025847573
    },
    {
        "question": "481,688,070 ÷ 66,746=？",
        "answer": 3.858340646128424
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 12,605,998=？",
        "answer": 8.562975231785726
    },
    {
        "question": "5,284,742 ÷ 21,593=？",
        "answer": 2.3887108052368946
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 57,620=？",
        "answer": 6.22297125184335
    },
    {
        "question": "451,828 ÷ 13,565=？",
        "answer": 1.5225533427600746
    },
    {
        "question": "609,705 ÷ 23,546=？",
        "answer": 1.413202616867208
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 11,997=？",
        "answer": 4.681132650181146
    },
    {
        "question": "1,344,180 ÷ 37,170=？",
        "answer": 1.5582648681670288
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,030,868=？",
        "answer": 6.013203058550506
    },
    {
        "question": "30,881 ÷ 1,421=？",
        "answer": 1.3370972774489907
    },
    {
        "question": "62,210,150 ÷ 38,933,128=？",
        "answer": 0.20354195091353286
    },
    {
        "question": "2,395,807 × 344=？",
        "answer": 8.916010272060493
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 360,497=？",
        "answer": 7.180150945337212
    },
    {
        "question": "336,826 × 2,483=？",
        "answer": 8.922382327384284
    },
    {
        "question": "360,779,979 ÷ 14,274,184=？",
        "answer": 1.4026911382617053
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 523,017=？",
        "answer": 6.1956370600041515
    },
    {
        "question": "10,069,866 ÷ 365,253=？",
        "answer": 1.4404298997306038
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,369,475=？",
        "answer": 6.136554108542409
    },
    {
        "question": "62,144 × 1,258=？",
        "answer": 7.893079845001142
    },
    {
        "question": "1,673,736 ÷ 287=？",
        "answer": 3.7658050606359312
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 5,141,242=？",
        "answer": 8.451430736230574
    },
    {
        "question": "994 ÷ 283=？",
        "answer": 0.5455999488730231
    },
    {
        "question": "21,709,773 ÷ 341=？",
        "answer": 4.803900903450278
    },
    {
        "question": "645 ÷ 538=？",
        "answer": 0.07877743896887861
    },
    {
        "question": "220 × 3,278=？",
        "answer": 5.858031630056686
    },
    {
        "question": "5,226,381 ÷ 871,554=？",
        "answer": 0.7779067659239165
    },
    {
        "question": "11,834 × 17,756=？",
        "answer": 8.322476701294322
    },
    {
        "question": "6,063 × 303=？",
        "answer": 6.264130196737272
    },
    {
        "question": "184,040,230 ÷ 7,507=？",
        "answer": 4.389446351476147
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 412=？",
        "answer": 2.6148972160331345
    },
    {
        "question": "734 ÷ 502=？",
        "answer": 0.1649923427710512
    },
    {
        "question": "1,160,096 ÷ 40,794=？",
        "answer": 1.4538976377943023
    },
    {
        "question": "506,110,725 ÷ 59,180,719=？",
        "answer": 0.93206530334822
    },
    {
        "question": "499,015,266 ÷ 271,877=？",
        "answer": 3.2637413627752387
    },
    {
        "question": "29,444,504 ÷ 84,891=？",
        "answer": 2.540142593399353
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 3,196=？",
        "answer": 4.9359705348009415
    },
    {
        "question": "94,806 ÷ 5,733=？",
        "answer": 1.2184538816861117
    },
    {
        "question": "709,502 ÷ 3,320=？",
        "answer": 2.3298155403146006
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,303=？",
        "answer": 4.212267528548938
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 95,102=？",
        "answer": 5.756340900652608
    },
    {
        "question": "2,520 × 255,157=？",
        "answer": 8.808208028086957
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 1,009=？",
        "answer": 4.972374114790846
    },
    {
        "question": "116,178 × 936=？",
        "answer": 8.036399744579123
    },
    {
        "question": "250,155,774 ÷ 36,187,850=？",
        "answer": 0.8396477500729996
    },
    {
        "question": "300,922 ÷ 1,749=？",
        "answer": 2.2356641301036633
    },
    {
        "question": "8,217 ÷ 1,117=？",
        "answer": 0.8666601138580148
    },
    {
        "question": "1,041 × 13,238=？",
        "answer": 7.1392731062627215
    },
    {
        "question": "4,379,576 ÷ 95,268=？",
        "answer": 1.66248501918477
    },
    {
        "question": "12,737 × 1,882=？",
        "answer": 7.379686767901362
    },
    {
        "question": "193 × 1,081,721=？",
        "answer": 8.319672569976943
    },
    {
        "question": "865,901 × 1,113=？",
        "answer": 8.983963405530496
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,838=？",
        "answer": 4.151982395457474
    },
    {
        "question": "9,461,953 ÷ 3,580,696=？",
        "answer": 0.42201333535566726
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 14,921=？",
        "answer": 5.018895970384717
    },
    {
        "question": "613,656 ÷ 7,583=？",
        "answer": 1.9080839288873042
    },
    {
        "question": "745,527,366 ÷ 236,299,667=？",
        "answer": 0.49900048007355946
    },
    {
        "question": "181 × 230=？",
        "answer": 4.619406410886778
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 30,760=？",
        "answer": 5.090046322457356
    },
    {
        "question": "84,525 ÷ 21,487=？",
        "answer": 0.5948093956073832
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 1,207=？",
        "answer": 4.805983139698138
    },
    {
        "question": "33,491,427 ÷ 52,766=？",
        "answer": 2.8025794791902445
    },
    {
        "question": "497,189,051 ÷ 10,108,926=？",
        "answer": 1.6918165387207929
    },
    {
        "question": "16,161,110 ÷ 1,983=？",
        "answer": 3.9111484720797707
    },
    {
        "question": "318 × 1,974=？",
        "answer": 5.797774268318051
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 2,557,513=？",
        "answer": 7.870215847835027
    },
    {
        "question": "32,504 ÷ 19,611=？",
        "answer": 0.21943706963277468
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,405=？",
        "answer": 3.9733587998863977
    },
    {
        "question": "229,561,954 ÷ 178,948=？",
        "answer": 3.1081730638551948
    },
    {
        "question": "7,108,338 ÷ 222=？",
        "answer": 4.505415095786294
    },
    {
        "question": "58,467,972 ÷ 443,616=？",
        "answer": 2.1199108287509825
    },
    {
        "question": "11,293,703 ÷ 37,385=？",
        "answer": 2.480138977561324
    },
    {
        "question": "1,513 ÷ 815=？",
        "answer": 0.2686813192832101
    },
    {
        "question": "1,877,394 ÷ 559,665=？",
        "answer": 0.5256272774583425
    },
    {
        "question": "31,126,128 ÷ 10,368=？",
        "answer": 3.4774301105427
    },
    {
        "question": "50,376,512 ÷ 181,268=？",
        "answer": 2.44390695121762
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 1,304,049=？",
        "answer": 7.291385169492839
    },
    {
        "question": "396 ÷ 302=？",
        "answer": 0.11768824296836168
    },
    {
        "question": "88,228,199 ÷ 4,814,952=？",
        "answer": 1.263015452051335
    },
    {
        "question": "837,113 × 1,086=？",
        "answer": 8.958613911637995
    },
    {
        "question": "136,549 ÷ 204=？",
        "answer": 2.8256583565586624
    },
    {
        "question": "380,013 × 1,910=？",
        "answer": 8.860831821053205
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 4,349=？",
        "answer": 4.337359412001355
    },
    {
        "question": "199,057 ÷ 1,357=？",
        "answer": 2.1663976068447535
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 407=？",
        "answer": 3.0867156639448825
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 671,701=？",
        "answer": 7.0824484999617106
    },
    {
        "question": "14,130 × 9,441=？",
        "answer": 8.12516015948144
    },
    {
        "question": "21,009 ÷ 710=？",
        "answer": 1.4711470323485787
    },
    {
        "question": "10,806,740 ÷ 7,551=？",
        "answer": 3.155690232608764
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 39,253=？",
        "answer": 4.593872854295451
    },
    {
        "question": "213,932 × 1,871=？",
        "answer": 8.602349538803558
    },
    {
        "question": "486,385 ÷ 768=？",
        "answer": 2.801618952899122
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 374,020,741=？",
        "answer": 8.57289568629697
    },
    {
        "question": "4,952,749 ÷ 718,064=？",
        "answer": 0.8386831649592915
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 13,199=？",
        "answer": 5.940084964404288
    },
    {
        "question": "131,570,953 ÷ 457=？",
        "answer": 5.459243820331045
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 51,776=？",
        "answer": 5.015158491260141
    },
    {
        "question": "438,025,246 ÷ 584,122=？",
        "answer": 2.8749955786600925
    },
    {
        "question": "56,472,769 ÷ 1,154,915=？",
        "answer": 1.6892890608088171
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,439=？",
        "answer": 3.635182048656268
    },
    {
        "question": "4,249,116 ÷ 9,499=？",
        "answer": 2.6506206997281208
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,174=？",
        "answer": 3.0696680969115957
    },
    {
        "question": "4,847,677 ÷ 133,021=？",
        "answer": 1.5616134667783164
    },
    {
        "question": "1,449,303 ÷ 1,211,064=？",
        "answer": 0.07799209666374111
    },
    {
        "question": "952,766,357 ÷ 230,875,689=？",
        "answer": 0.6156082089226714
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,568=？",
        "answer": 3.6724673130680823
    },
    {
        "question": "1,545 × 328=？",
        "answer": 5.704802327472533
    },
    {
        "question": "5,657 ÷ 632=？",
        "answer": 0.9518691004580242
    },
    {
        "question": "249,458,788 ÷ 1,511=？",
        "answer": 5.217734343646259
    },
    {
        "question": "1,459 × 23,010=？",
        "answer": 7.525971910562095
    },
    {
        "question": "760 × 8,742=？",
        "answer": 6.822424394434425
    },
    {
        "question": "365 × 1,102,708=？",
        "answer": 8.604753389790977
    },
    {
        "question": "196 × 11,309=？",
        "answer": 6.345680275425821
    },
    {
        "question": "8,319,076 ÷ 64,990=？",
        "answer": 2.1072285549022594
    },
    {
        "question": "4,352 ÷ 1,586=？",
        "answer": 0.4383857037085385
    },
    {
        "question": "42,520 ÷ 1,594=？",
        "answer": 1.4261049387911657
    },
    {
        "question": "258 × 1,112=？",
        "answer": 5.457724493209269
    },
    {
        "question": "241,697 ÷ 205,099=？",
        "answer": 0.07130771698941724
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,916=？",
        "answer": 4.370993933514744
    },
    {
        "question": "328,780,883 ÷ 7,658,372=？",
        "answer": 1.6327700994313674
    },
    {
        "question": "6,352,834 ÷ 4,437=？",
        "answer": 3.1558780786215586
    },
    {
        "question": "2,002,240 ÷ 3,013=？",
        "answer": 2.82251700162407
    },
    {
        "question": "198,122,150 ÷ 1,633=？",
        "answer": 5.083946847515754
    },
    {
        "question": "43,197,979 ÷ 115,174=？",
        "answer": 2.574108978825595
    },
    {
        "question": "240,258,223 ÷ 179,834=？",
        "answer": 3.1258064563319112
    },
    {
        "question": "6,262,785 ÷ 418,348=？",
        "answer": 1.1752298056341581
    },
    {
        "question": "1,360,921 ÷ 28,236=？",
        "answer": 1.6830297423839067
    },
    {
        "question": "3,652 ÷ 3,327=？",
        "answer": 0.0404779679934388
    },
    {
        "question": "1,627,031 × 477=？",
        "answer": 8.889914206716174
    },
    {
        "question": "27,345 ÷ 1,030=？",
        "answer": 1.4240407030054854
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 60,229=？",
        "answer": 5.624903692524248
    },
    {
        "question": "3,610,645 ÷ 84,996=？",
        "answer": 1.6281863026799324
    },
    {
        "question": "9,794,460 ÷ 23,742=？",
        "answer": 2.6154631962931307
    },
    {
        "question": "651,794,253 ÷ 44,649,640=？",
        "answer": 1.1642925652648914
    },
    {
        "question": "84,034 × 269=？",
        "answer": 7.354207316359899
    },
    {
        "question": "2,180 × 417,701=？",
        "answer": 8.959322008596711
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 768=？",
        "answer": 4.575557300060026
    },
    {
        "question": "160 × 3,724=？",
        "answer": 5.77512965496523
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 249=？",
        "answer": 2.3961993470957363
    },
    {
        "question": "7,181,574 ÷ 3,823,256=？",
        "answer": 0.2737862611108078
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 561,382=？",
        "answer": 7.0714777781552485
    },
    {
        "question": "34,883,374 ÷ 243,232=？",
        "answer": 2.1565977733988997
    },
    {
        "question": "5,839,128 ÷ 3,219=？",
        "answer": 3.258627018874697
    },
    {
        "question": "1,369 × 921=？",
        "answer": 6.100663078330839
    },
    {
        "question": "128 × 4,132,585=？",
        "answer": 8.723431764656343
    },
    {
        "question": "27,351 ÷ 3,781=？",
        "answer": 0.8593665321567321
    },
    {
        "question": "8,388 ÷ 3,614=？",
        "answer": 0.36567027356839316
    },
    {
        "question": "343 × 23,335=？",
        "answer": 6.903301925263945
    },
    {
        "question": "414 × 15,354=？",
        "answer": 6.803221877391728
    },
    {
        "question": "86,398,165 ÷ 1,032=？",
        "answer": 4.922824821358566
    },
    {
        "question": "123,594,471 ÷ 107,159,881=？",
        "answer": 0.061966820362324246
    },
    {
        "question": "686 × 14,614=？",
        "answer": 7.00109321871595
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 12,957,359=？",
        "answer": 7.112516491611116
    },
    {
        "question": "2,046 × 461=？",
        "answer": 5.974606554765789
    },
    {
        "question": "7,882,130 ÷ 6,659,485=？",
        "answer": 0.07320294836895093
    },
    {
        "question": "61,055,081 ÷ 460,245=？",
        "answer": 2.1227327326219383
    },
    {
        "question": "104,665,221 ÷ 334,962=？",
        "answer": 2.4948068538045476
    },
    {
        "question": "8,968,695 ÷ 3,186=？",
        "answer": 3.4494834836715107
    },
    {
        "question": "150,903,582 ÷ 5,518=？",
        "answer": 4.436917852607711
    },
    {
        "question": "2,192 × 289=？",
        "answer": 5.801738392568879
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 174,999=？",
        "answer": 6.834100174022949
    },
    {
        "question": "4,375,762 ÷ 17,113=？",
        "answer": 2.4077275421122626
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 357,414=？",
        "answer": 6.594564245089645
    },
    {
        "question": "366 × 515,384=？",
        "answer": 8.275612017227516
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 178,294,882=？",
        "answer": 8.552168872484541
    },
    {
        "question": "240,139,775 ÷ 212=？",
        "answer": 6.054128238455072
    },
    {
        "question": "58,014,873 ÷ 62,525=？",
        "answer": 2.9674856454671783
    },
    {
        "question": "18,275,618 ÷ 3,742=？",
        "answer": 3.6887682886192215
    },
    {
        "question": "238 × 6,403=？",
        "answer": 6.18296045888068
    },
    {
        "question": "457,700 × 219=？",
        "answer": 8.001025027267417
    },
    {
        "question": "217 × 967=？",
        "answer": 5.321886207931531
    },
    {
        "question": "14,379,810 ÷ 685=？",
        "answer": 4.322062576272331
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,093=？",
        "answer": 3.7069736761761782
    },
    {
        "question": "637,716 ÷ 432,880=？",
        "answer": 0.16825979244745573
    },
    {
        "question": "268,000 ÷ 4,584=？",
        "answer": 1.7668901850694552
    },
    {
        "question": "1,223,590 × 479=？",
        "answer": 8.76797143239526
    },
    {
        "question": "19,850,922 ÷ 851=？",
        "answer": 4.367851122813699
    },
    {
        "question": "154 × 114,274=？",
        "answer": 7.245468150348196
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 90,642=？",
        "answer": 6.681605349194227
    },
    {
        "question": "22,128,190 ÷ 75,635=？",
        "answer": 2.4662230805446117
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 93,201=？",
        "answer": 6.820678920860096
    },
    {
        "question": "1,361 × 4,177=？",
        "answer": 6.7547226004684555
    },
    {
        "question": "1,435,660 ÷ 78,685=？",
        "answer": 1.2611596511914291
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 19,539=？",
        "answer": 4.892962324221707
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 365,679=？",
        "answer": 5.5631000206443355
    },
    {
        "question": "395,927,964 ÷ 37,307,974=？",
        "answer": 1.0258145111944006
    },
    {
        "question": "200,082 × 659=？",
        "answer": 8.120093434503094
    },
    {
        "question": "280 × 3,594=？",
        "answer": 6.002736104115174
    },
    {
        "question": "640,020 × 379=？",
        "answer": 8.384832755442465
    },
    {
        "question": "388,786,632 ÷ 5,985=？",
        "answer": 4.812647169031243
    },
    {
        "question": "331 × 1,300,915=？",
        "answer": 8.634076915059115
    },
    {
        "question": "113 × 863=？",
        "answer": 4.98908923919863
    },
    {
        "question": "125,847 ÷ 4,529=？",
        "answer": 1.4438405464086157
    },
    {
        "question": "830,557,458 ÷ 12,832=？",
        "answer": 4.811075331397202
    },
    {
        "question": "81,813 × 1,168=？",
        "answer": 7.980265160869255
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 786=？",
        "answer": 4.439490590389684
    },
    {
        "question": "497,284,990 ÷ 3,556=？",
        "answer": 5.145643598431026
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,710=？",
        "answer": 3.673020907128896
    },
    {
        "question": "301,971,828 ÷ 132,397=？",
        "answer": 3.3580882835245425
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 4,685,931=？",
        "answer": 7.448947139736377
    },
    {
        "question": "655,908,876 ÷ 1,129,280=？",
        "answer": 2.7640418712944865
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 6,335=？",
        "answer": 5.080500220172289
    },
    {
        "question": "391 × 16,056=？",
        "answer": 6.797814116875296
    },
    {
        "question": "6,841,257 ÷ 619=？",
        "answer": 4.043445256502425
    },
    {
        "question": "744 × 9,481=？",
        "answer": 6.848427082122098
    },
    {
        "question": "61,663 × 4,061=？",
        "answer": 8.398657639490509
    },
    {
        "question": "2,823 ÷ 814=？",
        "answer": 0.5400864732577181
    },
    {
        "question": "933,626 × 515=？",
        "answer": 8.681980166657876
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 181,997,736=？",
        "answer": 8.561095981182998
    },
    {
        "question": "9,161,755 ÷ 423,546=？",
        "answer": 1.3350780892783363
    },
    {
        "question": "104,160,549 ÷ 596,804=？",
        "answer": 2.241871534994439
    },
    {
        "question": "291,158,368 ÷ 2,517,204=？",
        "answer": 2.0632108632106445
    },
    {
        "question": "1,254 × 4,106=？",
        "answer": 6.711716481529271
    },
    {
        "question": "50,486 × 7,988=？",
        "answer": 8.605609019155114
    },
    {
        "question": "50,148,225 ÷ 13,702=？",
        "answer": 3.5634716025609534
    },
    {
        "question": "43,926,688 ÷ 40,421=？",
        "answer": 3.036121405819648
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 1,500,125=？",
        "answer": 7.352218707810304
    },
    {
        "question": "5,219 × 99,160=？",
        "answer": 8.713923814951244
    },
    {
        "question": "3,731 × 25,930=？",
        "answer": 7.985627765810181
    },
    {
        "question": "75,870,078 ÷ 61,295=？",
        "answer": 3.0926454811706656
    },
    {
        "question": "241,383 ÷ 1,271=？",
        "answer": 2.2785611300119224
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 4,874,399=？",
        "answer": 7.943193581122697
    },
    {
        "question": "94,979 × 281=？",
        "answer": 7.426333912643519
    },
    {
        "question": "250,149,602 ÷ 236,202=？",
        "answer": 3.0249162456294085
    },
    {
        "question": "3,275 × 209,338=？",
        "answer": 8.836059374961538
    },
    {
        "question": "1,690 × 854=？",
        "answer": 6.159344575302678
    },
    {
        "question": "523,111,476 ÷ 217,479=？",
        "answer": 3.3811769202828326
    },
    {
        "question": "59,988 × 10,335=？",
        "answer": 8.792374863763522
    },
    {
        "question": "714,269 × 237=？",
        "answer": 8.228610147722087
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 401,549=？",
        "answer": 6.205798540024013
    },
    {
        "question": "517 × 1,206,861=？",
        "answer": 8.795147796282238
    },
    {
        "question": "16,014,934 ÷ 1,516,139=？",
        "answer": 1.0237861338620702
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 17,367=？",
        "answer": 5.987912831292666
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,792,149=？",
        "answer": 6.55440410991181
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 1,576,080=？",
        "answer": 7.476331858952029
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,129=？",
        "answer": 3.7964355588101744
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 1,242,797=？",
        "answer": 7.270491455292127
    },
    {
        "question": "1,320 ÷ 212=？",
        "answer": 0.7942380702770985
    },
    {
        "question": "231 × 121,205=？",
        "answer": 7.447132515791881
    },
    {
        "question": "363,268,953 ÷ 656,012=？",
        "answer": 2.743316498494862
    },
    {
        "question": "12,013,999 ÷ 3,212=？",
        "answer": 3.5729120548556588
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 33,591,651=？",
        "answer": 7.526231349556725
    },
    {
        "question": "9,693 × 51,184=？",
        "answer": 8.695592435477339
    },
    {
        "question": "126,628,656 ÷ 1,184=？",
        "answer": 5.0291802950353715
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 2,855,931=？",
        "answer": 7.631838969624368
    },
    {
        "question": "40,042,435 ÷ 79,836=？",
        "answer": 2.7003217097758703
    },
    {
        "question": "123,779 × 532=？",
        "answer": 7.818558602037881
    },
    {
        "question": "560,828,289 ÷ 4,905,079=？",
        "answer": 2.0581839055478683
    },
    {
        "question": "94,738 ÷ 343=？",
        "answer": 2.4412300921189365
    },
    {
        "question": "2,546 × 67,854=？",
        "answer": 8.237433853770625
    },
    {
        "question": "4,055 × 1,512=？",
        "answer": 6.787542649712362
    },
    {
        "question": "23,072,966 ÷ 616,804=？",
        "answer": 1.5729562446347356
    },
    {
        "question": "18,644 × 31,701=？",
        "answer": 8.7716120564036
    },
    {
        "question": "1,330 × 6,617=？",
        "answer": 6.944512775610681
    },
    {
        "question": "2,601,332 ÷ 3,321=？",
        "answer": 2.893926907803411
    },
    {
        "question": "893,257,144 ÷ 311=？",
        "answer": 6.458216109217214
    },
    {
        "question": "449 × 12,804=？",
        "answer": 6.759592006475418
    },
    {
        "question": "69,001,065 ÷ 767,635=？",
        "answer": 1.953701025934482
    },
    {
        "question": "750 × 260=？",
        "answer": 5.290034611362518
    },
    {
        "question": "4,062,726 ÷ 2,194,437=？",
        "answer": 0.26749441623317743
    },
    {
        "question": "265,665 ÷ 10,951=？",
        "answer": 1.3848805631485641
    },
    {
        "question": "93,859,337 ÷ 12,288,840=？",
        "answer": 0.8829665923624342
    },
    {
        "question": "126,370 × 5,566=？",
        "answer": 8.847187187488338
    },
    {
        "question": "401,485 ÷ 3,321=？",
        "answer": 2.0824004485146443
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 360,101=？",
        "answer": 6.786873248786435
    },
    {
        "question": "420,980,761 ÷ 7,631=？",
        "answer": 4.741680795292008
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 4,726=？",
        "answer": 5.466885406794604
    },
    {
        "question": "1,195,769 ÷ 1,065,913=？",
        "answer": 0.04992553131095665
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,542=？",
        "answer": 3.7062055418819706
    },
    {
        "question": "127,549,407 ÷ 743=？",
        "answer": 5.234689630077225
    },
    {
        "question": "804 × 35,828=？",
        "answer": 7.459478614290877
    },
    {
        "question": "161,207,104 ÷ 455,202=？",
        "answer": 2.5491800146480585
    },
    {
        "question": "13,594 × 1,402=？",
        "answer": 7.280095279216883
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 472=？",
        "answer": 2.673941998634088
    },
    {
        "question": "2,981 × 2,667=？",
        "answer": 6.900384991722507
    },
    {
        "question": "738 × 482=？",
        "answer": 5.5511034000618915
    },
    {
        "question": "53,373,371 ÷ 906=？",
        "answer": 4.770196435527094
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 4,464,415=？",
        "answer": 8.357334734749855
    },
    {
        "question": "5,954,418 ÷ 24,189=？",
        "answer": 2.391221404324006
    },
    {
        "question": "4,307,629 ÷ 547=？",
        "answer": 3.8962509657411997
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 18,584,738=？",
        "answer": 8.269156442969743
    },
    {
        "question": "124,076 ÷ 45,080=？",
        "answer": 0.4397038767389494
    },
    {
        "question": "1,855 × 283,631=？",
        "answer": 8.72109761011362
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 13,493=？",
        "answer": 6.03319850735288
    },
    {
        "question": "216,899 ÷ 6,274=？",
        "answer": 1.5387130353680822
    },
    {
        "question": "26,147 × 21,693=？",
        "answer": 8.753741483139946
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 535,907=？",
        "answer": 6.683331939260542
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 19,613,519=？",
        "answer": 8.523004441877964
    },
    {
        "question": "310 × 1,655,968=？",
        "answer": 8.710413634038147
    },
    {
        "question": "104,349 ÷ 441=？",
        "answer": 2.3740497020116136
    },
    {
        "question": "67,968 ÷ 1,187=？",
        "answer": 1.7578537717747462
    },
    {
        "question": "115,381 × 2,657=？",
        "answer": 8.48652585305216
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,229=？",
        "answer": 3.6916118742144164
    },
    {
        "question": "40,802 ÷ 1,051=？",
        "answer": 1.5890787354850582
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 186,332=？",
        "answer": 6.474407428158745
    },
    {
        "question": "197,560,942 ÷ 407,465=？",
        "answer": 2.685610778167769
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 57,556=？",
        "answer": 5.714333113357627
    },
    {
        "question": "22,442,706 ÷ 466=？",
        "answer": 4.682689303541896
    },
    {
        "question": "7,080 ÷ 203=？",
        "answer": 1.5425372197765561
    },
    {
        "question": "275 × 346,270=？",
        "answer": 7.978747560780144
    },
    {
        "question": "16,604,635 ÷ 269,484=？",
        "answer": 1.7896963484183301
    },
    {
        "question": "13,293,386 ÷ 6,644,103=？",
        "answer": 0.30119925907339146
    },
    {
        "question": "62,979,120 ÷ 20,357=？",
        "answer": 3.490482811357073
    },
    {
        "question": "1,825,660 ÷ 103,598=？",
        "answer": 1.2460685290567564
    },
    {
        "question": "9,237 ÷ 374=？",
        "answer": 1.3926593414223805
    },
    {
        "question": "662 × 295,597=？",
        "answer": 8.291558011550658
    },
    {
        "question": "57,915,100 ÷ 2,718=？",
        "answer": 4.328542358165163
    },
    {
        "question": "208 × 2,038,161=？",
        "answer": 8.627301822115932
    },
    {
        "question": "827,945,467 ÷ 43,127,190=？",
        "answer": 1.2832505705977073
    },
    {
        "question": "46,319,987 ÷ 5,390=？",
        "answer": 3.93417966364514
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 28,676=？",
        "answer": 6.360608558705942
    },
    {
        "question": "500 × 397=？",
        "answer": 5.297760511099134
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 3,311=？",
        "answer": 4.599140426799694
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 1,483,317=？",
        "answer": 7.449987575068755
    },
    {
        "question": "250 × 293=？",
        "answer": 4.8648076290261475
    },
    {
        "question": "680,168 ÷ 33,410=？",
        "answer": 1.3087397200998052
    },
    {
        "question": "13,441,749 ÷ 6,562,055=？",
        "answer": 0.31141591537437313
    },
    {
        "question": "5,042,146 ÷ 460,502=？",
        "answer": 1.039383896205374
    },
    {
        "question": "8,800,965 ÷ 110,164=？",
        "answer": 1.9024905973256097
    },
    {
        "question": "232,162,345 ÷ 36,170,417=？",
        "answer": 0.8074382661233245
    },
    {
        "question": "14,039 × 20,654=？",
        "answer": 8.462340346721636
    },
    {
        "question": "1,481 ÷ 470=？",
        "answer": 0.49845720058549103
    },
    {
        "question": "13,248 × 2,916=？",
        "answer": 7.586937839086742
    },
    {
        "question": "7,692,883 ÷ 1,157=？",
        "answer": 3.8227557684111533
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 413=？",
        "answer": 3.218010042984363
    },
    {
        "question": "1,459 × 1,409=？",
        "answer": 6.312966285002808
    },
    {
        "question": "152,883 ÷ 3,342=？",
        "answer": 1.6603527506681717
    },
    {
        "question": "375,784,266 ÷ 3,060,925=？",
        "answer": 2.089085903864188
    },
    {
        "question": "255 × 246=？",
        "answer": 4.797475287537334
    },
    {
        "question": "10,022,986 ÷ 2,972=？",
        "answer": 3.527948318651777
    },
    {
        "question": "12,532,965 ÷ 3,532=？",
        "answer": 3.5500331319393217
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 9,499=？",
        "answer": 5.409041651832982
    },
    {
        "question": "67,791,953 ÷ 341=？",
        "answer": 5.298423766569188
    },
    {
        "question": "404 ÷ 296=？",
        "answer": 0.1350896540516664
    },
    {
        "question": "635,318 ÷ 68,090=？",
        "answer": 0.9699078258789907
    },
    {
        "question": "4,060 × 5,773=？",
        "answer": 7.369927591075825
    },
    {
        "question": "8,270 × 1,968=？",
        "answer": 7.211530603647869
    },
    {
        "question": "7,875 × 3,735=？",
        "answer": 7.468541168613056
    },
    {
        "question": "645,520 ÷ 239=？",
        "answer": 3.4315118015103514
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 425,774=？",
        "answer": 5.629179137606563
    },
    {
        "question": "204,245 ÷ 6,277=？",
        "answer": 1.512399304979747
    },
    {
        "question": "211 × 373=？",
        "answer": 4.89599128710638
    },
    {
        "question": "45,444,342 ÷ 26,371,708=？",
        "answer": 0.2363415611613305
    },
    {
        "question": "213 × 3,157=？",
        "answer": 5.827654185330955
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 637,493=？",
        "answer": 6.406535411684051
    },
    {
        "question": "428,349 × 456=？",
        "answer": 8.29076260002249
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 68,735,410=？",
        "answer": 8.615331777919673
    },
    {
        "question": "13,191,393 ÷ 3,445=？",
        "answer": 3.5831014328561617
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 19,268,134=？",
        "answer": 8.947597489630086
    },
    {
        "question": "38,543,067 ÷ 1,187,458=？",
        "answer": 1.5113280122352881
    },
    {
        "question": "163 × 3,658,500=？",
        "answer": 8.77549066377337
    },
    {
        "question": "129,768,768 ÷ 160,620=？",
        "answer": 2.9073705599741535
    },
    {
        "question": "11,980 × 280=？",
        "answer": 6.525614849395512
    },
    {
        "question": "2,545,761 ÷ 579,021=？",
        "answer": 0.6431233139352114
    },
    {
        "question": "1,498,582 ÷ 89,191=？",
        "answer": 1.2253594786129198
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,468=？",
        "answer": 3.467756051244033
    },
    {
        "question": "7,628,156 ÷ 444=？",
        "answer": 4.235036595911998
    },
    {
        "question": "278,829,152 ÷ 660=？",
        "answer": 5.625794242387954
    },
    {
        "question": "242,586,385 ÷ 117,816,078=？",
        "answer": 0.313661861388975
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 204,648=？",
        "answer": 6.21409749168685
    },
    {
        "question": "1,132 × 198,102=？",
        "answer": 8.350735286967172
    },
    {
        "question": "14,509 × 508=？",
        "answer": 6.8675011929885095
    },
    {
        "question": "726,650 × 284=？",
        "answer": 8.314643617935136
    },
    {
        "question": "373,314,527 ÷ 56,868=？",
        "answer": 3.8172069354556895
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,015=？",
        "answer": 3.784617292632875
    },
    {
        "question": "25,744 ÷ 8,174=？",
        "answer": 0.49824139337937967
    },
    {
        "question": "519,516 ÷ 320,993=？",
        "answer": 0.20910336575024258
    },
    {
        "question": "102,633 ÷ 92,058=？",
        "answer": 0.04722548825191172
    },
    {
        "question": "605,236,549 ÷ 475=？",
        "answer": 6.105231536675621
    },
    {
        "question": "367,797,563 ÷ 99,067,553=？",
        "answer": 0.5696774113943291
    },
    {
        "question": "2,172 ÷ 652=？",
        "answer": 0.5226122251848891
    },
    {
        "question": "772,981,328 ÷ 27,251=？",
        "answer": 4.452786559572055
    },
    {
        "question": "1,831 × 459,958=？",
        "answer": 8.92540652119848
    },
    {
        "question": "3,734 × 3,254=？",
        "answer": 7.0845918622139
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 61,024=？",
        "answer": 6.693985690244562
    },
    {
        "question": "208,237 ÷ 101,515=？",
        "answer": 0.3120276794548404
    },
    {
        "question": "41,575 × 1,010=？",
        "answer": 7.6231536316741995
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 9,617=？",
        "answer": 5.937282125485427
    },
    {
        "question": "402,360 ÷ 1,365=？",
        "answer": 2.46948214809967
    },
    {
        "question": "52,896,951 ÷ 12,193,054=？",
        "answer": 0.6373181426728725
    },
    {
        "question": "372,117,164 ÷ 305=？",
        "answer": 6.086379863081549
    },
    {
        "question": "649,719,585 ÷ 392,571,780=？",
        "answer": 0.21880688108518678
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,073=？",
        "answer": 3.72956972630197
    },
    {
        "question": "50,700,060 ÷ 11,350,721=？",
        "answer": 0.6499850244159259
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 269=？",
        "answer": 4.4425895047075805
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,078=？",
        "answer": 3.509740015570382
    },
    {
        "question": "219 × 3,909=？",
        "answer": 5.932509785272366
    },
    {
        "question": "41,171 ÷ 282=？",
        "answer": 2.1643423073593877
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 559,748=？",
        "answer": 5.747992550503832
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 5,975,327=？",
        "answer": 8.22351970839497
    },
    {
        "question": "948,867,994 ÷ 204=？",
        "answer": 6.667575630391261
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 41,193=？",
        "answer": 4.614823421866625
    },
    {
        "question": "150,644,513 ÷ 4,107,441=？",
        "answer": 1.5643819839034956
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 103,297=？",
        "answer": 6.46124574006063
    },
    {
        "question": "776,755 × 239=？",
        "answer": 8.268681958453419
    },
    {
        "question": "12,375,495 ÷ 2,706,955=？",
        "answer": 0.6600815428510379
    },
    {
        "question": "4,740,753 ÷ 6,318=？",
        "answer": 2.8752677069766857
    },
    {
        "question": "47,549,283 ÷ 379,680=？",
        "answer": 2.097726251683213
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 12,598=？",
        "answer": 4.799271608349873
    },
    {
        "question": "381 × 8,271=？",
        "answer": 6.498482996501055
    },
    {
        "question": "493,968,791 ÷ 7,571,273=？",
        "answer": 1.8145306050471206
    },
    {
        "question": "949,413 ÷ 93,009=？",
        "answer": 1.0089301990559019
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,418=？",
        "answer": 3.452706226511029
    },
    {
        "question": "13,495 × 1,442=？",
        "answer": 7.289138149275946
    },
    {
        "question": "2,161 × 5,955=？",
        "answer": 7.1095365327020374
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 613,167=？",
        "answer": 6.933706809219423
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 249=？",
        "answer": 3.4375920322539613
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,914=？",
        "answer": 4.060093183824469
    },
    {
        "question": "73,898,849 ÷ 32,242=？",
        "answer": 3.3602157005190483
    },
    {
        "question": "419,356,235 ÷ 24,553=？",
        "answer": 4.2324785406783105
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 49,673,582=？",
        "answer": 7.696125478431775
    },
    {
        "question": "2,314 × 7,618=？",
        "answer": 7.246204322940658
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 62,929=？",
        "answer": 5.8780320765090375
    },
    {
        "question": "27,998,388 ÷ 20,400=？",
        "answer": 3.137502860242821
    },
    {
        "question": "180,784,574 ÷ 830=？",
        "answer": 5.338083277831333
    },
    {
        "question": "125,895,572 ÷ 17,424,854=？",
        "answer": 0.8588413074648146
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 77,028=？",
        "answer": 6.187678617395884
    },
    {
        "question": "1,866 × 10,529=？",
        "answer": 7.293298765096919
    },
    {
        "question": "1,241 × 29,517=？",
        "answer": 7.5638439967888385
    },
    {
        "question": "2,018 × 625=？",
        "answer": 6.100801179244967
    },
    {
        "question": "300 × 561,489=？",
        "answer": 8.226462507238608
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 34,801=？",
        "answer": 6.109793447560764
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 6,959=？",
        "answer": 5.444606827822978
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 606=？",
        "answer": 3.7367151336056112
    },
    {
        "question": "868 × 304=？",
        "answer": 5.4213933087852455
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 1,845,686=？",
        "answer": 7.627885654014853
    },
    {
        "question": "6,234,979 ÷ 4,210,529=？",
        "answer": 0.1704983321703042
    },
    {
        "question": "540,722 ÷ 55,863=？",
        "answer": 0.985849784964017
    },
    {
        "question": "4,009 × 4,380=？",
        "answer": 7.244510166754621
    },
    {
        "question": "1,877 × 4,868=？",
        "answer": 6.960814842179373
    },
    {
        "question": "2,088,183 ÷ 95,360=？",
        "answer": 1.3404023134319618
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 302,222=？",
        "answer": 6.957447329980241
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 248=？",
        "answer": 4.04766419460156
    },
    {
        "question": "54,086,870 ÷ 2,078,148=？",
        "answer": 1.4154153760208756
    },
    {
        "question": "19,272 × 3,102=？",
        "answer": 7.776568580467873
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 201,309=？",
        "answer": 5.604893187159506
    },
    {
        "question": "75,167,841 ÷ 4,546=？",
        "answer": 4.218402645061055
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,596,715=？",
        "answer": 7.12035771718554
    },
    {
        "question": "31,137,223 ÷ 305=？",
        "answer": 5.008980037685723
    },
    {
        "question": "18,036,642 ÷ 9,416,694=？",
        "answer": 0.28225722723713254
    },
    {
        "question": "58,874 ÷ 1,235=？",
        "answer": 1.6782565859269118
    },
    {
        "question": "7,509 × 107,887=？",
        "answer": 8.908551221222083
    },
    {
        "question": "338,025,009 ÷ 206,184,521=？",
        "answer": 0.2146927748747796
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,880=？",
        "answer": 4.070407321740119
    },
    {
        "question": "167 × 67,111=？",
        "answer": 7.049510181298196
    },
    {
        "question": "280,410,615 ÷ 1,004,597=？",
        "answer": 2.445802573006441
    },
    {
        "question": "116,558 ÷ 2,947=？",
        "answer": 1.5971619509866848
    },
    {
        "question": "216 × 30,914=？",
        "answer": 6.824608953740441
    },
    {
        "question": "560 × 10,293=？",
        "answer": 6.760729999782036
    },
    {
        "question": "801,733 ÷ 780,561=？",
        "answer": 0.011622911519073588
    },
    {
        "question": "429,430 ÷ 15,563=？",
        "answer": 1.4407990635409507
    },
    {
        "question": "6,966,146 ÷ 231,858=？",
        "answer": 1.477770487046419
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 1,859=？",
        "answer": 4.310672074930124
    },
    {
        "question": "28,458,170 ÷ 19,565=？",
        "answer": 3.162727117142811
    },
    {
        "question": "917 ÷ 580=？",
        "answer": 0.1989413421070838
    },
    {
        "question": "20,263 × 2,379=？",
        "answer": 7.683098186466907
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 280,844=？",
        "answer": 6.925586404688183
    },
    {
        "question": "478,889 ÷ 44,330=？",
        "answer": 1.0335371301864416
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 849=？",
        "answer": 4.774005730258209
    },
    {
        "question": "389,774,377 ÷ 265,683,219=？",
        "answer": 0.16644916155101497
    },
    {
        "question": "285 × 1,117,496=？",
        "answer": 8.503090837288067
    },
    {
        "question": "15,857,386 ÷ 33,705=？",
        "answer": 2.672537266428593
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 22,564,494=？",
        "answer": 8.432606845128173
    },
    {
        "question": "221 × 507,721=？",
        "answer": 8.050017400445055
    },
    {
        "question": "2,115,410 ÷ 4,925=？",
        "answer": 2.632988318192309
    },
    {
        "question": "6,463 × 134,430=？",
        "answer": 8.938930354555378
    },
    {
        "question": "768,723,177 ÷ 27,599=？",
        "answer": 4.444876628770317
    },
    {
        "question": "161,041,171 ÷ 138,000=？",
        "answer": 3.0670578334338408
    },
    {
        "question": "7,105 ÷ 4,161=？",
        "answer": 0.23236636647054124
    },
    {
        "question": "4,991 × 13,906=？",
        "answer": 7.841389794915719
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 12,128,468=？",
        "answer": 7.083805946689701
    },
    {
        "question": "53,838 ÷ 5,493=？",
        "answer": 0.9912793191132653
    },
    {
        "question": "499,773,202 ÷ 1,042=？",
        "answer": 5.680905246441285
    },
    {
        "question": "934,844 ÷ 21,591=？",
        "answer": 1.636466387591916
    },
    {
        "question": "21,684 ÷ 1,101=？",
        "answer": 1.2943520796368049
    },
    {
        "question": "283,685 ÷ 17,541=？",
        "answer": 1.2087820242870124
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 28,302=？",
        "answer": 5.928938381349008
    },
    {
        "question": "551,777,362 ÷ 570=？",
        "answer": 5.985889022855307
    },
    {
        "question": "402 × 688,483=？",
        "answer": 8.442119274224483
    },
    {
        "question": "1,207 × 7,343=？",
        "answer": 6.947580798305164
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,697=？",
        "answer": 3.8863214865594795
    },
    {
        "question": "508 × 21,903=？",
        "answer": 7.046367315444369
    },
    {
        "question": "1,179 × 1,763=？",
        "answer": 6.317766117394411
    },
    {
        "question": "1,609,509 ÷ 13,079=？",
        "answer": 2.0901188697252433
    },
    {
        "question": "15,191 ÷ 9,085=？",
        "answer": 0.2232614320928032
    },
    {
        "question": "293,813,360 ÷ 24,233,537=？",
        "answer": 1.0836547336171
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,188,114=？",
        "answer": 6.0748581133687685
    },
    {
        "question": "3,732 × 57,871=？",
        "answer": 8.334402622029847
    },
    {
        "question": "93,851,229 ÷ 337,494=？",
        "answer": 2.4441739078572366
    },
    {
        "question": "3,480 × 259=？",
        "answer": 5.954879008027833
    },
    {
        "question": "43,389 × 313=？",
        "answer": 7.132923978468781
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 12,043,164=？",
        "answer": 8.828928627484567
    },
    {
        "question": "409,866 ÷ 66,062=？",
        "answer": 0.7926901757298014
    },
    {
        "question": "487,916,952 ÷ 22,563,277=？",
        "answer": 1.3349437322521767
    },
    {
        "question": "1,619 ÷ 521=？",
        "answer": 0.49240912545384924
    },
    {
        "question": "423,849,677 ÷ 2,106=？",
        "answer": 5.303753489684391
    },
    {
        "question": "777 × 64,149=？",
        "answer": 7.697610909474965
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 522,740,498=？",
        "answer": 8.718286147269389
    },
    {
        "question": "291,981,825 ÷ 80,801=？",
        "answer": 3.557939083077198
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 110,477=？",
        "answer": 5.344301868139557
    },
    {
        "question": "365 × 837=？",
        "answer": 5.485018322449735
    },
    {
        "question": "3,420,997 ÷ 61,768=？",
        "answer": 1.7433891538897919
    },
    {
        "question": "24,370 ÷ 3,823=？",
        "answer": 0.8044512311656962
    },
    {
        "question": "3,344 ÷ 201=？",
        "answer": 1.22107021134649
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,205,571=？",
        "answer": 6.505905400488736
    },
    {
        "question": "49,649 × 552=？",
        "answer": 7.437849583353035
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,867=？",
        "answer": 3.8958091501691308
    },
    {
        "question": "553,208,464 ÷ 151,754=？",
        "answer": 3.5617486688964983
    },
    {
        "question": "68,197 × 1,326=？",
        "answer": 7.956308794442208
    },
    {
        "question": "11,664 ÷ 1,825=？",
        "answer": 0.8055846421814059
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 8,243=？",
        "answer": 5.258507980665909
    },
    {
        "question": "765,176,094 ÷ 889,105=？",
        "answer": 2.934808340564782
    },
    {
        "question": "317,324 ÷ 12,006=？",
        "answer": 1.4221045810899948
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 1,359,023=？",
        "answer": 8.047040659144583
    },
    {
        "question": "20,596,037 ÷ 1,997,463=？",
        "answer": 1.0133049199414987
    },
    {
        "question": "495,227 ÷ 336=？",
        "answer": 3.168465037199264
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 2,463=？",
        "answer": 4.646736916942409
    },
    {
        "question": "23,085 × 852=？",
        "answer": 7.29376947365386
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 92,980=？",
        "answer": 5.44551079656673
    },
    {
        "question": "241,186,879 ÷ 2,805,701=？",
        "answer": 1.934312290764127
    },
    {
        "question": "118,388 ÷ 15,500=？",
        "answer": 0.8829759856532761
    },
    {
        "question": "30,037,259 ÷ 22,746,691=？",
        "answer": 0.12074207129350346
    },
    {
        "question": "3,345 ÷ 306=？",
        "answer": 1.038674695622262
    },
    {
        "question": "1,004 × 21,391=？",
        "answer": 7.33196480052828
    },
    {
        "question": "1,092,412 ÷ 50,020=？",
        "answer": 1.339242774766327
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 15,803,583=？",
        "answer": 8.675876816403063
    },
    {
        "question": "33,891 ÷ 1,574=？",
        "answer": 1.3330796554521198
    },
    {
        "question": "8,511,865 ÷ 369,479=？",
        "answer": 1.362434967473776
    },
    {
        "question": "2,046,044 ÷ 61,035=？",
        "answer": 1.5253360200330273
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 501,074=？",
        "answer": 6.301961859746994
    },
    {
        "question": "1,775,631 ÷ 1,046,776=？",
        "answer": 0.22949896180817622
    },
    {
        "question": "445 × 14,747=？",
        "answer": 6.817063691230008
    },
    {
        "question": "703 × 49,098=？",
        "answer": 7.538019126579565
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 6,522=？",
        "answer": 4.960508830148176
    },
    {
        "question": "11,497 × 241=？",
        "answer": 6.442601573935733
    },
    {
        "question": "744,913 ÷ 256,626=？",
        "answer": 0.4628048988119173
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 8,038=？",
        "answer": 4.507207993183979
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 76,911=？",
        "answer": 6.3483864560054375
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 17,391=？",
        "answer": 5.5413545507544155
    },
    {
        "question": "272 × 102,427=？",
        "answer": 7.4449833568203125
    },
    {
        "question": "110,268 × 5,953=？",
        "answer": 8.817185380125613
    },
    {
        "question": "49,334,940 ÷ 61,540=？",
        "answer": 2.9039971124484274
    },
    {
        "question": "44,359,218 ÷ 41,109,908=？",
        "answer": 0.03303737657954123
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 168,927=？",
        "answer": 6.506452670380962
    },
    {
        "question": "277,691 ÷ 125,174=？",
        "answer": 0.34604767388140495
    },
    {
        "question": "140,868 ÷ 519=？",
        "answer": 2.4336449908195097
    },
    {
        "question": "3,714,196 ÷ 4,913=？",
        "answer": 2.8785180538129502
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 528,569=？",
        "answer": 5.7231016886410755
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,065=？",
        "answer": 3.704579449696299
    },
    {
        "question": "114 × 2,230,282=？",
        "answer": 8.405264630663048
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 10,804=？",
        "answer": 5.9086458389071135
    },
    {
        "question": "565,924,900 ÷ 3,068,654=？",
        "answer": 2.265810879600427
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 219=？",
        "answer": 3.9739125704197047
    },
    {
        "question": "7,502,556 ÷ 316=？",
        "answer": 4.375522163117969
    },
    {
        "question": "116,600,198 ÷ 722=？",
        "answer": 5.208162090333926
    },
    {
        "question": "13,753 × 320=？",
        "answer": 6.643547421310452
    },
    {
        "question": "1,417 ÷ 366=？",
        "answer": 0.5878887648530498
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 15,862,686=？",
        "answer": 8.823626017907284
    },
    {
        "question": "1,741,030 ÷ 8,730=？",
        "answer": 2.2997920108822987
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 154,826,230=？",
        "answer": 8.666965793619847
    },
    {
        "question": "1,058,969 × 220=？",
        "answer": 8.367305927685125
    },
    {
        "question": "408 × 656,602=？",
        "answer": 8.427962364339797
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,037,802=？",
        "answer": 7.208205010141695
    },
    {
        "question": "383,162 × 1,685=？",
        "answer": 8.809982336697802
    },
    {
        "question": "441,965,472 ÷ 11,961=？",
        "answer": 4.567620851578797
    },
    {
        "question": "780,840,432 ÷ 559=？",
        "answer": 6.145150485168563
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 22,209=？",
        "answer": 5.249618991093808
    },
    {
        "question": "18,819 × 5,321=？",
        "answer": 8.00058980118172
    },
    {
        "question": "250,072,028 ÷ 32,439,113=？",
        "answer": 0.8869961455468033
    },
    {
        "question": "1,676 ÷ 877=？",
        "answer": 0.2812744209282172
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 410=？",
        "answer": 3.214843848047698
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 19,268=？",
        "answer": 6.142169134073665
    },
    {
        "question": "111,277,716 ÷ 105,288=？",
        "answer": 3.0240293269675793
    },
    {
        "question": "16,937 × 1,089=？",
        "answer": 7.265864367283709
    },
    {
        "question": "99,335 × 2,906=？",
        "answer": 8.460397906077631
    },
    {
        "question": "175,343 ÷ 952=？",
        "answer": 2.265251484381922
    },
    {
        "question": "732,852 ÷ 4,525=？",
        "answer": 2.209397693865069
    },
    {
        "question": "526,313 ÷ 103,174=？",
        "answer": 0.7076738290508207
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 462,509=？",
        "answer": 6.142241442848352
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,684=？",
        "answer": 3.8284020784915933
    },
    {
        "question": "374,814,657 ÷ 163,099,995=？",
        "answer": 0.3613626177596517
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 160,930=？",
        "answer": 5.507667006947517
    },
    {
        "question": "152,896,738 ÷ 136,607=？",
        "answer": 3.048925266002804
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,924,733=？",
        "answer": 6.840403032774445
    },
    {
        "question": "109,848,337 ÷ 452=？",
        "answer": 5.385655051686928
    },
    {
        "question": "3,214,567 ÷ 2,966,504=？",
        "answer": 0.034877543755337456
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 31,219,460=？",
        "answer": 8.397515373833382
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 9,030=？",
        "answer": 4.73383900069715
    },
    {
        "question": "452 × 393=？",
        "answer": 5.249530985186809
    },
    {
        "question": "4,860 ÷ 867=？",
        "answer": 0.7486171717860831
    },
    {
        "question": "105,672 ÷ 33,957=？",
        "answer": 0.4930306125308114
    },
    {
        "question": "31,757,094 ÷ 428,547=？",
        "answer": 1.869842295324464
    },
    {
        "question": "2,914 × 212,581=？",
        "answer": 8.792013993115608
    },
    {
        "question": "332,690 × 200=？",
        "answer": 7.823069742700256
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 261=？",
        "answer": 3.796851749049887
    },
    {
        "question": "2,558 × 211,112=？",
        "answer": 8.732413460260634
    },
    {
        "question": "247,766,617 ÷ 6,647=？",
        "answer": 4.571417112251586
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 760=？",
        "answer": 4.719662683018047
    },
    {
        "question": "5,549,415 ÷ 4,214=？",
        "answer": 3.119552672451924
    },
    {
        "question": "261 × 3,091=？",
        "answer": 5.906739512401586
    },
    {
        "question": "118,270,947 ÷ 9,659,348=？",
        "answer": 1.087930261440856
    },
    {
        "question": "346,891,319 ÷ 1,953=？",
        "answer": 5.249491188414768
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 569,992=？",
        "answer": 6.4548387646045855
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 40,889,204=？",
        "answer": 7.611608656121162
    },
    {
        "question": "27,171,194 ÷ 98,212=？",
        "answer": 2.4419441681455316
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 2,930,178=？",
        "answer": 8.191169872913846
    },
    {
        "question": "35,144 ÷ 521=？",
        "answer": 1.8290134669577396
    },
    {
        "question": "423,960 ÷ 209,390=？",
        "answer": 0.3063689465814905
    },
    {
        "question": "3,822 ÷ 2,957=？",
        "answer": 0.1114393581928764
    },
    {
        "question": "396,505,725 ÷ 1,020=？",
        "answer": 5.589649290554906
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 870,177=？",
        "answer": 6.939607600095412
    },
    {
        "question": "82,776,257 ÷ 1,286=？",
        "answer": 4.808664815870863
    },
    {
        "question": "885,424 ÷ 570=？",
        "answer": 3.191276433967517
    },
    {
        "question": "163,069,589 ÷ 448,010=？",
        "answer": 2.561085268644594
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 311=？",
        "answer": 3.5341530741850624
    },
    {
        "question": "379,581,593 ÷ 11,190=？",
        "answer": 4.530475057552636
    },
    {
        "question": "6,122,857 ÷ 15,491=？",
        "answer": 2.596874662617176
    },
    {
        "question": "463 × 71,896=？",
        "answer": 7.5222857197005375
    },
    {
        "question": "6,857 × 858=？",
        "answer": 6.76962143731408
    },
    {
        "question": "138,992,182 ÷ 84,558=？",
        "answer": 3.215835670533651
    },
    {
        "question": "37,382 ÷ 7,243=？",
        "answer": 0.7127440479503881
    },
    {
        "question": "311,727,088 ÷ 3,899,517=？",
        "answer": 1.9027637246025222
    },
    {
        "question": "193,120,712 ÷ 595=？",
        "answer": 5.511311888190327
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 4,716,609=？",
        "answer": 8.053841117071004
    },
    {
        "question": "899 × 128,252=？",
        "answer": 8.061823838087774
    },
    {
        "question": "152,513,134 ÷ 6,608,099=？",
        "answer": 1.3632307047123724
    },
    {
        "question": "989 × 745=？",
        "answer": 5.867352564345472
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 2,274,264=？",
        "answer": 7.9479054838638685
    },
    {
        "question": "566 × 2,473=？",
        "answer": 6.1460405475495685
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 11,057=？",
        "answer": 5.520758564312233
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 24,849=？",
        "answer": 6.1113122597133875
    },
    {
        "question": "21,674,168 ÷ 796=？",
        "answer": 4.435029367594245
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 14,289,625=？",
        "answer": 7.155020831830322
    },
    {
        "question": "8,452,546 ÷ 1,718=？",
        "answer": 3.6919643834435365
    },
    {
        "question": "732,135 ÷ 87,706=？",
        "answer": 0.92156186433829
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 4,969=？",
        "answer": 4.975022597698362
    },
    {
        "question": "331,148,944 ÷ 428,578=？",
        "answer": 2.887993500628171
    },
    {
        "question": "3,847 × 54,173=？",
        "answer": 8.31890507298077
    },
    {
        "question": "6,290,022 ÷ 10,257=？",
        "answer": 2.787631808921364
    },
    {
        "question": "156,684,449 ÷ 29,123,008=？",
        "answer": 0.7307896651780763
    },
    {
        "question": "197,981 ÷ 7,490=？",
        "answer": 1.422141695839381
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 500,260,455=？",
        "answer": 8.699196173772739
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,285=？",
        "answer": 3.631950826259217
    },
    {
        "question": "763,288,942 ÷ 459,491,859=？",
        "answer": 0.22041114944814164
    },
    {
        "question": "3,742 ÷ 939=？",
        "answer": 0.6004381908978802
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 21,750=？",
        "answer": 4.814580516010318
    },
    {
        "question": "16,473 ÷ 1,100=？",
        "answer": 1.175380013270814
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 645,060=？",
        "answer": 7.549962801737271
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 679=？",
        "answer": 2.8318697742805017
    },
    {
        "question": "565 × 1,491,131=？",
        "answer": 8.925564246924996
    },
    {
        "question": "896,366 ÷ 103,795=？",
        "answer": 0.9363089417440639
    },
    {
        "question": "755,584,672 ÷ 1,497=？",
        "answer": 5.703061338777919
    },
    {
        "question": "122,708,650 ÷ 21,373,717=？",
        "answer": 0.7589951233800318
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 352=？",
        "answer": 4.475961589192424
    },
    {
        "question": "604,644 ÷ 568,631=？",
        "answer": 0.026669215252356684
    },
    {
        "question": "3,362,484 ÷ 7,295=？",
        "answer": 2.6636349302447138
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,568,964=？",
        "answer": 6.496642974444853
    },
    {
        "question": "5,763 × 50,909=？",
        "answer": 8.467443185902779
    },
    {
        "question": "933,553,213 ÷ 3,307=？",
        "answer": 5.450704883079599
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 36,092=？",
        "answer": 5.460500935687566
    },
    {
        "question": "39,200 ÷ 27,270=？",
        "answer": 0.15760092907882736
    },
    {
        "question": "62,138,126 ÷ 20,680=？",
        "answer": 3.477807616973209
    },
    {
        "question": "69,176,364 ÷ 24,426,634=？",
        "answer": 0.4520941060513103
    },
    {
        "question": "19,433,169 ÷ 135,185=？",
        "answer": 2.1576151221433233
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 343=？",
        "answer": 4.4491079724264875
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 407,503,874=？",
        "answer": 8.61013174178477
    },
    {
        "question": "9,011 × 690=？",
        "answer": 6.793622080426973
    },
    {
        "question": "472,129 ÷ 4,088=？",
        "answer": 2.0625497901806087
    },
    {
        "question": "176 × 207,216=？",
        "answer": 7.561935953846005
    },
    {
        "question": "96,383 × 355=？",
        "answer": 7.534228793002945
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 978=？",
        "answer": 4.949380247108695
    },
    {
        "question": "213 × 917,297=？",
        "answer": 8.290889576597946
    },
    {
        "question": "1,156,074 ÷ 957,356=？",
        "answer": 0.08191217058526641
    },
    {
        "question": "52,605 ÷ 476=？",
        "answer": 2.0434200722166906
    },
    {
        "question": "980,809,195 ÷ 277,008,660=？",
        "answer": 0.5490911822318139
    },
    {
        "question": "119,461 × 4,704=？",
        "answer": 8.749693458944263
    },
    {
        "question": "10,446,444 ÷ 261=？",
        "answer": 4.602327973156768
    },
    {
        "question": "312,569,670 ÷ 3,759,987=？",
        "answer": 1.9197604908625843
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 144,904=？",
        "answer": 6.794548829690861
    },
    {
        "question": "10,959 × 228=？",
        "answer": 6.397705773932033
    },
    {
        "question": "335,465,257 ÷ 306,872,064=？",
        "answer": 0.03869019405372073
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 3,996,741=？",
        "answer": 7.300676010010355
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,691,966=？",
        "answer": 7.1290395747075594
    },
    {
        "question": "27,125 × 1,486=？",
        "answer": 7.6053885562811425
    },
    {
        "question": "9,893,633 ÷ 2,175,188=？",
        "answer": 0.6578589976769474
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 118,881=？",
        "answer": 6.791115793253312
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 424,162=？",
        "answer": 7.367894447664562
    },
    {
        "question": "843,935 ÷ 1,102=？",
        "answer": 2.8841274039719718
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 264,570=？",
        "answer": 5.422540597322725
    },
    {
        "question": "131,245 × 1,437=？",
        "answer": 8.275539535345386
    },
    {
        "question": "158,163,193 ÷ 1,325=？",
        "answer": 5.076889545662299
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 217=？",
        "answer": 4.2449447527271795
    },
    {
        "question": "138,687 ÷ 46,952=？",
        "answer": 0.4703816573373001
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,779,828=？",
        "answer": 7.204620544186334
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,943=？",
        "answer": 3.899984562549391
    },
    {
        "question": "189,142,629 ÷ 81,587,844=？",
        "answer": 0.36516396441602766
    },
    {
        "question": "4,875 × 4,339=？",
        "answer": 7.325364270163767
    },
    {
        "question": "12,122 ÷ 884=？",
        "answer": 1.1371220146609182
    },
    {
        "question": "701,955 ÷ 1,190=？",
        "answer": 2.7707623104550825
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 535=？",
        "answer": 3.807535028068853
    },
    {
        "question": "189,295,197 ÷ 161,755=？",
        "answer": 3.068281880718641
    },
    {
        "question": "13,724,665 ÷ 1,366=？",
        "answer": 4.002051053381205
    },
    {
        "question": "6,936 × 39,874=？",
        "answer": 8.441798888999154
    },
    {
        "question": "7,049,551 ÷ 6,232,965=？",
        "answer": 0.05346676858541891
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 200=？",
        "answer": 2.3010299956639813
    },
    {
        "question": "137,871,979 ÷ 7,477=？",
        "answer": 4.2657486288051665
    },
    {
        "question": "2,002 × 6,301=？",
        "answer": 7.100873552758427
    },
    {
        "question": "342,711 ÷ 24,145=？",
        "answer": 1.1521008344735792
    },
    {
        "question": "49,031,229 ÷ 552,298=？",
        "answer": 1.9482993087145983
    },
    {
        "question": "617,606 ÷ 32,685=？",
        "answer": 1.2763630171873912
    },
    {
        "question": "110 × 11,551=？",
        "answer": 6.104012269012567
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 25,570=？",
        "answer": 6.220644084669191
    },
    {
        "question": "115,074,394 ÷ 810,863=？",
        "answer": 2.152031212667247
    },
    {
        "question": "137 × 66,068=？",
        "answer": 6.956711727270149
    },
    {
        "question": "16,345,180 ÷ 10,381=？",
        "answer": 3.1971505165336636
    },
    {
        "question": "174,200 ÷ 89,366=？",
        "answer": 0.2898758312152293
    },
    {
        "question": "2,392 × 234=？",
        "answer": 5.747977032726516
    },
    {
        "question": "552 × 22,374=？",
        "answer": 7.091682711474149
    },
    {
        "question": "1,136,854 ÷ 3,365=？",
        "answer": 2.5287196256214135
    },
    {
        "question": "3,459,584 ÷ 406=？",
        "answer": 3.9304978463236115
    },
    {
        "question": "426,062,440 ÷ 25,344=？",
        "answer": 4.225598090273864
    },
    {
        "question": "523,902,973 ÷ 116,706=？",
        "answer": 3.6521576787157786
    },
    {
        "question": "1,159 ÷ 244=？",
        "answer": 0.6766936096248666
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 282=？",
        "answer": 2.450249108319361
    },
    {
        "question": "172,107 ÷ 1,849=？",
        "answer": 1.9688616233145186
    },
    {
        "question": "5,095,790 ÷ 36,241=？",
        "answer": 2.148011349525146
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 83,809=？",
        "answer": 5.877533168170562
    },
    {
        "question": "3,296 ÷ 314=？",
        "answer": 1.0210575549518632
    },
    {
        "question": "283,139,664 ÷ 1,908=？",
        "answer": 5.171422341984382
    },
    {
        "question": "81,290,174 ÷ 13,248,319=？",
        "answer": 0.7878772764148521
    },
    {
        "question": "5,083 × 10,098=？",
        "answer": 7.710355476062171
    },
    {
        "question": "320,641 ÷ 1,353=？",
        "answer": 2.3747212577127312
    },
    {
        "question": "97,665 × 1,064=？",
        "answer": 8.016680582361607
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 264=？",
        "answer": 4.272862275588906
    },
    {
        "question": "7,028,853 ÷ 324=？",
        "answer": 4.336339450458652
    },
    {
        "question": "795,233,372 ÷ 1,799=？",
        "answer": 5.645463433611287
    },
    {
        "question": "268,892,741 ÷ 9,549=？",
        "answer": 4.44962118487298
    },
    {
        "question": "529,805 × 314=？",
        "answer": 8.221045700679506
    },
    {
        "question": "7,803,706 ÷ 5,164=？",
        "answer": 3.179314665649006
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,022=？",
        "answer": 3.3057811512549824
    },
    {
        "question": "292,026 ÷ 1,412=？",
        "answer": 2.315586823067731
    },
    {
        "question": "2,914,237 ÷ 60,967=？",
        "answer": 1.6794300425789672
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 933=？",
        "answer": 4.5931309341444
    },
    {
        "question": "869,347,585 ÷ 23,157=？",
        "answer": 4.574511156364005
    },
    {
        "question": "60,177 ÷ 927=？",
        "answer": 1.8123507989451504
    },
    {
        "question": "37,994,441 ÷ 4,031,307=？",
        "answer": 0.9742741866001853
    },
    {
        "question": "9,734,778 ÷ 1,546,228=？",
        "answer": 0.7990525184912782
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 153,378=？",
        "answer": 5.486793066073557
    },
    {
        "question": "1,733,130 ÷ 1,192=？",
        "answer": 3.1625548844390474
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 78,100=？",
        "answer": 4.8926510338773
    },
    {
        "question": "3,410,104 ÷ 2,819,848=？",
        "answer": 0.08254192522754404
    },
    {
        "question": "95,852 × 2,414=？",
        "answer": 8.36433844484189
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 790=？",
        "answer": 3.9390197764486663
    },
    {
        "question": "36,494 × 2,516=？",
        "answer": 7.9629321044875825
    },
    {
        "question": "1,813 × 12,065=？",
        "answer": 7.339925130340314
    },
    {
        "question": "3,086 ÷ 893=？",
        "answer": 0.538544462838583
    },
    {
        "question": "1,089 × 994=？",
        "answer": 6.034414264153089
    },
    {
        "question": "269,636,071 ÷ 29,218=？",
        "answer": 3.9651275054503596
    },
    {
        "question": "313,370 ÷ 789=？",
        "answer": 2.598980414391929
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 2,155,418=？",
        "answer": 7.780689536692685
    },
    {
        "question": "399,707,530 ÷ 7,607=？",
        "answer": 4.720528913657938
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 3,176,362=？",
        "answer": 7.103989983081599
    },
    {
        "question": "293,991,173 ÷ 708,088=？",
        "answer": 2.618247056601162
    },
    {
        "question": "538,866 ÷ 20,837=？",
        "answer": 1.412645590721193
    },
    {
        "question": "62,538 ÷ 19,337=？",
        "answer": 0.509754890921558
    },
    {
        "question": "2,234,669 × 369=？",
        "answer": 8.916239570531156
    },
    {
        "question": "8,258 × 3,035=？",
        "answer": 7.39903357394996
    },
    {
        "question": "36,126,747 ÷ 422=？",
        "answer": 4.932516406716145
    },
    {
        "question": "9,892,339 ÷ 73,983=？",
        "answer": 2.1261670528419003
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 35,721,906=？",
        "answer": 8.251904627654396
    },
    {
        "question": "864,493 ÷ 104,206=？",
        "answer": 0.9188687554378406
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 534=？",
        "answer": 3.727541257028556
    },
    {
        "question": "2,797,570 ÷ 2,129=？",
        "answer": 3.118605300690892
    },
    {
        "question": "18,872,647 ÷ 855=？",
        "answer": 4.343866702070162
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,196,922=？",
        "answer": 7.049098652836799
    },
    {
        "question": "150,624,186 ÷ 1,839=？",
        "answer": 4.91331298368227
    },
    {
        "question": "17,747,525 ÷ 3,445,753=？",
        "answer": 0.7118536536768857
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 10,999=？",
        "answer": 4.041353202046975
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 282,146=？",
        "answer": 5.927595152351625
    },
    {
        "question": "2,063 × 261=？",
        "answer": 5.731139735311433
    },
    {
        "question": "167,636,669 ÷ 6,263,059=？",
        "answer": 1.4275825197501455
    },
    {
        "question": "184 × 39,000=？",
        "answer": 6.8558824300360355
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 13,676=？",
        "answer": 5.928350781622811
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 49,669=？",
        "answer": 5.997115411973805
    },
    {
        "question": "98,249 ÷ 8,235=？",
        "answer": 1.0766645352191255
    },
    {
        "question": "11,589,988 ÷ 1,625=？",
        "answer": 3.8532296209906804
    },
    {
        "question": "918 × 424=？",
        "answer": 5.590208537793975
    },
    {
        "question": "149 × 173,992=？",
        "answer": 7.413715548673449
    },
    {
        "question": "476,070,102 ÷ 114,873,971=？",
        "answer": 0.6174492737530967
    },
    {
        "question": "73 × 8,333=？",
        "answer": 5.7841242419461105
    },
    {
        "question": "35,665 ÷ 1,717=？",
        "answer": 1.3174719331957856
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 4,985=？",
        "answer": 4.4758164130313185
    },
    {
        "question": "1,122,278 ÷ 8,360=？",
        "answer": 2.1278941720936158
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 372=？",
        "answer": 4.183326796601633
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 614,802=？",
        "answer": 7.8057686109234155
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 24,217=？",
        "answer": 4.861241596493545
    },
    {
        "question": "915,221,966 ÷ 17,947,608=？",
        "answer": 1.707519859574317
    },
    {
        "question": "804,813,230 ÷ 12,613,535=？",
        "answer": 1.8048582903459525
    },
    {
        "question": "11,558 ÷ 996=？",
        "answer": 1.0646233517066654
    },
    {
        "question": "39,302,874 ÷ 22,794,911=？",
        "answer": 0.23658640817969323
    },
    {
        "question": "29,787 × 351=？",
        "answer": 7.019333881881153
    },
    {
        "question": "52,134,868 ÷ 1,396=？",
        "answer": 4.572242860003248
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 8,199=？",
        "answer": 5.1690333915156295
    },
    {
        "question": "790,280,821 ÷ 302=？",
        "answer": 6.417774499395919
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 24,861=？",
        "answer": 5.5416466292416
    },
    {
        "question": "10,497 ÷ 286=？",
        "answer": 1.564699164073526
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 733=？",
        "answer": 4.263043983313166
    },
    {
        "question": "2,408,628 ÷ 43,578=？",
        "answer": 1.7425024361206
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 546,351,506=？",
        "answer": 8.737472144532832
    },
    {
        "question": "426,943,184 ÷ 19,882,561=？",
        "answer": 1.331897761038089
    },
    {
        "question": "184,070,555 ÷ 3,008,437=？",
        "answer": 1.7866434004648084
    },
    {
        "question": "429,159,505 ÷ 207,569,853=？",
        "answer": 0.3154544579386932
    },
    {
        "question": "1,035 × 7,495=？",
        "answer": 6.889711986977235
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 77,672,880=？",
        "answer": 8.191299404139222
    },
    {
        "question": "1,135,345 ÷ 1,770=？",
        "answer": 2.807154585325139
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,988=？",
        "answer": 3.998956440470486
    },
    {
        "question": "202,537 ÷ 23,029=？",
        "answer": 0.9442292930909614
    },
    {
        "question": "106,781 ÷ 5,892=？",
        "answer": 1.2582312455216313
    },
    {
        "question": "113,605 × 633=？",
        "answer": 7.856801156045728
    },
    {
        "question": "42,232 × 16,641=？",
        "answer": 8.8468210695914
    },
    {
        "question": "76,995,103 ÷ 62,839,781=？",
        "answer": 0.08822844146209302
    },
    {
        "question": "6,238,476 ÷ 12,053=？",
        "answer": 2.7139833520910424
    },
    {
        "question": "817 × 29,775=？",
        "answer": 7.38607382668723
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 23,875=？",
        "answer": 6.332185889695109
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 73,539,970=？",
        "answer": 8.343644703085833
    },
    {
        "question": "27,355 × 226=？",
        "answer": 6.791145158260889
    },
    {
        "question": "135,458 × 1,146=？",
        "answer": 8.190989276710837
    },
    {
        "question": "46,451 ÷ 39,797=？",
        "answer": 0.06714473287386048
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,122,683=？",
        "answer": 7.046209559867273
    },
    {
        "question": "58,813 ÷ 1,144=？",
        "answer": 1.7110473084940148
    },
    {
        "question": "255,261,500 ÷ 9,313,641=？",
        "answer": 1.4378658231923924
    },
    {
        "question": "3,654 × 925=？",
        "answer": 6.5289102757555515
    },
    {
        "question": "1,226,890 ÷ 7,387=？",
        "answer": 2.2203375276550608
    },
    {
        "question": "412,731,603 ÷ 459=？",
        "answer": 5.95385503869037
    },
    {
        "question": "3,483 × 862=？",
        "answer": 6.477460740282949
    },
    {
        "question": "16,499 ÷ 508=？",
        "answer": 1.5115939102546614
    },
    {
        "question": "355,518 × 2,730=？",
        "answer": 8.987024241143882
    },
    {
        "question": "105 × 3,886,178=？",
        "answer": 8.610711987934668
    },
    {
        "question": "214 × 752,467=？",
        "answer": 8.206901231725155
    },
    {
        "question": "111,427,583 ÷ 433,039=？",
        "answer": 2.4104656990594395
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 8,244,143=？",
        "answer": 7.69429676667523
    },
    {
        "question": "170,877 × 354=？",
        "answer": 7.781686872755321
    },
    {
        "question": "112,147,332 ÷ 13,216=？",
        "answer": 3.9286889161418737
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 664,993=？",
        "answer": 6.96894510943642
    },
    {
        "question": "303,012,552 ÷ 663=？",
        "answer": 5.659947090696306
    },
    {
        "question": "125,630 ÷ 4,032=？",
        "answer": 1.4935728363356309
    },
    {
        "question": "167,309 ÷ 5,148=？",
        "answer": 1.5118807652238102
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,083=？",
        "answer": 3.636688447953283
    },
    {
        "question": "616,138 × 219=？",
        "answer": 8.130122109352387
    },
    {
        "question": "87,528,687 ÷ 19,171,888=？",
        "answer": 0.6594855305253692
    },
    {
        "question": "158,394 ÷ 330=？",
        "answer": 2.681224786515459
    },
    {
        "question": "127,865,452 ÷ 1,013=？",
        "answer": 5.101143772827941
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 1,523,748=？",
        "answer": 7.329041184270528
    },
    {
        "question": "59,580 × 618=？",
        "answer": 7.56608897396784
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 329,825=？",
        "answer": 6.995404825829724
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 389,178=？",
        "answer": 6.0672695366020735
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 4,926=？",
        "answer": 4.6924944075030846
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,310,721=？",
        "answer": 6.816480261963967
    },
    {
        "question": "116,982,327 ÷ 533=？",
        "answer": 5.341393047026274
    },
    {
        "question": "47,198 × 492=？",
        "answer": 7.365888698703002
    },
    {
        "question": "1,010 × 1,146=？",
        "answer": 6.063505991414014
    },
    {
        "question": "1,669 × 10,087=？",
        "answer": 7.226218357507493
    },
    {
        "question": "1,343 ÷ 550=？",
        "answer": 0.38771332317447155
    },
    {
        "question": "408,366,914 ÷ 804=？",
        "answer": 5.7057944994330585
    },
    {
        "question": "605 × 69,311=？",
        "answer": 7.622557539425821
    },
    {
        "question": "257 × 91,267=？",
        "answer": 7.370246898580856
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,813=？",
        "answer": 3.860457795423471
    },
    {
        "question": "3,964 × 330=？",
        "answer": 6.116647585691125
    },
    {
        "question": "862,862 × 325=？",
        "answer": 8.447824704282906
    },
    {
        "question": "12,726 × 466=？",
        "answer": 6.773077835590206
    },
    {
        "question": "315,302 × 344=？",
        "answer": 8.03528516811236
    },
    {
        "question": "202 × 233,813=？",
        "answer": 7.674220023711743
    },
    {
        "question": "453,955 × 621=？",
        "answer": 8.450104404090286
    },
    {
        "question": "4,312 × 100,883=？",
        "answer": 8.638496740732538
    },
    {
        "question": "195 × 7,579=？",
        "answer": 6.169646518428369
    },
    {
        "question": "16,871,871 ÷ 765=？",
        "answer": 4.343501811034763
    },
    {
        "question": "163,499,016 ÷ 5,629,083=？",
        "answer": 1.46307749093724
    },
    {
        "question": "40,200 ÷ 11,476=？",
        "answer": 0.5444355135105092
    },
    {
        "question": "54,709,056 ÷ 1,916=？",
        "answer": 4.4556637163861055
    },
    {
        "question": "737,028 × 634=？",
        "answer": 8.669573245082038
    },
    {
        "question": "85,112,810 ÷ 182,790=？",
        "answer": 2.6680424961433453
    },
    {
        "question": "16,097 × 25,900=？",
        "answer": 8.620044708135
    },
    {
        "question": "1,300 × 2,945=？",
        "answer": 6.583028651429958
    },
    {
        "question": "3,679,245 ÷ 168,112=？",
        "answer": 1.3401599934410078
    },
    {
        "question": "42,038 × 10,179=？",
        "answer": 8.631347160217048
    },
    {
        "question": "2,365 × 30,755=？",
        "answer": 7.861746876433597
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 221,429=？",
        "answer": 6.623988099678015
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 1,205=？",
        "answer": 4.625055091261163
    },
    {
        "question": "404,296 × 330=？",
        "answer": 8.1252133844356
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 21,396=？",
        "answer": 6.520664287393271
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 163,934=？",
        "answer": 6.7461479528643675
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 3,891,078=？",
        "answer": 8.639287959367026
    },
    {
        "question": "207,953,329 ÷ 42,151=？",
        "answer": 3.6931579947312696
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 27,331=？",
        "answer": 4.913776776882016
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 883=？",
        "answer": 3.7241119539612124
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,028,543=？",
        "answer": 6.857320492848454
    },
    {
        "question": "4,982,964 ÷ 1,239=？",
        "answer": 3.6044164431955905
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 492,034=？",
        "answer": 6.595085100942638
    },
    {
        "question": "919 ÷ 474=？",
        "answer": 0.2875371697120262
    },
    {
        "question": "246,937,860 ÷ 857,602=？",
        "answer": 2.4593018950039416
    },
    {
        "question": "1,645 × 13,586=？",
        "answer": 7.349257512540701
    },
    {
        "question": "5,342 × 358=？",
        "answer": 6.281586910329229
    },
    {
        "question": "17,283 ÷ 3,338=？",
        "answer": 0.7141327976029611
    },
    {
        "question": "559,555,667 ÷ 2,852,171=？",
        "answer": 2.292667738698309
    },
    {
        "question": "439 ÷ 376=？",
        "answer": 0.06727667531446034
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 571,756,138=？",
        "answer": 8.757210835605365
    },
    {
        "question": "1,037,037 ÷ 363=？",
        "answer": 3.455887626636602
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 5,267=？",
        "answer": 5.0437826130914
    },
    {
        "question": "3,014 × 187,299=？",
        "answer": 8.751678706637133
    },
    {
        "question": "184,208,850 ÷ 6,748,727=？",
        "answer": 1.4360886309152283
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 201=？",
        "answer": 4.189686782592971
    },
    {
        "question": "77,197,014 ÷ 6,642=？",
        "answer": 4.065301630777994
    },
    {
        "question": "33,247 ÷ 1,134=？",
        "answer": 1.4671394088498764
    },
    {
        "question": "15,985 ÷ 1,930=？",
        "answer": 0.918155331599933
    },
    {
        "question": "1,733,169 ÷ 2,170=？",
        "answer": 2.902381178657045
    },
    {
        "question": "328,292,424 ÷ 1,697,194=？",
        "answer": 2.2865293728778404
    },
    {
        "question": "634,998,342 ÷ 672,932=？",
        "answer": 2.974801410496472
    },
    {
        "question": "91,336,189 ÷ 45,098=？",
        "answer": 3.3064856044514657
    },
    {
        "question": "406,833 ÷ 456=？",
        "answer": 2.950451330535714
    },
    {
        "question": "272,330,579 ÷ 32,552,086=？",
        "answer": 0.9225175851915799
    },
    {
        "question": "9,812,002 ÷ 213=？",
        "answer": 4.663378024618733
    },
    {
        "question": "455 ÷ 365=？",
        "answer": 0.09571853220063774
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 485,376,344=？",
        "answer": 8.68607860611084
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,385=？",
        "answer": 4.106190897263415
    },
    {
        "question": "142,493 × 417=？",
        "answer": 7.773929585030259
    },
    {
        "question": "953,744 ÷ 11,140=？",
        "answer": 1.9325466279888306
    },
    {
        "question": "684,621 × 551=？",
        "answer": 8.576601815365946
    },
    {
        "question": "133,304 ÷ 76,691=？",
        "answer": 0.24009878059098658
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 263=？",
        "answer": 3.6240757311456826
    },
    {
        "question": "464 ÷ 381=？",
        "answer": 0.08559300487926157
    },
    {
        "question": "540 × 1,309,857=？",
        "answer": 8.84961764517277
    },
    {
        "question": "207,920 × 2,555=？",
        "answer": 8.725287170963687
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,884=？",
        "answer": 3.752202153176521
    },
    {
        "question": "235 × 3,476,471=？",
        "answer": 8.912206473213994
    },
    {
        "question": "450,772 × 2,104=？",
        "answer": 8.977002667205468
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 959=？",
        "answer": 4.781159156624246
    },
    {
        "question": "4,210,658 ÷ 28,744=？",
        "answer": 2.16580276419005
    },
    {
        "question": "996,716 ÷ 384=？",
        "answer": 3.414240205555834
    },
    {
        "question": "37,230 ÷ 20,687=？",
        "answer": 0.25519552176881605
    },
    {
        "question": "1,507,377 ÷ 251,006=？",
        "answer": 0.7785377814954936
    },
    {
        "question": "136 × 1,836,162=？",
        "answer": 8.397449903646292
    },
    {
        "question": "536,368 × 593=？",
        "answer": 8.502517553077052
    },
    {
        "question": "4,569,272 ÷ 4,473,753=？",
        "answer": 0.009175008916459167
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,702,343=？",
        "answer": 6.2310470692616295
    },
    {
        "question": "22,025,681 ÷ 9,712=？",
        "answer": 3.3556206712743557
    },
    {
        "question": "7,741 × 8,380=？",
        "answer": 7.812041086086957
    },
    {
        "question": "149,112 ÷ 3,940=？",
        "answer": 1.578016373499147
    },
    {
        "question": "74,153,037 ÷ 860=？",
        "answer": 4.935630491380871
    },
    {
        "question": "148,139,489 ÷ 690,774=？",
        "answer": 2.331334859420543
    },
    {
        "question": "33,774 ÷ 3,637=？",
        "answer": 0.9678391979891339
    },
    {
        "question": "398,005 ÷ 6,258=？",
        "answer": 1.8034529691900705
    },
    {
        "question": "515,810,346 ÷ 34,594,744=？",
        "answer": 1.1734799276775458
    },
    {
        "question": "67,414,557 ÷ 64,559,290=？",
        "answer": 0.018794939469873935
    },
    {
        "question": "40,498 × 538=？",
        "answer": 7.338215851710412
    },
    {
        "question": "88,587,234 ÷ 34,067,888=？",
        "answer": 0.41502593091029966
    },
    {
        "question": "11,391,001 ÷ 2,899=？",
        "answer": 3.594313674630567
    },
    {
        "question": "81,272 × 4,605=？",
        "answer": 8.573170581849084
    },
    {
        "question": "2,359 × 995=？",
        "answer": 6.370551021631321
    },
    {
        "question": "15,124,776 ÷ 523=？",
        "answer": 4.461187262544219
    },
    {
        "question": "977,791 ÷ 31,913=？",
        "answer": 1.4862784033007512
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 748=？",
        "answer": 4.564097677892975
    },
    {
        "question": "22,080 ÷ 1,114=？",
        "answer": 1.2971138782194511
    },
    {
        "question": "11,102,577 ÷ 1,067=？",
        "answer": 4.017259374405855
    },
    {
        "question": "336,747,484 ÷ 14,268=？",
        "answer": 4.37294125892099
    },
    {
        "question": "14,988,101 ÷ 3,354=？",
        "answer": 3.6501835527326167
    },
    {
        "question": "449 × 1,806=？",
        "answer": 5.90896408698081
    },
    {
        "question": "10,376 ÷ 3,056=？",
        "answer": 0.5308766131723713
    },
    {
        "question": "117,390,103 ÷ 55,813=？",
        "answer": 3.3228961168063575
    },
    {
        "question": "1,463,680 ÷ 3,841=？",
        "answer": 2.5810018314254597
    },
    {
        "question": "1,197 × 2,877=？",
        "answer": 6.537034012296736
    },
    {
        "question": "115,361 ÷ 2,788=？",
        "answer": 1.6167662426217084
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,854,303=？",
        "answer": 7.113278740953363
    },
    {
        "question": "63,431,539 ÷ 28,121=？",
        "answer": 3.3532744881419223
    },
    {
        "question": "285,846 × 1,742=？",
        "answer": 8.697180269943356
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 10,465,038=？",
        "answer": 8.019740809660883
    },
    {
        "question": "676,871 × 267=？",
        "answer": 8.257017168858535
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 22,403,429=？",
        "answer": 8.049284499536554
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 4,744=？",
        "answer": 5.091118028327024
    },
    {
        "question": "9,202,128 ÷ 2,978=？",
        "answer": 3.4899635765153434
    },
    {
        "question": "69,535 ÷ 1,395=？",
        "answer": 1.6976292513795725
    },
    {
        "question": "116 × 301,998=？",
        "answer": 7.544462056052149
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 24,804=？",
        "answer": 4.8716429773945755
    },
    {
        "question": "8,327,683 ÷ 1,911=？",
        "answer": 3.6392634979908127
    },
    {
        "question": "183,946 × 796=？",
        "answer": 8.16560341605151
    },
    {
        "question": "850,029,359 ÷ 145,530=？",
        "answer": 3.7664813966409185
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 153,681=？",
        "answer": 7.186620177810619
    },
    {
        "question": "1,311 × 3,389=？",
        "answer": 6.647674260527462
    },
    {
        "question": "2,711,862 ÷ 309=？",
        "answer": 3.943309106152422
    },
    {
        "question": "15,436,518 ÷ 1,762=？",
        "answer": 3.942543439596784
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 237,011=？",
        "answer": 6.736496338687782
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 34,790,995=？",
        "answer": 7.541466849467055
    },
    {
        "question": "1,771 × 100,723=？",
        "answer": 8.251347213794672
    },
    {
        "question": "42,949,373 ÷ 1,864,275=？",
        "answer": 1.3624468524217899
    },
    {
        "question": "1,258,644 ÷ 322=？",
        "answer": 3.592047038158979
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 11,751=？",
        "answer": 5.682858682987264
    },
    {
        "question": "33,825 × 230=？",
        "answer": 6.890965641287253
    },
    {
        "question": "5,552 × 4,949=？",
        "answer": 7.438966911257955
    },
    {
        "question": "2,317 × 1,889=？",
        "answer": 6.641157991711809
    },
    {
        "question": "391 ÷ 328=？",
        "answer": 0.07630291368418775
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,205,794=？",
        "answer": 6.984363105488457
    },
    {
        "question": "4,505,003 ÷ 21,934=？",
        "answer": 2.3125772453894355
    },
    {
        "question": "52,199,744 ÷ 687=？",
        "answer": 4.880711636064168
    },
    {
        "question": "711,965,872 ÷ 8,481=？",
        "answer": 4.924012113071904
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 4,073,974=？",
        "answer": 7.610018253016487
    },
    {
        "question": "37,506,646 ÷ 9,861=？",
        "answer": 3.580187270670176
    },
    {
        "question": "743 ÷ 343=？",
        "answer": 0.33569469371780475
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,238,440=？",
        "answer": 6.092874970711823
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,762,940=？",
        "answer": 7.360180884054637
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 700=？",
        "answer": 3.690196080028514
    },
    {
        "question": "2,331 × 703=？",
        "answer": 6.214497598540401
    },
    {
        "question": "26,841,514 ÷ 1,219=？",
        "answer": 4.342803303020951
    },
    {
        "question": "1,010,562 ÷ 212=？",
        "answer": 3.6782271025750912
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 181,160,510=？",
        "answer": 8.559093530295092
    },
    {
        "question": "1,692 ÷ 682=？",
        "answer": 0.3946159840465258
    },
    {
        "question": "1,660 ÷ 374=？",
        "answer": 0.6472364858395749
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 400=？",
        "answer": 4.488550716500444
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 13,779=？",
        "answer": 6.093460209576911
    },
    {
        "question": "442 × 35,756=？",
        "answer": 7.198771197954726
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 59,007,140=？",
        "answer": 8.725147074894815
    },
    {
        "question": "8,301,859 ÷ 373=？",
        "answer": 4.347466521174796
    },
    {
        "question": "203,528,864 ÷ 1,026,828=？",
        "answer": 2.297128305888524
    },
    {
        "question": "5,967 × 92,938=？",
        "answer": 8.743949360190632
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 19,276,536=？",
        "answer": 8.947786825395301
    },
    {
        "question": "1,598 ÷ 660=？",
        "answer": 0.38403283943610395
    },
    {
        "question": "146,576,069 ÷ 533,172=？",
        "answer": 2.4391957362583105
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 35,029,266=？",
        "answer": 8.389529077260883
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 2,185=？",
        "answer": 4.907653165373436
    },
    {
        "question": "623,857,730 ÷ 4,192,335=？",
        "answer": 2.1726295817916843
    },
    {
        "question": "45,841 × 1,362=？",
        "answer": 7.795431190570675
    },
    {
        "question": "1,780 ÷ 372=？",
        "answer": 0.6798770624269965
    },
    {
        "question": "1,050,057 ÷ 358=？",
        "answer": 3.4673298477723278
    },
    {
        "question": "206,350 ÷ 140,664=？",
        "answer": 0.1664215101202099
    },
    {
        "question": "28,516,028 ÷ 868=？",
        "answer": 4.516569307300129
    },
    {
        "question": "953,522,082 ÷ 528,614=？",
        "answer": 3.256192094086407
    },
    {
        "question": "9,562 ÷ 416=？",
        "answer": 1.361455408733028
    },
    {
        "question": "18,386 ÷ 2,962=？",
        "answer": 0.7929022015954992
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 35,820,025=？",
        "answer": 8.934337126333448
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 5,077,100=？",
        "answer": 8.22412965735389
    },
    {
        "question": "133,873,275 ÷ 123,178=？",
        "answer": 3.036160739535362
    },
    {
        "question": "909 ÷ 271=？",
        "answer": 0.5255945923475618
    },
    {
        "question": "104,980,943 ÷ 14,408,374=？",
        "answer": 0.8624954965407358
    },
    {
        "question": "154,843,666 ÷ 29,852,383=？",
        "answer": 0.7149144400102964
    },
    {
        "question": "80,277,361 ÷ 11,430,394=？",
        "answer": 0.8465318866904726
    },
    {
        "question": "897,916,054 ÷ 35,930=？",
        "answer": 4.397778519252502
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 14,537,269=？",
        "answer": 8.902845516262744
    },
    {
        "question": "1,931 ÷ 925=？",
        "answer": 0.3196405410403621
    },
    {
        "question": "160,863,117 ÷ 2,801=？",
        "answer": 4.759143370828203
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 355=？",
        "answer": 3.0273496077747564
    },
    {
        "question": "454 ÷ 329=？",
        "answer": 0.13985995490712963
    },
    {
        "question": "5,409,636 ÷ 301,103=？",
        "answer": 1.2544529610004973
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 85,594,704=？",
        "answer": 8.233476890075604
    },
    {
        "question": "1,094 × 20,247=？",
        "answer": 7.345378004858463
    },
    {
        "question": "486,129,651 ÷ 27,281,834=？",
        "answer": 1.250878549173839
    },
    {
        "question": "6,941,984 ÷ 245=？",
        "answer": 4.452317524002881
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,410,827=？",
        "answer": 6.149473762477453
    },
    {
        "question": "19,024,678 ÷ 4,166=？",
        "answer": 3.659598049291771
    },
    {
        "question": "6,718,372 ÷ 516=？",
        "answer": 4.11461434567159
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 2,381,588=？",
        "answer": 7.376866633384171
    },
    {
        "question": "96 × 2,986,551=？",
        "answer": 8.457441168439237
    },
    {
        "question": "473,559,941 ÷ 53,095,344=？",
        "answer": 0.9503185188792587
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 70,625,020=？",
        "answer": 8.149988579477506
    },
    {
        "question": "4,118 × 290=？",
        "answer": 6.077084340180969
    },
    {
        "question": "114 × 119,980=？",
        "answer": 7.1360137089379085
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 1,028,850=？",
        "answer": 7.752714751408412
    },
    {
        "question": "13,734 × 571=？",
        "answer": 6.8944331513040344
    },
    {
        "question": "100,403 ÷ 254=？",
        "answer": 2.5969129729219382
    },
    {
        "question": "4,474 × 434=？",
        "answer": 6.2881857092731215
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 22,361,512=？",
        "answer": 7.8266224202603425
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 1,059,036=？",
        "answer": 7.171038759086583
    },
    {
        "question": "8,206 × 45,942=？",
        "answer": 8.576341410108476
    },
    {
        "question": "355,494,433 ÷ 7,532,776=？",
        "answer": 1.6738777509856444
    },
    {
        "question": "29,888,949 ÷ 132,918=？",
        "answer": 2.351926846111811
    },
    {
        "question": "121,940 × 289=？",
        "answer": 7.547044033442449
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 11,862,711=？",
        "answer": 8.220311985903532
    },
    {
        "question": "696,724,283 ÷ 8,217=？",
        "answer": 4.928347660333046
    },
    {
        "question": "146,642,916 ÷ 63,059,557=？",
        "answer": 0.3665101725440981
    },
    {
        "question": "144,129 × 283=？",
        "answer": 7.610537808932485
    },
    {
        "question": "435,288,393 ÷ 2,327=？",
        "answer": 5.271980703527783
    },
    {
        "question": "2,005 ÷ 445=？",
        "answer": 0.6537543659752695
    },
    {
        "question": "217,174,113 ÷ 39,043,073=？",
        "answer": 0.7452640636424888
    },
    {
        "question": "174,347,592 ÷ 733,140=？",
        "answer": 2.376229038310278
    },
    {
        "question": "970 ÷ 359=？",
        "answer": 0.43167728568792574
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 16,828,508=？",
        "answer": 8.372173649212574
    },
    {
        "question": "934,502,349 ÷ 2,770,534=？",
        "answer": 2.5280169131834835
    },
    {
        "question": "194 × 57,882=？",
        "answer": 7.050345258838135
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 435=？",
        "answer": 3.1156105116742996
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,303,082=？",
        "answer": 6.362309401061727
    },
    {
        "question": "2,297 × 32,429=？",
        "answer": 7.8720945519106165
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,409=？",
        "answer": 3.3818367999983434
    },
    {
        "question": "17,402,144 ÷ 42,348=？",
        "answer": 2.6137698536455747
    },
    {
        "question": "2,209 × 747=？",
        "answer": 6.217516317686834
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 578,874=？",
        "answer": 7.7796173830612885
    },
    {
        "question": "6,502 × 76,068=？",
        "answer": 8.694248962979708
    },
    {
        "question": "1,271 × 175,757=？",
        "answer": 8.349058181547907
    },
    {
        "question": "102,472,509 ÷ 82,966=？",
        "answer": 3.0917072177058564
    },
    {
        "question": "1,945 × 466,217=？",
        "answer": 8.95750771112167
    },
    {
        "question": "352 × 97,002=？",
        "answer": 7.5333233521774625
    },
    {
        "question": "3,917 × 1,218=？",
        "answer": 6.678600859844723
    },
    {
        "question": "164 × 1,677=？",
        "answer": 5.439376910653784
    },
    {
        "question": "133 × 130,459=？",
        "answer": 7.239325686193364
    },
    {
        "question": "8,143,431 ÷ 359,309=？",
        "answer": 1.3553393253288661
    },
    {
        "question": "29,110 × 3,066=？",
        "answer": 7.950614355957167
    },
    {
        "question": "88,188 ÷ 6,034=？",
        "answer": 1.1648041875883024
    },
    {
        "question": "2,111,136 ÷ 35,552=？",
        "answer": 1.7736521743259146
    },
    {
        "question": "24,072 × 2,226=？",
        "answer": 7.729037334730713
    },
    {
        "question": "12,303,462 ÷ 41,760=？",
        "answer": 2.4692668422534894
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 23,222=？",
        "answer": 5.999368076303374
    },
    {
        "question": "66,293 ÷ 50,290=？",
        "answer": 0.11998603725035407
    },
    {
        "question": "1,146 × 96,424=？",
        "answer": 8.043369761184655
    },
    {
        "question": "135 × 262=？",
        "answer": 4.548635059814751
    },
    {
        "question": "397,205 ÷ 158,753=？",
        "answer": 0.3982927657123241
    },
    {
        "question": "110,836 ÷ 11,074=？",
        "answer": 1.000376324808386
    },
    {
        "question": "845,918,726 ÷ 531,607=？",
        "answer": 3.201737948056322
    },
    {
        "question": "581,250 ÷ 386,145=？",
        "answer": 0.177612550150962
    },
    {
        "question": "50,670,381 ÷ 649,039=？",
        "answer": 1.8924833760081046
    },
    {
        "question": "28,666 ÷ 2,871=？",
        "answer": 0.9993339040382849
    },
    {
        "question": "5,998,697 ÷ 261,650=？",
        "answer": 1.3603361867805306
    },
    {
        "question": "7,543 ÷ 540=？",
        "answer": 1.1451503478929754
    },
    {
        "question": "84,066,978 ÷ 50,733,058=？",
        "answer": 0.21933439512284986
    },
    {
        "question": "5,042 ÷ 3,957=？",
        "answer": 0.10523679107439934
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 39,719,346=？",
        "answer": 8.201062080322265
    },
    {
        "question": "1,590 × 74,512=？",
        "answer": 8.073623344909107
    },
    {
        "question": "6,003,100 ÷ 3,064=？",
        "answer": 3.292086816959103
    },
    {
        "question": "106,795 ÷ 93,745=？",
        "answer": 0.05660280666821424
    },
    {
        "question": "35,819,877 ÷ 6,534=？",
        "answer": 3.738944960075074
    },
    {
        "question": "10,649 × 1,656=？",
        "answer": 7.2463691594844075
    },
    {
        "question": "4,477 ÷ 2,373=？",
        "answer": 0.27568935616610607
    },
    {
        "question": "372,525 × 842=？",
        "answer": 8.496467514886573
    },
    {
        "question": "11,724,872 ÷ 3,605,093=？",
        "answer": 0.5121916376116415
    },
    {
        "question": "115,883 ÷ 51,088=？",
        "answer": 0.3557008285757481
    },
    {
        "question": "552,783 × 672=？",
        "answer": 8.569923951559407
    },
    {
        "question": "280 × 6,380=？",
        "answer": 6.251978710063382
    },
    {
        "question": "1,819 × 101,579=？",
        "answer": 8.266636632141418
    },
    {
        "question": "50,034 ÷ 29,727=？",
        "answer": 0.22611414108958522
    },
    {
        "question": "1,642 ÷ 1,217=？",
        "answer": 0.13008257455335695
    },
    {
        "question": "1,648,217 ÷ 686,312=？",
        "answer": 0.38049279672550923
    },
    {
        "question": "86 × 34,606=？",
        "answer": 6.473649854689061
    },
    {
        "question": "19,625,794 ÷ 577,585=？",
        "answer": 1.5312113300160712
    },
    {
        "question": "222,269 ÷ 2,849=？",
        "answer": 1.8921864463531215
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,652,097=？",
        "answer": 6.695156797297262
    },
    {
        "question": "6,018,616 ÷ 58,785=？",
        "answer": 2.0102301127994724
    },
    {
        "question": "114,443,515 ÷ 1,213,843=？",
        "answer": 1.9744286700199716
    },
    {
        "question": "8,665,116 ÷ 3,895,333=？",
        "answer": 0.34722979090276834
    },
    {
        "question": "573,887,699 ÷ 240=？",
        "answer": 6.378615674246929
    },
    {
        "question": "86,085,328 ÷ 342,683=？",
        "answer": 2.4000365782896678
    },
    {
        "question": "2,931,429 ÷ 1,130,250=？",
        "answer": 0.41390486421253064
    },
    {
        "question": "124 × 778,418=？",
        "answer": 7.984634555087344
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 863,485=？",
        "answer": 7.413376052357002
    },
    {
        "question": "13,296 × 40,062=？",
        "answer": 8.726453633057162
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 254,289,093=？",
        "answer": 8.882448987480903
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,216,144=？",
        "answer": 7.044567980777586
    },
    {
        "question": "39,710,187 ÷ 563=？",
        "answer": 4.848393537361791
    },
    {
        "question": "649 × 255,070=？",
        "answer": 8.218904078967123
    },
    {
        "question": "11,970,514 ÷ 175,664=？",
        "answer": 1.8334300311713518
    },
    {
        "question": "12,758 × 4,016=？",
        "answer": 7.7095763019514045
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 36,819=？",
        "answer": 6.043193243657361
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,513,928=？",
        "answer": 6.877474089863367
    },
    {
        "question": "484,274 × 1,523=？",
        "answer": 8.867791056339549
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 378,997=？",
        "answer": 7.11011468930953
    },
    {
        "question": "3,500,703 ÷ 3,323,249=？",
        "answer": 0.022592384000112913
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 1,142,265=？",
        "answer": 7.099159554993392
    },
    {
        "question": "14,393 × 290=？",
        "answer": 6.620549323291659
    },
    {
        "question": "244,522,664 ÷ 40,255=？",
        "answer": 3.7834992876713756
    },
    {
        "question": "7,602,175 ÷ 76,443=？",
        "answer": 1.9976001401500367
    },
    {
        "question": "413 × 92,748=？",
        "answer": 7.583254605001934
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 3,146=？",
        "answer": 4.776512319240097
    },
    {
        "question": "2,223 × 4,732=？",
        "answer": 7.021984198654883
    },
    {
        "question": "1,433 × 226,104=？",
        "answer": 8.510554435903082
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 125,308=？",
        "answer": 5.876130048791574
    },
    {
        "question": "222,085 ÷ 2,977=？",
        "answer": 1.8727403919016545
    },
    {
        "question": "138,135 × 281=？",
        "answer": 7.589010051930581
    },
    {
        "question": "16,706 × 46,635=？",
        "answer": 8.891584458168712
    },
    {
        "question": "10,871,555 ÷ 8,145=？",
        "answer": 3.1254005786818486
    },
    {
        "question": "23,313 × 32,596=？",
        "answer": 8.880762472811831
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 1,776,650=？",
        "answer": 8.069145815772616
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,474,453=？",
        "answer": 7.059731991399376
    },
    {
        "question": "2,089,046 ÷ 210=？",
        "answer": 3.997728708351328
    },
    {
        "question": "132,045,576 ÷ 5,952,872=？",
        "answer": 1.3459973110112011
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 34,196,295=？",
        "answer": 8.61316030098624
    },
    {
        "question": "3,023,494 ÷ 1,555,514=？",
        "answer": 0.2886351868861362
    },
    {
        "question": "4,424 ÷ 1,320=？",
        "answer": 0.5252411870907919
    },
    {
        "question": "57,486,886 ÷ 412=？",
        "answer": 5.144671568006043
    },
    {
        "question": "15,065,009 ÷ 573,797=？",
        "answer": 1.4192111221805948
    },
    {
        "question": "24,116 × 17,410=？",
        "answer": 8.623104046310646
    },
    {
        "question": "218,269 ÷ 10,473=？",
        "answer": 1.3189209551942862
    },
    {
        "question": "16,841,862 ÷ 17,806=？",
        "answer": 2.975823735440728
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 148,815=？",
        "answer": 6.515069389511253
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 576,506,398=？",
        "answer": 8.760804131406394
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 7,153,742=？",
        "answer": 7.331654527966662
    },
    {
        "question": "6,034,921 ÷ 833=？",
        "answer": 3.8600265879414715
    },
    {
        "question": "1,192,236 ÷ 1,753=？",
        "answer": 2.8325803152776206
    },
    {
        "question": "4,617 ÷ 2,206=？",
        "answer": 0.32075436644696936
    },
    {
        "question": "175,316,673 ÷ 60,291,896=？",
        "answer": 0.46356427907130415
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,286=？",
        "answer": 4.2948188094826865
    },
    {
        "question": "420,694 ÷ 342,161=？",
        "answer": 0.08973581156908872
    },
    {
        "question": "47,711,006 ÷ 207=？",
        "answer": 5.362648228420027
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 4,788,565=？",
        "answer": 8.127363418253243
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 114,787=？",
        "answer": 6.315165210691769
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 1,175=？",
        "answer": 4.7421357245434725
    },
    {
        "question": "3,484,554 ÷ 4,317=？",
        "answer": 2.906965150496766
    },
    {
        "question": "40,292 ÷ 276=？",
        "answer": 2.164309743213607
    },
    {
        "question": "163,811 × 451=？",
        "answer": 7.86851960339821
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 353=？",
        "answer": 2.8488047010518036
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 1,261=？",
        "answer": 4.179896332620706
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,027=？",
        "answer": 3.9089137400209713
    },
    {
        "question": "847 × 2,570=？",
        "answer": 6.337816533662002
    },
    {
        "question": "9,642,847 ÷ 1,527,521=？",
        "answer": 0.8002180864688877
    },
    {
        "question": "17,662 ÷ 7,152=？",
        "answer": 0.3926123746418848
    },
    {
        "question": "2,690,845 ÷ 191,294=？",
        "answer": 1.148187333489465
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 963=？",
        "answer": 2.9836262871245345
    },
    {
        "question": "4,436,994 ÷ 402,119=？",
        "answer": 1.0427342475654982
    },
    {
        "question": "51,148,455 ÷ 83,074=？",
        "answer": 2.7893673976847335
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 23,710=？",
        "answer": 5.918999598328464
    },
    {
        "question": "550,859,575 ÷ 67,387,490=？",
        "answer": 0.912461622318686
    },
    {
        "question": "14,537 × 835=？",
        "answer": 7.08416126592172
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 19,256,896=？",
        "answer": 8.761707539651926
    },
    {
        "question": "341 × 173,269=？",
        "answer": 7.771475247919752
    },
    {
        "question": "53,565,894 ÷ 64,305=？",
        "answer": 2.9206436149977812
    },
    {
        "question": "139 × 1,397,404=？",
        "answer": 8.288336782320725
    },
    {
        "question": "22,893,399 ÷ 742=？",
        "answer": 4.489306372207869
    },
    {
        "question": "422 × 1,272=？",
        "answer": 5.729799562274069
    },
    {
        "question": "39,922 ÷ 273=？",
        "answer": 2.165049643270126
    },
    {
        "question": "19,064,180 ÷ 6,291=？",
        "answer": 3.4814984446904105
    },
    {
        "question": "536,899 × 224=？",
        "answer": 8.080140613403964
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 29,001=？",
        "answer": 5.608541008990788
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 894=？",
        "answer": 3.7294887691795613
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 331=？",
        "answer": 4.428313012654368
    },
    {
        "question": "1,348,055 ÷ 1,523=？",
        "answer": 2.9470077082321198
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 22,897,752=？",
        "answer": 7.836914102041304
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 14,680,955=？",
        "answer": 7.467784303133684
    },
    {
        "question": "55,200,492 ÷ 525=？",
        "answer": 5.021783645191591
    },
    {
        "question": "29,426 ÷ 5,371=？",
        "answer": 0.7386760782598497
    },
    {
        "question": "422,218,113 ÷ 23,102=？",
        "answer": 4.261887280924693
    },
    {
        "question": "214,692,178 ÷ 1,304,947=？",
        "answer": 2.216223348528443
    },
    {
        "question": "943,589 ÷ 5,126=？",
        "answer": 2.265004267555724
    },
    {
        "question": "521,480,319 ÷ 566=？",
        "answer": 5.964421491332692
    },
    {
        "question": "80,817,663 ÷ 46,280,272=？",
        "answer": 0.24211038508048455
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,650=？",
        "answer": 3.5622928644564746
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 38,893=？",
        "answer": 5.191931434943297
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 220,487=？",
        "answer": 6.598655493489016
    },
    {
        "question": "7,811 × 398=？",
        "answer": 6.492589709879353
    },
    {
        "question": "1,018 × 18,967=？",
        "answer": 7.285746422201028
    },
    {
        "question": "721 × 51,779=？",
        "answer": 7.572088923435594
    },
    {
        "question": "1,640,780 ÷ 2,153=？",
        "answer": 2.882006323812679
    },
    {
        "question": "29,741,783 ÷ 3,014,096=？",
        "answer": 0.9942099200017702
    },
    {
        "question": "162 × 531,544=？",
        "answer": 7.935054234796648
    },
    {
        "question": "80,496,464 ÷ 13,028,122=？",
        "answer": 0.7908949865605193
    },
    {
        "question": "251 × 606,645=？",
        "answer": 8.182608343952259
    },
    {
        "question": "574,481,750 ÷ 32,519,818=？",
        "answer": 1.2471281303174753
    },
    {
        "question": "5,954,864 ÷ 3,011=？",
        "answer": 3.296161091796549
    },
    {
        "question": "19,985,909 ÷ 502,243=？",
        "answer": 1.5998100131528883
    },
    {
        "question": "76,464,288 ÷ 28,935,915=？",
        "answer": 0.4220214289302541
    },
    {
        "question": "686,940,231 ÷ 1,378,508=？",
        "answer": 2.6975096609727394
    },
    {
        "question": "851,711 ÷ 262,263=？",
        "answer": 0.5115552315202253
    },
    {
        "question": "726 × 2,326=？",
        "answer": 6.227546331092523
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 40,690,643=？",
        "answer": 8.931713847431773
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 250,598=？",
        "answer": 6.796917609278972
    },
    {
        "question": "11,498,716 ÷ 32,118=？",
        "answer": 2.5539008539563093
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 514=？",
        "answer": 2.710963118995276
    },
    {
        "question": "4,623 × 10,509=？",
        "answer": 7.686485285475436
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 21,704=？",
        "answer": 6.142719754737427
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 16,427=？",
        "answer": 5.806622864167661
    },
    {
        "question": "2,485,260 ÷ 160,698=？",
        "answer": 1.1893613582583906
    },
    {
        "question": "190 × 502=？",
        "answer": 4.9794573180978485
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 90,210,042=？",
        "answer": 8.909497394458418
    },
    {
        "question": "54,184 ÷ 844=？",
        "answer": 1.8075286159726498
    },
    {
        "question": "509,848,302 ÷ 19,958,192=？",
        "answer": 1.4073197809951707
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 9,410,519=？",
        "answer": 7.575673567212234
    },
    {
        "question": "630,458,765 ÷ 68,807=？",
        "answer": 3.962024063988166
    },
    {
        "question": "1,481 × 480,071=？",
        "answer": 8.85186053053834
    },
    {
        "question": "89 × 1,821,331=？",
        "answer": 8.209778886218178
    },
    {
        "question": "656,184,747 ÷ 99,260,557=？",
        "answer": 0.8202494230927518
    },
    {
        "question": "155,478 × 2,953=？",
        "answer": 8.661932392388739
    },
    {
        "question": "18,060,347 ÷ 67,998=？",
        "answer": 2.4242299511638365
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 5,885=？",
        "answer": 5.000195388557727
    },
    {
        "question": "7,370,078 ÷ 153,084=？",
        "answer": 1.682542282592484
    },
    {
        "question": "1,813 × 11,902=？",
        "answer": 7.334017750024285
    },
    {
        "question": "20,282 × 3,644=？",
        "answer": 7.868689146681036
    },
    {
        "question": "800,302 ÷ 4,529=？",
        "answer": 2.2472515815388516
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 708=？",
        "answer": 3.15106325335375
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,950,627=？",
        "answer": 6.4699143121497995
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 74,295=？",
        "answer": 4.870959587038137
    },
    {
        "question": "17,753 ÷ 1,280=？",
        "answer": 1.1420617834252325
    },
    {
        "question": "24,091,118 ÷ 17,152=？",
        "answer": 3.147542186820217
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 36,197=？",
        "answer": 4.558672577786327
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 21,859=？",
        "answer": 4.33963029007408
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 5,676,486=？",
        "answer": 7.708322080524012
    },
    {
        "question": "29,717 ÷ 2,653=？",
        "answer": 1.0492677142849418
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 839,983=？",
        "answer": 6.225300492343837
    },
    {
        "question": "216,440 × 2,664=？",
        "answer": 8.760871745758807
    },
    {
        "question": "19,056 ÷ 349=？",
        "answer": 1.7372063171795225
    },
    {
        "question": "573,223,867 ÷ 114,125=？",
        "answer": 3.7009434740346774
    },
    {
        "question": "6,589 × 1,856=？",
        "answer": 7.08739747943038
    },
    {
        "question": "660,515,223 ÷ 74,876,921=？",
        "answer": 0.9455348537660182
    },
    {
        "question": "2,276,346 ÷ 35,208=？",
        "answer": 1.8105969190706508
    },
    {
        "question": "580 × 1,833=？",
        "answer": 6.0265904585251535
    },
    {
        "question": "6,264,586 ÷ 6,970=？",
        "answer": 2.953659597494503
    },
    {
        "question": "749,657,828 ÷ 936=？",
        "answer": 5.903587231559737
    },
    {
        "question": "359,225 ÷ 8,433=？",
        "answer": 1.6293844531253845
    },
    {
        "question": "83 × 6,440,727=？",
        "answer": 8.728012983690618
    },
    {
        "question": "58,786 ÷ 54,891=？",
        "answer": 0.02977276751915177
    },
    {
        "question": "124,249 ÷ 645=？",
        "answer": 2.284733187428214
    },
    {
        "question": "340,095,598 ÷ 236,084=？",
        "answer": 3.158534455854824
    },
    {
        "question": "187,928,542 ÷ 1,267,988=？",
        "answer": 2.1708776009155035
    },
    {
        "question": "601 × 1,359=？",
        "answer": 5.912093928735234
    },
    {
        "question": "82,618 × 1,216=？",
        "answer": 8.002008252390683
    },
    {
        "question": "3,781,513 ÷ 1,010,360=？",
        "answer": 0.5731894535078748
    },
    {
        "question": "164,915 ÷ 50,070=？",
        "answer": 0.517682567708054
    },
    {
        "question": "17,398 × 411=？",
        "answer": 6.854341148383581
    },
    {
        "question": "124 × 6,998,419=？",
        "answer": 8.938421625586987
    },
    {
        "question": "44,476,351 ÷ 34,582,427=？",
        "answer": 0.10927368009191704
    },
    {
        "question": "161,338 ÷ 863=？",
        "answer": 2.2717258732649386
    },
    {
        "question": "52,298 × 201=？",
        "answer": 7.0216811381506306
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 193,692,128=？",
        "answer": 8.889171961888927
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 2,871=？",
        "answer": 5.101485868982693
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 87,606=？",
        "answer": 5.7206851017304565
    },
    {
        "question": "34,023,868 ÷ 137,514=？",
        "answer": 2.3934367698177748
    },
    {
        "question": "63,641,424 ÷ 353,281=？",
        "answer": 2.2556196075479598
    },
    {
        "question": "56,237,360 ÷ 348=？",
        "answer": 5.20844568107473
    },
    {
        "question": "418,814 × 2,306=？",
        "answer": 8.984880493685454
    },
    {
        "question": "157,601,791 ÷ 18,205,002=？",
        "answer": 0.9373704175590555
    },
    {
        "question": "1,742 × 259=？",
        "answer": 5.654347914752896
    },
    {
        "question": "11,266 × 5,434=？",
        "answer": 7.786889380981204
    },
    {
        "question": "1,195 × 4,563=？",
        "answer": 6.7366183740568175
    },
    {
        "question": "19,533,670 ÷ 1,199=？",
        "answer": 4.211964663415394
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 1,051=？",
        "answer": 4.69370057396396
    },
    {
        "question": "716,565,781 ÷ 10,325=？",
        "answer": 4.8413660046268125
    },
    {
        "question": "367,086,155 ÷ 377=？",
        "answer": 5.988426654781741
    },
    {
        "question": "27,108,697 ÷ 21,021,584=？",
        "answer": 0.11044320588687821
    },
    {
        "question": "21,489 × 5,248=？",
        "answer": 8.052210032245888
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 487=？",
        "answer": 2.6875289612146345
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 461=？",
        "answer": 3.2657609167176105
    },
    {
        "question": "1,143 × 15,903=？",
        "answer": 7.25952528934137
    },
    {
        "question": "936,388,654 ÷ 4,242,911=？",
        "answer": 2.343792220783305
    },
    {
        "question": "703,692 ÷ 3,474=？",
        "answer": 2.306552799619734
    },
    {
        "question": "125 × 7,691,790=？",
        "answer": 8.982937431699021
    },
    {
        "question": "19,874 ÷ 755=？",
        "answer": 1.420338333854896
    },
    {
        "question": "448,658,216 ÷ 2,383,109=？",
        "answer": 2.274771718315949
    },
    {
        "question": "42,093,179 ÷ 210=？",
        "answer": 5.301992431442289
    },
    {
        "question": "775 × 5,097=？",
        "answer": 6.5966163360950185
    },
    {
        "question": "232,570,767 ÷ 324=？",
        "answer": 5.856010114938821
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 588,487=？",
        "answer": 6.070766869146538
    },
    {
        "question": "356,098 × 514=？",
        "answer": 8.262532653491201
    },
    {
        "question": "2,113,175 ÷ 16,949=？",
        "answer": 2.0957913844174048
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,158,248=？",
        "answer": 6.063801558959619
    },
    {
        "question": "49,522 ÷ 757=？",
        "answer": 1.8157022963226535
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 901=？",
        "answer": 3.7998228309933197
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 233,090=？",
        "answer": 6.2126216818832765
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 722,067=？",
        "answer": 7.089026418643576
    },
    {
        "question": "6,766 × 52,145=？",
        "answer": 8.54754466524589
    },
    {
        "question": "9,963,933 ÷ 238=？",
        "answer": 4.62185384151208
    },
    {
        "question": "554,564,524 ÷ 1,415,457=？",
        "answer": 2.5930554033940054
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 64,651,737=？",
        "answer": 7.810580197574977
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 10,654,385=？",
        "answer": 7.981770895557604
    },
    {
        "question": "17,194,752 ÷ 447,719=？",
        "answer": 1.5843903912977833
    },
    {
        "question": "33,175,754 ÷ 12,380=？",
        "answer": 3.4281001573668632
    },
    {
        "question": "3,232 × 3,414=？",
        "answer": 7.042734868881263
    },
    {
        "question": "20,016 × 7,265=？",
        "answer": 8.162612910983386
    },
    {
        "question": "28,749,259 ÷ 3,211=？",
        "answer": 3.9519863498466825
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 645,377=？",
        "answer": 6.286934738639932
    },
    {
        "question": "258,054 ÷ 52,488=？",
        "answer": 0.6916505705476939
    },
    {
        "question": "11,042,350 ÷ 759,500=？",
        "answer": 1.1625337302872274
    },
    {
        "question": "83,465 ÷ 10,911=？",
        "answer": 0.8836398419433575
    },
    {
        "question": "195,172,456 ÷ 59,353,226=？",
        "answer": 0.5169741982567608
    },
    {
        "question": "441 × 161,726=？",
        "answer": 7.853218434660728
    },
    {
        "question": "1,247 × 405,857=？",
        "answer": 8.70423949432043
    },
    {
        "question": "12,730,359 ÷ 408,331=？",
        "answer": 1.4938282987719278
    },
    {
        "question": "34,009 × 263=？",
        "answer": 6.951549610623396
    },
    {
        "question": "465,210 ÷ 365,344=？",
        "answer": 0.10494706223257716
    },
    {
        "question": "305,983,606 ÷ 1,000=？",
        "answer": 5.485698158460449
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 9,923,454=？",
        "answer": 8.540730905219448
    },
    {
        "question": "306,633,250 ÷ 100,635=？",
        "answer": 3.483870195179021
    },
    {
        "question": "137 × 1,921=？",
        "answer": 5.420247932018101
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 101,874=？",
        "answer": 6.748426048208034
    },
    {
        "question": "133,355,841 ÷ 879=？",
        "answer": 5.181023167513157
    },
    {
        "question": "105 × 3,081,678=？",
        "answer": 8.509976557031539
    },
    {
        "question": "5,937,083 ÷ 113,323=？",
        "answer": 1.7192550572953575
    },
    {
        "question": "3,768 ÷ 3,058=？",
        "answer": 0.09067341304453844
    },
    {
        "question": "20,793,036 ÷ 12,349=？",
        "answer": 3.2262861148558724
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 465=？",
        "answer": 3.92272545799326
    },
    {
        "question": "19,624,540 ÷ 201=？",
        "answer": 4.989603428236137
    },
    {
        "question": "12,362 × 513=？",
        "answer": 6.802206104367623
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 213,044=？",
        "answer": 5.328469307587942
    },
    {
        "question": "92,540,099 ÷ 14,734,535=？",
        "answer": 0.7979935250606143
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 60,666,411=？",
        "answer": 8.260069557740188
    },
    {
        "question": "384,171,504 ÷ 153,733,221=？",
        "answer": 0.3977574212753859
    },
    {
        "question": "410,616 ÷ 7,540=？",
        "answer": 1.7360645221466
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 329,671=？",
        "answer": 6.296231995846761
    },
    {
        "question": "18,221,783 ÷ 158,395=？",
        "answer": 2.060849402149673
    },
    {
        "question": "477,356 ÷ 20,241=？",
        "answer": 1.3726104208099075
    },
    {
        "question": "118 × 13,817=？",
        "answer": 6.2122957648972
    },
    {
        "question": "389,376 ÷ 54,325=？",
        "answer": 0.8553694443722858
    },
    {
        "question": "47,583,144 ÷ 73,737=？",
        "answer": 2.8097676698451663
    },
    {
        "question": "788,254,353 ÷ 720,324,760=？",
        "answer": 0.039138034539136196
    },
    {
        "question": "12,135 × 577=？",
        "answer": 6.845215593823685
    },
    {
        "question": "4,739 × 35,790=？",
        "answer": 8.229448407089405
    },
    {
        "question": "17,036 ÷ 4,044=？",
        "answer": 0.6245564844827477
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 40,368=？",
        "answer": 6.560279742612824
    },
    {
        "question": "14,378,829 ÷ 5,186,476=？",
        "answer": 0.4428511463283149
    },
    {
        "question": "6,718,093 ÷ 2,346=？",
        "answer": 3.4569180037992604
    },
    {
        "question": "10,005 ÷ 520=？",
        "answer": 1.284213749337431
    },
    {
        "question": "5,924 × 54,477=？",
        "answer": 8.508828233201047
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 489,992=？",
        "answer": 7.246491490215765
    },
    {
        "question": "2,500 × 103,048=？",
        "answer": 8.410979575894569
    },
    {
        "question": "45,547 ÷ 14,897=？",
        "answer": 0.485360959232083
    },
    {
        "question": "591 × 293,774=？",
        "answer": 8.23960083749482
    },
    {
        "question": "226 × 558=？",
        "answer": 5.10074263808498
    },
    {
        "question": "1,249,686 ÷ 11,468=？",
        "answer": 2.0373132202551565
    },
    {
        "question": "1,631,022 ÷ 194,254=？",
        "answer": 0.9240898486683959
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 17,228=？",
        "answer": 4.236234863090562
    },
    {
        "question": "299 × 37,627=？",
        "answer": 7.05117078173375
    },
    {
        "question": "1,569 × 448,631=？",
        "answer": 8.847512223230192
    },
    {
        "question": "299,722 ÷ 34,500=？",
        "answer": 0.9388995268444676
    },
    {
        "question": "41,332,119 ÷ 58,306=？",
        "answer": 2.8505744228142933
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,157,456=？",
        "answer": 6.540625745277552
    },
    {
        "question": "378,259,265 ÷ 2,392,198=？",
        "answer": 2.198992451386125
    },
    {
        "question": "250 × 6,249=？",
        "answer": 6.193750533339446
    },
    {
        "question": "89,217,518 ÷ 1,895=？",
        "answer": 4.6728409228496846
    },
    {
        "question": "295,228,289 ÷ 1,281,814=？",
        "answer": 2.36233295892605
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 103,589=？",
        "answer": 5.617373631940489
    },
    {
        "question": "5,390 × 39,216=？",
        "answer": 8.325052059094741
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 7,401=？",
        "answer": 5.04538166326508
    },
    {
        "question": "78,345 ÷ 17,540=？",
        "answer": 0.6499816958626532
    },
    {
        "question": "11,075,955 ÷ 15,043=？",
        "answer": 2.8670467270958806
    },
    {
        "question": "2,129,270 ÷ 648=？",
        "answer": 3.5166557293466445
    },
    {
        "question": "4,537 × 3,118=？",
        "answer": 7.15064489011884
    },
    {
        "question": "28,070,408 ÷ 1,077,099=？",
        "answer": 1.415993102415251
    },
    {
        "question": "1,550,924 × 605=？",
        "answer": 8.972345891235049
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 76,456=？",
        "answer": 5.997354925307537
    },
    {
        "question": "322 × 915=？",
        "answer": 5.469276965762279
    },
    {
        "question": "1,378 × 24,447=？",
        "answer": 7.527474790095305
    },
    {
        "question": "229,174 ÷ 801=？",
        "answer": 2.456532828899467
    },
    {
        "question": "180,606,704 ÷ 4,393,314=？",
        "answer": 1.6139416226224559
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 207,367,946=？",
        "answer": 8.31674162596247
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 19,492,935=？",
        "answer": 7.988847238955892
    },
    {
        "question": "145,273,577 ÷ 1,016=？",
        "answer": 5.155292922133831
    },
    {
        "question": "13,233,461 ÷ 683=？",
        "answer": 4.287252738134822
    },
    {
        "question": "467,544,960 ÷ 22,416,810=？",
        "answer": 1.3192495689409052
    },
    {
        "question": "272 × 2,762,350=？",
        "answer": 8.875847608486291
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 712=？",
        "answer": 4.475729284034757
    },
    {
        "question": "156,395,754 ÷ 1,110,486=？",
        "answer": 2.14871187046238
    },
    {
        "question": "1,009 ÷ 219=？",
        "answer": 0.6634470513967922
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 204,381,065=？",
        "answer": 8.912500649195078
    },
    {
        "question": "185,556,191 ÷ 74,012,473=？",
        "answer": 0.39917053331127744
    },
    {
        "question": "368 × 125,285=？",
        "answer": 7.663746895994971
    },
    {
        "question": "128,558 ÷ 839=？",
        "answer": 2.1853371465815337
    },
    {
        "question": "90,518,136 ÷ 45,901=？",
        "answer": 3.2949134549526873
    },
    {
        "question": "13,772,342 ÷ 655=？",
        "answer": 4.322766498739417
    },
    {
        "question": "289 × 96,668=？",
        "answer": 7.446180576163246
    },
    {
        "question": "98,144 ÷ 7,330=？",
        "answer": 1.1267597796612636
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 4,532,114=？",
        "answer": 7.133422080215579
    },
    {
        "question": "134,538,105 ÷ 902,084=？",
        "answer": 2.1735983263183707
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,518=？",
        "answer": 3.8473258307854237
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,076=？",
        "answer": 3.0318122713303706
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,597=？",
        "answer": 3.5043349118024643
    },
    {
        "question": "19,265 ÷ 8,890=？",
        "answer": 0.33586725237880605
    },
    {
        "question": "40,826,315 ÷ 68,074=？",
        "answer": 2.7779589117752796
    },
    {
        "question": "12,065,552 ÷ 119,631=？",
        "answer": 2.003703462673749
    },
    {
        "question": "36,689 × 2,878=？",
        "answer": 8.02362666433281
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 36,840=？",
        "answer": 5.344470871908455
    },
    {
        "question": "566 ÷ 215=？",
        "answer": 0.4203779712726661
    },
    {
        "question": "173,490,120 ÷ 25,638,571=？",
        "answer": 0.8303809318787566
    },
    {
        "question": "5,892,905 ÷ 15,617=？",
        "answer": 2.5767318295568815
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 13,043=？",
        "answer": 5.319497476935042
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 146,734=？",
        "answer": 6.342622015717797
    },
    {
        "question": "50,957,935 ÷ 1,277=？",
        "answer": 4.601020923235856
    },
    {
        "question": "6,882 × 871=？",
        "answer": 6.777732823292575
    },
    {
        "question": "2,035 × 319,149=？",
        "answer": 8.81255790154009
    },
    {
        "question": "30,926 ÷ 9,626=？",
        "answer": 0.5068778942083333
    },
    {
        "question": "2,357 ÷ 1,316=？",
        "answer": 0.2531036932463871
    },
    {
        "question": "558,321,096 ÷ 1,441,306=？",
        "answer": 2.5881278432942554
    },
    {
        "question": "932,249 ÷ 76,506=？",
        "answer": 1.085836430046636
    },
    {
        "question": "89,029,721 ÷ 408,393=？",
        "answer": 2.3384567228746262
    },
    {
        "question": "8,972,240 ÷ 635=？",
        "answer": 4.1501271567925615
    },
    {
        "question": "71,754 ÷ 2,449=？",
        "answer": 1.4668573311455155
    },
    {
        "question": "1,852 × 15,564=？",
        "answer": 7.45976220447762
    },
    {
        "question": "690,890 ÷ 5,387=？",
        "answer": 2.1080619311685522
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 14,561,145=？",
        "answer": 7.765255517927936
    },
    {
        "question": "64,468 × 390=？",
        "answer": 7.40040880426666
    },
    {
        "question": "568,986,618 ÷ 3,474,209=？",
        "answer": 2.2142461113391554
    },
    {
        "question": "580,417 ÷ 524,411=？",
        "answer": 0.044068331290374844
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 919,089=？",
        "answer": 5.963357568336476
    },
    {
        "question": "212,777 ÷ 44,314=？",
        "answer": 0.6813837280020725
    },
    {
        "question": "97,035,668 ÷ 6,912,382=？",
        "answer": 1.1473036693036718
    },
    {
        "question": "155,561,075 ÷ 22,540,834=？",
        "answer": 0.8389309549703929
    },
    {
        "question": "902,450,294 ÷ 161,300,286=？",
        "answer": 0.7477881533263592
    },
    {
        "question": "154 × 60,386=？",
        "answer": 6.968456983505517
    },
    {
        "question": "1,767 × 1,006=？",
        "answer": 6.249834530226672
    },
    {
        "question": "8,740,442 ÷ 470,469=？",
        "answer": 1.2690023829490258
    },
    {
        "question": "768,338,497 ÷ 66,365,361=？",
        "answer": 1.0636111326011
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 13,917=？",
        "answer": 4.9216968776220655
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 525=？",
        "answer": 3.4191293077419758
    },
    {
        "question": "10,116 × 13,516=？",
        "answer": 8.135857003775225
    },
    {
        "question": "12,965,700 ÷ 138,749=？",
        "answer": 1.9705661069565792
    },
    {
        "question": "32,689,857 ÷ 14,903=？",
        "answer": 3.341139319334374
    },
    {
        "question": "798,037,460 ÷ 3,142,554=？",
        "answer": 2.4047405285676233
    },
    {
        "question": "1,423 ÷ 447=？",
        "answer": 0.5028973769523478
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 379=？",
        "answer": 2.578639209968072
    },
    {
        "question": "107,413,982 ÷ 550=？",
        "answer": 5.290698127346156
    },
    {
        "question": "153,174,941 ÷ 42,750=？",
        "answer": 3.5542516026580677
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,608,139=？",
        "answer": 6.206323584414915
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 222,703=？",
        "answer": 6.626479668344614
    },
    {
        "question": "2,727,978 ÷ 1,020,380=？",
        "answer": 0.4270789259810772
    },
    {
        "question": "2,753,877 ÷ 2,706,630=？",
        "answer": 0.007515647711205046
    },
    {
        "question": "179,063,215 ÷ 48,265,735=？",
        "answer": 0.5693674536929051
    },
    {
        "question": "6,599,624 ÷ 1,159=？",
        "answer": 3.755435757248455
    },
    {
        "question": "227,867 ÷ 79,193=？",
        "answer": 0.4589946393537443
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 25,401=？",
        "answer": 5.484032060538942
    },
    {
        "question": "8,077 × 53,447=？",
        "answer": 8.635173415999358
    },
    {
        "question": "133,542,195 ÷ 5,184=？",
        "answer": 4.41095351748448
    },
    {
        "question": "2,422,569 ÷ 4,509=？",
        "answer": 2.7301959202376955
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 5,797,290=？",
        "answer": 8.846010396105472
    },
    {
        "question": "374 × 258,167=？",
        "answer": 7.984772330317426
    },
    {
        "question": "326,797,658 ÷ 456,897=？",
        "answer": 2.854460629020126
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 35,221=？",
        "answer": 4.546801682361427
    },
    {
        "question": "43,733,618 ÷ 4,740=？",
        "answer": 3.9650370655230316
    },
    {
        "question": "445 × 757=？",
        "answer": 5.527455890481004
    },
    {
        "question": "1,055,918 ÷ 277,305=？",
        "answer": 0.5806724929869765
    },
    {
        "question": "51,494 ÷ 10,314=？",
        "answer": 0.6983295016074764
    },
    {
        "question": "92,319 × 568=？",
        "answer": 7.71963942726754
    },
    {
        "question": "15,924 × 14,534=？",
        "answer": 8.364437324769302
    },
    {
        "question": "1,658,151 × 279=？",
        "answer": 8.665228280441239
    },
    {
        "question": "388,283 ÷ 75,059=？",
        "answer": 0.7137456023904327
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,161,657=？",
        "answer": 7.065077913771073
    },
    {
        "question": "10,642 × 16,580=？",
        "answer": 8.24660778080296
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 276,039,508=？",
        "answer": 8.440971244668335
    },
    {
        "question": "776,338 ÷ 280,476=？",
        "answer": 0.4421551393060962
    },
    {
        "question": "105 × 92,501=？",
        "answer": 6.987335726859072
    },
    {
        "question": "5,424,902 ÷ 328=？",
        "answer": 4.218518053418353
    },
    {
        "question": "227,421,108 ÷ 6,289=？",
        "answer": 4.5582491763641135
    },
    {
        "question": "67,036,219 ÷ 5,828,537=？",
        "answer": 1.0607499533353233
    },
    {
        "question": "642,276,288 ÷ 6,511,682=？",
        "answer": 1.9940287052322054
    },
    {
        "question": "4,703,039 ÷ 149,550=？",
        "answer": 1.4975921627851994
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 15,819,573=？",
        "answer": 8.375286015951442
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 160,524,169=？",
        "answer": 8.506570426006766
    },
    {
        "question": "397,996,668 ÷ 117,732=？",
        "answer": 3.5289849144454584
    },
    {
        "question": "336 × 179,739=？",
        "answer": 7.780981598500502
    },
    {
        "question": "37,385,924 ÷ 9,001=？",
        "answer": 3.618417357082355
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 942,923=？",
        "answer": 7.530778730047067
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 5,553=？",
        "answer": 4.64761766046451
    },
    {
        "question": "873,960,316 ÷ 4,944,665=？",
        "answer": 2.2473548394595877
    },
    {
        "question": "2,142,017 ÷ 306,065=？",
        "answer": 0.8450092444829819
    },
    {
        "question": "709,434,997 ÷ 59,486,510=？",
        "answer": 1.0764941186090664
    },
    {
        "question": "13,629,916 ÷ 31,695=？",
        "answer": 2.633502423215388
    },
    {
        "question": "84,970 × 3,825=？",
        "answer": 8.511897057742702
    },
    {
        "question": "1,056,553 × 255=？",
        "answer": 8.43043146793702
    },
    {
        "question": "12,415 ÷ 1,244=？",
        "answer": 0.9991263435357832
    },
    {
        "question": "5,255 ÷ 263=？",
        "answer": 1.300616971874503
    },
    {
        "question": "233 × 386=？",
        "answer": 4.953943225697774
    },
    {
        "question": "198,979,857 ÷ 141,647=？",
        "answer": 3.1476017335645214
    },
    {
        "question": "6,602,125 ÷ 2,160,175=？",
        "answer": 0.48519480707779833
    },
    {
        "question": "463,754 ÷ 690=？",
        "answer": 2.8274385778059243
    },
    {
        "question": "1,669,009 ÷ 9,324=？",
        "answer": 2.2528564137359193
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 1,715=？",
        "answer": 4.836324115706752
    },
    {
        "question": "619,824 × 1,003=？",
        "answer": 8.793569321422181
    },
    {
        "question": "188,906 ÷ 83,776=？",
        "answer": 0.3531261315931674
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 27,745=？",
        "answer": 6.022968325766994
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 8,656=？",
        "answer": 3.9373172477624943
    },
    {
        "question": "32,740 × 3,909=？",
        "answer": 8.10714434550817
    },
    {
        "question": "79,814,296 ÷ 847=？",
        "answer": 4.974197276982984
    },
    {
        "question": "970,331,591 ÷ 1,561,755=？",
        "answer": 2.793307265872451
    },
    {
        "question": "1,602 × 224=？",
        "answer": 5.554910530082382
    },
    {
        "question": "393,314,435 ÷ 1,146,191=？",
        "answer": 2.5354828916936727
    },
    {
        "question": "16,554 ÷ 3,996=？",
        "answer": 0.6172774713088844
    },
    {
        "question": "16,625,878 ÷ 64,719=？",
        "answer": 2.4097527911501144
    },
    {
        "question": "384,144,451 ÷ 311,266,659=？",
        "answer": 0.09136195996964712
    },
    {
        "question": "7,356 × 417=？",
        "answer": 6.486777775539798
    },
    {
        "question": "2,110,997 ÷ 39,791=？",
        "answer": 1.7247027624461468
    },
    {
        "question": "7,045,235 ÷ 2,203=？",
        "answer": 3.5048809868100217
    },
    {
        "question": "12,049 × 520=？",
        "answer": 6.796954348014283
    },
    {
        "question": "49,782 × 410=？",
        "answer": 7.309856197194715
    },
    {
        "question": "44,719,641 ÷ 733=？",
        "answer": 4.785394333825235
    },
    {
        "question": "10,712 × 1,651=？",
        "answer": 7.247617637266746
    },
    {
        "question": "152,503,596 ÷ 36,469=？",
        "answer": 3.621356229484396
    },
    {
        "question": "3,383 × 7,659=？",
        "answer": 7.413474067311894
    },
    {
        "question": "123,204,571 ÷ 367,431=？",
        "answer": 2.525451026082185
    },
    {
        "question": "949,184 ÷ 138,011=？",
        "answer": 0.8374367061877944
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 9,929=？",
        "answer": 5.1729967697513475
    },
    {
        "question": "6,422,648 ÷ 67,127=？",
        "answer": 1.9808168823113554
    },
    {
        "question": "3,325 × 27,669=？",
        "answer": 7.963785112996561
    },
    {
        "question": "23,394,373 ÷ 296=？",
        "answer": 4.897819698961282
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,204,856=？",
        "answer": 6.343380230789094
    },
    {
        "question": "11,190 × 35,268=？",
        "answer": 8.596210918648588
    },
    {
        "question": "396,244 ÷ 15,703=？",
        "answer": 1.4019800684197972
    },
    {
        "question": "4,684,996 × 202=？",
        "answer": 8.976060593874546
    },
    {
        "question": "21,126 ÷ 3,348=？",
        "answer": 0.8000318261326055
    },
    {
        "question": "4,160,953 ÷ 335,641=？",
        "answer": 1.09331780390531
    },
    {
        "question": "190 × 370,606=？",
        "answer": 7.847666047090047
    },
    {
        "question": "694 × 449=？",
        "answer": 5.4936058114581785
    },
    {
        "question": "1,869 × 15,406=？",
        "answer": 7.459299194904016
    },
    {
        "question": "115,798,718 ÷ 14,145=？",
        "answer": 3.9131007995793428
    },
    {
        "question": "25,511 ÷ 7,329=？",
        "answer": 0.5416827610629036
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 117,835=？",
        "answer": 6.217402341827145
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 650=？",
        "answer": 2.8129133566428557
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 1,821,247=？",
        "answer": 7.9927626092217325
    },
    {
        "question": "11,219,068 ÷ 41,863=？",
        "answer": 2.4281264326653433
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 13,396=？",
        "answer": 4.126975138867829
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 411,130,653=？",
        "answer": 8.613979858031794
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 904,193=？",
        "answer": 7.524462864596346
    },
    {
        "question": "131,588 ÷ 22,194=？",
        "answer": 0.7729807044527196
    },
    {
        "question": "23,679,438 ÷ 1,705,936=？",
        "answer": 1.1424086566520784
    },
    {
        "question": "32,340 × 497=？",
        "answer": 7.206096404303715
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 263,124,399=？",
        "answer": 8.420161121212876
    },
    {
        "question": "1,078 × 830,922=？",
        "answer": 8.9521790186186
    },
    {
        "question": "167,773,477 ÷ 868,540=？",
        "answer": 2.2859334807329983
    },
    {
        "question": "99,409,462 ÷ 89,060=？",
        "answer": 3.0477450326244027
    },
    {
        "question": "383,262,921 ÷ 20,629,375=？",
        "answer": 1.26901073468321
    },
    {
        "question": "31,458,159 ÷ 1,605,411=？",
        "answer": 1.2921470688096632
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 207,585,150=？",
        "answer": 8.794317536922426
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,810=？",
        "answer": 4.160768561861128
    },
    {
        "question": "1,980 × 7,209=？",
        "answer": 7.154540215785094
    },
    {
        "question": "5,432,366 ÷ 2,066,337=？",
        "answer": 0.4197878701184675
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 188,341=？",
        "answer": 6.274944871984339
    },
    {
        "question": "1,236,893 ÷ 347,039=？",
        "answer": 0.5519538484636917
    },
    {
        "question": "850,644,798 ÷ 4,124,807=？",
        "answer": 2.3143446177892817
    },
    {
        "question": "395,856,551 ÷ 418,207=？",
        "answer": 2.976146538624867
    },
    {
        "question": "1,626 × 47,190=？",
        "answer": 7.884970518600999
    },
    {
        "question": "10,037,965 ÷ 4,749,231=？",
        "answer": 0.3250223831249782
    },
    {
        "question": "425,198,696 ÷ 79,345,944=？",
        "answer": 0.7290671925327438
    },
    {
        "question": "1,518 × 1,015=？",
        "answer": 6.187737813808694
    },
    {
        "question": "270,345,533 ÷ 1,567,994=？",
        "answer": 2.23657480148936
    },
    {
        "question": "4,299,987 ÷ 247,047=？",
        "answer": 1.2406875581650698
    },
    {
        "question": "4,393,274 ÷ 3,380=？",
        "answer": 3.11387158993899
    },
    {
        "question": "287,457 ÷ 47,410=？",
        "answer": 0.7827029335000801
    },
    {
        "question": "744,492 × 798=？",
        "answer": 8.773862926716934
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,095=？",
        "answer": 3.490660653356137
    },
    {
        "question": "443,104,735 ÷ 1,209=？",
        "answer": 5.564080090049614
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 16,109,476=？",
        "answer": 7.508111409825619
    },
    {
        "question": "95,021,270 ÷ 206=？",
        "answer": 5.663953610284715
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 51,810,314=？",
        "answer": 8.79359747041454
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 180,402,777=？",
        "answer": 8.85830320982487
    },
    {
        "question": "2,292 × 8,999=？",
        "answer": 7.314408865111215
    },
    {
        "question": "220 × 13,207=？",
        "answer": 6.4632268586630035
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 10,128,011=？",
        "answer": 8.677622022295086
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 63,343=？",
        "answer": 5.102728623891415
    },
    {
        "question": "459,325 ÷ 1,886=？",
        "answer": 2.3865783953065587
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 274=？",
        "answer": 3.0398105541483504
    },
    {
        "question": "2,698,887 ÷ 293,517=？",
        "answer": 0.963551441511398
    },
    {
        "question": "334,384 ÷ 176,215=？",
        "answer": 0.27820261440621874
    },
    {
        "question": "1,203,744 × 218=？",
        "answer": 8.418990629024103
    },
    {
        "question": "95,578,624 ÷ 2,491=？",
        "answer": 4.583987046362135
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 133,470=？",
        "answer": 6.02847364745965
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 269,794=？",
        "answer": 6.431032287085825
    },
    {
        "question": "536 × 154,816=？",
        "answer": 7.9189806320385365
    },
    {
        "question": "192 × 1,019,532=？",
        "answer": 8.291702090210862
    },
    {
        "question": "1,168 × 1,936=？",
        "answer": 6.354348195748756
    },
    {
        "question": "88,763 ÷ 6,507=？",
        "answer": 1.1348511653009699
    },
    {
        "question": "623,863,467 ÷ 2,558,695=？",
        "answer": 2.3870710339330685
    },
    {
        "question": "477,681,944 ÷ 1,575=？",
        "answer": 5.481858267479763
    },
    {
        "question": "9,228,308 ÷ 2,636,992=？",
        "answer": 0.5440132686646184
    },
    {
        "question": "141 × 3,415=？",
        "answer": 5.682609820672932
    },
    {
        "question": "409,129,763 ÷ 1,200,762=？",
        "answer": 2.5324041387862066
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,519=？",
        "answer": 3.6586790285824486
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 81,965=？",
        "answer": 4.913628443215937
    },
    {
        "question": "199,376 × 224=？",
        "answer": 7.64992089700949
    },
    {
        "question": "31,089,714 ÷ 6,143,060=？",
        "answer": 0.7042319697604102
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 1,607,950=？",
        "answer": 8.174755488574759
    },
    {
        "question": "1,949,434 ÷ 2,248=？",
        "answer": 2.9381122294102515
    },
    {
        "question": "706 ÷ 242=？",
        "answer": 0.46498933507137247
    },
    {
        "question": "9,621 ÷ 5,603=？",
        "answer": 0.2347995921805345
    },
    {
        "question": "180,923 × 1,793=？",
        "answer": 8.511074070010393
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 259,274=？",
        "answer": 5.714788963560697
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,606=？",
        "answer": 3.7170044070405472
    },
    {
        "question": "76,968 ÷ 2,282=？",
        "answer": 1.5279945615578507
    },
    {
        "question": "815,372 ÷ 493,809=？",
        "answer": 0.217796792656774
    },
    {
        "question": "75,507 ÷ 7,369=？",
        "answer": 1.0105786589534438
    },
    {
        "question": "3,105,506 ÷ 171,940=？",
        "answer": 1.2567554502597946
    },
    {
        "question": "131 × 480=？",
        "answer": 4.798512533031351
    },
    {
        "question": "849,644,304 ÷ 1,165,577=？",
        "answer": 2.862696181217872
    },
    {
        "question": "751 × 283,326=？",
        "answer": 8.327926367290269
    },
    {
        "question": "4,371,805 ÷ 3,155,249=？",
        "answer": 0.1416271446708145
    },
    {
        "question": "573,798,243 ÷ 1,009,546=？",
        "answer": 2.7546331017054912
    },
    {
        "question": "3,964,011 ÷ 485,323=？",
        "answer": 0.9121039774633696
    },
    {
        "question": "108,508 × 1,867=？",
        "answer": 8.306606076666112
    },
    {
        "question": "798,418 ÷ 552=？",
        "answer": 3.160291241648005
    },
    {
        "question": "13,555 ÷ 968=？",
        "answer": 1.1462241646081106
    },
    {
        "question": "1,295 × 37,031=？",
        "answer": 7.680835208487721
    },
    {
        "question": "28,269,921 ÷ 24,204,968=？",
        "answer": 0.06742008203834483
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 5,217,138=？",
        "answer": 8.018462320185062
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 2,212,370=？",
        "answer": 8.25867161313601
    },
    {
        "question": "2,544,322 ÷ 8,173=？",
        "answer": 2.4931905742422473
    },
    {
        "question": "2,116 × 84,212=？",
        "answer": 8.250889645153176
    },
    {
        "question": "15,482,588 ÷ 4,337=？",
        "answer": 3.552654134984699
    },
    {
        "question": "220 × 439,541=？",
        "answer": 7.985422072730893
    },
    {
        "question": "412,158 ÷ 2,369=？",
        "answer": 2.240498673208591
    },
    {
        "question": "1,633 × 37,895=？",
        "answer": 7.791568096138538
    },
    {
        "question": "117,483 ÷ 1,013=？",
        "answer": 2.064365582606337
    },
    {
        "question": "962,915 × 867=？",
        "answer": 8.921607049543397
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,115=？",
        "answer": 3.6143698395482886
    },
    {
        "question": "187,800 ÷ 172,042=？",
        "answer": 0.038061105315678655
    },
    {
        "question": "13,228 ÷ 1,323=？",
        "answer": 0.9999343420541642
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 123,225=？",
        "answer": 6.044941336266087
    },
    {
        "question": "121,518 ÷ 459=？",
        "answer": 2.422827927554865
    },
    {
        "question": "117,160 ÷ 84,115=？",
        "answer": 0.14390591374738215
    },
    {
        "question": "4,377,494 ÷ 232,627=？",
        "answer": 1.2745654395095332
    },
    {
        "question": "25,442 ÷ 513=？",
        "answer": 1.6954338831704936
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 2,862=？",
        "answer": 4.836880871135364
    },
    {
        "question": "6,649,596 ÷ 538,300=？",
        "answer": 1.0917708804798205
    },
    {
        "question": "1,605 × 15,008=？",
        "answer": 7.38179785777588
    },
    {
        "question": "440,667,501 ÷ 1,664,173=？",
        "answer": 2.4229125510796186
    },
    {
        "question": "7,160 × 2,281=？",
        "answer": 7.213038307584504
    },
    {
        "question": "31,156,163 ÷ 12,199,309=？",
        "answer": 0.40720873545263847
    },
    {
        "question": "31,955,169 ÷ 585=？",
        "answer": 4.737385252643995
    },
    {
        "question": "6,031,712 ÷ 16,449=？",
        "answer": 2.5643010962179904
    },
    {
        "question": "609 × 247=？",
        "answer": 5.177314245892541
    },
    {
        "question": "155,077 ÷ 37,448=？",
        "answer": 0.6171187627710619
    },
    {
        "question": "41,627 ÷ 3,494=？",
        "answer": 1.0760522123683043
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 5,072=？",
        "answer": 5.136543009032664
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 25,564=？",
        "answer": 5.106598813212537
    },
    {
        "question": "24,367 × 3,397=？",
        "answer": 7.917897610168573
    },
    {
        "question": "1,048 × 6,478=？",
        "answer": 6.831802226321866
    },
    {
        "question": "11,205,137 ÷ 968=？",
        "answer": 4.063541813511842
    },
    {
        "question": "175,818,787 ÷ 119,521=？",
        "answer": 3.1676210613549896
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 269=？",
        "answer": 4.009535876619218
    },
    {
        "question": "1,796,959 ÷ 647=？",
        "answer": 3.443633887549405
    },
    {
        "question": "1,796 ÷ 346=？",
        "answer": 0.7152302335385089
    },
    {
        "question": "17,605,803 ÷ 902=？",
        "answer": 4.290449300470673
    },
    {
        "question": "1,341,333 ÷ 90,484=？",
        "answer": 1.170964818329896
    },
    {
        "question": "37,543 × 629=？",
        "answer": 7.373179618882133
    },
    {
        "question": "3,524,598 ÷ 2,937,875=？",
        "answer": 0.0790762768614908
    },
    {
        "question": "2,769,403 ÷ 662=？",
        "answer": 3.6215281688848546
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,009,972=？",
        "answer": 7.118252686075564
    },
    {
        "question": "186,006,931 ÷ 12,292=？",
        "answer": 4.179906575638802
    },
    {
        "question": "41,676,123 ÷ 17,793=？",
        "answer": 3.369638132353697
    },
    {
        "question": "271,600,369 ÷ 125,640=？",
        "answer": 3.334802427920859
    },
    {
        "question": "32,548,002 ÷ 11,435,462=？",
        "answer": 0.45427061893712445
    },
    {
        "question": "79,617,421 ÷ 1,550,132=？",
        "answer": 1.7106394239577964
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 237,516=？",
        "answer": 5.676722866372905
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 3,531,614=？",
        "answer": 7.5022157392171795
    },
    {
        "question": "362 × 14,763=？",
        "answer": 6.727883190286909
    },
    {
        "question": "3,765,301 ÷ 514=？",
        "answer": 3.8648365806420806
    },
    {
        "question": "36,532 × 315=？",
        "answer": 7.060984002765472
    },
    {
        "question": "310 × 32,934=？",
        "answer": 7.009006174999532
    },
    {
        "question": "15,091 ÷ 4,430=？",
        "answer": 0.532314292882699
    },
    {
        "question": "449,436,422 ÷ 42,837,086=？",
        "answer": 1.0208483442082594
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 161,673=？",
        "answer": 5.208637497147614
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 326,029=？",
        "answer": 5.513256231907883
    },
    {
        "question": "4,620,159 ÷ 6,901=？",
        "answer": 2.82574489439134
    },
    {
        "question": "3,499 × 280,487=？",
        "answer": 8.991856679878655
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 9,360,444=？",
        "answer": 8.201745370776278
    },
    {
        "question": "17,621,701 ÷ 812,150=？",
        "answer": 1.3364115793388398
    },
    {
        "question": "193 × 755=？",
        "answer": 5.163504260636962
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 12,418,102=？",
        "answer": 8.474266464451013
    },
    {
        "question": "13,285,773 ÷ 419=？",
        "answer": 4.501172804870562
    },
    {
        "question": "37,807 × 315=？",
        "answer": 7.075882771085051
    },
    {
        "question": "585,053 ÷ 9,398=？",
        "answer": 1.7941597699506762
    },
    {
        "question": "2,940,025 ÷ 111,205=？",
        "answer": 1.4222267089401308
    },
    {
        "question": "834,313,062 ÷ 511,391,566=？",
        "answer": 0.21257548169456525
    },
    {
        "question": "129,255 ÷ 12,422=？",
        "answer": 1.0172558270917225
    },
    {
        "question": "43,165 × 2,010=？",
        "answer": 7.938327802667665
    },
    {
        "question": "125,990,431 ÷ 428,226=？",
        "answer": 2.4686645294014555
    },
    {
        "question": "2,206,960 ÷ 136,068=？",
        "answer": 1.2100384605293557
    },
    {
        "question": "674,293,878 ÷ 12,993,243=？",
        "answer": 1.7151316559664198
    },
    {
        "question": "20,843 × 1,164=？",
        "answer": 7.38491320884141
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 1,513,392=？",
        "answer": 7.759735030513564
    },
    {
        "question": "3,579,349 ÷ 2,945,786=？",
        "answer": 0.08460285196902306
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 18,760,943=？",
        "answer": 8.704618428127604
    },
    {
        "question": "884 × 367,104=？",
        "answer": 8.511241381656705
    },
    {
        "question": "17,498,265 ÷ 48,855=？",
        "answer": 2.554085971735415
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,561,821=？",
        "answer": 6.98054060932004
    },
    {
        "question": "582,765,966 ÷ 718,152=？",
        "answer": 2.9092778064015508
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 1,686,989=？",
        "answer": 8.065961341521476
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 7,478,490=？",
        "answer": 7.475873908594997
    },
    {
        "question": "21,193,418 ÷ 16,756,267=？",
        "answer": 0.10202373190892394
    },
    {
        "question": "251 × 11,021=？",
        "answer": 6.44189472387142
    },
    {
        "question": "71,864 ÷ 47,047=？",
        "answer": 0.18397945125794268
    },
    {
        "question": "149,125 ÷ 109,980=？",
        "answer": 0.132236741332538
    },
    {
        "question": "2,324 × 3,233=？",
        "answer": 6.8758418283298495
    },
    {
        "question": "8,803,889 ÷ 5,651=？",
        "answer": 3.1925492510051083
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,881=？",
        "answer": 3.9733587998863977
    },
    {
        "question": "8,546 ÷ 2,106=？",
        "answer": 0.60830452163171
    },
    {
        "question": "24,677 ÷ 3,492=？",
        "answer": 0.8492181260554384
    },
    {
        "question": "3,529,402 ÷ 576=？",
        "answer": 3.787278644032429
    },
    {
        "question": "11,545,305 ÷ 19,831=？",
        "answer": 2.765060795916191
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 711=？",
        "answer": 3.550839605065785
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 447=？",
        "answer": 3.6503075231319366
    },
    {
        "question": "2,811 ÷ 1,129=？",
        "answer": 0.39616690368247287
    },
    {
        "question": "350,159 ÷ 18,678=？",
        "answer": 1.2729349222627335
    },
    {
        "question": "30,986 ÷ 13,257=？",
        "answer": 0.3687202602590562
    },
    {
        "question": "22,474,147 ÷ 44,899=？",
        "answer": 2.6994465487790587
    },
    {
        "question": "302,020,652 ÷ 95,720=？",
        "answer": 3.499033950840201
    },
    {
        "question": "522,553,571 ÷ 186,305=？",
        "answer": 3.4479063094219398
    },
    {
        "question": "256,523,525 ÷ 45,676=？",
        "answer": 3.7494391348297915
    },
    {
        "question": "587,634 ÷ 740=？",
        "answer": 2.8998751960210107
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 16,950=？",
        "answer": 5.007320952922744
    },
    {
        "question": "189,228,002 ÷ 929=？",
        "answer": 5.308969689817564
    },
    {
        "question": "25,481 ÷ 276=？",
        "answer": 1.9653073857880428
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,072=？",
        "answer": 3.3163897510731952
    },
    {
        "question": "3,630,237 ÷ 2,002=？",
        "answer": 3.258470905730917
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 20,756,980=？",
        "answer": 8.095315417250672
    },
    {
        "question": "86,385 × 4,911=？",
        "answer": 8.627608271717191
    },
    {
        "question": "14,669,843 ÷ 16,233=？",
        "answer": 2.956026677297479
    },
    {
        "question": "1,723 × 87,567=？",
        "answer": 8.178625748706882
    },
    {
        "question": "376,960 ÷ 19,979=？",
        "answer": 1.2757215218855547
    },
    {
        "question": "14,415,559 ÷ 68,708=？",
        "answer": 2.3218241809442923
    },
    {
        "question": "13,848,870 ÷ 156,397=？",
        "answer": 1.9471859203551887
    },
    {
        "question": "686,515,272 ÷ 29,163,300=？",
        "answer": 1.3718135374393166
    },
    {
        "question": "4,323,508 ÷ 1,886,002=？",
        "answer": 0.36029411796222993
    },
    {
        "question": "17,040 ÷ 5,406=？",
        "answer": 0.4985935490679747
    },
    {
        "question": "21,824 ÷ 1,451=？",
        "answer": 1.177266940538649
    },
    {
        "question": "5,373,428 ÷ 8,970=？",
        "answer": 2.777458990979907
    },
    {
        "question": "22,037 × 15,304=？",
        "answer": 8.527957428681496
    },
    {
        "question": "37,082,522 ÷ 13,029,133=？",
        "answer": 0.4542537457153949
    },
    {
        "question": "943,999,634 ÷ 2,669,107=？",
        "answer": 2.5486058416467867
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 431,484=？",
        "answer": 7.454508631675269
    },
    {
        "question": "49,852 ÷ 36,217=？",
        "answer": 0.13877011324304594
    },
    {
        "question": "6,211,332 ÷ 1,140,324=？",
        "answer": 0.7361564783441221
    },
    {
        "question": "211,372,292 ÷ 5,690,661=？",
        "answer": 1.5698853417720677
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,865,155=？",
        "answer": 6.895707285761771
    },
    {
        "question": "68 × 7,189=？",
        "answer": 5.689177396317771
    },
    {
        "question": "523,465 × 391=？",
        "answer": 8.3110644065148
    },
    {
        "question": "401,848 ÷ 411=？",
        "answer": 2.990219989306857
    },
    {
        "question": "2,094 × 7,843=？",
        "answer": 7.215458892352914
    },
    {
        "question": "156,519 ÷ 359=？",
        "answer": 2.6394726159514397
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 2,093,752=？",
        "answer": 7.166023279243439
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 65,684,613=？",
        "answer": 8.993554904538783
    },
    {
        "question": "187,348,136 ÷ 71,618,180=？",
        "answer": 0.4176260961959769
    },
    {
        "question": "564 × 211=？",
        "answer": 5.075561559281035
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 774,536=？",
        "answer": 7.2692528500405285
    },
    {
        "question": "1,610 ÷ 1,459=？",
        "answer": 0.04277058413839811
    },
    {
        "question": "281 × 430=？",
        "answer": 5.082174775484666
    },
    {
        "question": "827 × 98,769=？",
        "answer": 7.9121261662706255
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 182,901=？",
        "answer": 6.376159432268189
    },
    {
        "question": "51,005,858 ÷ 202,249=？",
        "answer": 2.40173367452572
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,389,461=？",
        "answer": 6.142846361316704
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,478,758=？",
        "answer": 6.470927102815747
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 22,679,484=？",
        "answer": 8.054603173670559
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,823,358=？",
        "answer": 6.862931938183829
    },
    {
        "question": "1,132 × 619=？",
        "answer": 5.845537075872371
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 214,234,121=？",
        "answer": 8.330888641948127
    },
    {
        "question": "21,785 × 23,686=？",
        "answer": 8.71264928921559
    },
    {
        "question": "1,987,900 ÷ 6,016=？",
        "answer": 2.51908670612936
    },
    {
        "question": "191 × 32,480=？",
        "answer": 6.792649387816866
    },
    {
        "question": "728,178,087 ÷ 27,537,606=？",
        "answer": 1.4223114237246004
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 3,152,890=？",
        "answer": 8.581494189390915
    },
    {
        "question": "877,172 ÷ 223=？",
        "answer": 3.5947798971671134
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 53,755=？",
        "answer": 6.2744869105456775
    },
    {
        "question": "20,856 × 4,430=？",
        "answer": 7.965634744383342
    },
    {
        "question": "2,237,490 ÷ 870,150=？",
        "answer": 0.4101669784794092
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,762,307=？",
        "answer": 6.246081566273608
    },
    {
        "question": "157,715,676 ÷ 10,355=？",
        "answer": 4.1827247585328475
    },
    {
        "question": "20,606 ÷ 12,966=？",
        "answer": 0.20118767822287395
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 533,394=？",
        "answer": 7.451323995724899
    },
    {
        "question": "9,207,482 ÷ 4,731,914=？",
        "answer": 0.2891040355534066
    },
    {
        "question": "7,767 × 12,804=？",
        "answer": 7.997598970626629
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 92,701=？",
        "answer": 5.666054423401114
    },
    {
        "question": "21,862,936 ÷ 749,735=？",
        "answer": 1.4648006979002457
    },
    {
        "question": "505,913 ÷ 5,373=？",
        "answer": 1.9738589986653847
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 13,159=？",
        "answer": 5.663290931273859
    },
    {
        "question": "1,516 × 15,822=？",
        "answer": 7.379960581473113
    },
    {
        "question": "265 × 35,647=？",
        "answer": 6.975268860066668
    },
    {
        "question": "6,730 × 2,529=？",
        "answer": 7.230963893568382
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 64,281=？",
        "answer": 6.64693171506851
    },
    {
        "question": "140,566 ÷ 11,225=？",
        "answer": 1.0976939368830048
    },
    {
        "question": "2,945,406 ÷ 2,490=？",
        "answer": 3.0729458200772033
    },
    {
        "question": "3,328,508 ÷ 293=？",
        "answer": 4.055381984752621
    },
    {
        "question": "944,731,975 ÷ 87,157=？",
        "answer": 4.035006341416761
    },
    {
        "question": "450,077,506 ÷ 146,762,999=？",
        "answer": 0.48667073060492766
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 28,414=？",
        "answer": 5.972046316002994
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 13,677=？",
        "answer": 4.135990846921625
    },
    {
        "question": "23,407,088 ÷ 2,498,819=？",
        "answer": 0.9716125884028164
    },
    {
        "question": "152 × 377=？",
        "answer": 4.758184938150565
    },
    {
        "question": "4,008,562 ÷ 16,015=？",
        "answer": 2.398461662171846
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,805=？",
        "answer": 4.064832219738574
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 13,465=？",
        "answer": 5.634356336067436
    },
    {
        "question": "494 × 11,423=？",
        "answer": 6.751507125718229
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 10,503=？",
        "answer": 5.860162456221951
    },
    {
        "question": "113,836,328 ÷ 73,431=？",
        "answer": 3.1904014357666166
    },
    {
        "question": "57,347,151 ÷ 797=？",
        "answer": 4.85705352567617
    },
    {
        "question": "9,364,344 ÷ 885=？",
        "answer": 4.02453408846577
    },
    {
        "question": "117 × 17,696=？",
        "answer": 6.316060971370766
    },
    {
        "question": "47,466 ÷ 9,397=？",
        "answer": 0.7033934080413916
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 523=？",
        "answer": 3.621591675859218
    },
    {
        "question": "4,145 × 437=？",
        "answer": 6.258005971856714
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 22,472=？",
        "answer": 5.050611730529541
    },
    {
        "question": "1,664,302 ÷ 30,456=？",
        "answer": 1.7375592712692558
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 889=？",
        "answer": 4.179350682348487
    },
    {
        "question": "682 ÷ 577=？",
        "answer": 0.07260856150074749
    },
    {
        "question": "733,193,820 ÷ 11,489=？",
        "answer": 4.8049365662528025
    },
    {
        "question": "17,430,392 ÷ 3,809,110=？",
        "answer": 0.6604836398080817
    },
    {
        "question": "16,881,638 ÷ 2,982=？",
        "answer": 3.752906944158943
    },
    {
        "question": "268,111,773 ÷ 107,873,910=？",
        "answer": 0.3953994641509188
    },
    {
        "question": "294 × 407=？",
        "answer": 5.077941739637377
    },
    {
        "question": "385 × 1,121,228=？",
        "answer": 8.635154664202934
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 554,156,690=？",
        "answer": 8.743632580578277
    },
    {
        "question": "297,615,665 ÷ 8,126=？",
        "answer": 4.563778968574349
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 1,583,280=？",
        "answer": 7.561285561809652
    },
    {
        "question": "12,455,396 ÷ 689=？",
        "answer": 4.257138317903951
    },
    {
        "question": "348 × 17,057=？",
        "answer": 6.773481893403224
    },
    {
        "question": "157 × 6,523=？",
        "answer": 6.0103470309317215
    },
    {
        "question": "391,005 ÷ 2,430=？",
        "answer": 2.206576037399922
    },
    {
        "question": "408,388,523 ÷ 260=？",
        "answer": 6.196100180576751
    },
    {
        "question": "204,768 ÷ 11,367=？",
        "answer": 1.2556162284943415
    },
    {
        "question": "3,344,185 ÷ 278=？",
        "answer": 4.0802454986433965
    },
    {
        "question": "334,856 ÷ 888=？",
        "answer": 2.576445119316939
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 37,465,529=？",
        "answer": 8.652813115109304
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 15,187,977=？",
        "answer": 8.905775800392709
    },
    {
        "question": "737 × 19,443=？",
        "answer": 7.156230764031865
    },
    {
        "question": "11,378 ÷ 593=？",
        "answer": 1.2830112360674901
    },
    {
        "question": "6,086 × 11,833=？",
        "answer": 7.857426812537894
    },
    {
        "question": "9,468,542 ÷ 1,788,705=？",
        "answer": 0.7237443889491052
    },
    {
        "question": "510,436 ÷ 6,678=？",
        "answer": 1.8832948819704542
    },
    {
        "question": "320,468,690 ÷ 3,905,267=？",
        "answer": 1.914134873476525
    },
    {
        "question": "1,120 × 40,408=？",
        "answer": 7.655685378174475
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 1,580=？",
        "answer": 4.3747483460101035
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 305,988=？",
        "answer": 6.6898243776473985
    },
    {
        "question": "26,810 ÷ 493=？",
        "answer": 1.7354498947056496
    },
    {
        "question": "203 × 3,092,020=？",
        "answer": 8.797738332299716
    },
    {
        "question": "770,329,955 ÷ 33,388=？",
        "answer": 4.3630863813070375
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 18,753=？",
        "answer": 4.875130744950428
    },
    {
        "question": "80,640 ÷ 63,639=？",
        "answer": 0.10282717241813902
    },
    {
        "question": "10,740 × 7,684=？",
        "answer": 7.916591637553193
    },
    {
        "question": "14,491 ÷ 570=？",
        "answer": 1.4052235007784337
    },
    {
        "question": "3,112 × 406=？",
        "answer": 6.101565621894846
    },
    {
        "question": "348 ÷ 220=？",
        "answer": 0.19915656312437466
    },
    {
        "question": "179 × 328=？",
        "answer": 4.7687268746915725
    },
    {
        "question": "286,930,926 ÷ 74,435,423=？",
        "answer": 0.5859976992018321
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 63,186=？",
        "answer": 6.380404459768223
    },
    {
        "question": "60,909,884 ÷ 112,101=？",
        "answer": 2.7350782856609452
    },
    {
        "question": "291,715,520 ÷ 1,672=？",
        "answer": 5.241723262193082
    },
    {
        "question": "14,621,164 ÷ 465,910=？",
        "answer": 1.496679916480566
    },
    {
        "question": "144,268,267 ÷ 3,311,461=？",
        "answer": 1.6391511703244872
    },
    {
        "question": "3,688 ÷ 2,297=？",
        "answer": 0.20562991718656567
    },
    {
        "question": "1,492 × 88,515=？",
        "answer": 8.12078569683133
    },
    {
        "question": "56,145 × 1,508=？",
        "answer": 7.927712427703859
    },
    {
        "question": "3,989 × 1,555=？",
        "answer": 6.792594429672696
    },
    {
        "question": "224,315,572 ÷ 315=？",
        "answer": 5.852548869587967
    },
    {
        "question": "503 × 802,731=？",
        "answer": 8.606138020013484
    },
    {
        "question": "359 × 3,122=？",
        "answer": 6.049527347304718
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 3,697,666=？",
        "answer": 7.169987671296617
    },
    {
        "question": "721 × 345,448=？",
        "answer": 8.396317947362505
    },
    {
        "question": "150,299 ÷ 11,685=？",
        "answer": 1.1093273743315388
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 546=？",
        "answer": 3.3392526340327
    },
    {
        "question": "236,544,716 ÷ 1,011=？",
        "answer": 5.369162095514051
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 13,200=？",
        "answer": 4.722633922533812
    },
    {
        "question": "41,798 ÷ 443=？",
        "answer": 1.9747517754145467
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 714=？",
        "answer": 3.7567881987681178
    },
    {
        "question": "35,180,849 ÷ 15,425,482=？",
        "answer": 0.3580675725208329
    },
    {
        "question": "290,930 ÷ 1,126=？",
        "answer": 2.412250116440508
    },
    {
        "question": "639,717 ÷ 286=？",
        "answer": 3.3496218587923536
    },
    {
        "question": "562 ÷ 474=？",
        "answer": 0.073957973894976
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,365,167=？",
        "answer": 6.729583244670972
    },
    {
        "question": "428,250 ÷ 416,528=？",
        "answer": 0.01205317060839389
    },
    {
        "question": "1,542 × 45,572=？",
        "answer": 7.846782462422553
    },
    {
        "question": "18,323,383 ÷ 1,150=？",
        "answer": 4.202307819076195
    },
    {
        "question": "142,910 ÷ 76,287=？",
        "answer": 0.2726120827013826
    },
    {
        "question": "6,906 ÷ 776=？",
        "answer": 0.949364852755247
    },
    {
        "question": "44,220,372 ÷ 685=？",
        "answer": 4.809931820229865
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 519,656=？",
        "answer": 6.192837200778289
    },
    {
        "question": "3,138 × 9,179=？",
        "answer": 7.459448309108151
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 306=？",
        "answer": 3.087781417809542
    },
    {
        "question": "30,786 × 5,609=？",
        "answer": 8.237238705048545
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 33,636=？",
        "answer": 4.8278343394718926
    },
    {
        "question": "4,030,237 ÷ 2,049,068=？",
        "answer": 0.29377421472676396
    },
    {
        "question": "15,623 × 3,117=？",
        "answer": 7.687501235041225
    },
    {
        "question": "16,209,204 ÷ 378=？",
        "answer": 4.632269888244126
    },
    {
        "question": "29,115,899 ÷ 49,068=？",
        "answer": 2.7733318475865993
    },
    {
        "question": "15,569,887 ÷ 154,939=？",
        "answer": 2.002124712007508
    },
    {
        "question": "81,077,937 ÷ 60,744,979=？",
        "answer": 0.12539230343038688
    },
    {
        "question": "39,898 ÷ 3,799=？",
        "answer": 1.0212818324394544
    },
    {
        "question": "1,202 × 461,934=？",
        "answer": 8.744484396722005
    },
    {
        "question": "205 × 567,641=？",
        "answer": 8.065827617521753
    },
    {
        "question": "7,839,739 ÷ 2,083,907=？",
        "answer": 0.5754232709347566
    },
    {
        "question": "346,234,122 ÷ 8,891,932=？",
        "answer": 1.5903737333326722
    },
    {
        "question": "21,136 × 1,711=？",
        "answer": 7.558272809811553
    },
    {
        "question": "2,816,287 ÷ 938,204=？",
        "answer": 0.47737963025743857
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 751,036=？",
        "answer": 6.176690750546484
    },
    {
        "question": "553,690,840 ÷ 6,673=？",
        "answer": 4.918946213957604
    },
    {
        "question": "281 × 2,216,353=？",
        "answer": 8.794345251838228
    },
    {
        "question": "228,481 ÷ 902=？",
        "answer": 2.403643553348657
    },
    {
        "question": "90,791,242 ÷ 2,140=？",
        "answer": 4.627630183822581
    },
    {
        "question": "22,449,150 ÷ 5,724=？",
        "answer": 3.593500276719391
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,287=？",
        "answer": 4.234213474838595
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 38,528=？",
        "answer": 5.284746469577731
    },
    {
        "question": "13,377 ÷ 755=？",
        "answer": 1.2484117754400814
    },
    {
        "question": "52,870,653 ÷ 1,103,273=？",
        "answer": 1.6805316843873914
    },
    {
        "question": "2,478 × 13,542=？",
        "answer": 7.5257841115014505
    },
    {
        "question": "224,356,001 ÷ 38,739=？",
        "answer": 3.7627892846435618
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 368=？",
        "answer": 2.866877814337499
    },
    {
        "question": "266 × 30,344=？",
        "answer": 6.906954466325801
    },
    {
        "question": "3,727,595 ÷ 7,254=？",
        "answer": 2.710851169277675
    },
    {
        "question": "2,415,993 ÷ 137,639=？",
        "answer": 1.2443541629989538
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 397,755=？",
        "answer": 6.979826889386004
    },
    {
        "question": "9,016 ÷ 2,538=？",
        "answer": 0.5505222852793641
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 15,999=？",
        "answer": 5.772294562469534
    },
    {
        "question": "304,090 ÷ 41,659=？",
        "answer": 0.863293297853333
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 48,324,135=？",
        "answer": 8.462315339300705
    },
    {
        "question": "5,718 × 47,977=？",
        "answer": 8.438277239085222
    },
    {
        "question": "567,526 ÷ 206=？",
        "answer": 3.440118542232349
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 24,199=？",
        "answer": 5.985857410884626
    },
    {
        "question": "60,082,327 ÷ 2,852=？",
        "answer": 4.323597223450251
    },
    {
        "question": "314,017 × 397=？",
        "answer": 8.095743666958436
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 83,202,811=？",
        "answer": 8.765236039155534
    },
    {
        "question": "7,245,367 ÷ 16,392=？",
        "answer": 2.645428443315103
    },
    {
        "question": "763,307,642 ÷ 6,536=？",
        "answer": 5.067387566901018
    },
    {
        "question": "657,883 × 649=？",
        "answer": 8.630393360972928
    },
    {
        "question": "49,826 ÷ 8,430=？",
        "answer": 0.7716284490573416
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 8,799=？",
        "answer": 4.245463313364196
    },
    {
        "question": "135 × 1,712,035=？",
        "answer": 8.363846407429302
    },
    {
        "question": "83,992 ÷ 27,629=？",
        "answer": 0.48287275630316606
    },
    {
        "question": "5,273 ÷ 719=？",
        "answer": 0.8653288809485815
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 79,800=？",
        "answer": 5.943395576508954
    },
    {
        "question": "317 × 2,397,845=？",
        "answer": 8.880880368495037
    },
    {
        "question": "126,223,373 ÷ 3,802=？",
        "answer": 4.521127668884636
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 780=？",
        "answer": 3.971275848738105
    },
    {
        "question": "417 × 404=？",
        "answer": 5.226517420084362
    },
    {
        "question": "1,280 × 1,886=？",
        "answer": 6.382751658049178
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 17,815=？",
        "answer": 4.727907081406697
    },
    {
        "question": "3,084,633 ÷ 6,955=？",
        "answer": 2.6469063661137686
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 715,188=？",
        "answer": 7.345781912740836
    },
    {
        "question": "12,276 ÷ 505=？",
        "answer": 1.3857655016411237
    },
    {
        "question": "57,481 × 11,822=？",
        "answer": 8.832215269984871
    },
    {
        "question": "110,454 ÷ 109,010=？",
        "answer": 0.005715108463201927
    },
    {
        "question": "6,170 ÷ 5,641=？",
        "answer": 0.03892906430784803
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 10,933,696=？",
        "answer": 8.400494830636429
    },
    {
        "question": "299,248 ÷ 186,984=？",
        "answer": 0.20422681045524926
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,330=？",
        "answer": 3.367355921026019
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 3,831=？",
        "answer": 5.354164163625222
    },
    {
        "question": "4,653 ÷ 241=？",
        "answer": 1.285716009958399
    },
    {
        "question": "217 × 1,410,714=？",
        "answer": 8.485898710174386
    },
    {
        "question": "82,412,147 ÷ 62,744,125=？",
        "answer": 0.11841816130849044
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 1,039=？",
        "answer": 4.584817271624172
    },
    {
        "question": "738,902,648 ÷ 24,866=？",
        "answer": 4.472981293626273
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 5,568=？",
        "answer": 4.921790485658187
    },
    {
        "question": "22,695 × 391=？",
        "answer": 6.948106944474735
    },
    {
        "question": "193,320 ÷ 328=？",
        "answer": 2.770402942755164
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 35,540,317=？",
        "answer": 8.912449133171085
    },
    {
        "question": "2,924 × 158,290=？",
        "answer": 8.665430847380653
    },
    {
        "question": "752,715,751 ÷ 452,117,544=？",
        "answer": 0.22137964423144227
    },
    {
        "question": "73 × 3,144,298=？",
        "answer": 8.360846559581514
    },
    {
        "question": "298,338 ÷ 31,528=？",
        "answer": 0.976012152118807
    },
    {
        "question": "83,715,946 ÷ 1,195,488=？",
        "answer": 1.8452629680408577
    },
    {
        "question": "23,786,283 ÷ 961=？",
        "answer": 4.393603193977335
    },
    {
        "question": "4,585 × 25,323=？",
        "answer": 8.064854494995384
    },
    {
        "question": "5,269,128 ÷ 38,542=？",
        "answer": 2.135804501704005
    },
    {
        "question": "47,229,424 ÷ 314,361=？",
        "answer": 2.1767839874272923
    },
    {
        "question": "225,523 ÷ 862=？",
        "answer": 2.4176835742416527
    },
    {
        "question": "175,299 ÷ 1,460=？",
        "answer": 2.0794265828665703
    },
    {
        "question": "2,010,729 ÷ 49,100=？",
        "answer": 1.612272049515321
    },
    {
        "question": "6,061 ÷ 1,311=？",
        "answer": 0.6649415923199258
    },
    {
        "question": "382,701 × 325=？",
        "answer": 8.094742958018934
    },
    {
        "question": "6,284 × 7,061=？",
        "answer": 7.647102387862715
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 2,071=？",
        "answer": 4.357572784051678
    },
    {
        "question": "789 × 1,690=？",
        "answer": 6.124963707823094
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 3,732=？",
        "answer": 5.3353696286374
    },
    {
        "question": "101 × 505=？",
        "answer": 4.707612751901304
    },
    {
        "question": "116,102 × 5,410=？",
        "answer": 8.798036966167128
    },
    {
        "question": "3,574,208 ÷ 9,419=？",
        "answer": 2.5791750256493025
    },
    {
        "question": "29,907 ÷ 395=？",
        "answer": 1.8791757550915758
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 31,355=？",
        "answer": 5.195276809447387
    },
    {
        "question": "726,100 × 473=？",
        "answer": 8.535857577495007
    },
    {
        "question": "45,508,743 ÷ 11,378=？",
        "answer": 3.6020289105636984
    },
    {
        "question": "9,150,852 ÷ 6,458,178=？",
        "answer": 0.15135152055740625
    },
    {
        "question": "2,719 × 149,402=？",
        "answer": 8.608765618876452
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 483,294,426=？",
        "answer": 8.684211786300889
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 1,919=？",
        "answer": 4.7302330060776905
    },
    {
        "question": "10,656,288 ÷ 1,480=？",
        "answer": 3.857344233961354
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 1,057=？",
        "answer": 5.214406685477718
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 55,838=？",
        "answer": 5.977378775754856
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,613=？",
        "answer": 3.894260664446988
    },
    {
        "question": "936,413,713 ÷ 399,568,731=？",
        "answer": 0.36987627059764633
    },
    {
        "question": "8,140,858 ÷ 20,545=？",
        "answer": 2.59796403386484
    },
    {
        "question": "1,004,536 ÷ 3,483=？",
        "answer": 2.460012030907956
    },
    {
        "question": "9,389,675 ÷ 2,313=？",
        "answer": 3.6084749277437034
    },
    {
        "question": "67,729 ÷ 1,290=？",
        "answer": 1.7201849531162368
    },
    {
        "question": "253,298 × 1,389=？",
        "answer": 8.546334006422782
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 25,191=？",
        "answer": 5.816218755876306
    },
    {
        "question": "550,173 ÷ 41,385=？",
        "answer": 1.1236563138348012
    },
    {
        "question": "10,964,431 ÷ 896,528=？",
        "answer": 1.087422241032712
    },
    {
        "question": "1,711 × 111,493=？",
        "answer": 8.280497610944964
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 842=？",
        "answer": 2.9253120914996495
    },
    {
        "question": "513 × 3,641=？",
        "answer": 6.27133804404576
    },
    {
        "question": "25,702,351 ÷ 477,525=？",
        "answer": 1.7309767369095572
    },
    {
        "question": "528,121 ÷ 15,722=？",
        "answer": 1.526225645010628
    },
    {
        "question": "12,840 ÷ 609=？",
        "answer": 1.323947731099959
    },
    {
        "question": "1,677 × 4,158=？",
        "answer": 6.843417547601536
    },
    {
        "question": "237,634,179 ÷ 1,272=？",
        "answer": 5.2714217942036425
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 2,268,258=？",
        "answer": 7.802850482622928
    },
    {
        "question": "3,670,246 ÷ 5,159=？",
        "answer": 2.8521296461504666
    },
    {
        "question": "4,883 × 45,764=？",
        "answer": 8.349210701214338
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 17,358,089=？",
        "answer": 7.239501910792186
    },
    {
        "question": "4,642 × 50,980=？",
        "answer": 8.374104967253148
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 27,852=？",
        "answer": 5.700128891606848
    },
    {
        "question": "3,951,961 ÷ 2,280=？",
        "answer": 3.2388778030931813
    },
    {
        "question": "663 ÷ 268=？",
        "answer": 0.3933787343759843
    },
    {
        "question": "3,535,599 ÷ 191,934=？",
        "answer": 1.265311088081753
    },
    {
        "question": "675,630,180 ÷ 2,788=？",
        "answer": 5.384416271583595
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 735,503=？",
        "answer": 6.8665844484854235
    },
    {
        "question": "848 × 791,232=？",
        "answer": 8.826699695484852
    },
    {
        "question": "249 × 14,924=？",
        "answer": 6.570084587464528
    },
    {
        "question": "59,820,086 ÷ 268=？",
        "answer": 5.348712239027905
    },
    {
        "question": "10,428,577 ÷ 380,155=？",
        "answer": 1.4382643451949861
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 36,645=？",
        "answer": 5.1660747173570805
    },
    {
        "question": "439 × 1,353=？",
        "answer": 5.773762316839744
    },
    {
        "question": "397 × 31,054=？",
        "answer": 7.090908055431647
    },
    {
        "question": "88,707,868 ÷ 866,706=？",
        "answer": 2.0100903384696958
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 223=？",
        "answer": 3.1264561134318045
    },
    {
        "question": "1,177 × 1,142=？",
        "answer": 6.128442566753264
    },
    {
        "question": "2,401,278 ÷ 310=？",
        "answer": 3.8890807481373395
    },
    {
        "question": "1,252 × 1,256=？",
        "answer": 6.196593968275589
    },
    {
        "question": "50,109 ÷ 3,449=？",
        "answer": 1.1622225414659786
    },
    {
        "question": "34,651,687 ÷ 2,392,386=？",
        "answer": 1.1608931305712393
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 77,596=？",
        "answer": 5.366960589087364
    },
    {
        "question": "590,820,729 ÷ 10,729=？",
        "answer": 4.740896478878185
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 31,895=？",
        "answer": 4.980843861206142
    },
    {
        "question": "15,220,043 ÷ 8,767,135=？",
        "answer": 0.23955818536127463
    },
    {
        "question": "1,193,122 ÷ 45,067=？",
        "answer": 1.4228262046325906
    },
    {
        "question": "11,554 ÷ 1,033=？",
        "answer": 1.0486320416857733
    },
    {
        "question": "8,245,966 ÷ 2,328=？",
        "answer": 3.549258563795902
    },
    {
        "question": "1,961,931 ÷ 61,850=？",
        "answer": 1.5013440254568766
    },
    {
        "question": "879,793,015 ÷ 338,564=？",
        "answer": 3.4147397325638367
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 5,267=？",
        "answer": 4.420533322693499
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 2,654=？",
        "answer": 4.679173423631723
    },
    {
        "question": "113,141 × 727=？",
        "answer": 7.915154423804728
    },
    {
        "question": "665,789 ÷ 819=？",
        "answer": 2.910052713814263
    },
    {
        "question": "606,305,376 ÷ 1,293,308=？",
        "answer": 2.670989455070483
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 2,856=？",
        "answer": 4.4557582031041365
    },
    {
        "question": "19,611 ÷ 1,618=？",
        "answer": 1.083521222409327
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 459=？",
        "answer": 2.661812685537261
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 273,219=？",
        "answer": 7.199938891018392
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 84,997=？",
        "answer": 5.8324935843951975
    },
    {
        "question": "253,418,142 ÷ 4,143=？",
        "answer": 4.7865227691530725
    },
    {
        "question": "2,666 × 144,295=？",
        "answer": 8.58511142759177
    },
    {
        "question": "38,807 × 630=？",
        "answer": 7.388250620078046
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 986=？",
        "answer": 3.993876914941211
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,279=？",
        "answer": 3.3577443251803754
    },
    {
        "question": "430,061 ÷ 319=？",
        "answer": 3.1297393773700626
    },
    {
        "question": "916,269 ÷ 565,092=？",
        "answer": 0.20990383434938192
    },
    {
        "question": "3,155 × 263=？",
        "answer": 5.918955112069911
    },
    {
        "question": "535,005 ÷ 11,076=？",
        "answer": 1.683974893755659
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 282,064=？",
        "answer": 6.491740345581465
    },
    {
        "question": "40,935,450 ÷ 179,058=？",
        "answer": 2.3591058396115026
    },
    {
        "question": "122,916 ÷ 3,297=？",
        "answer": 1.571489471621521
    },
    {
        "question": "109,701 ÷ 293=？",
        "answer": 2.5733429661312894
    },
    {
        "question": "90,034 ÷ 88,846=？",
        "answer": 0.005768665365407489
    },
    {
        "question": "37,323,578 ÷ 1,129,642=？",
        "answer": 1.5190424393797313
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,776=？",
        "answer": 3.8780619812900126
    },
    {
        "question": "26,665 × 1,989=？",
        "answer": 7.724576371143331
    },
    {
        "question": "31,030,557 ÷ 13,854=？",
        "answer": 3.350214387960282
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 3,333,154=？",
        "answer": 7.522855379608669
    },
    {
        "question": "631,188,948 ÷ 6,838=？",
        "answer": 4.9652302893925055
    },
    {
        "question": "167,501 × 1,019=？",
        "answer": 8.232191588174429
    },
    {
        "question": "3,074 × 11,453=？",
        "answer": 7.546623123882611
    },
    {
        "question": "12,421 × 2,148=？",
        "answer": 7.426190838810041
    },
    {
        "question": "742,087,285 ÷ 36,823=？",
        "answer": 4.304335822469377
    },
    {
        "question": "50,845,094 ÷ 67,149=？",
        "answer": 2.8792095051451367
    },
    {
        "question": "838,513,715 ÷ 207,275,848=？",
        "answer": 0.6069614698687416
    },
    {
        "question": "436,600,056 ÷ 1,119,346=？",
        "answer": 2.5911194354337077
    },
    {
        "question": "13,073 ÷ 599=？",
        "answer": 1.3389484387903936
    },
    {
        "question": "312,420 × 880=？",
        "answer": 8.439221500209504
    },
    {
        "question": "58,189,933 ÷ 697=？",
        "answer": 4.921615079048193
    },
    {
        "question": "745,709,841 ÷ 412,391,213=？",
        "answer": 0.25726047142789166
    },
    {
        "question": "49,961,631 ÷ 6,195=？",
        "answer": 3.9065952967870143
    },
    {
        "question": "110,506,815 ÷ 1,278,396=？",
        "answer": 1.9367236588645236
    },
    {
        "question": "502,539 × 1,051=？",
        "answer": 8.722772487250227
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 234=？",
        "answer": 3.2723058444020863
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,352,730=？",
        "answer": 6.970938397062985
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 455=？",
        "answer": 2.9590413923210934
    },
    {
        "question": "75,629 × 700=？",
        "answer": 7.72378639801511
    },
    {
        "question": "3,592 × 20,372=？",
        "answer": 7.864369995499407
    },
    {
        "question": "250,114,875 ÷ 3,563,655=？",
        "answer": 1.8462438681128186
    },
    {
        "question": "11,584,576 ÷ 208=？",
        "answer": 4.745816808106685
    },
    {
        "question": "1,318 × 1,437=？",
        "answer": 6.277372178392216
    },
    {
        "question": "807 × 2,555=？",
        "answer": 6.314264439192802
    },
    {
        "question": "55,420,001 ÷ 11,236,291=？",
        "answer": 0.6930435511509477
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 2,957=？",
        "answer": 5.379336343404767
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 562=？",
        "answer": 2.749736315569061
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 131,494=？",
        "answer": 6.198087182703513
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 1,339=？",
        "answer": 4.272908612690247
    },
    {
        "question": "32,733 × 1,490=？",
        "answer": 7.688172078906311
    },
    {
        "question": "1,047,319 ÷ 33,244=？",
        "answer": 1.4983657087461852
    },
    {
        "question": "7,254 ÷ 632=？",
        "answer": 1.0598604729620305
    },
    {
        "question": "1,639 × 661=？",
        "answer": 6.034780413056139
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 4,063=？",
        "answer": 5.2216306790461475
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 7,469,226=？",
        "answer": 7.776365587288616
    },
    {
        "question": "606,643 ÷ 191,472=？",
        "answer": 0.5008279169922488
    },
    {
        "question": "615 × 17,302=？",
        "answer": 7.026971423456826
    },
    {
        "question": "4,803 × 29,588=？",
        "answer": 8.152628196668832
    },
    {
        "question": "450,280,122 ÷ 1,250=？",
        "answer": 5.556572762077768
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 20,725,245=？",
        "answer": 8.520619655847797
    },
    {
        "question": "454,581,190 ÷ 229,607,752=？",
        "answer": 0.2966249146075515
    },
    {
        "question": "19,055,700 ÷ 20,107=？",
        "answer": 2.976677629030548
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 2,866=？",
        "answer": 4.411518695500651
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 140,237,945=？",
        "answer": 8.623986793845765
    },
    {
        "question": "2,727,298 ÷ 502,337=？",
        "answer": 0.7347374263888752
    },
    {
        "question": "127 × 6,511=？",
        "answer": 5.917451416302853
    },
    {
        "question": "18,676,529 ÷ 2,608=？",
        "answer": 3.8549885794693535
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 4,227=？",
        "answer": 5.599160101428717
    },
    {
        "question": "52,841 ÷ 236=？",
        "answer": 2.3500590249423383
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 20,049,256=？",
        "answer": 7.302098261191132
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 14,581=？",
        "answer": 5.367907292617928
    },
    {
        "question": "7,953,082 ÷ 382,070=？",
        "answer": 1.3183925218758874
    },
    {
        "question": "286,785,160 ÷ 148,347,490=？",
        "answer": 0.28627647198392536
    },
    {
        "question": "116,700,417 ÷ 319,912=？",
        "answer": 2.5620418769791633
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 17,765=？",
        "answer": 4.550595207489328
    },
    {
        "question": "162 × 216=？",
        "answer": 4.5439687656935615
    },
    {
        "question": "252,414 × 2,134=？",
        "answer": 8.731307854226824
    },
    {
        "question": "26,030 ÷ 12,639=？",
        "answer": 0.3137614542627255
    },
    {
        "question": "249 × 596,518=？",
        "answer": 8.171822900186303
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 7,000,061=？",
        "answer": 8.498314338339311
    },
    {
        "question": "9,954 × 533=？",
        "answer": 6.724724845434577
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 1,099=？",
        "answer": 5.0663035576882605
    },
    {
        "question": "273 × 488=？",
        "answer": 5.1245824690434665
    },
    {
        "question": "1,178 × 3,540=？",
        "answer": 6.620148552476871
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 47,676,316=？",
        "answer": 8.523400729643159
    },
    {
        "question": "206,758 ÷ 98,855=？",
        "answer": 0.3204636820799736
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,303,614=？",
        "answer": 7.053217318644796
    },
    {
        "question": "2,244,789 ÷ 1,349,894=？",
        "answer": 0.22087585854637587
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 263=？",
        "answer": 2.7209857441537393
    },
    {
        "question": "828,885 ÷ 1,640=？",
        "answer": 2.7036504324062194
    },
    {
        "question": "163 × 113,111=？",
        "answer": 7.2656924463497585
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 206,716,903=？",
        "answer": 8.315375989832377
    },
    {
        "question": "205,763,214 ÷ 10,039,931=？",
        "answer": 1.3116370068261503
    },
    {
        "question": "16,156 ÷ 1,366=？",
        "answer": 1.0728831451524368
    },
    {
        "question": "43,142 ÷ 214=？",
        "answer": 2.3044865011407993
    },
    {
        "question": "1,070 × 488,841=？",
        "answer": 8.71855140152982
    },
    {
        "question": "3,075 × 4,366=？",
        "answer": 7.127928851484556
    },
    {
        "question": "277 × 3,547=？",
        "answer": 5.992340957536391
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,315=？",
        "answer": 4.118925752825777
    },
    {
        "question": "8,817,406 ÷ 1,308,209=？",
        "answer": 0.8286637058736375
    },
    {
        "question": "687,701 ÷ 970=？",
        "answer": 2.850627921592669
    },
    {
        "question": "264,128 ÷ 4,182=？",
        "answer": 1.8004304143796501
    },
    {
        "question": "942,773 ÷ 328=？",
        "answer": 3.4585332925940233
    },
    {
        "question": "5,059,859 ÷ 993=？",
        "answer": 3.7071891662939938
    },
    {
        "question": "8,377 × 431=？",
        "answer": 6.55756578560313
    },
    {
        "question": "730,204,916 ÷ 515,213,120=？",
        "answer": 0.1514578385648626
    },
    {
        "question": "4,020 × 1,392=？",
        "answer": 6.747865288359013
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 879,049=？",
        "answer": 7.0901411198947795
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 7,097=？",
        "answer": 5.282438569387875
    },
    {
        "question": "266,017 × 368=？",
        "answer": 7.990757210080071
    },
    {
        "question": "43,033 × 8,816=？",
        "answer": 8.579073205025313
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 78,888=？",
        "answer": 6.294950954465268
    },
    {
        "question": "12,769,856 ÷ 2,650=？",
        "answer": 3.6829401260080483
    },
    {
        "question": "3,021 × 16,249=？",
        "answer": 7.690977363951536
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 278,019,514=？",
        "answer": 8.444075279821284
    },
    {
        "question": "740 × 38,710=？",
        "answer": 7.457054891049931
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 4,775=？",
        "answer": 5.678973375919766
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 32,551,664=？",
        "answer": 7.8136031897217
    },
    {
        "question": "143 × 124,197=？",
        "answer": 7.249447142974051
    },
    {
        "question": "90,796 × 3,801=？",
        "answer": 8.537964585787266
    },
    {
        "question": "9,848,544 ÷ 345,440=？",
        "answer": 1.4549994045424708
    },
    {
        "question": "17,963 ÷ 17,574=？",
        "answer": 0.009508247829650887
    },
    {
        "question": "1,528 × 15,331=？",
        "answer": 7.369693837881892
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 170,158,390=？",
        "answer": 8.230853367718463
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 44,637=？",
        "answer": 6.35726517458957
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 8,052=？",
        "answer": 4.6048737705526355
    },
    {
        "question": "22,074 × 1,290=？",
        "answer": 7.454470748514019
    },
    {
        "question": "90,653,488 ÷ 622,527=？",
        "answer": 2.163226326517667
    },
    {
        "question": "196,781 ÷ 14,693=？",
        "answer": 1.1268726846373558
    },
    {
        "question": "72,773 × 1,061=？",
        "answer": 7.88768566258245
    },
    {
        "question": "26,326 ÷ 17,564=？",
        "answer": 0.17576144852805728
    },
    {
        "question": "3,868 × 137,747=？",
        "answer": 8.726568614512766
    },
    {
        "question": "916 × 167,448=？",
        "answer": 8.1857754383586
    },
    {
        "question": "345 × 1,665,065=？",
        "answer": 8.759250287023912
    },
    {
        "question": "185,662,397 ÷ 14,740,301=？",
        "answer": 1.1002176011286824
    },
    {
        "question": "21,414 ÷ 722=？",
        "answer": 1.472160600769665
    },
    {
        "question": "1,043 × 70,743=？",
        "answer": 7.867967781431693
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 103,347=？",
        "answer": 6.315327869928151
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 83,190=？",
        "answer": 6.879112516618617
    },
    {
        "question": "277,861 ÷ 2,469=？",
        "answer": 2.0513065044402796
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,627,111=？",
        "answer": 6.8213242448152975
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 704,325=？",
        "answer": 6.148803099602747
    },
    {
        "question": "718 × 799=？",
        "answer": 5.758671223556291
    },
    {
        "question": "1,118,476 ÷ 25,263=？",
        "answer": 1.646141747468055
    },
    {
        "question": "1,721 ÷ 1,201=？",
        "answer": 0.15623786292465422
    },
    {
        "question": "204 × 2,865,036=？",
        "answer": 8.766760250798459
    },
    {
        "question": "628 × 2,404=？",
        "answer": 6.178894107067898
    },
    {
        "question": "82,000,389 ÷ 170,678=？",
        "answer": 2.681638367462906
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 5,819,785=？",
        "answer": 7.878850293135706
    },
    {
        "question": "24,031,655 ÷ 78,720=？",
        "answer": 2.484698595185753
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 19,008,691=？",
        "answer": 7.881012202299116
    },
    {
        "question": "588,280 ÷ 24,609=？",
        "answer": 1.3784901174775384
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 144,905=？",
        "answer": 5.638204625939252
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 18,103=？",
        "answer": 6.021178544978192
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 7,097,131=？",
        "answer": 8.575358691181945
    },
    {
        "question": "31,809 ÷ 15,476=？",
        "answer": 0.31289129507769614
    },
    {
        "question": "232 × 698=？",
        "answer": 5.20934340751406
    },
    {
        "question": "87,274 ÷ 1,185=？",
        "answer": 1.867166530950234
    },
    {
        "question": "41,045 ÷ 7,101=？",
        "answer": 0.7619407473532227
    },
    {
        "question": "4,236,588 ÷ 51,210=？",
        "answer": 1.9176614559205403
    },
    {
        "question": "3,891 × 3,611=？",
        "answer": 7.147688719230569
    },
    {
        "question": "20,290,360 ÷ 1,771,391=？",
        "answer": 1.0589753187304716
    },
    {
        "question": "1,155 ÷ 243=？",
        "answer": 0.676975710629851
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 4,214=？",
        "answer": 5.650000396536852
    },
    {
        "question": "334,402 ÷ 1,737=？",
        "answer": 2.284469047767148
    },
    {
        "question": "896 × 1,064=？",
        "answer": 5.979249637621154
    },
    {
        "question": "693 × 451=？",
        "answer": 5.494909776489767
    },
    {
        "question": "47,371,959 ÷ 1,407=？",
        "answer": 4.527227247295287
    },
    {
        "question": "831 ÷ 625=？",
        "answer": 0.12372100644003574
    },
    {
        "question": "98,586 ÷ 17,225=？",
        "answer": 0.7576560154524279
    },
    {
        "question": "1,548,791 × 277=？",
        "answer": 8.632472585357736
    },
    {
        "question": "256,327 × 1,816=？",
        "answer": 8.667910198841483
    },
    {
        "question": "2,927,211 ÷ 3,022=？",
        "answer": 2.986159568489184
    },
    {
        "question": "470 × 2,772=？",
        "answer": 6.114891083875486
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 17,340=？",
        "answer": 6.198090485461285
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 2,273,195=？",
        "answer": 7.81903469002143
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 4,701=？",
        "answer": 4.950943852141082
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 139,214=？",
        "answer": 5.921834162504551
    },
    {
        "question": "187,113 ÷ 13,894=？",
        "answer": 1.1292766673717929
    },
    {
        "question": "182,354,802 ÷ 541=？",
        "answer": 5.527719939091863
    },
    {
        "question": "2,192 ÷ 678=？",
        "answer": 0.5096108559452682
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 14,590,070=？",
        "answer": 7.766117366877398
    },
    {
        "question": "33,909 ÷ 936=？",
        "answer": 1.559039133582427
    },
    {
        "question": "20,999 × 38,195=？",
        "answer": 8.90420512791559
    },
    {
        "question": "152,503 ÷ 5,152=？",
        "answer": 1.4713025327450202
    },
    {
        "question": "5,871,293 ÷ 5,267=？",
        "answer": 3.047170435518404
    },
    {
        "question": "10,571,725 ÷ 2,142,302=？",
        "answer": 0.6932651641568376
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 3,238=？",
        "answer": 4.686368103473036
    },
    {
        "question": "172,618 × 464=？",
        "answer": 7.903604061001741
    },
    {
        "question": "22,814 × 666=？",
        "answer": 7.181675666381548
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 41,779=？",
        "answer": 5.399109291109806
    },
    {
        "question": "29,808,801 ÷ 5,132=？",
        "answer": 3.764057860045402
    },
    {
        "question": "439,890 × 1,524=？",
        "answer": 8.826329056295329
    },
    {
        "question": "2,415 ÷ 304=？",
        "answer": 0.9000435514787772
    },
    {
        "question": "424,385,287 ÷ 82,507=？",
        "answer": 3.7112695227332515
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 1,679=？",
        "answer": 4.4803232012413545
    },
    {
        "question": "195,983,488 ÷ 62,605,851=？",
        "answer": 0.4956045594423112
    },
    {
        "question": "5,819 × 835=？",
        "answer": 6.686534832677013
    },
    {
        "question": "691,478 × 227=？",
        "answer": 8.195804224385245
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 6,677=？",
        "answer": 5.125611371897464
    },
    {
        "question": "6,900 ÷ 4,394=？",
        "answer": 0.19598903815276383
    },
    {
        "question": "424,321,752 ÷ 332,260=？",
        "answer": 3.1062172348348884
    },
    {
        "question": "864,385,815 ÷ 230,623,130=？",
        "answer": 0.5738047692267922
    },
    {
        "question": "8,783 × 4,415=？",
        "answer": 7.588573590665717
    },
    {
        "question": "148 × 4,123=？",
        "answer": 5.7854750501963155
    },
    {
        "question": "98,472,002 ÷ 53,749,540=？",
        "answer": 0.2629380156802248
    },
    {
        "question": "37,579,514 ÷ 1,447=？",
        "answer": 4.414482628134479
    },
    {
        "question": "438,958,410 ÷ 1,025=？",
        "answer": 5.63169950869283
    },
    {
        "question": "67 × 230=？",
        "answer": 4.187802638718419
    },
    {
        "question": "242,118,107 ÷ 4,404,900=？",
        "answer": 1.74009121621256
    },
    {
        "question": "2,097 ÷ 226=？",
        "answer": 0.9674899913179429
    },
    {
        "question": "136 × 31,871=？",
        "answer": 6.6369345986926644
    },
    {
        "question": "776,834,890 ÷ 73,326=？",
        "answer": 4.02507072833147
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 45,544,941=？",
        "answer": 7.959470139480069
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 35,032,839=？",
        "answer": 8.389573373223307
    },
    {
        "question": "6,607,111 ÷ 1,553,526=？",
        "answer": 0.628693076995019
    },
    {
        "question": "1,740 × 473=？",
        "answer": 5.915410389020411
    },
    {
        "question": "261,287,834 ÷ 35,410=？",
        "answer": 3.867993261960136
    },
    {
        "question": "567 × 60,935=？",
        "answer": 7.538449874360514
    },
    {
        "question": "6,179 × 39,158=？",
        "answer": 8.383738697264343
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 12,837,717=？",
        "answer": 8.011577784676621
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 709=？",
        "answer": 3.8048887446223913
    },
    {
        "question": "18,413,486 ÷ 5,029,834=？",
        "answer": 0.5635823637100122
    },
    {
        "question": "832 × 1,020=？",
        "answer": 5.9287234980526415
    },
    {
        "question": "1,305 × 6,616=？",
        "answer": 6.93620600821879
    },
    {
        "question": "81,449,952 ÷ 1,077,842=？",
        "answer": 1.8783357300723014
    },
    {
        "question": "236,110 ÷ 40,931=？",
        "answer": 0.7610620260236992
    },
    {
        "question": "217,929 × 644=？",
        "answer": 8.147200893392919
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 359,107=？",
        "answer": 5.555223870822936
    },
    {
        "question": "11,609 × 67,273=？",
        "answer": 8.89263560641787
    },
    {
        "question": "587,619,240 ÷ 234,852,954=？",
        "answer": 0.3982999800014531
    },
    {
        "question": "81,270 ÷ 1,473=？",
        "answer": 1.7417275129101997
    },
    {
        "question": "177,595,152 ÷ 31,710=？",
        "answer": 3.748234864188098
    },
    {
        "question": "199,054,008 ÷ 388,991=？",
        "answer": 2.7090313733661318
    },
    {
        "question": "17,125 × 275=？",
        "answer": 6.672963273994726
    },
    {
        "question": "140 × 1,441=？",
        "answer": 5.304792016492227
    },
    {
        "question": "2,615 × 4,859=？",
        "answer": 7.104018592266299
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,143=？",
        "answer": 3.0580462303952816
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 4,016=？",
        "answer": 5.490284429309445
    },
    {
        "question": "308 × 834=？",
        "answer": 5.409716767138183
    },
    {
        "question": "325,731,677 ÷ 855=？",
        "answer": 5.5808938804880635
    },
    {
        "question": "929,555,824 ÷ 1,201=？",
        "answer": 5.8887324688213765
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 243,290=？",
        "answer": 6.164275508783955
    },
    {
        "question": "765,421,284 ÷ 5,304,963=？",
        "answer": 2.159218175226315
    },
    {
        "question": "190,286 × 393=？",
        "answer": 7.873799387288779
    },
    {
        "question": "135,453 × 2,618=？",
        "answer": 8.549758270402807
    },
    {
        "question": "15,238,056 ÷ 4,944=？",
        "answer": 3.4888511031954965
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 755=？",
        "answer": 3.656098202012832
    },
    {
        "question": "68,754,966 ÷ 2,840=？",
        "answer": 4.383985731597204
    },
    {
        "question": "462 × 862,538=？",
        "answer": 8.60042021301364
    },
    {
        "question": "1,647 × 24,704=？",
        "answer": 7.609460877825397
    },
    {
        "question": "850,697,810 ÷ 41,059=？",
        "answer": 4.3163669469411605
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 456=？",
        "answer": 4.271748699384171
    },
    {
        "question": "705,430 ÷ 5,270=？",
        "answer": 2.1266433098629176
    },
    {
        "question": "31,124 ÷ 8,126=？",
        "answer": 0.5832185886528803
    },
    {
        "question": "1,026,075 ÷ 789,383=？",
        "answer": 0.11389133701014816
    },
    {
        "question": "36,452 × 2,149=？",
        "answer": 7.8939577770929015
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 50,515=？",
        "answer": 5.402390361661262
    },
    {
        "question": "61,428 × 4,396=？",
        "answer": 8.431424059349323
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,544,415=？",
        "answer": 6.790824002348863
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 2,802,217=？",
        "answer": 7.561445115752487
    },
    {
        "question": "7,677 ÷ 4,488=？",
        "answer": 0.23313869235874288
    },
    {
        "question": "148 × 84,583=？",
        "answer": 7.097544800087844
    },
    {
        "question": "37,132 ÷ 15,963=？",
        "answer": 0.36663382813689016
    },
    {
        "question": "589,480 ÷ 506=？",
        "answer": 3.066318558007789
    },
    {
        "question": "8,205,655 ÷ 1,502=？",
        "answer": 3.737443320793114
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 1,330=？",
        "answer": 4.916243330465339
    },
    {
        "question": "4,987,651 ÷ 11,631=？",
        "answer": 2.6322790013336608
    },
    {
        "question": "239,366,101 ÷ 69,747,530=？",
        "answer": 0.5355338133338094
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 264,475=？",
        "answer": 5.422384625803387
    },
    {
        "question": "4,419 × 12,958=？",
        "answer": 7.7578619771716015
    },
    {
        "question": "1,255,767 × 214=？",
        "answer": 8.42932283950088
    },
    {
        "question": "851 × 24,226=？",
        "answer": 7.314211272970172
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,572,654=？",
        "answer": 7.047092074687243
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 947=？",
        "answer": 4.768741668501527
    },
    {
        "question": "68,234,568 ÷ 491,232=？",
        "answer": 2.142717796320055
    },
    {
        "question": "8,739 × 39,350=？",
        "answer": 8.536406476042414
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 197,518=？",
        "answer": 5.596636675092103
    },
    {
        "question": "7,748,069 ÷ 219,290=？",
        "answer": 1.5481746520937425
    },
    {
        "question": "301,567 ÷ 22,473=？",
        "answer": 1.1277227638486327
    },
    {
        "question": "879,405 ÷ 205,076=？",
        "answer": 0.6322740925898095
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 3,567=？",
        "answer": 5.029424364058016
    },
    {
        "question": "198 × 277,944=？",
        "answer": 7.740622493586581
    },
    {
        "question": "194 × 16,525=？",
        "answer": 6.505943198087904
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 618,631=？",
        "answer": 5.791431678990164
    },
    {
        "question": "184 × 1,249,427=？",
        "answer": 8.361528709783869
    },
    {
        "question": "102,813 × 2,897=？",
        "answer": 8.473996526899123
    },
    {
        "question": "440 × 3,722=？",
        "answer": 6.214229045280936
    },
    {
        "question": "113,448 ÷ 53,778=？",
        "answer": 0.3241921972078431
    },
    {
        "question": "588,233 × 617=？",
        "answer": 8.559834548903185
    },
    {
        "question": "351,556,247 ÷ 344,037=？",
        "answer": 3.009389667595939
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 620,676=？",
        "answer": 7.15459278863824
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,802,311=？",
        "answer": 6.954799737666076
    },
    {
        "question": "2,799,222 ÷ 4,588=？",
        "answer": 2.7854139335212187
    },
    {
        "question": "7,537 ÷ 505=？",
        "answer": 1.1739071371531284
    },
    {
        "question": "4,958,408 ÷ 708,794=？",
        "answer": 0.8448222270399027
    },
    {
        "question": "459 × 1,042=？",
        "answer": 5.6796804045007665
    },
    {
        "question": "126,245,689 ÷ 90,614,825=？",
        "answer": 0.1440173008317585
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 275,195=？",
        "answer": 6.983708583317324
    },
    {
        "question": "79,386,862 ÷ 13,845,310=？",
        "answer": 0.7584459513586345
    },
    {
        "question": "630 × 4,434=？",
        "answer": 6.446136238232051
    },
    {
        "question": "1,849,801 ÷ 9,795=？",
        "answer": 2.276120569558489
    },
    {
        "question": "62,365 × 5,448=？",
        "answer": 8.531178025584461
    },
    {
        "question": "120 × 115,533=？",
        "answer": 7.141887296690545
    },
    {
        "question": "3,750 ÷ 3,216=？",
        "answer": 0.06671522765130522
    },
    {
        "question": "55,308,169 ÷ 30,592=？",
        "answer": 3.257181410611203
    },
    {
        "question": "15,773,727 ÷ 1,023,761=？",
        "answer": 1.1877357389519592
    },
    {
        "question": "5,576 ÷ 370=？",
        "answer": 1.1781210410229581
    },
    {
        "question": "358,924 ÷ 63,543=？",
        "answer": 0.7519347841261338
    },
    {
        "question": "57,974 ÷ 6,077=？",
        "answer": 0.9795440298332997
    },
    {
        "question": "68,168,693 ÷ 5,327,973=？",
        "answer": 1.1070229519996349
    },
    {
        "question": "4,558 ÷ 262=？",
        "answer": 1.2404730295246114
    },
    {
        "question": "20,933 × 16,542=？",
        "answer": 8.539419489934662
    },
    {
        "question": "81,195 ÷ 1,051=？",
        "answer": 1.8879265701185004
    },
    {
        "question": "324,966,515 ÷ 5,486=？",
        "answer": 4.7725828097105705
    },
    {
        "question": "231,885 ÷ 339=？",
        "answer": 2.8350729580333365
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 8,973,557=？",
        "answer": 7.651934630129871
    },
    {
        "question": "264,358 × 361=？",
        "answer": 7.979699659462314
    },
    {
        "question": "24,849,406 ÷ 26,690=？",
        "answer": 2.968967438034137
    },
    {
        "question": "958 × 24,276=？",
        "answer": 7.366542637896974
    },
    {
        "question": "25,312 × 21,071=？",
        "answer": 8.727011608919572
    },
    {
        "question": "65,042 ÷ 25,228=？",
        "answer": 0.4113110647482688
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 37,673,390=？",
        "answer": 7.877064697153468
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 60,513,896=？",
        "answer": 8.56000636492296
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 118,540=？",
        "answer": 5.550986177622661
    },
    {
        "question": "26,779 ÷ 4,186=？",
        "answer": 0.8059951312502207
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 26,160=？",
        "answer": 5.5637657753304675
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 79,278=？",
        "answer": 4.899152685373284
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 42,807,694=？",
        "answer": 7.631521833532765
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 4,940=？",
        "answer": 5.212240888801534
    },
    {
        "question": "1,333,223 ÷ 647,857=？",
        "answer": 0.3134236416361101
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 239=？",
        "answer": 4.031610414723481
    },
    {
        "question": "78,703 × 327=？",
        "answer": 7.410539039766666
    },
    {
        "question": "192,704 ÷ 29,127=？",
        "answer": 0.8205949736894423
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 18,531=？",
        "answer": 5.347080102104981
    },
    {
        "question": "959,166,994 ÷ 144,248,316=？",
        "answer": 0.8227834740255319
    },
    {
        "question": "19,571 × 228=？",
        "answer": 6.649547863940334
    },
    {
        "question": "388,474,403 ÷ 2,069=？",
        "answer": 5.273601917279207
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 44,249,072=？",
        "answer": 7.645904167022424
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,219=？",
        "answer": 3.984842231405276
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 1,236=？",
        "answer": 4.296138453408722
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 5,275=？",
        "answer": 5.493074475611874
    },
    {
        "question": "1,316,121 ÷ 888=？",
        "answer": 3.170882852995242
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 433=？",
        "answer": 3.9587071910872846
    },
    {
        "question": "222 × 387=？",
        "answer": 4.93406393946955
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 18,041=？",
        "answer": 4.557290602176188
    },
    {
        "question": "1,734,964 ÷ 47,459=？",
        "answer": 1.5629718846984981
    },
    {
        "question": "32,535,809 ÷ 5,042,236=？",
        "answer": 0.8097384410883286
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 231,454,687=？",
        "answer": 8.364465979751046
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,121,921=？",
        "answer": 6.895060317191098
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,501,769=？",
        "answer": 6.740502351933094
    },
    {
        "question": "6,697,492 ÷ 1,791,170=？",
        "answer": 0.5727753968179116
    },
    {
        "question": "500 × 244=？",
        "answer": 5.086359830674748
    },
    {
        "question": "1,203,308 ÷ 21,669=？",
        "answer": 1.7445379344680731
    },
    {
        "question": "273,991,895 ÷ 10,296=？",
        "answer": 4.425069182176475
    },
    {
        "question": "403 × 291,217=？",
        "answer": 8.06952176977213
    },
    {
        "question": "452,044 ÷ 80,783=？",
        "answer": 0.7478607318859263
    },
    {
        "question": "897,190 ÷ 203,904=？",
        "answer": 0.6434586788812102
    },
    {
        "question": "22,781,946 ÷ 227=？",
        "answer": 5.001564960924216
    },
    {
        "question": "812,919,694 ÷ 739=？",
        "answer": 6.0414032066146435
    },
    {
        "question": "53,914 ÷ 781=？",
        "answer": 1.839050520423669
    },
    {
        "question": "2,711 ÷ 444=？",
        "answer": 0.7857465474658657
    },
    {
        "question": "76,597,360 ÷ 558=？",
        "answer": 5.137579602585492
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,913=？",
        "answer": 3.281714970027296
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 119,735=？",
        "answer": 6.439948954552931
    },
    {
        "question": "283 × 701,691=？",
        "answer": 8.297932341758958
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 30,325,818=？",
        "answer": 8.259963774616233
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 47,862,568=？",
        "answer": 8.759177242420947
    },
    {
        "question": "5,889,995 ÷ 97,067=？",
        "answer": 1.7830433188012458
    },
    {
        "question": "159,365,704 ÷ 310,190=？",
        "answer": 2.710767072793765
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 57,937,463=？",
        "answer": 7.762959474139689
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 119,183=？",
        "answer": 5.854365563399311
    },
    {
        "question": "304 × 2,262,375=？",
        "answer": 8.837438176652878
    },
    {
        "question": "1,062 × 5,490=？",
        "answer": 6.765696861195543
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 474,910,137=？",
        "answer": 8.676611439736108
    },
    {
        "question": "467,160,175 ÷ 2,368,766=？",
        "answer": 2.2949436516588912
    },
    {
        "question": "87 × 1,029=？",
        "answer": 4.951934627381052
    },
    {
        "question": "368 ÷ 357=？",
        "answer": 0.013179602561324418
    },
    {
        "question": "1,005 × 482=？",
        "answer": 5.685213099995357
    },
    {
        "question": "881,487,911 ÷ 108,364,860=？",
        "answer": 0.9103278863779969
    },
    {
        "question": "935,062 ÷ 2,146=？",
        "answer": 2.639210690424591
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 37,445=？",
        "answer": 4.573393834922521
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 1,127=？",
        "answer": 4.228015175101787
    },
    {
        "question": "114 × 760=？",
        "answer": 4.937718443617264
    },
    {
        "question": "168 × 4,227=？",
        "answer": 5.851341529554881
    },
    {
        "question": "10,765,847 ÷ 8,076=？",
        "answer": 3.124851893228884
    },
    {
        "question": "226 × 153,096=？",
        "answer": 7.539072283009467
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 1,086,404=？",
        "answer": 7.760267225556665
    },
    {
        "question": "3,033 × 3,078=？",
        "answer": 6.970141025806123
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 120,332,347=？",
        "answer": 8.080382387400293
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 910=？",
        "answer": 2.9590413923210934
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 231,864=？",
        "answer": 5.666263319485123
    },
    {
        "question": "70,237,954 ÷ 399,496=？",
        "answer": 2.245059417031483
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 110,658=？",
        "answer": 5.9470728036308484
    },
    {
        "question": "135,801,587 ÷ 114,502=？",
        "answer": 3.0740917726724324
    },
    {
        "question": "3,539 ÷ 1,475=？",
        "answer": 0.3800885423233331
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 4,301,614=？",
        "answer": 7.332601441258879
    },
    {
        "question": "110,262,684 ÷ 834,143=？",
        "answer": 2.1211880501968006
    },
    {
        "question": "388 ÷ 233=？",
        "answer": 0.22147580456818824
    },
    {
        "question": "4,733 ÷ 559=？",
        "answer": 0.9277246965815708
    },
    {
        "question": "28,331 × 26,012=？",
        "answer": 8.867435649429796
    },
    {
        "question": "183,134 ÷ 5,584=？",
        "answer": 1.5158235717242625
    },
    {
        "question": "24,853 ÷ 473=？",
        "answer": 1.7205176790843426
    },
    {
        "question": "334,321,926 ÷ 4,043=？",
        "answer": 4.917461118742439
    },
    {
        "question": "714,522 ÷ 22,783=？",
        "answer": 1.4964046950210428
    },
    {
        "question": "351,379,753 ÷ 1,847,924=？",
        "answer": 2.2790926272946472
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 6,797,267=？",
        "answer": 8.832334329558751
    },
    {
        "question": "48,432,124 ÷ 3,180,560=？",
        "answer": 1.182629922748624
    },
    {
        "question": "3,032,957 ÷ 37,367=？",
        "answer": 1.9093780210799371
    },
    {
        "question": "593,950 × 1,116=？",
        "answer": 8.821414081269511
    },
    {
        "question": "3,453 × 445=？",
        "answer": 6.186556589330386
    },
    {
        "question": "2,861 × 314,590=？",
        "answer": 8.954262771216994
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 2,861,536=？",
        "answer": 8.473632553287029
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 18,952,663=？",
        "answer": 7.277670240422874
    },
    {
        "question": "15,927,191 ÷ 84,356=？",
        "answer": 2.2760232100392512
    },
    {
        "question": "1,326,269 ÷ 695=？",
        "answer": 3.2806468140241276
    },
    {
        "question": "42,542,181 ÷ 308,589=？",
        "answer": 2.139439309920079
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 109,049=？",
        "answer": 5.037621687370261
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 25,347=？",
        "answer": 4.7049565604952495
    },
    {
        "question": "533,302 ÷ 479=？",
        "answer": 3.046637698971361
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,954=？",
        "answer": 3.470410490975931
    },
    {
        "question": "449,042 × 596=？",
        "answer": 8.4275332232718
    },
    {
        "question": "15,265 × 59,097=？",
        "answer": 8.955262243551216
    },
    {
        "question": "62,103,976 ÷ 47,219=？",
        "answer": 3.1190026199346756
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 35,641=？",
        "answer": 5.154009872113373
    },
    {
        "question": "181,593,389 ÷ 18,357=？",
        "answer": 3.9952983258442973
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 423,837=？",
        "answer": 5.627198866943962
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 1,274,853=？",
        "answer": 7.8836113606678255
    },
    {
        "question": "70,179 ÷ 770=？",
        "answer": 1.9597164503686884
    },
    {
        "question": "698,952 × 895=？",
        "answer": 8.796270387240547
    },
    {
        "question": "178 × 2,626,620=？",
        "answer": 8.669817249118433
    },
    {
        "question": "22,206 × 33,776=？",
        "answer": 8.875078551442337
    },
    {
        "question": "86 × 3,275=？",
        "answer": 5.449709755571369
    },
    {
        "question": "119,245,153 ÷ 460,152=？",
        "answer": 2.4135394211693497
    },
    {
        "question": "3,100 ÷ 752=？",
        "answer": 0.6151438532426304
    },
    {
        "question": "3,939 × 27,091=？",
        "answer": 8.02821101708876
    },
    {
        "question": "294 × 377=？",
        "answer": 5.04468868061795
    },
    {
        "question": "5,204 ÷ 1,628=？",
        "answer": 0.5046828873363662
    },
    {
        "question": "55,604,614 ÷ 4,328,541=？",
        "answer": 1.10876929476378
    },
    {
        "question": "770,054,600 ÷ 438=？",
        "answer": 6.245047409003495
    },
    {
        "question": "264,153 ÷ 1,223=？",
        "answer": 2.3344290903207527
    },
    {
        "question": "5,689 ÷ 1,103=？",
        "answer": 0.7124604213275809
    },
    {
        "question": "10,713,571 ÷ 2,244,035=？",
        "answer": 0.6789046257873166
    },
    {
        "question": "7,424 ÷ 4,625=？",
        "answer": 0.20552622613575425
    },
    {
        "question": "662,457 ÷ 36,173=？",
        "answer": 1.262773165148844
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 19,987=？",
        "answer": 6.139596703203515
    },
    {
        "question": "29,028 ÷ 2,559=？",
        "answer": 1.0547468285223192
    },
    {
        "question": "23,775,024 ÷ 8,986,654=？",
        "answer": 0.4225229430067054
    },
    {
        "question": "1,857 ÷ 572=？",
        "answer": 0.5114158749467562
    },
    {
        "question": "1,669 × 1,194=？",
        "answer": 6.299460663472597
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 4,203,729=？",
        "answer": 8.003845952493554
    },
    {
        "question": "100,198 × 7,040=？",
        "answer": 8.848431712034293
    },
    {
        "question": "174,917,234 ÷ 13,793,776=？",
        "answer": 1.103149432032923
    },
    {
        "question": "303,391,909 ÷ 241,209,868=？",
        "answer": 0.09960892362635416
    },
    {
        "question": "4,966,650 ÷ 562,493=？",
        "answer": 0.9459464341299143
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 588=？",
        "answer": 3.246498580795801
    },
    {
        "question": "47,716,034 ÷ 102,423=？",
        "answer": 2.6682668470690136
    },
    {
        "question": "2,090,392 ÷ 4,568=？",
        "answer": 2.660501639425171
    },
    {
        "question": "240,251,638 ÷ 5,859,490=？",
        "answer": 1.612806539892761
    },
    {
        "question": "890,006 ÷ 43,667=？",
        "answer": 1.3092395783145105
    },
    {
        "question": "8,027 × 8,014=？",
        "answer": 7.808402601073454
    },
    {
        "question": "787,456 ÷ 591=？",
        "answer": 3.1246388155599876
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 1,204,221=？",
        "answer": 7.599220136328652
    },
    {
        "question": "17,335 ÷ 6,594=？",
        "answer": 0.41977490318528127
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 2,358,019=？",
        "answer": 7.548638559204876
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 2,678,610=？",
        "answer": 8.477127508515174
    },
    {
        "question": "37,506,622 ÷ 266,499=？",
        "answer": 2.1484123678354448
    },
    {
        "question": "348 × 921=？",
        "answer": 5.505838874143429
    },
    {
        "question": "73,686 ÷ 236=？",
        "answer": 2.4944729787789353
    },
    {
        "question": "55,177,448 ÷ 13,727=？",
        "answer": 3.6041859764671473
    },
    {
        "question": "74,397 ÷ 2,338=？",
        "answer": 1.5027109164927157
    },
    {
        "question": "557,390,109 ÷ 365,934,757=？",
        "answer": 0.18275559645348485
    },
    {
        "question": "288 × 1,199=？",
        "answer": 5.53821167085808
    },
    {
        "question": "1,870,910 ÷ 538=？",
        "answer": 3.5412706206291937
    },
    {
        "question": "1,943 × 240=？",
        "answer": 5.668684042311389
    },
    {
        "question": "576,315,988 ÷ 20,724,097=？",
        "answer": 1.4441850514735552
    },
    {
        "question": "3,452,245 × 275=？",
        "answer": 8.977434303113407
    },
    {
        "question": "3,786,251 ÷ 26,997=？",
        "answer": 2.1468938945084375
    },
    {
        "question": "953,112,796 ÷ 254,593=？",
        "answer": 3.5732978415853767
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 9,179,547=？",
        "answer": 7.263851245464945
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 104,217,123=？",
        "answer": 8.017939079937339
    },
    {
        "question": "68,971 × 2,708=？",
        "answer": 8.27131518281709
    },
    {
        "question": "9,549,518 ÷ 355=？",
        "answer": 4.4297530986100115
    },
    {
        "question": "113,475,805 ÷ 444=？",
        "answer": 5.4075203022063505
    },
    {
        "question": "66,674,884 ÷ 4,090,085=？",
        "answer": 1.212229935189808
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 782=？",
        "answer": 3.3703280077795106
    },
    {
        "question": "113,245,333 ÷ 4,876,756=？",
        "answer": 1.3658892861986343
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 3,634,161=？",
        "answer": 8.338555413824217
    },
    {
        "question": "169,163,553 ÷ 1,391=？",
        "answer": 5.084979668214251
    },
    {
        "question": "535,558,967 ÷ 8,673=？",
        "answer": 4.790637948820202
    },
    {
        "question": "77,545,116 ÷ 1,895=？",
        "answer": 4.611945235672169
    },
    {
        "question": "477,590 ÷ 5,634=？",
        "answer": 1.9282383821083127
    },
    {
        "question": "3,334,157 ÷ 837,258=？",
        "answer": 0.6001267402749286
    },
    {
        "question": "117,634,058 ÷ 12,364,353=？",
        "answer": 0.9783616834577376
    },
    {
        "question": "91,516,943 ÷ 24,871,281=？",
        "answer": 0.5658033504051755
    },
    {
        "question": "3,494,550 ÷ 13,917=？",
        "answer": 2.399845631498663
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 2,234,625=？",
        "answer": 7.2522946401444495
    },
    {
        "question": "116,083 ÷ 93,539=？",
        "answer": 0.09377590062463247
    },
    {
        "question": "427 × 2,474=？",
        "answer": 6.023827570318126
    },
    {
        "question": "258,291,203 ÷ 876=？",
        "answer": 5.469605508856895
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 7,879=？",
        "answer": 5.238893781301483
    },
    {
        "question": "1,120 × 127,586=？",
        "answer": 8.155021044576328
    },
    {
        "question": "554,825 ÷ 552=？",
        "answer": 3.002216944097844
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 1,497=？",
        "answer": 5.224439823013234
    },
    {
        "question": "1,245 × 1,096=？",
        "answer": 6.1349799055801055
    },
    {
        "question": "3,291,902 ÷ 9,046=？",
        "answer": 2.560990314365831
    },
    {
        "question": "372,197,901 ÷ 48,639,377=？",
        "answer": 0.88378591599291
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,976=？",
        "answer": 3.295786940251609
    },
    {
        "question": "8,220 ÷ 624=？",
        "answer": 1.1196872278576264
    },
    {
        "question": "193 × 50,518=？",
        "answer": 6.989003457578375
    },
    {
        "question": "830 × 10,211=？",
        "answer": 6.928146368568292
    },
    {
        "question": "193,465 ÷ 2,665=？",
        "answer": 1.8609051943296149
    },
    {
        "question": "806 × 405=？",
        "answer": 5.5137900650197595
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 9,962=？",
        "answer": 4.600406528724327
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 34,003=？",
        "answer": 5.30966848583675
    },
    {
        "question": "800 × 241=？",
        "answer": 5.285107029566812
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 27,034=？",
        "answer": 5.130880313793652
    },
    {
        "question": "226 × 303=？",
        "answer": 4.835551067649706
    },
    {
        "question": "1,885 × 1,715=？",
        "answer": 6.509575478920601
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 12,637,551=？",
        "answer": 7.4026929169019215
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 6,104,195=？",
        "answer": 8.3041423386896
    },
    {
        "question": "7,876,715 ÷ 578,927=？",
        "answer": 1.1337213271845124
    },
    {
        "question": "405,016,312 ÷ 3,349=？",
        "answer": 5.082557367203021
    },
    {
        "question": "275,186 ÷ 8,116=？",
        "answer": 1.530284297170893
    },
    {
        "question": "82,662 ÷ 6,201=？",
        "answer": 1.124844177443597
    },
    {
        "question": "394,061,512 ÷ 3,025=？",
        "answer": 5.114838640393034
    },
    {
        "question": "1,065,252 ÷ 600=？",
        "answer": 3.2493011078731686
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 558=？",
        "answer": 3.2237554536572413
    },
    {
        "question": "421,425,855 ÷ 260=？",
        "answer": 6.209747828624889
    },
    {
        "question": "187,866,728 ÷ 47,612=？",
        "answer": 3.596133446577018
    },
    {
        "question": "626,852,629 ÷ 2,710,903=？",
        "answer": 2.3640514734417413
    },
    {
        "question": "262,593 ÷ 30,179=？",
        "answer": 0.9395782997638942
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 58,227=？",
        "answer": 5.367184406079487
    },
    {
        "question": "2,181,962 ÷ 12,657=？",
        "answer": 2.2365164027529714
    },
    {
        "question": "7,989,866 ÷ 18,244=？",
        "answer": 2.641419432147021
    },
    {
        "question": "47,260 × 5,588=？",
        "answer": 8.421750114738494
    },
    {
        "question": "20,588,253 ÷ 7,529=？",
        "answer": 3.436882199324431
    },
    {
        "question": "559,962 ÷ 10,303=？",
        "answer": 1.7351948561978026
    },
    {
        "question": "421,217,564 ÷ 288,277=？",
        "answer": 3.1646964783175178
    },
    {
        "question": "428,725,850 ÷ 3,892,899=？",
        "answer": 2.0419065338253644
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 57,110=？",
        "answer": 6.390180615744359
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 97,835=？",
        "answer": 4.990494249344085
    },
    {
        "question": "249 × 57,137=？",
        "answer": 7.1531167809434875
    },
    {
        "question": "24,408 × 3,867=？",
        "answer": 7.974906366707416
    },
    {
        "question": "248 × 344,613=？",
        "answer": 7.931783337344417
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,052,804=？",
        "answer": 6.022347526321768
    },
    {
        "question": "17,284 ÷ 323=？",
        "answer": 1.7284417353080896
    },
    {
        "question": "363,773,649 ÷ 107,582=？",
        "answer": 3.5290916227260007
    },
    {
        "question": "272,420,260 ÷ 136,305,754=？",
        "answer": 0.3007252135967315
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 197,814=？",
        "answer": 7.15358952134453
    },
    {
        "question": "769 × 2,558=？",
        "answer": 6.293826879944066
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 321=？",
        "answer": 3.5478977175630972
    },
    {
        "question": "156,514 × 4,027=？",
        "answer": 8.799534820376854
    },
    {
        "question": "59,788 ÷ 45,193=？",
        "answer": 0.12154285424096388
    },
    {
        "question": "18,540 × 15,073=？",
        "answer": 8.446309428956539
    },
    {
        "question": "64,685,601 ÷ 18,031,837=？",
        "answer": 0.5547676446887935
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 25,817=？",
        "answer": 4.712935770420799
    },
    {
        "question": "764,129,328 ÷ 44,384,436=？",
        "answer": 1.2359361630293644
    },
    {
        "question": "30,968 ÷ 473=？",
        "answer": 1.816052017573087
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 38,750,312=？",
        "answer": 8.66745644964693
    },
    {
        "question": "180 × 2,690,280=？",
        "answer": 8.685069988126763
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 19,220,116=？",
        "answer": 8.06190725484041
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 869=？",
        "answer": 4.018201022496291
    },
    {
        "question": "2,709 × 195,122=？",
        "answer": 8.723115243878983
    },
    {
        "question": "12,312 × 7,144=？",
        "answer": 7.944270052703913
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 13,322,136=？",
        "answer": 7.425603858534443
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 1,314,001=？",
        "answer": 7.858958385231184
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 11,191,858=？",
        "answer": 7.650962182607333
    },
    {
        "question": "4,160 × 2,057=？",
        "answer": 6.932327622321467
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 337,122=？",
        "answer": 5.527787094754258
    },
    {
        "question": "236,794,141 ÷ 15,787,811=？",
        "answer": 1.176049033728572
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 86,871=？",
        "answer": 5.239904816509099
    },
    {
        "question": "31,549,973 ÷ 79,445=？",
        "answer": 2.5989324225420356
    },
    {
        "question": "6,555 × 342=？",
        "answer": 6.350598802082238
    },
    {
        "question": "7,451,999 ÷ 57,191=？",
        "answer": 2.1149450975765287
    },
    {
        "question": "2,712 × 8,935=？",
        "answer": 7.384384242036689
    },
    {
        "question": "229,334 ÷ 532=？",
        "answer": 2.6345568137029245
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 16,913,594=？",
        "answer": 8.968598590913501
    },
    {
        "question": "9,162,629 ÷ 7,632,225=？",
        "answer": 0.07936893709296136
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 61,460,374=？",
        "answer": 8.487565203042614
    },
    {
        "question": "127,865,543 ÷ 124,298=？",
        "answer": 3.0122893865274447
    },
    {
        "question": "550,039,359 ÷ 388,514,367=？",
        "answer": 0.15098668393327386
    },
    {
        "question": "17,188,343 ÷ 1,750=？",
        "answer": 3.992195962925581
    },
    {
        "question": "203,710 ÷ 107,490=？",
        "answer": 0.27764428588965384
    },
    {
        "question": "461,184,941 ÷ 822,075=？",
        "answer": 2.7489636767627856
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,561=？",
        "answer": 3.5515719736742537
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 351,405=？",
        "answer": 6.960781284575059
    },
    {
        "question": "1,441 × 326=？",
        "answer": 5.671881580881928
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 169,335,116=？",
        "answer": 8.830807020928958
    },
    {
        "question": "2,503,831 ÷ 370,189=？",
        "answer": 0.8301815023974944
    },
    {
        "question": "685,180,393 ÷ 358,353,516=？",
        "answer": 0.28149325685347976
    },
    {
        "question": "185,298,399 ÷ 6,976,737=？",
        "answer": 1.4242193151630846
    },
    {
        "question": "2,266 × 1,144=？",
        "answer": 6.413685929984384
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,393=？",
        "answer": 3.8429211207599825
    },
    {
        "question": "4,234 ÷ 2,548=？",
        "answer": 0.22055143002008037
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 347=？",
        "answer": 4.230525554819387
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 278,716,389=？",
        "answer": 8.746192502385878
    },
    {
        "question": "53,566,404 ÷ 1,328=？",
        "answer": 4.6056944174230665
    },
    {
        "question": "4,699,209 ÷ 2,977,164=？",
        "answer": 0.19822200210391694
    },
    {
        "question": "136,924,464 ÷ 135,488=？",
        "answer": 3.004580217525967
    },
    {
        "question": "215,327 ÷ 4,912=？",
        "answer": 1.6418401315873483
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 29,343=？",
        "answer": 5.546685759673521
    },
    {
        "question": "65,663 × 541=？",
        "answer": 7.550517985925755
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 949,632=？",
        "answer": 6.278585336392809
    },
    {
        "question": "14,685,380 ÷ 2,913,992=？",
        "answer": 0.70239683370646
    },
    {
        "question": "88,804 ÷ 232=？",
        "answer": 2.5829445432616107
    },
    {
        "question": "229 × 677,764=？",
        "answer": 8.190913979540328
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 470,936=？",
        "answer": 7.178111869025426
    },
    {
        "question": "40,591,466 ÷ 107,227=？",
        "answer": 2.5781305811097925
    },
    {
        "question": "819,200,093 ÷ 14,086=？",
        "answer": 4.764602308878891
    },
    {
        "question": "48,089,019 ÷ 4,997=？",
        "answer": 3.9833365682585384
    },
    {
        "question": "379 × 16,233=？",
        "answer": 6.789037998620317
    },
    {
        "question": "18,129 ÷ 9,930=？",
        "answer": 0.2614246004727377
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 152,814=？",
        "answer": 6.763946740412921
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 983,609=？",
        "answer": 6.594882485197464
    },
    {
        "question": "37,249,347 ÷ 23,406=？",
        "answer": 3.201791463052435
    },
    {
        "question": "61,157,172 ÷ 179,411=？",
        "answer": 2.532598327898491
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 1,101=？",
        "answer": 4.120968565019377
    },
    {
        "question": "386 × 254=？",
        "answer": 4.991421021291693
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 1,820=？",
        "answer": 4.82827311205207
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 1,393=？",
        "answer": 4.884313805918207
    },
    {
        "question": "19,876,159 ÷ 19,211,967=？",
        "answer": 0.014760630251773887
    },
    {
        "question": "56,271,487 ÷ 1,110,716=？",
        "answer": 1.704685363759804
    },
    {
        "question": "538 × 3,360=？",
        "answer": 6.257121553056233
    },
    {
        "question": "16,317,269 ÷ 4,490=？",
        "answer": 3.56040113219644
    },
    {
        "question": "6,177 × 98,980=？",
        "answer": 8.786325050812831
    },
    {
        "question": "1,238,412 ÷ 7,305=？",
        "answer": 2.2292449313279765
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 291=？",
        "answer": 2.4638929889859074
    },
    {
        "question": "13,008 × 8,002=？",
        "answer": 8.01740907529297
    },
    {
        "question": "10,979,185 ÷ 4,406=？",
        "answer": 3.396525610219222
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,704,031=？",
        "answer": 6.231477491256078
    },
    {
        "question": "10,487,889 ÷ 53,394=？",
        "answer": 2.2931956251374794
    },
    {
        "question": "77,744,892 ÷ 181,696=？",
        "answer": 2.6313264980818905
    },
    {
        "question": "13,490,938 ÷ 4,163,227=？",
        "answer": 0.5106120549708294
    },
    {
        "question": "141,868 ÷ 13,130=？",
        "answer": 1.0336197201737247
    },
    {
        "question": "5,131,014 ÷ 1,270=？",
        "answer": 3.6063994786759337
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 9,824,889=？",
        "answer": 8.548630153253956
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 3,482=？",
        "answer": 4.93976877545335
    },
    {
        "question": "147 × 8,004=？",
        "answer": 6.07062441471235
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 10,653,359=？",
        "answer": 8.425426570922077
    },
    {
        "question": "623 × 3,918=？",
        "answer": 6.387552478317887
    },
    {
        "question": "119,330 ÷ 15,021=？",
        "answer": 0.9000507945054286
    },
    {
        "question": "977,141,302 ÷ 543,131=？",
        "answer": 3.2550527790209065
    },
    {
        "question": "20,868 ÷ 563=？",
        "answer": 1.568972433198991
    },
    {
        "question": "30,774 ÷ 1,793=？",
        "answer": 1.2346036598872143
    },
    {
        "question": "398,140 ÷ 5,191=？",
        "answer": 1.884784783235769
    },
    {
        "question": "2,477,269 ÷ 171,276=？",
        "answer": 1.1602766561800235
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 51,531=？",
        "answer": 5.01309856603633
    },
    {
        "question": "1,387 × 918=？",
        "answer": 6.104919142274527
    },
    {
        "question": "418,842,298 ÷ 353,070=？",
        "answer": 3.0741897161361322
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 1,307,891=？",
        "answer": 7.458994232095579
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 7,199,334=？",
        "answer": 8.448356929360111
    },
    {
        "question": "170,524 ÷ 289=？",
        "answer": 2.7708876686308908
    },
    {
        "question": "578,394 ÷ 193,794=？",
        "answer": 0.4748834522766164
    },
    {
        "question": "433,349 ÷ 109,455=？",
        "answer": 0.5976021934108834
    },
    {
        "question": "363,948,291 ÷ 375,333=？",
        "answer": 2.9866229342958484
    },
    {
        "question": "77,425 ÷ 56,816=？",
        "answer": 0.13441055907128413
    },
    {
        "question": "51,931 × 378=？",
        "answer": 7.292918485426705
    },
    {
        "question": "503,149,948 ÷ 51,467=？",
        "answer": 3.990168578082947
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 1,841=？",
        "answer": 5.194472714218308
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 12,591,759=？",
        "answer": 7.10008640291431
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 181,687=？",
        "answer": 7.145814579116488
    },
    {
        "question": "66,809,022 ÷ 26,170,287=？",
        "answer": 0.40702662886029173
    },
    {
        "question": "124 × 781,648=？",
        "answer": 7.9864329061583295
    },
    {
        "question": "5,677,710 ÷ 145,430=？",
        "answer": 1.5915192022076086
    },
    {
        "question": "91,594,221 ÷ 50,559,442=？",
        "answer": 0.2580658011696976
    },
    {
        "question": "21,826,538 ÷ 288=？",
        "answer": 4.879592368118003
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 13,430,297=？",
        "answer": 8.031175603833027
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 19,317=？",
        "answer": 4.763060934531449
    },
    {
        "question": "485,411,597 ÷ 308,249,281=？",
        "answer": 0.19720807561252157
    },
    {
        "question": "103,771,458 ÷ 1,888=？",
        "answer": 4.740075928698411
    },
    {
        "question": "424,485,880 ÷ 1,037,819=？",
        "answer": 2.611741631217416
    },
    {
        "question": "2,737,009 ÷ 429=？",
        "answer": 3.8048189333013624
    },
    {
        "question": "345,746 × 2,752=？",
        "answer": 8.978405593939973
    },
    {
        "question": "203,496,039 ÷ 73,760=？",
        "answer": 3.4407350521634066
    },
    {
        "question": "94,997,717 ÷ 2,521,122=？",
        "answer": 1.5761193061857084
    },
    {
        "question": "89 × 99,056=？",
        "answer": 6.9452707933137425
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 675=？",
        "answer": 4.084576277934331
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 173,649=？",
        "answer": 6.892884800438926
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 428,700,201=？",
        "answer": 8.63215368713361
    },
    {
        "question": "12,924,597 ÷ 6,751,211=？",
        "answer": 0.28203532881373605
    },
    {
        "question": "136,526,817 ÷ 58,800,214=？",
        "answer": 0.3658390584898452
    },
    {
        "question": "7,577,319 ÷ 6,639=？",
        "answer": 3.0574129024910484
    },
    {
        "question": "1,335,377 ÷ 321=？",
        "answer": 3.619098859442341
    },
    {
        "question": "406,491,708 ÷ 251,583=？",
        "answer": 3.2083703993132473
    },
    {
        "question": "7,479 ÷ 2,113=？",
        "answer": 0.5489440361711225
    },
    {
        "question": "1,328,773 ÷ 381=？",
        "answer": 3.5425258192116207
    },
    {
        "question": "7,894 × 7,171=？",
        "answer": 7.752876844561214
    },
    {
        "question": "2,320,992 ÷ 179,836=？",
        "answer": 1.110797009324618
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 150,106,744=？",
        "answer": 8.778460196004215
    },
    {
        "question": "805 × 391=？",
        "answer": 5.497972637763735
    },
    {
        "question": "27,583,954 ÷ 2,026,067=？",
        "answer": 1.1340027169561373
    },
    {
        "question": "92,860,422 ÷ 32,951=？",
        "answer": 3.449962053827138
    },
    {
        "question": "165,788,184 ÷ 7,071,604=？",
        "answer": 1.3700356416279014
    },
    {
        "question": "354,016 ÷ 38,231=？",
        "answer": 0.9666072327968805
    },
    {
        "question": "60,640 ÷ 22,657=？",
        "answer": 0.4275567879659442
    },
    {
        "question": "211 × 941,344=？",
        "answer": 8.298030814113845
    },
    {
        "question": "18,028 ÷ 1,349=？",
        "answer": 1.1259355997270357
    },
    {
        "question": "78 × 370=？",
        "answer": 4.460296326757476
    },
    {
        "question": "4,330,542 ÷ 493,795=？",
        "answer": 0.9429955668856099
    },
    {
        "question": "187 × 1,601=？",
        "answer": 5.476232938455799
    },
    {
        "question": "22,896 ÷ 374=？",
        "answer": 1.786888014215221
    },
    {
        "question": "235 × 36,864=？",
        "answer": 6.937670319678835
    },
    {
        "question": "1,288,666 ÷ 17,799=？",
        "answer": 1.8597447672418836
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 119,169=？",
        "answer": 6.620231339352638
    },
    {
        "question": "1,276,182 ÷ 180,066=？",
        "answer": 0.8504808975658582
    },
    {
        "question": "617 × 12,210=？",
        "answer": 6.877000827978124
    },
    {
        "question": "120,678,517 ÷ 1,030,971=？",
        "answer": 2.0683835152936534
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 6,394=？",
        "answer": 4.407832623263632
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 96,282=？",
        "answer": 6.262298703951152
    },
    {
        "question": "6,030,238 ÷ 258=？",
        "answer": 4.368714747146561
    },
    {
        "question": "522,483 × 275=？",
        "answer": 8.15740485822809
    },
    {
        "question": "277,074,731 ÷ 51,957=？",
        "answer": 3.7269528533312237
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,962=？",
        "answer": 3.47158505418519
    },
    {
        "question": "167,432,349 ÷ 9,499=？",
        "answer": 4.246161482559891
    },
    {
        "question": "89,399,140 ÷ 558=？",
        "answer": 5.204699142061349
    },
    {
        "question": "367,592,246 ÷ 11,181,162=？",
        "answer": 1.516879401930014
    },
    {
        "question": "190,095 ÷ 268=？",
        "answer": 2.8508358998962704
    },
    {
        "question": "112,969,138 ÷ 25,050,410=？",
        "answer": 0.6541449765682477
    },
    {
        "question": "65,902 × 990=？",
        "answer": 7.81453378940072
    },
    {
        "question": "282,878 ÷ 4,815=？",
        "answer": 1.7690028813406302
    },
    {
        "question": "7,513,900 ÷ 14,494=？",
        "answer": 2.7146771539025214
    },
    {
        "question": "20,049,939 ÷ 28,617=？",
        "answer": 2.845488952152195
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,179=？",
        "answer": 4.025756314534414
    },
    {
        "question": "5,719 × 9,593=？",
        "answer": 7.739274541016646
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 860=？",
        "answer": 3.934498451243568
    },
    {
        "question": "148,380 × 6,572=？",
        "answer": 8.989072921507965
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 172,761=？",
        "answer": 7.050359065871205
    },
    {
        "question": "134,616 ÷ 3,203=？",
        "answer": 1.6235397430573009
    },
    {
        "question": "1,807,059 ÷ 1,227=？",
        "answer": 3.1681277696657646
    },
    {
        "question": "43,456,367 ÷ 8,080=？",
        "answer": 3.730642055231929
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,474=？",
        "answer": 4.318981064494723
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 40,817,016=？",
        "answer": 8.56508376111522
    },
    {
        "question": "723,904,557 ÷ 584=？",
        "answer": 6.0932684634209044
    },
    {
        "question": "20,291,583 ÷ 1,873,349=？",
        "answer": 1.0346972359805748
    },
    {
        "question": "150,774,880 ÷ 72,123=？",
        "answer": 3.320255208324232
    },
    {
        "question": "2,835 × 2,003=？",
        "answer": 6.7542340125225016
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 10,179=？",
        "answer": 6.03708889204999
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 471=？",
        "answer": 3.8771408897848207
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 13,949=？",
        "answer": 5.649693052592694
    },
    {
        "question": "10,716 ÷ 7,626=？",
        "answer": 0.14773590399851946
    },
    {
        "question": "544,484 ÷ 4,537=？",
        "answer": 2.0792163430006063
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 148,172=？",
        "answer": 5.7728261342804545
    },
    {
        "question": "905,326,883 ÷ 147,912=？",
        "answer": 3.786802007167265
    },
    {
        "question": "4,229,721 ÷ 271=？",
        "answer": 4.193342430600731
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,352,486=？",
        "answer": 6.970927066763074
    },
    {
        "question": "111,592 × 217=？",
        "answer": 7.384092795113261
    },
    {
        "question": "4,569 ÷ 1,587=？",
        "answer": 0.45924423130085684
    },
    {
        "question": "521,722,807 ÷ 385,851=？",
        "answer": 3.1310201920898306
    },
    {
        "question": "3,484 × 8,604=？",
        "answer": 7.47677854805105
    },
    {
        "question": "470 × 1,458=？",
        "answer": 5.835855381917673
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 398,639=？",
        "answer": 7.1320587017635875
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 266=？",
        "answer": 3.424881636631067
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 138,807,035=？",
        "answer": 8.142411477532782
    },
    {
        "question": "6,855,345 ÷ 7,395=？",
        "answer": 2.9670911375141378
    },
    {
        "question": "847,980 ÷ 633=？",
        "answer": 3.1269818993241847
    },
    {
        "question": "1,126,727 × 531=？",
        "answer": 8.77691322261478
    },
    {
        "question": "730,281,383 ÷ 24,873,149=？",
        "answer": 1.4677594578828348
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 332=？",
        "answer": 2.5211380837040362
    },
    {
        "question": "180 × 36,083=？",
        "answer": 6.8125751434322535
    },
    {
        "question": "13,231,244 ÷ 5,795=？",
        "answer": 3.3585472381234864
    },
    {
        "question": "516,268,138 ÷ 5,011=？",
        "answer": 5.012950920217256
    },
    {
        "question": "14,981 × 942=？",
        "answer": 7.1495917068096455
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 670=？",
        "answer": 3.1271047983648077
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 10,797,584=？",
        "answer": 8.49572458923341
    },
    {
        "question": "50,205,757 ÷ 10,529,713=？",
        "answer": 0.6783369856061905
    },
    {
        "question": "1,116 × 260,374=？",
        "answer": 8.463261809596476
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 6,225=？",
        "answer": 5.095169351431755
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 12,145=？",
        "answer": 4.561518773860811
    },
    {
        "question": "26,733 ÷ 9,422=？",
        "answer": 0.4529045984853598
    },
    {
        "question": "19,704,135 ÷ 4,279,575=？",
        "answer": 0.6631567325106622
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 57,146=？",
        "answer": 5.359045828181326
    },
    {
        "question": "42,684,048 ÷ 293=？",
        "answer": 5.163397979261908
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 13,066=？",
        "answer": 5.292233912909475
    },
    {
        "question": "417 × 1,841=？",
        "answer": 5.8851898434777725
    },
    {
        "question": "40,827,665 ÷ 6,915=？",
        "answer": 3.7711623581861407
    },
    {
        "question": "848,223,187 ÷ 9,043=？",
        "answer": 4.972197609303852
    },
    {
        "question": "243,063,851 ÷ 967=？",
        "answer": 5.400293900315304
    },
    {
        "question": "3,645 × 305=？",
        "answer": 6.045997372000779
    },
    {
        "question": "3,577 × 4,046=？",
        "answer": 7.160544818583755
    },
    {
        "question": "16,751,049 ÷ 1,383,210=？",
        "answer": 1.0831538889880727
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,096,838=？",
        "answer": 7.214508782448037
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 5,002=？",
        "answer": 4.398113691730503
    },
    {
        "question": "8,947,985 ÷ 2,498,560=？",
        "answer": 0.5540354644149054
    },
    {
        "question": "501,662 ÷ 5,290=？",
        "answer": 1.9769555332075546
    },
    {
        "question": "13,277,894 ÷ 95,547=？",
        "answer": 2.1429121417103185
    },
    {
        "question": "436,952,155 ÷ 2,772=？",
        "answer": 5.197640659641509
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,584,396=？",
        "answer": 7.154106246743835
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 79,883=？",
        "answer": 5.379575621120888
    },
    {
        "question": "134,542 ÷ 328=？",
        "answer": 2.6129840355776337
    },
    {
        "question": "15,782,353 ÷ 712=？",
        "answer": 4.345691759275499
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,562,524=？",
        "answer": 6.193826696728124
    },
    {
        "question": "149 × 3,942,702=？",
        "answer": 8.768980221583282
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 3,292,153=？",
        "answer": 7.471722519913844
    },
    {
        "question": "4,070 × 504=？",
        "answer": 6.312024945670745
    },
    {
        "question": "4,708 ÷ 957=？",
        "answer": 0.6919245163945534
    },
    {
        "question": "829,900 ÷ 22,537=？",
        "answer": 1.5661296598940497
    },
    {
        "question": "40,567 × 1,257=？",
        "answer": 7.707508169747697
    },
    {
        "question": "807,238,262 ÷ 5,478,632=？",
        "answer": 2.1683296088556236
    },
    {
        "question": "1,723 × 14,827=？",
        "answer": 7.407338565007405
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 833,727=？",
        "answer": 7.097115125277603
    },
    {
        "question": "27,560 ÷ 1,156=？",
        "answer": 1.3773213791510779
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 39,344,790=？",
        "answer": 8.373038482020158
    },
    {
        "question": "307,457,896 ÷ 225,776=？",
        "answer": 3.1341078763684336
    },
    {
        "question": "787,436 ÷ 11,466=？",
        "answer": 1.836803328545084
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 65,493,359=？",
        "answer": 8.293318519659916
    },
    {
        "question": "100,887,123 ÷ 67,798,742=？",
        "answer": 0.17261410178295292
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 914,626=？",
        "answer": 6.563303534202534
    },
    {
        "question": "459 × 6,574=？",
        "answer": 6.479642385282867
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 7,716=？",
        "answer": 4.36451347369151
    },
    {
        "question": "430,316 ÷ 14,271=？",
        "answer": 1.479333088171031
    },
    {
        "question": "37,746 ÷ 254=？",
        "answer": 2.172037218948712
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 2,694,533=？",
        "answer": 7.8284235154499315
    },
    {
        "question": "7,265,840 ÷ 102,795=？",
        "answer": 1.8493138392236472
    },
    {
        "question": "49,447 ÷ 6,993=？",
        "answer": 0.8494764194023919
    },
    {
        "question": "46,212,392 ÷ 51,401=？",
        "answer": 2.953786880398662
    },
    {
        "question": "11,270,332 ÷ 71,880=？",
        "answer": 2.195328641188963
    },
    {
        "question": "66,070,720 ÷ 9,607=？",
        "answer": 3.837421248819281
    },
    {
        "question": "5,987 × 2,038=？",
        "answer": 7.086413437816092
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 44,862,914=？",
        "answer": 8.4300387294616
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 16,465=？",
        "answer": 4.693682989767589
    },
    {
        "question": "3,575 ÷ 2,899=？",
        "answer": 0.09102783078210198
    },
    {
        "question": "517,097,984 ÷ 192,516,620=？",
        "answer": 0.4291046164035079
    },
    {
        "question": "47,125 ÷ 1,304=？",
        "answer": 1.5579737718179478
    },
    {
        "question": "361 × 12,586=？",
        "answer": 6.657394929317125
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 1,096=？",
        "answer": 4.1189918001959756
    },
    {
        "question": "76,790,858 ÷ 1,520=？",
        "answer": 4.703465932132589
    },
    {
        "question": "8,077,652 ÷ 14,878=？",
        "answer": 2.7347405846652175
    },
    {
        "question": "343,683,277 ÷ 15,376,234=？",
        "answer": 1.3493084210812707
    },
    {
        "question": "485 × 679=？",
        "answer": 5.517611512882765
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 70,195,854=？",
        "answer": 8.749401449006433
    },
    {
        "question": "429,502 ÷ 17,121=？",
        "answer": 1.3994360632198082
    },
    {
        "question": "73 × 81,532=？",
        "answer": 6.774650955925541
    },
    {
        "question": "798,744,992 ÷ 295,647=？",
        "answer": 3.431634671751165
    },
    {
        "question": "248,526,655 ÷ 2,461=？",
        "answer": 5.0042613608498945
    },
    {
        "question": "56,240,763 ÷ 1,032,600=？",
        "answer": 1.7361190832714368
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,387,464=？",
        "answer": 6.443251719131359
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 10,060=？",
        "answer": 5.17868923977559
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,534=？",
        "answer": 3.9792751475910233
    },
    {
        "question": "166 × 1,538=？",
        "answer": 5.407064423505467
    },
    {
        "question": "871 × 1,924=？",
        "answer": 6.224223222709457
    },
    {
        "question": "1,212 × 74,743=？",
        "answer": 7.957073145204979
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 5,086,657=？",
        "answer": 7.85256048924638
    },
    {
        "question": "50,547,086 ÷ 108,709=？",
        "answer": 2.667430623168687
    },
    {
        "question": "57,103 ÷ 21,319=？",
        "answer": 0.4278920956284131
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 296,038=？",
        "answer": 6.3164455015160215
    },
    {
        "question": "19,453,623 ÷ 1,172,874=？",
        "answer": 1.2197491361926347
    },
    {
        "question": "337,440 ÷ 2,339=？",
        "answer": 2.1591663405862582
    },
    {
        "question": "56,014,336 ÷ 21,780,874=？",
        "answer": 0.4102238894835004
    },
    {
        "question": "46,372 × 730=？",
        "answer": 7.529578687313061
    },
    {
        "question": "2,128,816 ÷ 3,796=？",
        "answer": 2.748811921920733
    },
    {
        "question": "89 × 461=？",
        "answer": 4.613090932034561
    },
    {
        "question": "127,130,270 ÷ 874,079=？",
        "answer": 2.1626982830372863
    },
    {
        "question": "142 × 2,338,799=？",
        "answer": 8.521281243857104
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 20,460=？",
        "answer": 6.0962354643869086
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 4,697=？",
        "answer": 4.5169186001975055
    },
    {
        "question": "109,296 ÷ 52,137=？",
        "answer": 0.321458230052348
    },
    {
        "question": "210,974,000 ÷ 6,921=？",
        "answer": 4.48406008779968
    },
    {
        "question": "138,016 × 3,233=？",
        "answer": 8.649535141077413
    },
    {
        "question": "440,202 × 874=？",
        "answer": 8.585163444016182
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,077,244=？",
        "answer": 6.317487513208027
    },
    {
        "question": "585 × 637,764=？",
        "answer": 8.571815866968103
    },
    {
        "question": "14,810 ÷ 626=？",
        "answer": 1.3739807253107787
    },
    {
        "question": "106,130,276 ÷ 439=？",
        "answer": 5.383374773405474
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,136,557=？",
        "answer": 6.055591221112212
    },
    {
        "question": "80,324 ÷ 282=？",
        "answer": 2.4545962191543
    },
    {
        "question": "171,742 × 387=？",
        "answer": 7.822587481133182
    },
    {
        "question": "5,866 × 130,870=？",
        "answer": 8.885182161057198
    },
    {
        "question": "16,303,430 ÷ 11,007,008=？",
        "answer": 0.1706097010127791
    },
    {
        "question": "5,365,153 ÷ 24,333=？",
        "answer": 2.343386455290122
    },
    {
        "question": "49,654 ÷ 27,965=？",
        "answer": 0.24933941623570124
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 13,258=？",
        "answer": 5.755946470261098
    },
    {
        "question": "4,737,360 ÷ 268,695=？",
        "answer": 1.2462768037971863
    },
    {
        "question": "11,356,940 ÷ 916,057=？",
        "answer": 1.093338833661309
    },
    {
        "question": "7,546 × 25,068=？",
        "answer": 8.27683648689291
    },
    {
        "question": "1,658 × 348=？",
        "answer": 5.761163770160835
    },
    {
        "question": "343,890,819 ÷ 318,722=？",
        "answer": 3.0330085394550697
    },
    {
        "question": "11,577,601 ÷ 1,281,488=？",
        "answer": 0.9559040345991439
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,829=？",
        "answer": 4.216456214915742
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 178,900=？",
        "answer": 5.951580344903392
    },
    {
        "question": "1,292,575 ÷ 751,269=？",
        "answer": 0.23566028318277663
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 1,227,348=？",
        "answer": 7.344240224351484
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 31,124=？",
        "answer": 4.493095406643273
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 24,968=？",
        "answer": 6.121659625258065
    },
    {
        "question": "2,721,054 ÷ 45,954=？",
        "answer": 1.7724138406407852
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 808,923=？",
        "answer": 7.083998442884719
    },
    {
        "question": "2,155,375 ÷ 2,433=？",
        "answer": 2.947380732277007
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 6,449=？",
        "answer": 5.20743238560938
    },
    {
        "question": "101,230,236 ÷ 49,299=？",
        "answer": 3.3124721393596057
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 10,877=？",
        "answer": 4.638569119860692
    },
    {
        "question": "193,112 ÷ 8,501=？",
        "answer": 1.3563392455452343
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 22,854=？",
        "answer": 4.659992218708571
    },
    {
        "question": "1,034 × 1,615=？",
        "answer": 6.222693065425045
    },
    {
        "question": "221 × 1,117=？",
        "answer": 5.3924454468007195
    },
    {
        "question": "581 × 368,832=？",
        "answer": 8.331004725955575
    },
    {
        "question": "195 × 1,918,397=？",
        "answer": 8.572973097965674
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 18,059=？",
        "answer": 4.733814952717858
    },
    {
        "question": "24,043 × 4,977=？",
        "answer": 8.07795629717613
    },
    {
        "question": "834,470,677 ÷ 198,221,776=？",
        "answer": 0.6242597173809993
    },
    {
        "question": "169,902,746 ÷ 1,830,855=？",
        "answer": 1.9675464476523776
    },
    {
        "question": "185,241 × 4,716=？",
        "answer": 8.94131091323481
    },
    {
        "question": "457,174,348 ÷ 240,841=？",
        "answer": 3.278351432413182
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 2,389=？",
        "answer": 4.457397395797503
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 120,188=？",
        "answer": 5.380891103980092
    },
    {
        "question": "975,216 ÷ 516,186=？",
        "answer": 0.27629459654419364
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 622=？",
        "answer": 4.325269301733074
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 1,146=？",
        "answer": 4.401607298453578
    },
    {
        "question": "2,212,441 ÷ 977=？",
        "answer": 3.3549771343104875
    },
    {
        "question": "629,294,106 ÷ 2,626=？",
        "answer": 5.379558942389284
    },
    {
        "question": "9,375 ÷ 353=？",
        "answer": 1.424196571011934
    },
    {
        "question": "1,728,549 ÷ 87,232=？",
        "answer": 1.2970058653864411
    },
    {
        "question": "180,917 ÷ 547=？",
        "answer": 2.5194920512467074
    },
    {
        "question": "87,578 × 4,546=？",
        "answer": 8.600024454468379
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,705=？",
        "answer": 3.5327543789924976
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 47,670=？",
        "answer": 4.979275147591023
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,126,823=？",
        "answer": 6.916645837991419
    },
    {
        "question": "66,912,211 ÷ 477=？",
        "answer": 5.146987001597571
    },
    {
        "question": "7,664,421 ÷ 756=？",
        "answer": 4.005957556643815
    },
    {
        "question": "11,439,760 ÷ 738,292=？",
        "answer": 1.1901887507777174
    },
    {
        "question": "2,676,214 ÷ 116,053=？",
        "answer": 1.3628644667208345
    },
    {
        "question": "5,677,909 ÷ 35,555=？",
        "answer": 2.2032877448200066
    },
    {
        "question": "66,431,465 ÷ 26,720=？",
        "answer": 3.3955373761542313
    },
    {
        "question": "749,728 ÷ 34,247=？",
        "answer": 1.3402811969221708
    },
    {
        "question": "78 × 3,748=？",
        "answer": 5.4658941849062215
    },
    {
        "question": "29,116,914 ÷ 41,987=？",
        "answer": 2.841030498617744
    },
    {
        "question": "34,657 × 1,157=？",
        "answer": 7.6031243252974905
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 35,936,106=？",
        "answer": 8.917258851630434
    },
    {
        "question": "7,789 × 33,945=？",
        "answer": 8.42225751684993
    },
    {
        "question": "355,830,960 ÷ 77,513,817=？",
        "answer": 0.6618646090086331
    },
    {
        "question": "602,969 ÷ 7,372=？",
        "answer": 1.912709658105523
    },
    {
        "question": "291,781,748 ÷ 4,507=？",
        "answer": 4.811170563650946
    },
    {
        "question": "8,571,505 ÷ 4,060,931=？",
        "answer": 0.32443147243321535
    },
    {
        "question": "17,430 ÷ 228=？",
        "answer": 1.8833625401095393
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 749,875=？",
        "answer": 7.255200116657117
    },
    {
        "question": "171 × 662,214=？",
        "answer": 8.053994468412666
    },
    {
        "question": "54,487,371 ÷ 24,061=？",
        "answer": 3.35498218071967
    },
    {
        "question": "24,106,158 ÷ 21,534=？",
        "answer": 3.049003290032261
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,638,102=？",
        "answer": 7.26840028663253
    },
    {
        "question": "24,711 ÷ 1,880=？",
        "answer": 1.1187324714396667
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 138,287=？",
        "answer": 6.587939386479504
    },
    {
        "question": "1,279,831 ÷ 462=？",
        "answer": 3.4425106498627307
    },
    {
        "question": "5,525 × 9,640=？",
        "answer": 7.726409316259979
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 153,118=？",
        "answer": 6.546754083810363
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 31,757,573=？",
        "answer": 8.732296226437407
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 1,660=？",
        "answer": 5.183895915385611
    },
    {
        "question": "224,615,026 ÷ 807,174=？",
        "answer": 2.4444716414262144
    },
    {
        "question": "8,181,283 ÷ 24,325=？",
        "answer": 2.52676856672697
    },
    {
        "question": "29,945 × 1,918=？",
        "answer": 7.759172920254873
    },
    {
        "question": "10,242 ÷ 602=？",
        "answer": 1.2307882802405528
    },
    {
        "question": "16,113 ÷ 2,908=？",
        "answer": 0.743582004908162
    },
    {
        "question": "138,376,248 ÷ 3,827=？",
        "answer": 4.5582030885336025
    },
    {
        "question": "373,087,341 ÷ 169,859,247=？",
        "answer": 0.34172131901860264
    },
    {
        "question": "133 × 653=？",
        "answer": 4.93876482224216
    },
    {
        "question": "10,869,120 ÷ 184,019=？",
        "answer": 1.771331717267998
    },
    {
        "question": "196,047,797 ÷ 12,841=？",
        "answer": 4.183763120498828
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 2,764,925=？",
        "answer": 7.617774614396975
    },
    {
        "question": "262,884,448 ÷ 7,782,031=？",
        "answer": 1.528671937908921
    },
    {
        "question": "1,804,956 ÷ 1,314,935=？",
        "answer": 0.13756233416516636
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 295,143=？",
        "answer": 6.54921373342722
    },
    {
        "question": "9,475,178 ÷ 584=？",
        "answer": 4.210174530228677
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 1,158=？",
        "answer": 4.707161235877605
    },
    {
        "question": "42,122 × 9,548=？",
        "answer": 8.604421394128856
    },
    {
        "question": "167,211,424 ÷ 37,264,671=？",
        "answer": 0.65196865410445
    },
    {
        "question": "6,888,737 ÷ 105,953=？",
        "answer": 1.8130263464339904
    },
    {
        "question": "700,506,557 ÷ 17,127,562=？",
        "answer": 1.6117166565022136
    },
    {
        "question": "6,705,446 ÷ 261=？",
        "answer": 4.409787162082319
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,565,685=？",
        "answer": 6.671825645568954
    },
    {
        "question": "78,576 ÷ 48,875=？",
        "answer": 0.20620314638360546
    },
    {
        "question": "325 × 6,125=？",
        "answer": 6.2989894540154445
    },
    {
        "question": "168,493,880 ÷ 174,848=？",
        "answer": 2.9839234621457367
    },
    {
        "question": "31,219 ÷ 2,839=？",
        "answer": 1.0412535951999828
    },
    {
        "question": "2,178,378 ÷ 1,603=？",
        "answer": 3.1331997199481783
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 403,396=？",
        "answer": 6.781822846570156
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 493,858=？",
        "answer": 5.693602093292868
    },
    {
        "question": "1,894,639 ÷ 150,703=？",
        "answer": 1.0994045749785566
    },
    {
        "question": "450,488,559 ÷ 678,102=？",
        "answer": 2.822388740443172
    },
    {
        "question": "10,059,252 ÷ 305,396=？",
        "answer": 1.5177023435632184
    },
    {
        "question": "362 × 1,003=？",
        "answer": 5.560009503553584
    },
    {
        "question": "1,464 ÷ 308=？",
        "answer": 0.6769903602219287
    },
    {
        "question": "18,965,851 ÷ 704,827=？",
        "answer": 1.4298898019615507
    },
    {
        "question": "417,302,538 ÷ 254,496,674=？",
        "answer": 0.214768915119011
    },
    {
        "question": "389 × 1,676,088=？",
        "answer": 8.814246418072894
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 88,096=？",
        "answer": 6.359929537684054
    },
    {
        "question": "83 × 49,926=？",
        "answer": 6.61740486476974
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 21,864=？",
        "answer": 4.339729618684604
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,919=？",
        "answer": 3.5841049703994527
    },
    {
        "question": "7,080,458 ÷ 1,581=？",
        "answer": 3.651129481039964
    },
    {
        "question": "1,613 × 36,762=？",
        "answer": 7.773033498104559
    },
    {
        "question": "91,614,741 ÷ 2,038,101=？",
        "answer": 1.6527396560917782
    },
    {
        "question": "46,371,631 ÷ 11,063,578=？",
        "answer": 0.6223567692826955
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,678=？",
        "answer": 3.42781057267599
    },
    {
        "question": "14,743,129 ÷ 1,582,984=？",
        "answer": 0.9691131403036585
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 3,215,591=？",
        "answer": 7.621204156767883
    },
    {
        "question": "3,902,815 ÷ 50,574=？",
        "answer": 1.8874506612593334
    },
    {
        "question": "3,633,056 ÷ 10,266=？",
        "answer": 2.5488708322136513
    },
    {
        "question": "622 × 8,327=？",
        "answer": 6.714278949349117
    },
    {
        "question": "836,861,942 ÷ 2,502=？",
        "answer": 5.524366512524791
    },
    {
        "question": "125,860,620 ÷ 28,573=？",
        "answer": 3.643934025598499
    },
    {
        "question": "620,462,282 ÷ 347,907=？",
        "answer": 3.2512522188278723
    },
    {
        "question": "105,760,005 ÷ 572=？",
        "answer": 5.266925433880616
    },
    {
        "question": "37,181,298 ÷ 3,495,884=？",
        "answer": 1.0267675334367627
    },
    {
        "question": "83,638 ÷ 40,423=？",
        "answer": 0.3157750975540186
    },
    {
        "question": "805 × 2,569=？",
        "answer": 6.3155599846342145
    },
    {
        "question": "166,323 × 378=？",
        "answer": 7.7984441096845405
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,798,157=？",
        "answer": 6.856887599335258
    },
    {
        "question": "17,265 × 20,406=？",
        "answer": 8.546924465001839
    },
    {
        "question": "2,253 ÷ 531=？",
        "answer": 0.6276666706423617
    },
    {
        "question": "4,867 ÷ 2,503=？",
        "answer": 0.2888004966352832
    },
    {
        "question": "2,977,018 ÷ 8,708=？",
        "answer": 2.533863040168512
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 3,653=？",
        "answer": 4.604042357370142
    },
    {
        "question": "56,148 × 1,424=？",
        "answer": 7.902844280540642
    },
    {
        "question": "174,183,999 ÷ 27,782,199=？",
        "answer": 0.797241639292124
    },
    {
        "question": "3,589,494 ÷ 110,025=？",
        "answer": 1.5135418544920634
    },
    {
        "question": "16,122 × 1,116=？",
        "answer": 7.255083111418372
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 962=？",
        "answer": 2.983175072037813
    },
    {
        "question": "767,297 ÷ 2,907=？",
        "answer": 2.4215184684164996
    },
    {
        "question": "10,131 × 56,623=？",
        "answer": 8.758645190785614
    },
    {
        "question": "4,277 × 244=？",
        "answer": 6.018529076595541
    },
    {
        "question": "3,408,910 ÷ 2,294,628=？",
        "answer": 0.17190324667548482
    },
    {
        "question": "699,966,432 ÷ 10,105,489=？",
        "answer": 1.840519879561674
    },
    {
        "question": "13,869 ÷ 919=？",
        "answer": 1.178729636771633
    },
    {
        "question": "66,549 ÷ 10,873=？",
        "answer": 0.7867921458923817
    },
    {
        "question": "87,643,506 ÷ 118,193=？",
        "answer": 2.8701279861583546
    },
    {
        "question": "146,597,091 ÷ 10,910,655=？",
        "answer": 1.1282745290688048
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 241,114=？",
        "answer": 6.558313686962068
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 568,634=？",
        "answer": 6.3568928149745565
    },
    {
        "question": "30,418,402 ÷ 607=？",
        "answer": 4.699947704019397
    },
    {
        "question": "733,087 × 1,206=？",
        "answer": 8.946502825934793
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 7,412,246=？",
        "answer": 8.602343584213711
    },
    {
        "question": "921,513 ÷ 91,575=？",
        "answer": 1.0027245389558308
    },
    {
        "question": "80,714,355 ÷ 6,909,321=？",
        "answer": 1.0675154105756108
    },
    {
        "question": "766 × 793=？",
        "answer": 5.783501956950207
    },
    {
        "question": "378 × 18,393=？",
        "answer": 6.842144370684122
    },
    {
        "question": "1,205 × 47,878=？",
        "answer": 7.761123047310564
    },
    {
        "question": "10,709,088 ÷ 4,820,561=？",
        "answer": 0.34665490446787867
    },
    {
        "question": "365,194,047 ÷ 98,409=？",
        "answer": 3.5694888708479335
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 106,668=？",
        "answer": 5.806185402630982
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 253,482=？",
        "answer": 5.704977120760457
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,706,534=？",
        "answer": 6.2321149453338425
    },
    {
        "question": "348 × 95,607=？",
        "answer": 7.522068934863679
    },
    {
        "question": "243 × 243,242=？",
        "answer": 7.771644839237617
    },
    {
        "question": "260 × 310=？",
        "answer": 4.90633504180509
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 19,075,719=？",
        "answer": 8.321873601475714
    },
    {
        "question": "286,014,777 ÷ 694,061=？",
        "answer": 2.6149908299685296
    },
    {
        "question": "631 × 134,292=？",
        "answer": 7.928079501031689
    },
    {
        "question": "78,956 × 5,276=？",
        "answer": 8.619689925244995
    },
    {
        "question": "4,359,629 ÷ 900=？",
        "answer": 3.6852070233824024
    },
    {
        "question": "647,586 × 836=？",
        "answer": 8.7335037287179
    },
    {
        "question": "17,326 × 2,596=？",
        "answer": 7.653002998191318
    },
    {
        "question": "40,167 ÷ 998=？",
        "answer": 1.6047388549924833
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 489,453=？",
        "answer": 6.166832249488753
    },
    {
        "question": "5,302 × 28,840=？",
        "answer": 8.184434979444466
    },
    {
        "question": "803,550 ÷ 566,267=？",
        "answer": 0.15199165218183688
    },
    {
        "question": "4,078,219 ÷ 2,612=？",
        "answer": 3.1934973710406
    },
    {
        "question": "1,430,281 ÷ 840,790=？",
        "answer": 0.23073383172916997
    },
    {
        "question": "10,748,470 ÷ 639=？",
        "answer": 4.225845790479514
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 40,254=？",
        "answer": 4.905839037923494
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 1,734=？",
        "answer": 4.600776929157784
    },
    {
        "question": "756,474,211 ÷ 229,538,480=？",
        "answer": 0.5179386256331134
    },
    {
        "question": "70,997 ÷ 3,067=？",
        "answer": 1.3645262218778265
    },
    {
        "question": "93,900,892 ÷ 266,175=？",
        "answer": 2.547502455073547
    },
    {
        "question": "8,183,338 ÷ 3,682,656=？",
        "answer": 0.34676933646605856
    },
    {
        "question": "461 × 236,111=？",
        "answer": 8.036817145962731
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,520,205=？",
        "answer": 6.702465864520014
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 417=？",
        "answer": 3.09725730969342
    },
    {
        "question": "202,191,512 ÷ 3,499=？",
        "answer": 4.761818977471697
    },
    {
        "question": "100,870,274 ÷ 951,606=？",
        "answer": 2.025306028872866
    },
    {
        "question": "139 × 183,363=？",
        "answer": 7.406326506086698
    },
    {
        "question": "1,710 ÷ 746=？",
        "answer": 0.36025728291948506
    },
    {
        "question": "173,356,930 ÷ 1,534=？",
        "answer": 5.053115847790487
    },
    {
        "question": "87,100,361 ÷ 9,376,209=？",
        "answer": 0.9679926756023223
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 3,083,657=？",
        "answer": 8.221459824632602
    },
    {
        "question": "2,945,722 ÷ 14,572=？",
        "answer": 2.305672595699508
    },
    {
        "question": "163 × 464,424=？",
        "answer": 7.879102259049833
    },
    {
        "question": "244,044 ÷ 204,367=？",
        "answer": 0.0770573649114223
    },
    {
        "question": "197,926 × 209=？",
        "answer": 7.616649133954885
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,539=？",
        "answer": 3.664359874551141
    },
    {
        "question": "142 × 77,573=？",
        "answer": 7.0419989317309675
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 5,169=？",
        "answer": 4.754799217325916
    },
    {
        "question": "882 × 9,383=？",
        "answer": 6.917810301457568
    },
    {
        "question": "555 × 29,753=？",
        "answer": 7.217823745380809
    },
    {
        "question": "432,294,103 ÷ 2,894=？",
        "answer": 5.174280784503519
    },
    {
        "question": "103,655,961 ÷ 90,854,030=？",
        "answer": 0.057250086344878874
    },
    {
        "question": "173 × 2,216=？",
        "answer": 5.583615859185188
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 586,970=？",
        "answer": 6.671705892042961
    },
    {
        "question": "7,866 ÷ 3,446=？",
        "answer": 0.3584386689617183
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 1,579,123=？",
        "answer": 8.227799736788382
    },
    {
        "question": "251,294,397 ÷ 2,024,857=？",
        "answer": 2.0937884476575706
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 14,481=？",
        "answer": 6.186104418803125
    },
    {
        "question": "157 × 1,997=？",
        "answer": 5.496277717279936
    },
    {
        "question": "85,028,732 ÷ 486,845=？",
        "answer": 2.2421749885921956
    },
    {
        "question": "41,506,857 ÷ 1,482,587=？",
        "answer": 1.4470996610807865
    },
    {
        "question": "12,152,429 ÷ 2,205,229=？",
        "answer": 0.7412093973475646
    },
    {
        "question": "15,784 × 2,652=？",
        "answer": 7.62179059197687
    },
    {
        "question": "312 × 128,976=？",
        "answer": 7.6046634978271985
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 4,575,528=？",
        "answer": 8.002863898187579
    },
    {
        "question": "728,299,457 ÷ 93,071=？",
        "answer": 3.8934956059477526
    },
    {
        "question": "519,657,209 ÷ 1,806=？",
        "answer": 5.4589992104830545
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 213,020=？",
        "answer": 7.328420380348951
    },
    {
        "question": "45,623,664 ÷ 332,907=？",
        "answer": 2.136867233067577
    },
    {
        "question": "1,264 × 356=？",
        "answer": 5.653197071919242
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,017,448=？",
        "answer": 6.007512222427827
    },
    {
        "question": "88,462,763 ÷ 1,032=？",
        "answer": 4.933080802482545
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 183,202=？",
        "answer": 6.376873562818923
    },
    {
        "question": "173,313,843 ÷ 542=？",
        "answer": 5.504833965722053
    },
    {
        "question": "1,081 ÷ 384=？",
        "answer": 0.44949446958577954
    },
    {
        "question": "16,228,173 ÷ 715,398=？",
        "answer": 1.3557219071608142
    },
    {
        "question": "348,786 × 2,487=？",
        "answer": 8.938234829636054
    },
    {
        "question": "74,997 ÷ 55,342=？",
        "answer": 0.1319890412437704
    },
    {
        "question": "2,944 × 945=？",
        "answer": 6.444369614174724
    },
    {
        "question": "709 × 8,683=？",
        "answer": 6.789316036205745
    },
    {
        "question": "344,419 ÷ 35,727=？",
        "answer": 0.9840905514767758
    },
    {
        "question": "356,522 ÷ 124,122=？",
        "answer": 0.45823756930923787
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 77,368=？",
        "answer": 6.189591365945512
    },
    {
        "question": "12,713,320 ÷ 6,432=？",
        "answer": 3.295912942775667
    },
    {
        "question": "30,895 ÷ 592=？",
        "answer": 1.7175664928276773
    },
    {
        "question": "1,513 ÷ 462=？",
        "answer": 0.5151969524670612
    },
    {
        "question": "5,265 × 2,939=？",
        "answer": 7.189597961594118
    },
    {
        "question": "457 × 296,117=？",
        "answer": 8.131379540908187
    },
    {
        "question": "4,371 × 8,469=？",
        "answer": 7.568412939356234
    },
    {
        "question": "829,998,707 ÷ 2,941,712=？",
        "answer": 2.450477263719225
    },
    {
        "question": "32,359 × 7,960=？",
        "answer": 8.410908159751068
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 6,624=？",
        "answer": 4.520090328112842
    },
    {
        "question": "572 × 123,934=？",
        "answer": 7.850586495675534
    },
    {
        "question": "10,916,210 ÷ 6,563,194=？",
        "answer": 0.22095664013364977
    },
    {
        "question": "1,279 × 286,682=？",
        "answer": 8.564270970086168
    },
    {
        "question": "736,389,673 ÷ 1,774,578=？",
        "answer": 2.6180125962734118
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 519,591=？",
        "answer": 7.058084300736306
    },
    {
        "question": "127 × 1,792,013=？",
        "answer": 8.357144876844444
    },
    {
        "question": "4,234 × 7,861=？",
        "answer": 7.522228649959108
    },
    {
        "question": "4,887,317 ÷ 3,735,685=？",
        "answer": 0.1167002604751097
    },
    {
        "question": "125,577,950 ÷ 298,287=？",
        "answer": 2.6242790628594914
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,672=？",
        "answer": 3.8849085941626074
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 415,089=？",
        "answer": 7.417481774032777
    },
    {
        "question": "14,733,290 ÷ 144,287=？",
        "answer": 2.009072533588867
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,816=？",
        "answer": 3.833529581758644
    },
    {
        "question": "28,855 × 2,651=？",
        "answer": 7.883630806377775
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 152,547=？",
        "answer": 7.137646180635994
    },
    {
        "question": "4,528 × 48,527=？",
        "answer": 8.341889861695833
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 499,916=？",
        "answer": 6.176018291453271
    },
    {
        "question": "5,139 × 16,445=？",
        "answer": 7.926912495503847
    },
    {
        "question": "234 × 47,280=？",
        "answer": 7.043893325283342
    },
    {
        "question": "406,133,240 ÷ 485,756=？",
        "answer": 2.9222503621448417
    },
    {
        "question": "6,189 × 970=？",
        "answer": 6.778392216959059
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 213,841=？",
        "answer": 6.029060981011671
    },
    {
        "question": "8,453,024 ÷ 41,656=？",
        "answer": 2.3073345373676117
    },
    {
        "question": "12,773 × 5,319=？",
        "answer": 7.832122902496238
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 8,120,000=？",
        "answer": 7.687707279624819
    },
    {
        "question": "150,817,097 ÷ 376=？",
        "answer": 5.603262732095985
    },
    {
        "question": "5,628 × 47,416=？",
        "answer": 8.42627900299367
    },
    {
        "question": "119,184,340 ÷ 2,502=？",
        "answer": 4.67793189049671
    },
    {
        "question": "269,638 ÷ 1,321=？",
        "answer": 2.3098782795490624
    },
    {
        "question": "166,045,957 ÷ 4,462=？",
        "answer": 4.570698739617621
    },
    {
        "question": "1,282 × 14,513=？",
        "answer": 7.269645220444525
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 732,365,446=？",
        "answer": 8.864727845507405
    },
    {
        "question": "590,384,416 ÷ 642,633=？",
        "answer": 2.963171861825147
    },
    {
        "question": "589,716,782 ÷ 954=？",
        "answer": 5.79109511228397
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,460,897=？",
        "answer": 6.391093436836589
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 155,353=？",
        "answer": 5.1913196442718155
    },
    {
        "question": "9,613 ÷ 4,491=？",
        "answer": 0.33051588724936043
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 7,217,203=？",
        "answer": 7.972312273281476
    },
    {
        "question": "391 × 1,123,190=？",
        "answer": 8.642629985582458
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 362,442,969=？",
        "answer": 8.559239679328646
    },
    {
        "question": "863,927,515 ÷ 1,751,789=？",
        "answer": 2.692995511003812
    },
    {
        "question": "419 × 973,087=？",
        "answer": 8.610365693584935
    },
    {
        "question": "461 × 349=？",
        "answer": 5.206526352348828
    },
    {
        "question": "37,064 ÷ 23,665=？",
        "answer": 0.19484577839108597
    },
    {
        "question": "320,318,453 ÷ 291,812=？",
        "answer": 3.040478811207735
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 13,848,921=？",
        "answer": 8.603813935775923
    },
    {
        "question": "2,197 ÷ 1,098=？",
        "answer": 0.30122771680643723
    },
    {
        "question": "12,052 × 3,664=？",
        "answer": 7.6450145879971325
    },
    {
        "question": "588,684 × 1,013=？",
        "answer": 8.775491677526892
    },
    {
        "question": "264 × 3,221,034=？",
        "answer": 8.929599235959765
    },
    {
        "question": "196 × 7,291=？",
        "answer": 6.155043169591821
    },
    {
        "question": "3,807 ÷ 810=？",
        "answer": 0.6720978579357175
    },
    {
        "question": "28,218,294 ÷ 865=？",
        "answer": 4.513514646504109
    },
    {
        "question": "2,713 ÷ 2,383=？",
        "answer": 0.05632575141513999
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 490=？",
        "answer": 4.051923916046107
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,109,970=？",
        "answer": 6.492756199670794
    },
    {
        "question": "3,333,665 ÷ 11,713=？",
        "answer": 2.454253812145718
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 4,486=？",
        "answer": 4.496957309261206
    },
    {
        "question": "1,978 × 6,886=？",
        "answer": 7.1341933056298155
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 3,654=？",
        "answer": 4.9607085516885565
    },
    {
        "question": "4,773,439 ÷ 25,628=？",
        "answer": 2.2701166617470845
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 943,098=？",
        "answer": 7.673526828195128
    },
    {
        "question": "17,394 × 313=？",
        "answer": 6.73594380328509
    },
    {
        "question": "3,646 × 29,705=？",
        "answer": 8.034646221031663
    },
    {
        "question": "571,291 × 1,095=？",
        "answer": 8.796271501505327
    },
    {
        "question": "3,595,027 ÷ 482,615=？",
        "answer": 0.8721013404972449
    },
    {
        "question": "3,429 × 16,088=？",
        "answer": 7.7416695427036295
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 34,342,144=？",
        "answer": 7.535827404928077
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 2,152=？",
        "answer": 5.103694278636496
    },
    {
        "question": "59,056 × 5,282=？",
        "answer": 8.494062424722488
    },
    {
        "question": "819 × 1,483=？",
        "answer": 6.0844250527888
    },
    {
        "question": "10,812 ÷ 841=？",
        "answer": 1.1091100412287758
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 381,471,622=？",
        "answer": 8.581462235954836
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 4,911=？",
        "answer": 5.168291188851266
    },
    {
        "question": "1,654,789 ÷ 457,862=？",
        "answer": 0.5580080243192896
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,005=？",
        "answer": 4.204255678480151
    },
    {
        "question": "12,051,958 ÷ 2,374=？",
        "answer": 3.705576894907803
    },
    {
        "question": "4,962 ÷ 1,845=？",
        "answer": 0.4296603894411111
    },
    {
        "question": "923,160 ÷ 758,970=？",
        "answer": 0.08505236871894425
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 75,791=？",
        "answer": 4.879617637262669
    },
    {
        "question": "31,668 ÷ 2,311=？",
        "answer": 1.1368206907885652
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 997,202=？",
        "answer": 5.998783140858704
    },
    {
        "question": "20,397,885 ÷ 63,626=？",
        "answer": 2.505950517834935
    },
    {
        "question": "23,822 × 200=？",
        "answer": 6.678008215971998
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 24,744=？",
        "answer": 6.406307131700295
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,235=？",
        "answer": 3.9367649976099415
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 11,580=？",
        "answer": 5.209836595069655
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 66,875,621=？",
        "answer": 7.825267827861002
    },
    {
        "question": "30,686,434 ÷ 419,280=？",
        "answer": 1.8644422763054163
    },
    {
        "question": "15,927,585 ÷ 17,019=？",
        "answer": 2.9712158931550046
    },
    {
        "question": "227,534,986 ÷ 36,879=？",
        "answer": 3.79026904732686
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 15,128=？",
        "answer": 4.878751520173002
    },
    {
        "question": "924,604,942 ÷ 424,484,495=？",
        "answer": 0.33809437886232685
    },
    {
        "question": "626,684,701 ÷ 44,785,620=？",
        "answer": 1.1459105017266022
    },
    {
        "question": "352,186,407 ÷ 11,221=？",
        "answer": 4.496741027539931
    },
    {
        "question": "155,332,788 ÷ 306,842=？",
        "answer": 2.704348332457103
    },
    {
        "question": "14,134,448 ÷ 18,579=？",
        "answer": 2.881256517697641
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,403,841=？",
        "answer": 6.448347917750531
    },
    {
        "question": "98 × 6,991,561=？",
        "answer": 8.835800226831562
    },
    {
        "question": "230 × 292,195=？",
        "answer": 7.827400616092981
    },
    {
        "question": "1,143,621 × 290=？",
        "answer": 8.520680119489056
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 255=？",
        "answer": 2.7075701760979363
    },
    {
        "question": "811 × 650=？",
        "answer": 5.721934210854012
    },
    {
        "question": "130,900,237 ÷ 292=？",
        "answer": 5.651557581410199
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 326=？",
        "answer": 2.513217600067939
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 231=？",
        "answer": 2.3636119798921444
    },
    {
        "question": "6,583,119 ÷ 1,394=？",
        "answer": 3.6741689319416992
    },
    {
        "question": "2,217 × 3,655=？",
        "answer": 6.908653074408368
    },
    {
        "question": "16,808,720 ÷ 23,788=？",
        "answer": 2.8491767129339243
    },
    {
        "question": "817,163,892 ÷ 86,771,769=？",
        "answer": 0.9739307168019008
    },
    {
        "question": "8,597 × 2,925=？",
        "answer": 7.400472797156455
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 214,520=？",
        "answer": 6.1096190386746745
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 227=？",
        "answer": 3.1341771075767664
    },
    {
        "question": "9,796 ÷ 384=？",
        "answer": 1.4067175520851458
    },
    {
        "question": "20,079,485 ÷ 17,859=？",
        "answer": 3.0508954325299324
    },
    {
        "question": "150,096 × 1,748=？",
        "answer": 8.418910546916905
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 9,093,766=？",
        "answer": 8.560803766112793
    },
    {
        "question": "939 × 689,453=？",
        "answer": 8.811170257939153
    },
    {
        "question": "2,041,415 ÷ 2,902=？",
        "answer": 2.8472338934732524
    },
    {
        "question": "9,240,357 ÷ 820,765=？",
        "answer": 1.0514699219749792
    },
    {
        "question": "44,531,580 ÷ 328,320=？",
        "answer": 2.1323707652676815
    },
    {
        "question": "49,608 × 215=？",
        "answer": 7.0279901782545
    },
    {
        "question": "893,848,851 ÷ 1,788=？",
        "answer": 5.6988965717561175
    },
    {
        "question": "950 × 1,670=？",
        "answer": 6.200440076436431
    },
    {
        "question": "65,544,086 ÷ 413,846=？",
        "answer": 2.1996947497751242
    },
    {
        "question": "1,013,127 ÷ 65,297=？",
        "answer": 1.190770660984717
    },
    {
        "question": "8,468 × 106,405=？",
        "answer": 8.95474288540217
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 1,493=？",
        "answer": 5.031392304156294
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 333=？",
        "answer": 3.2214142378423385
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 453,519=？",
        "answer": 7.29006394195322
    },
    {
        "question": "282,503 ÷ 195,417=？",
        "answer": 0.16006072230410065
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,446=？",
        "answer": 4.0144365278316725
    },
    {
        "question": "31,098 ÷ 5,732=？",
        "answer": 0.7344262774978679
    },
    {
        "question": "313,813,536 ÷ 57,518=？",
        "answer": 3.7368678959977
    },
    {
        "question": "35,017,280 ÷ 8,860=？",
        "answer": 3.596848686940098
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 65,179=？",
        "answer": 4.814107693075836
    },
    {
        "question": "264,851 × 1,083=？",
        "answer": 8.457630073669117
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 187,811=？",
        "answer": 5.273721025094085
    },
    {
        "question": "852,508 ÷ 5,206=？",
        "answer": 2.2141942993629353
    },
    {
        "question": "1,311,142 × 656=？",
        "answer": 8.934553568805494
    },
    {
        "question": "4,941,468 ÷ 97,797=？",
        "answer": 1.7035304546355297
    },
    {
        "question": "111,976,503 ÷ 216,273=？",
        "answer": 2.714124595916821
    },
    {
        "question": "4,012,539 ÷ 89,290=？",
        "answer": 1.652616443607767
    },
    {
        "question": "4,144 ÷ 332=？",
        "answer": 1.0962816630331402
    },
    {
        "question": "62,882,528 ÷ 1,586=？",
        "answer": 4.598226809884072
    },
    {
        "question": "302 × 83,069=？",
        "answer": 7.399445925336485
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 8,319,645=？",
        "answer": 7.397226050021161
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,408,454=？",
        "answer": 6.6827683516343654
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,960=？",
        "answer": 3.842609239610562
    },
    {
        "question": "56,128,179 ÷ 1,982=？",
        "answer": 4.45207730222398
    },
    {
        "question": "71,240 × 8,621=？",
        "answer": 8.78828155588422
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 3,237,336=？",
        "answer": 8.143656232329413
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 168,306=？",
        "answer": 5.226099598569074
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,520=？",
        "answer": 4.115277591395901
    },
    {
        "question": "416 ÷ 384=？",
        "answer": 0.03476210625921191
    },
    {
        "question": "9,098 ÷ 404=？",
        "answer": 1.3525645673833313
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 252=？",
        "answer": 3.5774917998372255
    },
    {
        "question": "841,844,949 ÷ 1,547,281=？",
        "answer": 2.73566291790343
    },
    {
        "question": "745 × 271,033=？",
        "answer": 8.305178444970958
    },
    {
        "question": "5,056,641 ÷ 50,391=？",
        "answer": 2.00150914473197
    },
    {
        "question": "836,437 ÷ 38,545=？",
        "answer": 1.3364651856885152
    },
    {
        "question": "827,283,395 ÷ 405,414,242=？",
        "answer": 0.30975530620457875
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 910,511=？",
        "answer": 7.421683194828844
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 933=？",
        "answer": 3.2709116394104814
    },
    {
        "question": "16,113 ÷ 11,305=？",
        "answer": 0.1539058404137837
    },
    {
        "question": "50,920,275 ÷ 606,143=？",
        "answer": 1.9243156463305437
    },
    {
        "question": "8,187,146 ÷ 445=？",
        "answer": 4.2647725241782615
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 27,447=？",
        "answer": 4.739524877978445
    },
    {
        "question": "901 × 506=？",
        "answer": 5.658875307818862
    },
    {
        "question": "511,897,115 ÷ 8,431=？",
        "answer": 4.7833035926161775
    },
    {
        "question": "264,233 × 1,423=？",
        "answer": 8.575191955690283
    },
    {
        "question": "876,361,039 ÷ 46,490,880=？",
        "answer": 1.2753152948026591
    },
    {
        "question": "466,145,856 ÷ 47,798=？",
        "answer": 3.9891121028155134
    },
    {
        "question": "8,576 × 5,028=？",
        "answer": 7.634680041362615
    },
    {
        "question": "852 × 1,132,534=？",
        "answer": 8.984490843677385
    },
    {
        "question": "606,393,269 ÷ 7,471=？",
        "answer": 4.909375635548
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 9,417,347=？",
        "answer": 8.087871925424723
    },
    {
        "question": "181,601,015 ÷ 19,812,185=？",
        "answer": 0.9621858969043845
    },
    {
        "question": "142,920,300 ÷ 241,133=？",
        "answer": 2.7728372697930084
    },
    {
        "question": "87 × 2,744,298=？",
        "answer": 8.377950521726433
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 523,844=？",
        "answer": 6.760594659115055
    },
    {
        "question": "175,572 ÷ 396=？",
        "answer": 2.6467600704333414
    },
    {
        "question": "257 × 47,386=？",
        "answer": 7.085583173426647
    },
    {
        "question": "203 × 478,889=？",
        "answer": 7.987730899398989
    },
    {
        "question": "48,593,508 ÷ 1,999,426=？",
        "answer": 1.3856729169650652
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 778=？",
        "answer": 4.524448052569276
    },
    {
        "question": "48,362,201 ÷ 416,413=？",
        "answer": 2.0649817784135167
    },
    {
        "question": "6,549 × 59,953=？",
        "answer": 8.593985910154704
    },
    {
        "question": "31,300,027 ÷ 442=？",
        "answer": 4.8501224428282175
    },
    {
        "question": "22,834 × 5,353=？",
        "answer": 8.087179240101946
    },
    {
        "question": "36,912 ÷ 15,887=？",
        "answer": 0.36612568163433834
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 13,039=？",
        "answer": 5.513184293999292
    },
    {
        "question": "2,892,416 ÷ 27,800=？",
        "answer": 2.017215959340559
    },
    {
        "question": "171 × 255=？",
        "answer": 4.639536290826109
    },
    {
        "question": "183,887 ÷ 18,182=？",
        "answer": 1.0049093741897084
    },
    {
        "question": "15,287,796 ÷ 672=？",
        "answer": 4.356975605816167
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 47,725=？",
        "answer": 5.6329884465050295
    },
    {
        "question": "519,578,457 ÷ 154,002=？",
        "answer": 3.5281247748696134
    },
    {
        "question": "677,001,883 ÷ 25,854=？",
        "answer": 4.418062132153121
    },
    {
        "question": "760,875,553 ÷ 100,249,790=？",
        "answer": 0.8802301588567097
    },
    {
        "question": "163,641,612 ÷ 493=？",
        "answer": 5.52104682971616
    },
    {
        "question": "2,287,937 ÷ 786=？",
        "answer": 3.4640215156335663
    },
    {
        "question": "86,271 ÷ 8,807=？",
        "answer": 0.991036835796494
    },
    {
        "question": "141,027,478 ÷ 2,288,281=？",
        "answer": 1.7897943848858051
    },
    {
        "question": "1,627,046 ÷ 118,934=？",
        "answer": 1.1360938061618162
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 2,136=？",
        "answer": 4.107752498740163
    },
    {
        "question": "4,360,436 ÷ 74,183=？",
        "answer": 1.7692255240977386
    },
    {
        "question": "11,173 ÷ 3,855=？",
        "answer": 0.46214541637904183
    },
    {
        "question": "360,836 × 478=？",
        "answer": 8.236737756472609
    },
    {
        "question": "234,370,274 ÷ 6,703,244=？",
        "answer": 1.5436174996288752
    },
    {
        "question": "572,133 ÷ 982=？",
        "answer": 2.7653855103275666
    },
    {
        "question": "671,957 × 218=？",
        "answer": 8.165797976092618
    },
    {
        "question": "254,189,429 ÷ 3,736,458=？",
        "answer": 1.8326973806550046
    },
    {
        "question": "11,916,023 ÷ 33,376=？",
        "answer": 2.5526970460613767
    },
    {
        "question": "4,251 × 424=？",
        "answer": 6.255856961559855
    },
    {
        "question": "408,693,325 ÷ 8,874=？",
        "answer": 4.663278120257067
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,475,585=？",
        "answer": 6.5410279142179935
    },
    {
        "question": "11,976,749 ÷ 64,339=？",
        "answer": 2.2698646415011052
    },
    {
        "question": "289 × 623=？",
        "answer": 5.2553858894157175
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 15,312,709=？",
        "answer": 7.185052029344675
    },
    {
        "question": "53,780,674 ÷ 1,529,980=？",
        "answer": 1.545940486937691
    },
    {
        "question": "322 × 488=？",
        "answer": 5.196275693698541
    },
    {
        "question": "6,553 × 151,568=？",
        "answer": 8.997047687917254
    },
    {
        "question": "1,092,240 ÷ 245=？",
        "answer": 3.6491519928534664
    },
    {
        "question": "2,806 ÷ 2,075=？",
        "answer": 0.1310695656442296
    },
    {
        "question": "3,409,842 ÷ 1,176,777=？",
        "answer": 0.4620400842347055
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 166,466,046=？",
        "answer": 8.698446918756552
    },
    {
        "question": "263 × 1,554=？",
        "answer": 5.611406762954653
    },
    {
        "question": "785,819,223 ÷ 250,332,221=？",
        "answer": 0.49680589594541225
    },
    {
        "question": "55,563,094 ÷ 2,543,306=？",
        "answer": 1.3393878053605677
    },
    {
        "question": "122 × 4,276=？",
        "answer": 5.717397527211489
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 3,619=？",
        "answer": 5.4336498464998995
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 476,399=？",
        "answer": 7.290754697912218
    },
    {
        "question": "23,857 ÷ 5,567=？",
        "answer": 0.631994609252842
    },
    {
        "question": "1,710,367 ÷ 4,993=？",
        "answer": 2.5347277425672163
    },
    {
        "question": "951 × 250,189=？",
        "answer": 8.37644872819282
    },
    {
        "question": "16,696 ÷ 831=？",
        "answer": 1.3030114122732865
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,376,500=？",
        "answer": 7.031529645803423
    },
    {
        "question": "83,533,233 ÷ 58,190,768=？",
        "answer": 0.1570052012628306
    },
    {
        "question": "1,069 × 50,792=？",
        "answer": 7.734773019275074
    },
    {
        "question": "845,834 ÷ 683=？",
        "answer": 3.092864434821009
    },
    {
        "question": "19,484,364 ÷ 286=？",
        "answer": 4.833320201182452
    },
    {
        "question": "157,777,069 ÷ 7,447=？",
        "answer": 4.326062530135065
    },
    {
        "question": "40,440 × 629=？",
        "answer": 7.405461792364233
    },
    {
        "question": "3,303 × 302=？",
        "answer": 5.998915516648565
    },
    {
        "question": "33,785 ÷ 4,650=？",
        "answer": 0.86127097037104
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 17,522=？",
        "answer": 5.775062593040446
    },
    {
        "question": "15,745 ÷ 4,664=？",
        "answer": 0.528384123221605
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 8,294=？",
        "answer": 5.948147808713209
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,372,299=？",
        "answer": 6.804296145503788
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 20,919,509=？",
        "answer": 7.922611478354315
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 33,996=？",
        "answer": 5.133487811896025
    },
    {
        "question": "80,595,963 ÷ 73,131=？",
        "answer": 3.0422117767709187
    },
    {
        "question": "415,407,933 ÷ 472=？",
        "answer": 5.9445327873185505
    },
    {
        "question": "1,752,710 × 360=？",
        "answer": 8.80001256528178
    },
    {
        "question": "7,775 × 735=？",
        "answer": 6.75698773678307
    },
    {
        "question": "137,345,853 ÷ 74,566,284=？",
        "answer": 0.26527305030526155
    },
    {
        "question": "77,014 × 7,074=？",
        "answer": 8.736234736106736
    },
    {
        "question": "219 × 3,258=？",
        "answer": 5.853395194812609
    },
    {
        "question": "54,765,222 ÷ 22,339=？",
        "answer": 3.389441124368448
    },
    {
        "question": "670,177 ÷ 3,888=？",
        "answer": 2.2364632628217307
    },
    {
        "question": "6,377 ÷ 478=？",
        "answer": 1.1251885203751362
    },
    {
        "question": "544,719,049 ÷ 210=？",
        "answer": 6.413953268222215
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 97,828=？",
        "answer": 5.893553161872541
    },
    {
        "question": "2,033,895 ÷ 187,171=？",
        "answer": 1.036089968011545
    },
    {
        "question": "88 × 947,161=？",
        "answer": 7.920906479525745
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 448,477=？",
        "answer": 5.952770170961116
    },
    {
        "question": "111 × 560,487=？",
        "answer": 7.793888522758257
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 791,175=？",
        "answer": 6.801362542712532
    },
    {
        "question": "155,343,290 ÷ 138,808,203=？",
        "answer": 0.0488773668813141
    },
    {
        "question": "151,050 ÷ 40,666=？",
        "answer": 0.5698892732942419
    },
    {
        "question": "5,433,405 ÷ 5,851=？",
        "answer": 2.9678419799599456
    },
    {
        "question": "28,337 ÷ 5,671=？",
        "answer": 0.6986942228875977
    },
    {
        "question": "2,794,443 ÷ 3,061=？",
        "answer": 2.9604319258690155
    },
    {
        "question": "260 × 744=？",
        "answer": 5.286546283516697
    },
    {
        "question": "1,221 × 768,163=？",
        "answer": 8.972169048676125
    },
    {
        "question": "64,576,718 ÷ 465=？",
        "answer": 5.142623016086178
    },
    {
        "question": "328 × 568,715=？",
        "answer": 8.270768526740211
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 20,957=？",
        "answer": 5.7837271112919755
    },
    {
        "question": "399,725,711 ÷ 348=？",
        "answer": 6.060182839730848
    },
    {
        "question": "510,260,305 ÷ 2,763,016=？",
        "answer": 2.26640838447844
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 1,059=？",
        "answer": 4.911386685279967
    },
    {
        "question": "38,321 × 403=？",
        "answer": 7.188741879763048
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 663=？",
        "answer": 2.821513528404773
    },
    {
        "question": "64,516,066 ÷ 3,151=？",
        "answer": 4.311219474349793
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 711=？",
        "answer": 3.1528995963937474
    },
    {
        "question": "88,906 × 8,617=？",
        "answer": 8.884287164140328
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 1,048,063=？",
        "answer": 7.877719885691581
    },
    {
        "question": "91,904 × 499=？",
        "answer": 7.661434959513558
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 102,437,798=？",
        "answer": 8.311490229978848
    },
    {
        "question": "702,692,092 ÷ 4,153,272=？",
        "answer": 2.2283746918557688
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 3,733,990=？",
        "answer": 7.174233141858367
    },
    {
        "question": "9,911,907 ÷ 4,230,539=？",
        "answer": 0.36976151552373815
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,835=？",
        "answer": 4.0417873189717515
    },
    {
        "question": "56,616,061 ÷ 627=？",
        "answer": 4.955672109689848
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 51,586=？",
        "answer": 4.712531853803205
    },
    {
        "question": "11,737 × 28,751=？",
        "answer": 8.528210059240662
    },
    {
        "question": "250,602,912 ÷ 2,894,406=？",
        "answer": 1.9374266633856327
    },
    {
        "question": "371 × 4,772=？",
        "answer": 6.24807434461335
    },
    {
        "question": "164,063 ÷ 96,072=？",
        "answer": 0.23241381683145823
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 37,756=？",
        "answer": 5.807434898795999
    },
    {
        "question": "650,760,763 ÷ 94,529=？",
        "answer": 3.8378562960632663
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,044,161=？",
        "answer": 7.132710820341558
    },
    {
        "question": "150,120,980 ÷ 313,382=？",
        "answer": 2.6803673429628807
    },
    {
        "question": "10,846 ÷ 3,977=？",
        "answer": 0.4357140091134559
    },
    {
        "question": "1,239 ÷ 682=？",
        "answer": 0.2592869317195845
    },
    {
        "question": "9,008,248 ÷ 654=？",
        "answer": 4.139062585616054
    },
    {
        "question": "193,313,845 ÷ 28,814,635=？",
        "answer": 0.8266498363357597
    },
    {
        "question": "111,606,963 ÷ 7,994,704=？",
        "answer": 1.144888901623639
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 2,380=？",
        "answer": 4.631849462159818
    },
    {
        "question": "22,023,637 ÷ 40,458=？",
        "answer": 2.7358846302158306
    },
    {
        "question": "264,960,284 ÷ 367=？",
        "answer": 5.858514716355288
    },
    {
        "question": "411,475,023 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 6.269951204496248
    },
    {
        "question": "138 × 7,338=？",
        "answer": 6.005456793821166
    },
    {
        "question": "3,420,855 ÷ 1,013,460=？",
        "answer": 0.5283280538004835
    },
    {
        "question": "63,970 ÷ 855=？",
        "answer": 1.87401023598939
    },
    {
        "question": "37,492,820 ÷ 49,551=？",
        "answer": 2.878895683343952
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 591=？",
        "answer": 3.885530833188092
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 67,169=？",
        "answer": 5.868561567806855
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,248=？",
        "answer": 3.9887372752888
    },
    {
        "question": "156 × 456=？",
        "answer": 4.852089441018896
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 32,689=？",
        "answer": 5.116461626465546
    },
    {
        "question": "864 × 31,159=？",
        "answer": 7.430097253692166
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 3,721=？",
        "answer": 5.03305766792049
    },
    {
        "question": "8,194,770 ÷ 2,087=？",
        "answer": 3.5940143198071914
    },
    {
        "question": "13,468,412 ÷ 126,171=？",
        "answer": 2.0283568478453273
    },
    {
        "question": "2,356 ÷ 629=？",
        "answer": 0.5735246406697951
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 3,127,943=？",
        "answer": 8.376072422662522
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 3,613=？",
        "answer": 4.460957948559966
    },
    {
        "question": "154,458 ÷ 16,891=？",
        "answer": 0.9611550451519681
    },
    {
        "question": "302,251 ÷ 722=？",
        "answer": 2.6218305488325284
    },
    {
        "question": "3,395,670 ÷ 2,405=？",
        "answer": 3.1498103970508837
    },
    {
        "question": "588,383 ÷ 19,528=？",
        "answer": 1.479002349867895
    },
    {
        "question": "89,907,162 ÷ 49,761,468=？",
        "answer": 0.2569011051086139
    },
    {
        "question": "128,545,239 ÷ 2,196,862=？",
        "answer": 1.7672532193193216
    },
    {
        "question": "136,498,471 ÷ 19,530=？",
        "answer": 3.844425543327148
    },
    {
        "question": "7,746,868 ÷ 213,940=？",
        "answer": 1.5588341645553625
    },
    {
        "question": "34,858 ÷ 17,830=？",
        "answer": 0.2911511223903222
    },
    {
        "question": "2,615,331 ÷ 727=？",
        "answer": 3.555992250748244
    },
    {
        "question": "398,556,853 ÷ 3,924,964=？",
        "answer": 2.0066546032970116
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 322,294=？",
        "answer": 5.809282216189824
    },
    {
        "question": "5,443,482 ÷ 1,516=？",
        "answer": 3.5551775898779767
    },
    {
        "question": "1,065,066 ÷ 75,369=？",
        "answer": 1.1501837678979068
    },
    {
        "question": "2,715,759 ÷ 609=？",
        "answer": 3.649273934826084
    },
    {
        "question": "991,167,648 ÷ 9,375=？",
        "answer": 5.024175841701524
    },
    {
        "question": "2,413 × 7,291=？",
        "answer": 7.24534442014413
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 52,320=？",
        "answer": 5.019697730980192
    },
    {
        "question": "8,815 ÷ 256=？",
        "answer": 1.5369823513234913
    },
    {
        "question": "198 × 636=？",
        "answer": 5.100122305909945
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 13,074,738=？",
        "answer": 8.417462990618644
    },
    {
        "question": "39,509 ÷ 1,339=？",
        "answer": 1.4699154605161089
    },
    {
        "question": "42,559 ÷ 1,699=？",
        "answer": 1.3987980360104244
    },
    {
        "question": "82,233 ÷ 10,523=？",
        "answer": 0.8929065639527027
    },
    {
        "question": "30,771,849 ÷ 1,302=？",
        "answer": 4.373542608419938
    },
    {
        "question": "13,660 × 707=？",
        "answer": 6.984870113142414
    },
    {
        "question": "26,443,151 ÷ 820=？",
        "answer": 4.508499352604447
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,762,217=？",
        "answer": 7.246059386539051
    },
    {
        "question": "512 × 15,954=？",
        "answer": 6.912139548691042
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 10,780,330=？",
        "answer": 8.111813301423895
    },
    {
        "question": "105 × 91,258=？",
        "answer": 6.981460245662161
    },
    {
        "question": "13,839 × 10,473=？",
        "answer": 8.16117581286177
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,293=？",
        "answer": 3.4126285205443754
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 543,922,112=？",
        "answer": 8.73553671449523
    },
    {
        "question": "603 ÷ 446=？",
        "answer": 0.13098245342800943
    },
    {
        "question": "323,782,946 ÷ 234,386=？",
        "answer": 3.1403223027757603
    },
    {
        "question": "3,426,646 ÷ 13,007=？",
        "answer": 2.420692100401461
    },
    {
        "question": "16,451 × 25,928=？",
        "answer": 8.62996132038808
    },
    {
        "question": "561,394 ÷ 154,842=？",
        "answer": 0.5593789945213309
    },
    {
        "question": "437,323 ÷ 31,558=？",
        "answer": 1.141692846832531
    },
    {
        "question": "11,698 × 15,177=？",
        "answer": 8.249297551155534
    },
    {
        "question": "5,387,278 ÷ 1,739,696=？",
        "answer": 0.49089602212956335
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 845,703=？",
        "answer": 7.85663679690049
    },
    {
        "question": "105,053,473 ÷ 349=？",
        "answer": 5.478584987515334
    },
    {
        "question": "222,747,266 ÷ 25,326,077=？",
        "answer": 0.9442444592661263
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,961,497=？",
        "answer": 7.292587648236933
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 28,640,906=？",
        "answer": 8.871960099894945
    },
    {
        "question": "624,237,290 ÷ 1,770,760=？",
        "answer": 2.54719000544447
    },
    {
        "question": "5,886,958 ÷ 95,217=？",
        "answer": 1.7911764433392485
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 100,017=？",
        "answer": 6.924353109848961
    },
    {
        "question": "82,166 ÷ 4,082=？",
        "answer": 1.3038191448117598
    },
    {
        "question": "17,046 × 5,633=？",
        "answer": 7.98236223534193
    },
    {
        "question": "121,426,565 ÷ 348=？",
        "answer": 5.5427344656165225
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,763=？",
        "answer": 3.575534218319864
    },
    {
        "question": "14,211,247 ÷ 743,786=？",
        "answer": 1.2811841882712922
    },
    {
        "question": "675,444,851 ÷ 3,294=？",
        "answer": 5.311866300516716
    },
    {
        "question": "1,306,406 ÷ 2,464=？",
        "answer": 2.724437462848064
    },
    {
        "question": "88 × 4,409=？",
        "answer": 5.588822770976491
    },
    {
        "question": "2,127 ÷ 396=？",
        "answer": 0.7300723039772167
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 22,507,131=？",
        "answer": 7.829441393421698
    },
    {
        "question": "7,896 × 8,633=？",
        "answer": 7.833568880572738
    },
    {
        "question": "25,871,089 ÷ 113,115=？",
        "answer": 2.3592945101535356
    },
    {
        "question": "190 × 4,012=？",
        "answer": 5.882114525301209
    },
    {
        "question": "88,117 ÷ 20,903=？",
        "answer": 0.6248510823369154
    },
    {
        "question": "490,180,541 ÷ 734,333=？",
        "answer": 2.8244630215083912
    },
    {
        "question": "1,753 × 149,088=？",
        "answer": 8.417224604861921
    },
    {
        "question": "814,216 ÷ 738,839=？",
        "answer": 0.04218982053064549
    },
    {
        "question": "77,116 × 377=？",
        "answer": 7.463485844868974
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 3,568,983=？",
        "answer": 8.427605742694018
    },
    {
        "question": "335,303,278 ÷ 17,151=？",
        "answer": 4.291148352275836
    },
    {
        "question": "761 × 596,271=？",
        "answer": 8.656828344455668
    },
    {
        "question": "48,354 × 430=？",
        "answer": 7.317900861735383
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 13,546=？",
        "answer": 6.0560903573322244
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 186,939=？",
        "answer": 6.839901639238693
    },
    {
        "question": "39,640,105 ÷ 22,752=？",
        "answer": 3.2411152171384443
    },
    {
        "question": "164 × 3,459=？",
        "answer": 5.753794410062059
    },
    {
        "question": "8,470,001 ÷ 254,956=？",
        "answer": 1.5214182247241634
    },
    {
        "question": "630 × 440=？",
        "answer": 5.442793225939769
    },
    {
        "question": "71,014,390 ÷ 839,820=？",
        "answer": 1.9271601479071325
    },
    {
        "question": "42,821 ÷ 744=？",
        "answer": 1.7600838696220416
    },
    {
        "question": "383,683 ÷ 251,932=？",
        "answer": 0.18268922276812447
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,263=？",
        "answer": 3.831805808674391
    },
    {
        "question": "4,284 ÷ 420=？",
        "answer": 1.0086001717619175
    },
    {
        "question": "3,262 × 4,579=？",
        "answer": 7.174254600231954
    },
    {
        "question": "818,573 ÷ 442,234=？",
        "answer": 0.26740528655917634
    },
    {
        "question": "1,819 × 126,880=？",
        "answer": 8.363225869037013
    },
    {
        "question": "728,240,339 ÷ 170,634,814=？",
        "answer": 0.6302070884955158
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 167,911,768=？",
        "answer": 8.924051138820499
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 64,426=？",
        "answer": 6.377262892323874
    },
    {
        "question": "182,070,725 ÷ 10,159=？",
        "answer": 4.253389161236505
    },
    {
        "question": "64,837 ÷ 11,180=？",
        "answer": 0.7633811083387907
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 547=？",
        "answer": 3.6922298357727557
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 5,346,350=？",
        "answer": 8.02908738220068
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 216,246=？",
        "answer": 5.812069337589489
    },
    {
        "question": "2,799 × 343,519=？",
        "answer": 8.98295366130847
    },
    {
        "question": "48,852,628 ÷ 262,305=？",
        "answer": 2.2700813622189466
    },
    {
        "question": "214,678,771 ÷ 408,888=？",
        "answer": 2.720184735244233
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,717=？",
        "answer": 3.735119634081872
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 3,649=？",
        "answer": 4.708301899042886
    },
    {
        "question": "549,058,572 ÷ 107,775,069=？",
        "answer": 0.7071003666450973
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 13,651,778=？",
        "answer": 8.089431726772347
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 801=？",
        "answer": 3.7487305560984945
    },
    {
        "question": "72,714,475 ÷ 46,662,236=？",
        "answer": 0.19265532700975127
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,079,763=？",
        "answer": 6.0333284415172
    },
    {
        "question": "300,106,641 ÷ 18,772,849=？",
        "answer": 1.2037454190431003
    },
    {
        "question": "348,127,504 ÷ 52,788,256=？",
        "answer": 0.8192010221397618
    },
    {
        "question": "188,483 ÷ 367=？",
        "answer": 2.7106061213818546
    },
    {
        "question": "68,525,094 ÷ 17,575=？",
        "answer": 3.5909543062679896
    },
    {
        "question": "757 × 84,166=？",
        "answer": 7.804232567265174
    },
    {
        "question": "5,211,141 ÷ 598=？",
        "answer": 3.9402316402229682
    },
    {
        "question": "15,724 × 2,937=？",
        "answer": 7.664466981670852
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 588,214=？",
        "answer": 7.501929116699884
    },
    {
        "question": "1,346 × 398,560=？",
        "answer": 8.729538770080389
    },
    {
        "question": "102,184 ÷ 56,046=？",
        "answer": 0.2608382767043572
    },
    {
        "question": "139,451 ÷ 16,682=？",
        "answer": 0.9221735160703135
    },
    {
        "question": "1,192 × 549,549=？",
        "answer": 8.816282677333628
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 41,403=？",
        "answer": 5.316001814931364
    },
    {
        "question": "106,810,145 ÷ 42,515,787=？",
        "answer": 0.40006228202994104
    },
    {
        "question": "590 × 244,160=？",
        "answer": 8.15852652791693
    },
    {
        "question": "113,215 ÷ 13,156=？",
        "answer": 0.9347801060845485
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 595=？",
        "answer": 4.387300822448285
    },
    {
        "question": "21,408,349 ÷ 2,456=？",
        "answer": 3.9403548135671573
    },
    {
        "question": "4,021,987 ÷ 584,899=？",
        "answer": 0.8373597836699063
    },
    {
        "question": "641,950,775 ÷ 88,512=？",
        "answer": 3.8604995734063525
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 11,470,630=？",
        "answer": 7.360617266922691
    },
    {
        "question": "1,121 × 4,872=？",
        "answer": 6.7373128922197925
    },
    {
        "question": "6,967 ÷ 1,343=？",
        "answer": 0.7149697978658539
    },
    {
        "question": "6,831 ÷ 738=？",
        "answer": 0.9664279235117637
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 13,581,669=？",
        "answer": 8.411706742985103
    },
    {
        "question": "1,200,954 ÷ 478,536=？",
        "answer": 0.3996117579141515
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 10,860,597=？",
        "answer": 7.336883694460043
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 192,474=？",
        "answer": 6.8406745726941365
    },
    {
        "question": "485 × 559,854=？",
        "answer": 8.43381652407034
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 1,500,574=？",
        "answer": 7.961587252298608
    },
    {
        "question": "5,586,524 ÷ 982=？",
        "answer": 3.7550301810709583
    },
    {
        "question": "556,636,058 ÷ 197,053,106=？",
        "answer": 0.4509880511031584
    },
    {
        "question": "999,146 ÷ 35,597=？",
        "answer": 1.4482155554721292
    },
    {
        "question": "2,071,809 ÷ 374=？",
        "answer": 3.7434781131248793
    },
    {
        "question": "24,676,850 ÷ 8,090,833=？",
        "answer": 0.484296484059416
    },
    {
        "question": "1,510,306 ÷ 207,978=？",
        "answer": 0.8610475501821525
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 188,471,811=？",
        "answer": 8.275246403652563
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 54,838,450=？",
        "answer": 7.7390851710270265
    },
    {
        "question": "33,297,639 ÷ 244,372=？",
        "answer": 2.134361997329804
    },
    {
        "question": "1,674 ÷ 1,133=？",
        "answer": 0.16952554379384394
    },
    {
        "question": "469,644 ÷ 2,149=？",
        "answer": 2.3395323628291114
    },
    {
        "question": "10,353,169 ÷ 109,264=？",
        "answer": 1.9765962079025783
    },
    {
        "question": "4,133 × 126,690=？",
        "answer": 8.719007741426278
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 376=？",
        "answer": 3.9731278535996988
    },
    {
        "question": "21,159,614 ÷ 113,893=？",
        "answer": 2.269010708264679
    },
    {
        "question": "1,683,930 ÷ 217,208=？",
        "answer": 0.8894482174316929
    },
    {
        "question": "130,418,057 ÷ 968=？",
        "answer": 5.129462368386202
    },
    {
        "question": "362 ÷ 250=？",
        "answer": 0.1607685618611281
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 158,542=？",
        "answer": 6.200144332496747
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 381,759=？",
        "answer": 7.194573141097214
    },
    {
        "question": "163 × 217=？",
        "answer": 4.548647338252487
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 290,400=？",
        "answer": 5.7640266076920375
    },
    {
        "question": "10,197,898 ÷ 11,186=？",
        "answer": 2.959835848820958
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 79,020=？",
        "answer": 5.976918271393052
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 1,787=？",
        "answer": 5.000312579511845
    },
    {
        "question": "2,996 × 1,402=？",
        "answer": 6.6232898226580685
    },
    {
        "question": "410 × 29,726=？",
        "answer": 7.085920330176212
    },
    {
        "question": "57,852 ÷ 2,084=？",
        "answer": 1.443420662903145
    },
    {
        "question": "252,384 ÷ 121,284=？",
        "answer": 0.3182583073975237
    },
    {
        "question": "531,053,793 ÷ 92,423,704=？",
        "answer": 0.7593551456454055
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 731,871=？",
        "answer": 6.818677048250059
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 45,107=？",
        "answer": 4.654243943773144
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 18,413=？",
        "answer": 6.0359765648013255
    },
    {
        "question": "134,299 × 905=？",
        "answer": 8.084721358098053
    },
    {
        "question": "893,424 × 408=？",
        "answer": 8.56171777781129
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 170,078=？",
        "answer": 6.677806171547836
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 6,879=？",
        "answer": 4.53649531378562
    },
    {
        "question": "14,168 × 4,371=？",
        "answer": 7.791889354671671
    },
    {
        "question": "606 × 1,182=？",
        "answer": 5.855090100711522
    },
    {
        "question": "632,299,380 ÷ 102,579=？",
        "answer": 3.789864294972642
    },
    {
        "question": "1,466,689 × 406=？",
        "answer": 8.774864068413889
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 123,847=？",
        "answer": 6.8410735179504565
    },
    {
        "question": "145 × 5,961,051=？",
        "answer": 8.936690839703411
    },
    {
        "question": "136,904 × 2,210=？",
        "answer": 8.480808411026912
    },
    {
        "question": "41,540,076 ÷ 346=？",
        "answer": 5.079391187974201
    },
    {
        "question": "252,179 ÷ 3,303=？",
        "answer": 1.8828003445335655
    },
    {
        "question": "16,466,450 ÷ 9,620=？",
        "answer": 3.233424907727499
    },
    {
        "question": "34,015,689 ÷ 177,908=？",
        "answer": 2.281483794706669
    },
    {
        "question": "29,742 ÷ 6,932=？",
        "answer": 0.6325116152469151
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 25,879,699=？",
        "answer": 8.015019212188642
    },
    {
        "question": "20,085 ÷ 874=？",
        "answer": 1.3613604034332871
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 680=？",
        "answer": 3.4345689040341987
    },
    {
        "question": "5,576,715 ÷ 1,733,861=？",
        "answer": 0.5073641722270742
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 68,232,191=？",
        "answer": 8.875382002267418
    },
    {
        "question": "486,768,479 ÷ 674,916=？",
        "answer": 2.8580727235229553
    },
    {
        "question": "94,441 × 8,124=？",
        "answer": 8.88493049174368
    },
    {
        "question": "28,810 × 3,995=？",
        "answer": 8.061060041930423
    },
    {
        "question": "74,363,660 ÷ 9,590=？",
        "answer": 3.889542149382223
    },
    {
        "question": "4,954 × 2,646=？",
        "answer": 7.1175458421013005
    },
    {
        "question": "46,760 ÷ 810=？",
        "answer": 1.7613894836111528
    },
    {
        "question": "1,879,734 ÷ 16,490=？",
        "answer": 2.0568757412225933
    },
    {
        "question": "88 × 188,503=？",
        "answer": 7.2198009384854975
    },
    {
        "question": "5,032,471 ÷ 2,894=？",
        "answer": 3.240282754129633
    },
    {
        "question": "1,002,031 ÷ 102,696=？",
        "answer": 0.9893276293842722
    },
    {
        "question": "59,257,957 ÷ 20,247=？",
        "answer": 3.466385991638344
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 7,523,528=？",
        "answer": 8.800700827668372
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 303,666=？",
        "answer": 6.8973695167774824
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 207=？",
        "answer": 4.229784197840634
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 152,523=？",
        "answer": 6.882305343231334
    },
    {
        "question": "463 × 34,064=？",
        "answer": 7.1978766351122
    },
    {
        "question": "1,050 × 184,348=？",
        "answer": 8.28682772935666
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 7,018,722=？",
        "answer": 7.846258041064874
    },
    {
        "question": "4,794 × 119,975=？",
        "answer": 8.759788788302094
    },
    {
        "question": "381 × 392,362=？",
        "answer": 8.174611915287077
    },
    {
        "question": "88,794,028 ÷ 62,165=？",
        "answer": 3.1548378195291127
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 66,460=？",
        "answer": 5.600711587326336
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 1,220=？",
        "answer": 4.4480876666923415
    },
    {
        "question": "78,538,622 ÷ 718=？",
        "answer": 5.038958832841753
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 525,122=？",
        "answer": 6.720260213446943
    },
    {
        "question": "140,779,778 ÷ 1,719=？",
        "answer": 4.913264399328273
    },
    {
        "question": "109,217,156 ÷ 4,475=？",
        "answer": 4.387497823725146
    },
    {
        "question": "5,886 × 15,417=？",
        "answer": 7.957820130168428
    },
    {
        "question": "127,995,095 ÷ 7,639=？",
        "answer": 4.224156817001048
    },
    {
        "question": "297,518,344 ÷ 7,235,089=？",
        "answer": 1.6140698702411507
    },
    {
        "question": "3,320 × 589=？",
        "answer": 6.291253378491138
    },
    {
        "question": "2,532 ÷ 715=？",
        "answer": 0.5491576595442369
    },
    {
        "question": "9,880 × 1,487=？",
        "answer": 7.167067913109582
    },
    {
        "question": "720,629,696 ÷ 360,682,193=？",
        "answer": 0.3005874531535767
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 16,415,778=？",
        "answer": 7.993412720641213
    },
    {
        "question": "2,574 × 84,949=？",
        "answer": 8.339766813389229
    },
    {
        "question": "272 × 70,377=？",
        "answer": 7.28199965401256
    },
    {
        "question": "120,069 × 4,740=？",
        "answer": 8.755209235282006
    },
    {
        "question": "28,612 ÷ 5,363=？",
        "answer": 0.7271404194093247
    },
    {
        "question": "1,629,428 ÷ 116,733=？",
        "answer": 1.1448415280376698
    },
    {
        "question": "74 × 25,677=？",
        "answer": 6.278776000827378
    },
    {
        "question": "448,441,586 ÷ 244,956,013=？",
        "answer": 0.26261777520138
    },
    {
        "question": "115,699 × 5,998=？",
        "answer": 8.841336066733437
    },
    {
        "question": "2,019,212 ÷ 13,030=？",
        "answer": 2.1902375028331798
    },
    {
        "question": "335,441,472 ÷ 1,114=？",
        "answer": 5.478731564353398
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 878=？",
        "answer": 4.265713810640022
    },
    {
        "question": "2,053,721 ÷ 2,409=？",
        "answer": 2.9307046439413558
    },
    {
        "question": "26,057 × 3,396=？",
        "answer": 7.94689209454308
    },
    {
        "question": "243 × 1,730,580=？",
        "answer": 8.623797953943564
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,069,806=？",
        "answer": 7.143248381610445
    },
    {
        "question": "265,933,536 ÷ 1,119=？",
        "answer": 5.375943021699667
    },
    {
        "question": "890 × 4,968=？",
        "answer": 6.645571593813437
    },
    {
        "question": "2,734,956 ÷ 2,909=？",
        "answer": 2.973206622544542
    },
    {
        "question": "54,416 × 413=？",
        "answer": 7.351676666245048
    },
    {
        "question": "303,550,386 ÷ 671,799=？",
        "answer": 2.654991436424593
    },
    {
        "question": "62,357 ÷ 3,933=？",
        "answer": 1.2001612666691786
    },
    {
        "question": "1,036,882 ÷ 8,353=？",
        "answer": 2.0938868538985504
    },
    {
        "question": "46,616,068 ÷ 429,790=？",
        "answer": 2.035279332132152
    },
    {
        "question": "1,485 × 469=？",
        "answer": 5.842899296368315
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,920,121=？",
        "answer": 6.465400847524978
    },
    {
        "question": "49,606 × 763=？",
        "answer": 7.578058746890587
    },
    {
        "question": "182,660 ÷ 558=？",
        "answer": 2.5150092543743114
    },
    {
        "question": "201,772,482 ÷ 10,590=？",
        "answer": 4.2799659761717175
    },
    {
        "question": "189 × 639=？",
        "answer": 5.0819626623316445
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 18,310=？",
        "answer": 5.376631696608533
    },
    {
        "question": "232 × 669,731=？",
        "answer": 8.191388386585551
    },
    {
        "question": "75,629,156 ÷ 5,623=？",
        "answer": 4.128721170310109
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 26,333=？",
        "answer": 4.4205003391374795
    },
    {
        "question": "50,311 × 16,593=？",
        "answer": 8.921587862797736
    },
    {
        "question": "605 × 308,271=？",
        "answer": 8.270688045884459
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,609=？",
        "answer": 3.2065560440990297
    },
    {
        "question": "42,355,635 ÷ 320,297=？",
        "answer": 2.1213583261657036
    },
    {
        "question": "274 × 2,658,598=？",
        "answer": 8.862403236526363
    },
    {
        "question": "1,264 × 215,962=？",
        "answer": 8.436124414716963
    },
    {
        "question": "870,164 ÷ 92,792=？",
        "answer": 0.9720905764836344
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 602,690=？",
        "answer": 7.324162029943211
    },
    {
        "question": "1,452 × 1,573=？",
        "answer": 6.358695338987362
    },
    {
        "question": "36,838,319 ÷ 1,612,420=？",
        "answer": 1.3588216279440246
    },
    {
        "question": "824,066,379 ÷ 58,927=？",
        "answer": 4.145647864234388
    },
    {
        "question": "235 × 1,218=？",
        "answer": 5.456715150568593
    },
    {
        "question": "41,620,381 ÷ 714,752=？",
        "answer": 1.7651506722358992
    },
    {
        "question": "175,362 × 1,157=？",
        "answer": 8.307268848903895
    },
    {
        "question": "1,691,037 ÷ 314,474=？",
        "answer": 0.7305683653145861
    },
    {
        "question": "11,801,319 ÷ 1,055,534=？",
        "answer": 1.0484583228746136
    },
    {
        "question": "174,627,396 ÷ 10,443,818=？",
        "answer": 1.223253083011706
    },
    {
        "question": "353 × 43,306=？",
        "answer": 7.184322776946037
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 24,030,763=？",
        "answer": 7.380767560293248
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 1,372,867=？",
        "answer": 7.845198641984449
    },
    {
        "question": "681,335 ÷ 5,748=？",
        "answer": 2.0738439396437176
    },
    {
        "question": "102,404 ÷ 307=？",
        "answer": 2.523178545459493
    },
    {
        "question": "2,678 × 5,450=？",
        "answer": 7.164207074952633
    },
    {
        "question": "17,112,746 ÷ 21,794=？",
        "answer": 2.8949827577175493
    },
    {
        "question": "16,112 × 31,175=？",
        "answer": 8.700955915360122
    },
    {
        "question": "1,541 × 267=？",
        "answer": 5.614313900082995
    },
    {
        "question": "285,904,367 ÷ 319=？",
        "answer": 5.952430105912273
    },
    {
        "question": "23,861,687 ÷ 2,821=？",
        "answer": 3.9272980584971187
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 261=？",
        "answer": 3.416640507338281
    },
    {
        "question": "329,587,906 ÷ 3,509=？",
        "answer": 4.972787898966745
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 9,282,470=？",
        "answer": 8.639761412240539
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 7,556=？",
        "answer": 5.157045550202625
    },
    {
        "question": "285,158,855 ÷ 2,863,332=？",
        "answer": 1.9982151553403626
    },
    {
        "question": "58,480 ÷ 501=？",
        "answer": 2.067169638082558
    },
    {
        "question": "370 × 14,250=？",
        "answer": 6.722016588411524
    },
    {
        "question": "76,077 ÷ 70,272=？",
        "answer": 0.034471064317015694
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 30,462=？",
        "answer": 4.483758413788249
    },
    {
        "question": "1,062,992 ÷ 18,899=？",
        "answer": 1.750091171045799
    },
    {
        "question": "183,295 × 272=？",
        "answer": 7.6977195222859605
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 710=？",
        "answer": 3.9304395947667
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 4,728,339=？",
        "answer": 7.996927900625632
    },
    {
        "question": "394 ÷ 271=？",
        "answer": 0.1625269309511684
    },
    {
        "question": "1,045 ÷ 822=？",
        "answer": 0.10424447290702242
    },
    {
        "question": "101 × 206=？",
        "answer": 4.318188594151796
    },
    {
        "question": "169,791 × 2,048=？",
        "answer": 8.541244618459507
    },
    {
        "question": "957,121,306 ÷ 44,725,140=？",
        "answer": 1.3304152752666718
    },
    {
        "question": "28,549,150 ÷ 170,440=？",
        "answer": 2.2240216569026647
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 282,567=？",
        "answer": 7.206996296430801
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 117,338=？",
        "answer": 5.546559936210627
    },
    {
        "question": "2,068,766 ÷ 761,444=？",
        "answer": 0.4340734011142862
    },
    {
        "question": "197,120,941 ÷ 34,516,580=？",
        "answer": 0.7567050056352184
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 31,639,628=？",
        "answer": 8.102291360006413
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 11,613=？",
        "answer": 5.320216931141924
    },
    {
        "question": "569,557 ÷ 58,845=？",
        "answer": 0.9858276266324045
    },
    {
        "question": "89,927,027 ÷ 713=？",
        "answer": 5.100800705963047
    },
    {
        "question": "50,289 ÷ 1,335=？",
        "answer": 1.5759917340324854
    },
    {
        "question": "9,417,817 ÷ 7,713=？",
        "answer": 3.086726915939515
    },
    {
        "question": "388,386,266 ÷ 50,145,566=？",
        "answer": 0.8890313264964449
    },
    {
        "question": "13,601 × 2,519=？",
        "answer": 7.534799008112152
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 9,355=？",
        "answer": 4.971043791836029
    },
    {
        "question": "1,713,457 ÷ 29,774=？",
        "answer": 1.760036026047644
    },
    {
        "question": "57,807,758 ÷ 10,132,441=？",
        "answer": 0.7562720425694724
    },
    {
        "question": "210,091,983 ÷ 9,632=？",
        "answer": 4.338693006358499
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 484=？",
        "answer": 3.161966616364075
    },
    {
        "question": "61,263,093 ÷ 6,800=？",
        "answer": 3.9546900066158184
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 823,028=？",
        "answer": 5.915414610471858
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 10,632=？",
        "answer": 5.172743003612913
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,872=？",
        "answer": 4.36608659902
    },
    {
        "question": "156,144 ÷ 49,911=？",
        "answer": 0.4953290293260572
    },
    {
        "question": "357 × 126,732=？",
        "answer": 7.655554504781855
    },
    {
        "question": "6,122,459 ÷ 1,893=？",
        "answer": 3.5097752715220722
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 22,197=？",
        "answer": 6.249384269033289
    },
    {
        "question": "1,644,886 ÷ 1,634=？",
        "answer": 3.002883752043064
    },
    {
        "question": "23,188,321 ÷ 174,531=？",
        "answer": 2.1233967267108484
    },
    {
        "question": "33,141 ÷ 25,541=？",
        "answer": 0.1131277116511851
    },
    {
        "question": "135 × 2,508=？",
        "answer": 5.529661300653685
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 3,263,193=？",
        "answer": 7.513642760688349
    },
    {
        "question": "35,867 ÷ 2,027=？",
        "answer": 1.2478413040930134
    },
    {
        "question": "36,324,730 ÷ 239,526=？",
        "answer": 2.1808497329087073
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 262,248=？",
        "answer": 5.895833439507943
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 467,648=？",
        "answer": 5.970949076993086
    },
    {
        "question": "10,165,515 ÷ 684,503=？",
        "answer": 1.1717540296563067
    },
    {
        "question": "7,644,846 ÷ 6,221=？",
        "answer": 3.0895085399395024
    },
    {
        "question": "7,688,363 ÷ 65,395=？",
        "answer": 2.070289335903334
    },
    {
        "question": "45,803 ÷ 724=？",
        "answer": 1.8011553581118909
    },
    {
        "question": "529,613,120 ÷ 2,667=？",
        "answer": 5.297935719565455
    },
    {
        "question": "233,144 ÷ 6,002=？",
        "answer": 1.589328252204053
    },
    {
        "question": "375,496,639 ÷ 590=？",
        "answer": 5.8037540424269745
    },
    {
        "question": "4,882,868 ÷ 11,677=？",
        "answer": 2.621343703824784
    },
    {
        "question": "306,463,537 ÷ 294,235=？",
        "answer": 3.0176844777203837
    },
    {
        "question": "64,268 ÷ 1,742=？",
        "answer": 1.5669466343409997
    },
    {
        "question": "784,239,516 ÷ 252,771,417=？",
        "answer": 0.4917207585615399
    },
    {
        "question": "412 × 383=？",
        "answer": 5.198095990001757
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 14,831,559=？",
        "answer": 8.375306786382327
    },
    {
        "question": "131 × 20,247=？",
        "answer": 6.423631978516815
    },
    {
        "question": "28,265,121 ÷ 186,932=？",
        "answer": 2.179567196419255
    },
    {
        "question": "432,507 ÷ 1,357=？",
        "answer": 2.503413293127852
    },
    {
        "question": "611 × 796,294=？",
        "answer": 8.687114653613278
    },
    {
        "question": "2,448,326 ÷ 5,429=？",
        "answer": 2.654149402935016
    },
    {
        "question": "21,583 × 5,809=？",
        "answer": 8.098213187207376
    },
    {
        "question": "576,068 ÷ 3,099=？",
        "answer": 2.2692521750340973
    },
    {
        "question": "84,823 × 2,381=？",
        "answer": 8.305273023825734
    },
    {
        "question": "43,552,029 ÷ 4,896,890=？",
        "answer": 0.9490880442391382
    },
    {
        "question": "282 × 75,802=？",
        "answer": 7.32992977275755
    },
    {
        "question": "573,644,306 ÷ 872=？",
        "answer": 5.818126202197564
    },
    {
        "question": "398,674 ÷ 1,311=？",
        "answer": 2.483015221863655
    },
    {
        "question": "290 × 357,316=？",
        "answer": 8.015450461501711
    },
    {
        "question": "373,669 ÷ 174,817=？",
        "answer": 0.32990340666380374
    },
    {
        "question": "1,324 × 27,477=？",
        "answer": 7.560857298841668
    },
    {
        "question": "11,649 × 3,860=？",
        "answer": 7.652875949937465
    },
    {
        "question": "56,302 ÷ 1,509=？",
        "answer": 1.5718345826696516
    },
    {
        "question": "5,393 ÷ 615=？",
        "answer": 0.9429553045127457
    },
    {
        "question": "32,788,215 ÷ 630,947=？",
        "answer": 1.7157248944658214
    },
    {
        "question": "783 × 14,252=？",
        "answer": 7.047637575736921
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 69,837=？",
        "answer": 5.145115570699561
    },
    {
        "question": "341,935 ÷ 681=？",
        "answer": 2.7007964449496145
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 147,607=？",
        "answer": 5.169106953620407
    },
    {
        "question": "10,331 ÷ 887=？",
        "answer": 1.0662187417132793
    },
    {
        "question": "115,566,554 ÷ 6,878=？",
        "answer": 4.225369992054125
    },
    {
        "question": "286,498 ÷ 275=？",
        "answer": 3.017788900738432
    },
    {
        "question": "1,440,758 ÷ 5,849=？",
        "answer": 2.391509418374513
    },
    {
        "question": "5,251 ÷ 462=？",
        "answer": 1.0556000427309316
    },
    {
        "question": "326,280,011 ÷ 2,966,274=？",
        "answer": 2.0413792031783924
    },
    {
        "question": "123,443,679 ÷ 307=？",
        "answer": 5.604330481077496
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 4,323,139=？",
        "answer": 7.590041708878251
    },
    {
        "question": "11,806,187 ÷ 6,984,210=？",
        "answer": 0.22799236861225433
    },
    {
        "question": "212,368,304 ÷ 1,045,994=？",
        "answer": 2.307560505380804
    },
    {
        "question": "16,131 ÷ 1,139=？",
        "answer": 1.1511375671176813
    },
    {
        "question": "114,947 × 3,102=？",
        "answer": 8.552139434585733
    },
    {
        "question": "1,052 ÷ 315=？",
        "answer": 0.5237051860281198
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 142,818,174=？",
        "answer": 8.455813471771492
    },
    {
        "question": "20,469,118 ÷ 730=？",
        "answer": 4.447776269499277
    },
    {
        "question": "57,666,897 ÷ 854=？",
        "answer": 4.829468712384219
    },
    {
        "question": "560,361,219 ÷ 141,168=？",
        "answer": 3.5987318094900105
    },
    {
        "question": "35,314,989 ÷ 17,051=？",
        "answer": 3.316209220913397
    },
    {
        "question": "12,002 ÷ 204=？",
        "answer": 1.769623455004179
    },
    {
        "question": "26,538 × 2,377=？",
        "answer": 7.7998973714814275
    },
    {
        "question": "31,908,504 ÷ 101,603=？",
        "answer": 2.496999911770663
    },
    {
        "question": "425,564 ÷ 30,370=？",
        "answer": 1.1465200903794792
    },
    {
        "question": "29,062,612 ÷ 451,177=？",
        "answer": 1.8089876917262022
    },
    {
        "question": "44,869,601 ÷ 1,179=？",
        "answer": 4.580438402519805
    },
    {
        "question": "17,785 ÷ 266=？",
        "answer": 1.8251722328907323
    },
    {
        "question": "193,304 × 258=？",
        "answer": 7.697860546851349
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 51,776=？",
        "answer": 6.075856331613752
    },
    {
        "question": "115,105,775 ÷ 36,689=？",
        "answer": 3.496561238538888
    },
    {
        "question": "433,008 ÷ 30,663=？",
        "answer": 1.149881277188565
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,642,605=？",
        "answer": 6.422032252371004
    },
    {
        "question": "232,549,143 ÷ 12,704,013=？",
        "answer": 1.2625738138737468
    },
    {
        "question": "35,702,439 ÷ 326=？",
        "answer": 5.0394802857378
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 488,782=？",
        "answer": 7.771900574415487
    },
    {
        "question": "218,457 ÷ 2,031=？",
        "answer": 2.031656041926734
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 36,157=？",
        "answer": 5.938403630951456
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 20,083=？",
        "answer": 5.779949842979918
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 791,761=？",
        "answer": 7.360992103673396
    },
    {
        "question": "3,366,823 ÷ 3,085,779=？",
        "answer": 0.03785546617697942
    },
    {
        "question": "144 × 22,910=？",
        "answer": 6.518387581284647
    },
    {
        "question": "95,702 × 7,499=？",
        "answer": 8.855924367446768
    },
    {
        "question": "5,338,174 ÷ 1,217,867=？",
        "answer": 0.6417928629445129
    },
    {
        "question": "157 × 3,357,850=？",
        "answer": 8.721960944084014
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 78,384=？",
        "answer": 5.1952574177762365
    },
    {
        "question": "13,697,720 ÷ 12,435,786=？",
        "answer": 0.04197504447398733
    },
    {
        "question": "826 × 418,132=？",
        "answer": 8.538293453071267
    },
    {
        "question": "249,798,608 ÷ 1,887,322=？",
        "answer": 2.1217440115566224
    },
    {
        "question": "105,701 ÷ 1,140=？",
        "answer": 1.967174244697799
    },
    {
        "question": "9,657 ÷ 3,400=？",
        "answer": 0.45336331436302085
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 63,695,675=？",
        "answer": 8.582261194690693
    },
    {
        "question": "48,364,958 ÷ 36,200,130=？",
        "answer": 0.1258206848179298
    },
    {
        "question": "313 × 70,923=？",
        "answer": 7.346331435257756
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 756=？",
        "answer": 4.0246498311794445
    },
    {
        "question": "162,995,047 ÷ 7,798=？",
        "answer": 4.32019117666088
    },
    {
        "question": "1,459 × 1,844=？",
        "answer": 6.429816208611062
    },
    {
        "question": "35,035 × 268=？",
        "answer": 6.972636915858383
    },
    {
        "question": "16,690 × 971=？",
        "answer": 7.209675566587252
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 81,199=？",
        "answer": 5.687701931137674
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,992,813=？",
        "answer": 6.9984365519685685
    },
    {
        "question": "1,672,496 ÷ 212,900=？",
        "answer": 0.8951894263288894
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 349,025=？",
        "answer": 6.1449165270928505
    },
    {
        "question": "204,990 ÷ 65,347=？",
        "answer": 0.4965070209910067
    },
    {
        "question": "319,088,153 ÷ 23,810=？",
        "answer": 4.127151284745263
    },
    {
        "question": "654,784 ÷ 19,765=？",
        "answer": 1.5202012399707991
    },
    {
        "question": "386,298 ÷ 1,426=？",
        "answer": 2.432802934140202
    },
    {
        "question": "10,780 × 509=？",
        "answer": 6.739336543187479
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 8,498,615=？",
        "answer": 7.531408146822591
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 352,798=？",
        "answer": 5.848556110129926
    },
    {
        "question": "86,011 × 2,111=？",
        "answer": 8.259042230293153
    },
    {
        "question": "7,690,638 ÷ 38,574=？",
        "answer": 2.299667693355404
    },
    {
        "question": "530,507,085 ÷ 46,274,746=？",
        "answer": 1.0593471447340501
    },
    {
        "question": "297,845,469 ÷ 4,806=？",
        "answer": 4.792207231274805
    },
    {
        "question": "1,445 × 119,722=？",
        "answer": 8.238041810370214
    },
    {
        "question": "830,248 ÷ 390=？",
        "answer": 3.32814323106505
    },
    {
        "question": "7,563,128 ÷ 66,537=？",
        "answer": 2.0556382349143996
    },
    {
        "question": "2,381 ÷ 1,426=？",
        "answer": 0.22263986988903312
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 4,461,508=？",
        "answer": 7.126602930782626
    },
    {
        "question": "89,238 × 256=？",
        "answer": 7.358789793634798
    },
    {
        "question": "11,701,473 ÷ 499,118=？",
        "answer": 1.3700373024882582
    },
    {
        "question": "835 × 33,686=？",
        "answer": 7.449135919796186
    },
    {
        "question": "1,106 × 6,935=？",
        "answer": 6.8848015923779835
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 6,751,951=？",
        "answer": 7.870821967041992
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 4,878,278=？",
        "answer": 7.642509055401816
    },
    {
        "question": "136,862 × 534=？",
        "answer": 7.863824139193432
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,575=？",
        "answer": 3.41077723337721
    },
    {
        "question": "18,296,172 ÷ 84,814=？",
        "answer": 2.3338926884659434
    },
    {
        "question": "897 × 7,921=？",
        "answer": 6.851572456333917
    },
    {
        "question": "149,415,433 ÷ 2,159,918=？",
        "answer": 1.8399581939915914
    },
    {
        "question": "523,103,270 ÷ 3,072,477=？",
        "answer": 2.231098794356634
    },
    {
        "question": "499,419,027 ÷ 17,941=？",
        "answer": 4.444618437999639
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 2,562,682=？",
        "answer": 8.031944008867136
    },
    {
        "question": "25,859,745 ÷ 22,961=？",
        "answer": 3.051633439458149
    },
    {
        "question": "3,107,218 ÷ 422,190=？",
        "answer": 0.8668637817007323
    },
    {
        "question": "74,982 × 1,295=？",
        "answer": 7.987226788623631
    },
    {
        "question": "102,517,173 ÷ 3,117,297=？",
        "answer": 1.5170184400410252
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 2,751=？",
        "answer": 4.854463938360501
    },
    {
        "question": "3,082,535 ÷ 47,622=？",
        "answer": 1.8111003857124957
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 70,700=？",
        "answer": 4.849419413796899
    },
    {
        "question": "54,917,851 ÷ 232=？",
        "answer": 5.374225549553244
    },
    {
        "question": "99,607 ÷ 43,720=？",
        "answer": 0.35760970677805026
    },
    {
        "question": "590 × 66,024=？",
        "answer": 7.590553843743434
    },
    {
        "question": "134,652,460 ÷ 29,130=？",
        "answer": 3.664873807428561
    },
    {
        "question": "195,424 ÷ 16,465=？",
        "answer": 1.074416163267845
    },
    {
        "question": "1,382 × 15,019=？",
        "answer": 7.317149060330847
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 227,130,890=？",
        "answer": 8.356276202666475
    },
    {
        "question": "5,965,952 ÷ 245=？",
        "answer": 4.386513670491382
    },
    {
        "question": "6,831,533 ÷ 9,366=？",
        "answer": 2.8629640171073887
    },
    {
        "question": "31,846 × 30,160=？",
        "answer": 8.982486227965756
    },
    {
        "question": "97 × 227=？",
        "answer": 4.342797591459368
    },
    {
        "question": "4,908 ÷ 267=？",
        "answer": 1.2643932926903914
    },
    {
        "question": "4,013,198 ÷ 11,909=？",
        "answer": 2.5276152918814616
    },
    {
        "question": "7,990,852 ÷ 1,838,419=？",
        "answer": 0.6381485873085808
    },
    {
        "question": "140 × 1,633,035=？",
        "answer": 8.359123528525117
    },
    {
        "question": "560 × 1,004,250=？",
        "answer": 8.750029867409909
    },
    {
        "question": "22,945 × 23,786=？",
        "answer": 8.737009476577962
    },
    {
        "question": "194,212,065 ÷ 1,673=？",
        "answer": 5.064780265042992
    },
    {
        "question": "541,567 ÷ 14,093=？",
        "answer": 1.5846487411293741
    },
    {
        "question": "136,505,218 ÷ 1,716=？",
        "answer": 4.90063196936807
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 890=？",
        "answer": 2.949390006644913
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 21,784,834=？",
        "answer": 7.815275509688765
    },
    {
        "question": "4,199 × 17,197=？",
        "answer": 7.858598565901159
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 855,542=？",
        "answer": 7.108332593704872
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,858=？",
        "answer": 4.068779363009561
    },
    {
        "question": "280 × 1,664=？",
        "answer": 5.668311353296924
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 3,943=？",
        "answer": 5.164028501140218
    },
    {
        "question": "53,160,690 ÷ 357=？",
        "answer": 5.1729223931270445
    },
    {
        "question": "582 ÷ 339=？",
        "answer": 0.23472328644680632
    },
    {
        "question": "99,500,573 ÷ 123,913=？",
        "answer": 2.9047087101441056
    },
    {
        "question": "515 × 23,604=？",
        "answer": 7.084792835008153
    },
    {
        "question": "415,858 ÷ 6,316=？",
        "answer": 1.8185029392323049
    },
    {
        "question": "10,267 ÷ 1,952=？",
        "answer": 0.7209637486914017
    },
    {
        "question": "521,160,783 ÷ 771,921=？",
        "answer": 2.82939887189131
    },
    {
        "question": "55,397 × 2,115=？",
        "answer": 8.068796618050978
    },
    {
        "question": "586 × 10,983=？",
        "answer": 6.808618599619284
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 879,334=？",
        "answer": 7.488221910101246
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 29,418=？",
        "answer": 4.468613143629822
    },
    {
        "question": "723 ÷ 577=？",
        "answer": 0.09796248413879942
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,404=？",
        "answer": 3.8330195470765314
    },
    {
        "question": "349,324 × 2,199=？",
        "answer": 8.885453653846143
    },
    {
        "question": "102,061 ÷ 2,169=？",
        "answer": 1.6726002672471014
    },
    {
        "question": "3,403 × 87,374=？",
        "answer": 8.473244167354931
    },
    {
        "question": "4,534 ÷ 460=？",
        "answer": 0.9937236841089245
    },
    {
        "question": "689 × 683=？",
        "answer": 5.672639925589158
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 318=？",
        "answer": 3.543819805142658
    },
    {
        "question": "1,184,045 ÷ 8,472=？",
        "answer": 2.145382261098543
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,627=？",
        "answer": 3.8605775512444156
    },
    {
        "question": "692 × 981,929=？",
        "answer": 8.832186180998317
    },
    {
        "question": "95,003,275 ÷ 56,424,877=？",
        "answer": 0.22626795572478514
    },
    {
        "question": "114 × 20,171=？",
        "answer": 6.361632280720106
    },
    {
        "question": "815,580 ÷ 1,490=？",
        "answer": 2.738280298870218
    },
    {
        "question": "135 × 209,507=？",
        "answer": 7.451532306587706
    },
    {
        "question": "165,014,074 ÷ 6,445=？",
        "answer": 4.408298064947966
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 8,767,198=？",
        "answer": 8.650430990948886
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 2,137=？",
        "answer": 5.028774526500088
    },
    {
        "question": "64,218 × 1,101=？",
        "answer": 7.849444094781973
    },
    {
        "question": "1,035,898 ÷ 133,241=？",
        "answer": 0.8906791110838714
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 324=？",
        "answer": 3.789298611159441
    },
    {
        "question": "3,531 ÷ 3,518=？",
        "answer": 0.001601882441654695
    },
    {
        "question": "398,711 × 580=？",
        "answer": 8.364086211099927
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 98,476=？",
        "answer": 5.294360395323143
    },
    {
        "question": "2,259 × 1,677=？",
        "answer": 6.5784492935264485
    },
    {
        "question": "209,734,398 ÷ 66,315=？",
        "answer": 3.50005788986802
    },
    {
        "question": "154,175 × 593=？",
        "answer": 7.961068650462605
    },
    {
        "question": "210,864 ÷ 4,412=？",
        "answer": 1.6793669368727546
    },
    {
        "question": "216 × 16,069=？",
        "answer": 6.540442601903383
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 217,631=？",
        "answer": 6.960970048014253
    },
    {
        "question": "33,155,328 ÷ 2,351,674=？",
        "answer": 1.1491762110171524
    },
    {
        "question": "1,424 ÷ 288=？",
        "answer": 0.6941175015416068
    },
    {
        "question": "482,951 × 1,084=？",
        "answer": 8.718932351858376
    },
    {
        "question": "4,840 × 394=？",
        "answer": 6.280341583469987
    },
    {
        "question": "462 × 18,311=？",
        "answer": 6.927354038187852
    },
    {
        "question": "8,883,517 ÷ 754=？",
        "answer": 4.071213591902077
    },
    {
        "question": "44,348,244 ÷ 391,318=？",
        "answer": 2.054346603102522
    },
    {
        "question": "6,345 ÷ 4,227=？",
        "answer": 0.1763993786017047
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 295,437=？",
        "answer": 7.443592738243769
    },
    {
        "question": "97,753 ÷ 58,726=？",
        "answer": 0.2212996738141238
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,246,424=？",
        "answer": 7.020893381693244
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 633,359,468=？",
        "answer": 8.801650267139497
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 313=？",
        "answer": 3.9579423354454044
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 2,768=？",
        "answer": 5.065415376182621
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 4,874,334=？",
        "answer": 8.049643120691313
    },
    {
        "question": "86,862,374 ÷ 44,736,451=？",
        "answer": 0.2881701667239607
    },
    {
        "question": "10,330,893 ÷ 230=？",
        "answer": 4.652410027439115
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 478,342=？",
        "answer": 6.855829774084941
    },
    {
        "question": "3,836 × 841=？",
        "answer": 6.508674594296538
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 24,679,661=？",
        "answer": 8.43373187508829
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 1,426,363=？",
        "answer": 7.685708981713028
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 56,326=？",
        "answer": 6.16568225880835
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 216,292=？",
        "answer": 6.590312961573801
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,705=？",
        "answer": 3.869818207979328
    },
    {
        "question": "639 × 213,496=？",
        "answer": 8.134890600778453
    },
    {
        "question": "15,926,319 ÷ 1,752,041=？",
        "answer": 0.9585711452848746
    },
    {
        "question": "358 × 80,002=？",
        "answer": 7.4569838708621505
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 125,889=？",
        "answer": 6.8634157773005935
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 13,074=？",
        "answer": 5.2625365163081375
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 89,873,448=？",
        "answer": 8.430752658462694
    },
    {
        "question": "109,176 × 263=？",
        "answer": 7.458082927031319
    },
    {
        "question": "65,266,868 ÷ 1,403,666=？",
        "answer": 1.667428992014611
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,433=？",
        "answer": 3.3861421089308186
    },
    {
        "question": "2,331 × 229=？",
        "answer": 5.727377755860465
    },
    {
        "question": "459,634,264 ÷ 2,240=？",
        "answer": 5.312164377903724
    },
    {
        "question": "476,186,407 ÷ 671=？",
        "answer": 5.851054473904596
    },
    {
        "question": "60,865,445 ÷ 283,691=？",
        "answer": 2.3315252434119826
    },
    {
        "question": "224,978 ÷ 1,796=？",
        "answer": 2.097833719354565
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 5,141,921=？",
        "answer": 8.67491322724329
    },
    {
        "question": "1,512 × 72,047=？",
        "answer": 8.037167692892975
    },
    {
        "question": "822 × 1,129=？",
        "answer": 5.967565759465018
    },
    {
        "question": "778,768,225 ÷ 163,095=？",
        "answer": 3.6789675762064378
    },
    {
        "question": "5,128 × 15,227=？",
        "answer": 7.8925623642471106
    },
    {
        "question": "224,644,432 ÷ 19,789,723=？",
        "answer": 1.0550559433529203
    },
    {
        "question": "5,754 ÷ 397=？",
        "answer": 1.1611793507911923
    },
    {
        "question": "1,866,805 ÷ 17,800=？",
        "answer": 2.020678953108371
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 80,875,199=？",
        "answer": 8.90781536229494
    },
    {
        "question": "52,670,895 ÷ 2,942,912=？",
        "answer": 1.2527934222192962
    },
    {
        "question": "56,685 × 10,101=？",
        "answer": 8.757832522080447
    },
    {
        "question": "23,430 × 1,537=？",
        "answer": 7.556446156096708
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,449=？",
        "answer": 3.1610683854711747
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 160,763,927=？",
        "answer": 8.683309860933367
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 60,544=？",
        "answer": 5.259192365105342
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 446=？",
        "answer": 4.434664693722909
    },
    {
        "question": "72,186 × 1,163=？",
        "answer": 7.924032691906004
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,793,587=？",
        "answer": 6.579050048380755
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 711,019=？",
        "answer": 5.8518812061937675
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,314,856=？",
        "answer": 6.118878192498933
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 39,231,359=？",
        "answer": 8.672814598683361
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 2,181,561=？",
        "answer": 7.71897860278554
    },
    {
        "question": "570,198,732 ÷ 58,532=？",
        "answer": 3.9886328832715483
    },
    {
        "question": "253 × 1,507=？",
        "answer": 5.58123377349045
    },
    {
        "question": "31,554,265 ÷ 7,363,429=？",
        "answer": 0.6319779649165641
    },
    {
        "question": "15,464,092 ÷ 2,730=？",
        "answer": 3.7531617777209125
    },
    {
        "question": "2,013,061 ÷ 639,190=？",
        "answer": 0.4982269632195263
    },
    {
        "question": "86,620 × 208=？",
        "answer": 7.255681514356585
    },
    {
        "question": "11,711 × 79,014=？",
        "answer": 8.966298029027412
    },
    {
        "question": "31,189 × 1,262=？",
        "answer": 7.595060805284236
    },
    {
        "question": "405,762,597 ÷ 21,963=？",
        "answer": 4.26658034991388
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 613,555=？",
        "answer": 5.787853499623537
    },
    {
        "question": "215,094,558 ÷ 117,569,302=？",
        "answer": 0.2623354828265212
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,539,879=？",
        "answer": 7.141729105797302
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 178,947=？",
        "answer": 6.294117107111033
    },
    {
        "question": "11,341 × 20,232=？",
        "answer": 8.36069016677809
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 4,301,180=？",
        "answer": 7.837707600371837
    },
    {
        "question": "159 × 221=？",
        "answer": 4.545789398005562
    },
    {
        "question": "49,117 × 5,927=？",
        "answer": 8.46406676006199
    },
    {
        "question": "35,427 ÷ 22,903=？",
        "answer": 0.1894420042359315
    },
    {
        "question": "456,853,389 ÷ 95,143,474=？",
        "answer": 0.6813978460267085
    },
    {
        "question": "17,143,224 ÷ 21,822=？",
        "answer": 2.895197948397482
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 6,929=？",
        "answer": 4.442730552661372
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 649,677=？",
        "answer": 5.812697492054126
    },
    {
        "question": "13,664 × 32,989=？",
        "answer": 8.653947004262681
    },
    {
        "question": "2,643 ÷ 1,597=？",
        "answer": 0.2187922469932274
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 86,880=？",
        "answer": 4.938919812244772
    },
    {
        "question": "43,135 × 264=？",
        "answer": 7.0564337292437305
    },
    {
        "question": "124,546 ÷ 58,626=？",
        "answer": 0.32723952034546633
    },
    {
        "question": "139,980,110 ÷ 870=？",
        "answer": 5.206547077838777
    },
    {
        "question": "153,173,418 ÷ 135,970,525=？",
        "answer": 0.05173862914284278
    },
    {
        "question": "17,422 × 33,026=？",
        "answer": 8.759953985967167
    },
    {
        "question": "1,092 × 40,051=？",
        "answer": 7.640836002460888
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 168,571=？",
        "answer": 5.226782863151952
    },
    {
        "question": "9,444,403 ÷ 4,375,578=？",
        "answer": 0.3341390804106087
    },
    {
        "question": "12,289,333 ÷ 334=？",
        "answer": 4.565781845506925
    },
    {
        "question": "9,124,422 ÷ 5,124=？",
        "answer": 3.250596241901227
    },
    {
        "question": "7,686,215 ÷ 5,126,483=？",
        "answer": 0.1758930069084603
    },
    {
        "question": "2,241,762 × 333=？",
        "answer": 8.87303373669244
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 780=？",
        "answer": 4.323458366849468
    },
    {
        "question": "82,806 ÷ 462=？",
        "answer": 2.2534198307032005
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 266,395=？",
        "answer": 6.856889833408047
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 2,540,193=？",
        "answer": 8.120870058542419
    },
    {
        "question": "305 × 212,058=？",
        "answer": 7.810754500440172
    },
    {
        "question": "50,047,989 ÷ 108,607=？",
        "answer": 2.663528814041232
    },
    {
        "question": "98,562 ÷ 36,368=？",
        "answer": 0.43299008914391013
    },
    {
        "question": "158,701 ÷ 226=？",
        "answer": 2.8464712241740107
    },
    {
        "question": "496,257,031 ÷ 285,490,132=？",
        "answer": 0.24011557152413526
    },
    {
        "question": "1,072 × 12,106=？",
        "answer": 7.113195454933284
    },
    {
        "question": "594 ÷ 211=？",
        "answer": 0.44950398968350086
    },
    {
        "question": "152 × 1,893,850=？",
        "answer": 8.45918916622763
    },
    {
        "question": "547,409 ÷ 11,995=？",
        "answer": 1.6593116811031121
    },
    {
        "question": "27,594 × 2,169=？",
        "answer": 7.7770742119718745
    },
    {
        "question": "26,918,404 ÷ 88,336=？",
        "answer": 2.483911577073084
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 14,610,142=？",
        "answer": 7.465684432646651
    },
    {
        "question": "496,908,575 ÷ 44,479=？",
        "answer": 4.048121476648403
    },
    {
        "question": "452,744 ÷ 101,929=？",
        "answer": 0.6475549400488408
    },
    {
        "question": "114,303,397 ÷ 863,385=？",
        "answer": 2.1218546382703676
    },
    {
        "question": "5,693 × 2,144=？",
        "answer": 7.08656596483228
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 11,605=？",
        "answer": 5.527043142690893
    },
    {
        "question": "5,946,333 ÷ 1,760=？",
        "answer": 3.528736558617664
    },
    {
        "question": "4,162,859 ÷ 10,890=？",
        "answer": 2.5823638214122924
    },
    {
        "question": "87,558 × 1,014=？",
        "answer": 7.948333787851139
    },
    {
        "question": "1,522 × 1,412=？",
        "answer": 6.332249349150339
    },
    {
        "question": "492,643,828 ÷ 103,859=？",
        "answer": 3.6760889094777314
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 32,976,108=？",
        "answer": 8.421289383786592
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 929=？",
        "answer": 4.290235008727561
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 31,423=？",
        "answer": 5.196217649751929
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 29,943,450=？",
        "answer": 8.175271841413306
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 1,580,624=？",
        "answer": 7.954703427599647
    },
    {
        "question": "5,320 × 3,447=？",
        "answer": 7.2633529157029955
    },
    {
        "question": "4,981 ÷ 416=？",
        "answer": 1.0782232111056407
    },
    {
        "question": "253,411,230 ÷ 240=？",
        "answer": 6.023614615161643
    },
    {
        "question": "612 × 13,406=？",
        "answer": 6.914050637203268
    },
    {
        "question": "4,266,855 ÷ 2,765,860=？",
        "answer": 0.18827769096207697
    },
    {
        "question": "47,701,162 ÷ 1,076=？",
        "answer": 4.646716687249393
    },
    {
        "question": "4,366 ÷ 3,347=？",
        "answer": 0.11542801901534323
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 12,997,652=？",
        "answer": 8.41489490062132
    },
    {
        "question": "376,312,406 ÷ 27,985,017=？",
        "answer": 1.1286229610049583
    },
    {
        "question": "675,802,747 ÷ 3,861=？",
        "answer": 5.2431201511366945
    },
    {
        "question": "20,224 × 3,071=？",
        "answer": 7.79314687304536
    },
    {
        "question": "6,212,224 ÷ 683=？",
        "answer": 3.958826403421677
    },
    {
        "question": "4,649 × 73,278=？",
        "answer": 8.532333153665792
    },
    {
        "question": "3,132 ÷ 456=？",
        "answer": 0.8368569107214708
    },
    {
        "question": "12,985,299 ÷ 162,085=？",
        "answer": 1.903709128817923
    },
    {
        "question": "1,464 ÷ 392=？",
        "answer": 0.5722550097019158
    },
    {
        "question": "1,913,551 ÷ 10,676=？",
        "answer": 2.253431476424623
    },
    {
        "question": "1,011,504 × 307=？",
        "answer": 8.492105980008125
    },
    {
        "question": "57,330,826 ÷ 8,540=？",
        "answer": 3.8269303282748877
    },
    {
        "question": "7,474,482 ÷ 283=？",
        "answer": 4.421794664838499
    },
    {
        "question": "663,228,537 ÷ 151,617=？",
        "answer": 3.640915305372712
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 5,294=？",
        "answer": 4.422753941301348
    },
    {
        "question": "31,419,918 ÷ 18,550,267=？",
        "answer": 0.22885488234241047
    },
    {
        "question": "98,244,644 ÷ 2,302,863=？",
        "answer": 1.630040781226395
    },
    {
        "question": "42,064,465 ÷ 138,355=？",
        "answer": 2.4829205109871153
    },
    {
        "question": "412,944 × 950=？",
        "answer": 8.593614765565146
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 709=？",
        "answer": 3.151676230847048
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 550,613=？",
        "answer": 7.138786469564465
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 2,528=？",
        "answer": 5.150965096616548
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 50,393=？",
        "answer": 5.00340020924228
    },
    {
        "question": "1,817,191 ÷ 644,064=？",
        "answer": 0.4504715523026426
    },
    {
        "question": "37,025 × 9,910=？",
        "answer": 8.564568721678521
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 5,512=？",
        "answer": 4.644399195891513
    },
    {
        "question": "857,993 ÷ 9,008=？",
        "answer": 1.978855367131907
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 283,206,768=？",
        "answer": 8.753133623459721
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,574=？",
        "answer": 3.1970047280230456
    },
    {
        "question": "462,162 ÷ 1,120=？",
        "answer": 2.6155762112709215
    },
    {
        "question": "294 × 828,457=？",
        "answer": 8.386617302253384
    },
    {
        "question": "865,275,548 ÷ 257,748=？",
        "answer": 3.525959127017997
    },
    {
        "question": "762 × 50,513=？",
        "answer": 7.585358133650314
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 7,178=？",
        "answer": 5.424205178064216
    },
    {
        "question": "174,517 ÷ 73,446=？",
        "answer": 0.3758695904063124
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 230=？",
        "answer": 2.361727836017593
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 64,848,702=？",
        "answer": 8.11293128341054
    },
    {
        "question": "32,811 ÷ 5,588=？",
        "answer": 0.7687630693920506
    },
    {
        "question": "8,432,295 ÷ 1,796=？",
        "answer": 3.6716394593976083
    },
    {
        "question": "528,997,348 ÷ 594=？",
        "answer": 5.949667049829317
    },
    {
        "question": "507 × 236,299=？",
        "answer": 8.078469843067268
    },
    {
        "question": "136 × 25,632=？",
        "answer": 6.542321402774361
    },
    {
        "question": "5,294 ÷ 853=？",
        "answer": 0.7928349057978065
    },
    {
        "question": "1,298,796 ÷ 393,863=？",
        "answer": 0.5181957578869537
    },
    {
        "question": "690,372,221 ÷ 8,436,410=？",
        "answer": 1.9129256302397852
    },
    {
        "question": "23,965,697 ÷ 236=？",
        "answer": 5.0066780612298905
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 22,018,071=？",
        "answer": 7.342779267825911
    },
    {
        "question": "152,734,946 ÷ 329=？",
        "answer": 5.6667425177481485
    },
    {
        "question": "8,468,806 ÷ 6,946,249=？",
        "answer": 0.08607183706601704
    },
    {
        "question": "4,119,090 ÷ 1,266,746=？",
        "answer": 0.5121117395768562
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 7,614=？",
        "answer": 4.3587341271980105
    },
    {
        "question": "2,393,262 ÷ 242,836=？",
        "answer": 0.993677174625201
    },
    {
        "question": "501,779,171 ÷ 66,775,855=？",
        "answer": 0.8758931722136551
    },
    {
        "question": "104,397,583 ÷ 8,161,427=？",
        "answer": 1.106924343624429
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 7,427,715=？",
        "answer": 8.31801326293367
    },
    {
        "question": "188,947 ÷ 15,770=？",
        "answer": 1.0785083074820088
    },
    {
        "question": "1,372,749 ÷ 128,999=？",
        "answer": 1.0270047923507641
    },
    {
        "question": "117,236,693 ÷ 29,077=？",
        "answer": 3.60551396295117
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 4,200,083=？",
        "answer": 8.442801808341157
    },
    {
        "question": "17,400,802 ÷ 72,640=？",
        "answer": 2.379393429789555
    },
    {
        "question": "360,998 ÷ 16,421=？",
        "answer": 1.3421051947414915
    },
    {
        "question": "2,481 ÷ 926=？",
        "answer": 0.42801577759027476
    },
    {
        "question": "2,563,819 ÷ 6,426=？",
        "answer": 2.600946640475309
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,470=？",
        "answer": 4.070407321740119
    },
    {
        "question": "952,593,887 ÷ 1,199=？",
        "answer": 5.900088607124501
    },
    {
        "question": "156,947 × 493=？",
        "answer": 7.888599937969565
    },
    {
        "question": "711,786 ÷ 35,174=？",
        "answer": 1.3061276824352643
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 948=？",
        "answer": 4.122936373016304
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 2,253,071=？",
        "answer": 7.528866136719311
    },
    {
        "question": "210 × 12,513=？",
        "answer": 6.419580739299413
    },
    {
        "question": "438 × 8,094=？",
        "answer": 6.549637310559647
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 3,519=？",
        "answer": 4.69254730251343
    },
    {
        "question": "9,844 × 931=？",
        "answer": 6.962121286012107
    },
    {
        "question": "4,096,059 ÷ 112,159=？",
        "answer": 1.5625320751217815
    },
    {
        "question": "439,673 ÷ 105,084=？",
        "answer": 0.6215932009741497
    },
    {
        "question": "6,087 ÷ 711=？",
        "answer": 0.9325337010232422
    },
    {
        "question": "95,418,650 ÷ 1,548,399=？",
        "answer": 1.7897503856236312
    },
    {
        "question": "705 × 29,084=？",
        "answer": 7.311843252963226
    },
    {
        "question": "510,924,148 ÷ 2,274=？",
        "answer": 5.351565969038928
    },
    {
        "question": "1,584,030 ÷ 34,815=？",
        "answer": 1.6579970029382642
    },
    {
        "question": "9,414,324 ÷ 262=？",
        "answer": 4.555487849431244
    },
    {
        "question": "6,151 × 56,008=？",
        "answer": 8.537195791667637
    },
    {
        "question": "378,675,020 ÷ 1,584=？",
        "answer": 5.378511479771295
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 888,660=？",
        "answer": 7.124826891378518
    },
    {
        "question": "3,989,453 ÷ 44,570=？",
        "answer": 1.9518707189021003
    },
    {
        "question": "43,335 × 10,730=？",
        "answer": 8.66743852286583
    },
    {
        "question": "1,416 × 61,609=？",
        "answer": 7.940707412999189
    },
    {
        "question": "73,194 ÷ 991=？",
        "answer": 1.8684018272057534
    },
    {
        "question": "578,999,248 ÷ 203=？",
        "answer": 6.455181961756084
    },
    {
        "question": "241,736 ÷ 1,078=？",
        "answer": 2.3507225707200106
    },
    {
        "question": "9,457 × 8,560=？",
        "answer": 7.90822715371344
    },
    {
        "question": "23,859 × 573=？",
        "answer": 7.135806859139808
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 608=？",
        "answer": 2.783903579272735
    },
    {
        "question": "160 × 1,720,384=？",
        "answer": 8.439745377509833
    },
    {
        "question": "425,016 ÷ 410,691=？",
        "answer": 0.014890093947981627
    },
    {
        "question": "3,563 ÷ 2,148=？",
        "answer": 0.21978154532349756
    },
    {
        "question": "38,301 × 2,739=？",
        "answer": 8.020802145356067
    },
    {
        "question": "110 × 1,456=？",
        "answer": 5.204554060135243
    },
    {
        "question": "8,379 × 424=？",
        "answer": 6.5505580470134
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 4,493,155=？",
        "answer": 8.415979394235551
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 11,054,159=？",
        "answer": 7.645585698391703
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 7,246,055=？",
        "answer": 8.27507497412336
    },
    {
        "question": "20,236 ÷ 2,936=？",
        "answer": 0.8383686194924967
    },
    {
        "question": "9,962,291 ÷ 66,739=？",
        "answer": 2.1739795283771968
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 26,503=？",
        "answer": 6.003078633183926
    },
    {
        "question": "1,316,128 ÷ 90,705=？",
        "answer": 1.1616669009707277
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 218,906=？",
        "answer": 7.264536951381208
    },
    {
        "question": "128,635,310 ÷ 6,680,165=？",
        "answer": 1.284573007785927
    },
    {
        "question": "102,127 ÷ 35,049=？",
        "answer": 0.4644649431991175
    },
    {
        "question": "5,485,430 ÷ 2,058=？",
        "answer": 3.4257653069369214
    },
    {
        "question": "96,016 ÷ 25,292=？",
        "answer": 0.5793604362808407
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 209=？",
        "answer": 2.621176281775035
    },
    {
        "question": "57,935,910 ÷ 453,927=？",
        "answer": 2.1059618170720285
    },
    {
        "question": "42,927 ÷ 214=？",
        "answer": 2.302316765049387
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 20,461=？",
        "answer": 6.001122935400207
    },
    {
        "question": "189,453,921 ÷ 7,058=？",
        "answer": 4.428821943979998
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 252=？",
        "answer": 3.8785217955012063
    },
    {
        "question": "15,018 × 915=？",
        "answer": 7.138033194058315
    },
    {
        "question": "408,787,262 ÷ 1,594,706=？",
        "answer": 2.4088167262790954
    },
    {
        "question": "2,452 × 35,747=？",
        "answer": 7.942760066162072
    },
    {
        "question": "144 × 1,947,096=？",
        "answer": 8.447749856682792
    },
    {
        "question": "12,227,910 ÷ 463,327=？",
        "answer": 1.4214646244722429
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 37,999=？",
        "answer": 5.783892150320198
    },
    {
        "question": "60,844 × 12,438=？",
        "answer": 8.878968310140248
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 309,571=？",
        "answer": 5.791790265730803
    },
    {
        "question": "260,646 ÷ 92,416=？",
        "answer": 0.45030389720280134
    },
    {
        "question": "40,133,311 ÷ 7,890,759=？",
        "answer": 0.7063862111881338
    },
    {
        "question": "7,837,555 ÷ 392=？",
        "answer": 4.300894534488197
    },
    {
        "question": "525,838 × 210=？",
        "answer": 8.04307126219082
    },
    {
        "question": "5,108 × 2,114=？",
        "answer": 7.033355871562785
    },
    {
        "question": "954 × 4,183=？",
        "answer": 6.601036239284725
    },
    {
        "question": "180,702,457 ÷ 4,515,156=？",
        "answer": 1.6022912977620452
    },
    {
        "question": "1,456,784 ÷ 1,033=？",
        "answer": 3.14929484139501
    },
    {
        "question": "36,733,332 ÷ 213=？",
        "answer": 5.236680720593501
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 7,190,315=？",
        "answer": 7.898140601934037
    },
    {
        "question": "1,516,968 ÷ 339,935=？",
        "answer": 0.649580537348614
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 115,166=？",
        "answer": 5.362354278641575
    },
    {
        "question": "19,800 × 602=？",
        "answer": 7.076261681519355
    },
    {
        "question": "1,417,229 × 660=？",
        "answer": 8.970983966029932
    },
    {
        "question": "235,222 ÷ 19,285=？",
        "answer": 1.086258295085455
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,928,400=？",
        "answer": 6.772937498603542
    },
    {
        "question": "346,095,283 ÷ 93,137,488=？",
        "answer": 0.5700711598000382
    },
    {
        "question": "666 ÷ 216=？",
        "answer": 0.4890204780193702
    },
    {
        "question": "376,897 × 478=？",
        "answer": 8.255650577206772
    },
    {
        "question": "2,946 × 8,430=？",
        "answer": 7.395060317131354
    },
    {
        "question": "108 × 46,230=？",
        "answer": 6.698347648925031
    },
    {
        "question": "443,144,903 ÷ 3,404=？",
        "answer": 5.11455620705301
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 312,843=？",
        "answer": 5.972447696611485
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 807=？",
        "answer": 2.90687353472207
    },
    {
        "question": "45,793,867 ÷ 18,703,046=？",
        "answer": 0.3888949764701185
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 339,824=？",
        "answer": 5.531254047574503
    },
    {
        "question": "587 × 177,592=？",
        "answer": 8.01806149943508
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 21,516=？",
        "answer": 4.332761535609808
    },
    {
        "question": "2,906,554 ÷ 25,613=？",
        "answer": 2.054917946494164
    },
    {
        "question": "44,253,103 ÷ 7,625,389=？",
        "answer": 0.7636817249680907
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 337,614=？",
        "answer": 7.046934387300348
    },
    {
        "question": "444 × 46,714=？",
        "answer": 7.316830026517163
    },
    {
        "question": "599,233,898 ÷ 29,302=？",
        "answer": 4.310699108928731
    },
    {
        "question": "19,182,117 ÷ 2,242=？",
        "answer": 3.932260927353703
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,852,812=？",
        "answer": 6.869891346154291
    },
    {
        "question": "16,260,139 ÷ 1,448,430=？",
        "answer": 1.0502267424649139
    },
    {
        "question": "29,746,937 ÷ 3,051,788=？",
        "answer": 0.9888878926880431
    },
    {
        "question": "225,218,833 ÷ 33,738,792=？",
        "answer": 0.8244751749481717
    },
    {
        "question": "91,988,443 ÷ 2,768=？",
        "answer": 4.521567182249912
    },
    {
        "question": "44,480 × 508=？",
        "answer": 7.35402849085792
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 3,032=？",
        "answer": 4.481729196960016
    },
    {
        "question": "948,632,030 ÷ 399,285=？",
        "answer": 3.3758147889657106
    },
    {
        "question": "107,525,294 ÷ 8,454=？",
        "answer": 4.104448395200259
    },
    {
        "question": "2,754 × 1,287=？",
        "answer": 6.5495424828252915
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 10,945,291=？",
        "answer": 8.36144660728147
    },
    {
        "question": "1,875,915 ÷ 467,819=？",
        "answer": 0.6031352998087998
    },
    {
        "question": "151,508 × 418=？",
        "answer": 7.801611847049836
    },
    {
        "question": "751,429 × 303=？",
        "answer": 8.35733058033819
    },
    {
        "question": "2,447,593 ÷ 363,343=？",
        "answer": 0.8284224047736621
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 6,443=？",
        "answer": 4.9552161670245845
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 13,756=？",
        "answer": 4.6156134218696385
    },
    {
        "question": "842,421,598 ÷ 168,874=？",
        "answer": 3.6979667024290506
    },
    {
        "question": "135 × 2,290,960=？",
        "answer": 8.49035127499958
    },
    {
        "question": "947,267,191 ÷ 467,881=？",
        "answer": 3.3063370861402372
    },
    {
        "question": "3,273 × 423=？",
        "answer": 6.141286372683046
    },
    {
        "question": "389,003,494 ÷ 46,569=？",
        "answer": 3.921856589938552
    },
    {
        "question": "6,182 × 249=？",
        "answer": 6.187328347823023
    },
    {
        "question": "134,845 ÷ 18,107=？",
        "answer": 0.871988346026322
    },
    {
        "question": "227,824 ÷ 470=？",
        "answer": 2.685501614742132
    },
    {
        "question": "96,692,968 ÷ 11,036=？",
        "answer": 3.942583199340552
    },
    {
        "question": "123,096,230 ÷ 303=？",
        "answer": 5.608802123736333
    },
    {
        "question": "381,317,970 ÷ 27,237=？",
        "answer": 4.146128001510339
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 212,439=？",
        "answer": 5.8043555031459935
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 471,388=？",
        "answer": 5.673378522608932
    },
    {
        "question": "190,471 × 2,989=？",
        "answer": 8.755354776947444
    },
    {
        "question": "1,912 × 110,735=？",
        "answer": 8.325772797928414
    },
    {
        "question": "157 × 48,586=？",
        "answer": 6.882410798242459
    },
    {
        "question": "113,537,821 ÷ 31,183,852=？",
        "answer": 0.5612107944612026
    },
    {
        "question": "25,160,119 ÷ 44,758=？",
        "answer": 2.74984201891397
    },
    {
        "question": "825,495,157 ÷ 35,908=？",
        "answer": 4.3615233131838975
    },
    {
        "question": "64,756 ÷ 1,611=？",
        "answer": 1.6041844739737372
    },
    {
        "question": "839,199,077 ÷ 38,655=？",
        "answer": 4.336659319916824
    },
    {
        "question": "18,564,474 ÷ 48,595=？",
        "answer": 2.582091062110979
    },
    {
        "question": "17,764,873 ÷ 593,463=？",
        "answer": 1.4761684594483198
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 188,029=？",
        "answer": 6.865289443357667
    },
    {
        "question": "52,080 ÷ 430=？",
        "answer": 2.083202519980549
    },
    {
        "question": "332,463 × 1,762=？",
        "answer": 8.767749223519797
    },
    {
        "question": "9,119,487 ÷ 3,077=？",
        "answer": 3.4718429123292576
    },
    {
        "question": "72,097,990 ÷ 2,812=？",
        "answer": 4.4089078409642
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 5,551,494=？",
        "answer": 7.522561125153494
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 5,266,656=？",
        "answer": 8.043754247384028
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 201,147=？",
        "answer": 6.344906244843723
    },
    {
        "question": "167 × 93,362=？",
        "answer": 7.192886617737385
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 37,472=？",
        "answer": 5.5279493828315935
    },
    {
        "question": "97,987,137 ÷ 499=？",
        "answer": 5.293068522961248
    },
    {
        "question": "71,764 ÷ 7,417=？",
        "answer": 0.9856783585146688
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 24,260=？",
        "answer": 5.964674393147364
    },
    {
        "question": "17,837,383 ÷ 5,477,129=？",
        "answer": 0.5127781677187981
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 22,891,776=？",
        "answer": 7.359679487610285
    },
    {
        "question": "535,487 ÷ 466,511=？",
        "answer": 0.059887043382731535
    },
    {
        "question": "28,245,392 ÷ 1,490,203=？",
        "answer": 1.277702173051914
    },
    {
        "question": "234,736 ÷ 1,905=？",
        "answer": 2.0906847197377703
    },
    {
        "question": "688,506,235 ÷ 29,076=？",
        "answer": 4.374373217325507
    },
    {
        "question": "289 × 106,899=？",
        "answer": 7.489871485322546
    },
    {
        "question": "110,405,754 ÷ 73,238=？",
        "answer": 3.1782552320640307
    },
    {
        "question": "712,870,385 ÷ 154,429,204=？",
        "answer": 0.6642811401590427
    },
    {
        "question": "850,012 ÷ 117,129=？",
        "answer": 0.8607606214160294
    },
    {
        "question": "8,072,992 ÷ 124,606=？",
        "answer": 1.8114955672392683
    },
    {
        "question": "3,031 ÷ 1,293=？",
        "answer": 0.36998741148722825
    },
    {
        "question": "454,184,563 ÷ 8,878=？",
        "answer": 4.708917228476957
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 88,706=？",
        "answer": 6.902195505581801
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 30,968=？",
        "answer": 5.813132453044818
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,479,815=？",
        "answer": 7.170207425191511
    },
    {
        "question": "99,377 ÷ 65,868=？",
        "answer": 0.17861140526520797
    },
    {
        "question": "209 × 1,464=？",
        "answer": 5.485687362833427
    },
    {
        "question": "15,196 ÷ 1,547=？",
        "answer": 0.9922389711833153
    },
    {
        "question": "1,364,740 ÷ 175,881=？",
        "answer": 0.8898309945324357
    },
    {
        "question": "7,050 ÷ 3,780=？",
        "answer": 0.2706973171541734
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 44,871,578=？",
        "answer": 8.129092597367112
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 218=？",
        "answer": 3.5689054149828787
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 5,856,684=？",
        "answer": 8.12937962812502
    },
    {
        "question": "23,124,436 ÷ 5,242=？",
        "answer": 3.6445741325810372
    },
    {
        "question": "25,581,892 ÷ 972=？",
        "answer": 4.420266396200477
    },
    {
        "question": "1,851 ÷ 343=？",
        "answer": 0.7321122987101336
    },
    {
        "question": "6,476 × 2,941=？",
        "answer": 7.279801864588405
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 19,648=？",
        "answer": 4.594348345125055
    },
    {
        "question": "185 × 3,319=？",
        "answer": 5.788178980811618
    },
    {
        "question": "205,190,766 ÷ 73,385=？",
        "answer": 3.446550514180533
    },
    {
        "question": "106,689 ÷ 261=？",
        "answer": 2.6114791371511625
    },
    {
        "question": "1,392 × 10,697=？",
        "answer": 7.172901231078718
    },
    {
        "question": "1,012 × 509=？",
        "answer": 5.711898294840539
    },
    {
        "question": "6,440,853 ÷ 548=？",
        "answer": 4.070162828853911
    },
    {
        "question": "754,817 ÷ 618=？",
        "answer": 3.0868531977011786
    },
    {
        "question": "400,441 ÷ 79,688=？",
        "answer": 0.7011456101537858
    },
    {
        "question": "132,685,234 ÷ 435=？",
        "answer": 5.484333337732456
    },
    {
        "question": "35,036,582 ÷ 1,325,062=？",
        "answer": 1.4222855323854857
    },
    {
        "question": "926,607 ÷ 30,967=？",
        "answer": 1.4759964426238594
    },
    {
        "question": "800,075 ÷ 179,272=？",
        "answer": 0.6496182365915669
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 9,051=？",
        "answer": 5.929824418494349
    },
    {
        "question": "83,765 ÷ 355=？",
        "answer": 2.3728342397751923
    },
    {
        "question": "57,471,616 ÷ 102,945=？",
        "answer": 2.7468481509502767
    },
    {
        "question": "1,627 × 20,365=？",
        "answer": 7.520271967358875
    },
    {
        "question": "4,042,630 ÷ 21,174=？",
        "answer": 2.280861085790266
    },
    {
        "question": "4,254 × 54,110=？",
        "answer": 8.362075019499292
    },
    {
        "question": "108,959,541 ÷ 8,532=？",
        "answer": 4.106214418298046
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 514=？",
        "answer": 3.5560611590095323
    },
    {
        "question": "2,790,771 ÷ 950,506=？",
        "answer": 0.467769338743192
    },
    {
        "question": "136,671 ÷ 7,946=？",
        "answer": 1.2355278113752646
    },
    {
        "question": "73 × 3,712,465=？",
        "answer": 8.432985228067672
    },
    {
        "question": "87 × 7,538,017=？",
        "answer": 8.816776365169439
    },
    {
        "question": "238,746 ÷ 664=？",
        "answer": 2.555768024688897
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 642,086,648=？",
        "answer": 8.8075936389864
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 5,465=？",
        "answer": 4.816771412333346
    },
    {
        "question": "6,302,277 ÷ 272=？",
        "answer": 4.364928583494312
    },
    {
        "question": "73,272,827 ÷ 1,514,656=？",
        "answer": 1.6846289381788868
    },
    {
        "question": "9,025 × 1,838=？",
        "answer": 7.219792717627788
    },
    {
        "question": "23,656,354 ÷ 9,636,060=？",
        "answer": 0.3900483149476675
    },
    {
        "question": "105 × 818,940=？",
        "answer": 7.934441383219301
    },
    {
        "question": "63,625,114 ÷ 1,290=？",
        "answer": 4.693038863191367
    },
    {
        "question": "5,233 × 481=？",
        "answer": 6.400895811113497
    },
    {
        "question": "50,753,742 ÷ 1,117,562=？",
        "answer": 1.6571964414488551
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 3,039=？",
        "answer": 4.658821959135624
    },
    {
        "question": "218,594,830 ÷ 62,753,688=？",
        "answer": 0.5420006320563744
    },
    {
        "question": "49,926 × 237=？",
        "answer": 7.073075118403771
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 14,187=？",
        "answer": 5.549830577407127
    },
    {
        "question": "8,371,573 ÷ 824,290=？",
        "answer": 1.006727037464849
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,183,602=？",
        "answer": 6.339173483412164
    },
    {
        "question": "108 × 7,533,213=？",
        "answer": 8.910404002677513
    },
    {
        "question": "590 × 18,143=？",
        "answer": 7.0295611122119706
    },
    {
        "question": "487 × 53,864=？",
        "answer": 7.418827562674523
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 11,647=？",
        "answer": 6.066214075471244
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 5,249=？",
        "answer": 5.021106568432121
    },
    {
        "question": "338,410 ÷ 47,652=？",
        "answer": 0.8513620548271432
    },
    {
        "question": "237,595,889 ÷ 203=？",
        "answer": 6.068342884085923
    },
    {
        "question": "137,037,453 ÷ 3,322,026=？",
        "answer": 1.615436251010009
    },
    {
        "question": "1,863,350 ÷ 2,551=？",
        "answer": 2.8635839791056257
    },
    {
        "question": "179 × 16,936=？",
        "answer": 6.481663875991249
    },
    {
        "question": "420 ÷ 242=？",
        "answer": 0.2394339244174692
    },
    {
        "question": "177,277,881 ÷ 2,507=？",
        "answer": 4.849500218005354
    },
    {
        "question": "37,195,948 ÷ 1,476=？",
        "answer": 4.4014092744086275
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 637=？",
        "answer": 2.8041394323353503
    },
    {
        "question": "1,296,165 ÷ 1,143=？",
        "answer": 3.054614059741377
    },
    {
        "question": "322,219,885 ÷ 3,141,171=？",
        "answer": 2.01106075902158
    },
    {
        "question": "66,787,632 ÷ 4,539,658=？",
        "answer": 1.1676729094881395
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 5,054,591=？",
        "answer": 8.584499612023961
    },
    {
        "question": "867,595,014 ÷ 22,254=？",
        "answer": 4.590908963780998
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 1,061=？",
        "answer": 4.47287341524356
    },
    {
        "question": "168,447,306 ÷ 133,908=？",
        "answer": 3.0996575460142957
    },
    {
        "question": "2,811 × 129,152=？",
        "answer": 8.55996198149222
    },
    {
        "question": "61,345,023 ÷ 1,165=？",
        "answer": 4.7214534082647015
    },
    {
        "question": "421 × 964,061=？",
        "answer": 8.608386610158885
    },
    {
        "question": "12,713 × 68,972=？",
        "answer": 8.942920866518175
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 29,827=？",
        "answer": 5.965971268048983
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 528,418=？",
        "answer": 6.421947607312439
    },
    {
        "question": "274 × 188,185=？",
        "answer": 7.712335566200416
    },
    {
        "question": "117,909,777 ÷ 21,317,898=？",
        "answer": 0.7428054380927535
    },
    {
        "question": "3,701 × 112,511=？",
        "answer": 8.619514069815935
    },
    {
        "question": "1,042 ÷ 242=？",
        "answer": 0.6340523529830744
    },
    {
        "question": "890 ÷ 741=？",
        "answer": 0.07957179866558461
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 271,420=？",
        "answer": 5.910763100879098
    },
    {
        "question": "23,170,218 ÷ 5,514=？",
        "answer": 3.623463358155381
    },
    {
        "question": "542,097 ÷ 938=？",
        "answer": 2.7618741654943157
    },
    {
        "question": "125 × 3,108,604=？",
        "answer": 8.589475414508136
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 10,151=？",
        "answer": 5.935927753489583
    },
    {
        "question": "188,225 × 300=？",
        "answer": 7.7517985605323645
    },
    {
        "question": "1,551,703 ÷ 414=？",
        "answer": 3.573808258659251
    },
    {
        "question": "22,781,761 ÷ 373,623=？",
        "answer": 1.7851536881500336
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 10,422=？",
        "answer": 5.810342758328996
    },
    {
        "question": "29,183,172 ÷ 9,214,687=？",
        "answer": 0.50065190689401
    },
    {
        "question": "7,121,919 ÷ 763=？",
        "answer": 3.9700724920330206
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 97,455=？",
        "answer": 5.687774130157068
    },
    {
        "question": "109 × 1,034,350=？",
        "answer": 8.052094016726219
    },
    {
        "question": "740 × 59,523=？",
        "answer": 7.643916531559996
    },
    {
        "question": "23,189,253 ÷ 20,170,876=？",
        "answer": 0.060561999272726666
    },
    {
        "question": "6,020 × 94,792=？",
        "answer": 8.756368177726051
    },
    {
        "question": "52,262,375 ÷ 194,633=？",
        "answer": 2.4289726650750225
    },
    {
        "question": "326 × 19,912=？",
        "answer": 6.8123324836684755
    },
    {
        "question": "519,172,430 ÷ 606=？",
        "answer": 5.932838997575219
    },
    {
        "question": "882,629,390 ÷ 1,978=？",
        "answer": 5.649552097330087
    },
    {
        "question": "523,185,204 ÷ 144,108,393=？",
        "answer": 0.5599661781297627
    },
    {
        "question": "1,157,067 ÷ 324,012=？",
        "answer": 0.5527974126255586
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 2,513,722=？",
        "answer": 7.96851897015286
    },
    {
        "question": "12,907 × 1,022=？",
        "answer": 7.120276205853659
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 139,781=？",
        "answer": 6.321539402168222
    },
    {
        "question": "672,818,633 ÷ 238,588=？",
        "answer": 3.4502494136339763
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,794=？",
        "answer": 4.156912425700017
    },
    {
        "question": "111,558,017 ÷ 1,184,654=？",
        "answer": 1.9739092606882698
    },
    {
        "question": "823,948,120 ÷ 5,704,774=？",
        "answer": 2.159661423040027
    },
    {
        "question": "45,913,192 ÷ 792,275=？",
        "answer": 1.7630615349440995
    },
    {
        "question": "217,454 × 1,552=？",
        "answer": 8.528259117711523
    },
    {
        "question": "337,349,816 ÷ 2,549,799=？",
        "answer": 2.1215745311542045
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 373,083=？",
        "answer": 5.57180546031288
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 10,171=？",
        "answer": 5.422337002283096
    },
    {
        "question": "194 × 415,877=？",
        "answer": 7.906766632383902
    },
    {
        "question": "179,983 ÷ 15,949=？",
        "answer": 1.0524980284197725
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 19,798=？",
        "answer": 4.773742574635997
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 13,630,557=？",
        "answer": 8.549486951207092
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 146,540=？",
        "answer": 6.6283541851019425
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 18,823,964=？",
        "answer": 7.274711083599739
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 2,071,943=？",
        "answer": 7.678105639636168
    },
    {
        "question": "256,852 ÷ 5,058=？",
        "answer": 1.705704126736152
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 1,784=？",
        "answer": 4.330576096087729
    },
    {
        "question": "7,851,215 ÷ 516=？",
        "answer": 4.1822871687440655
    },
    {
        "question": "48 × 5,975=？",
        "answer": 5.457579146995762
    },
    {
        "question": "38,267 × 6,875=？",
        "answer": 8.420097118881094
    },
    {
        "question": "399 × 628=？",
        "answer": 5.398932539423944
    },
    {
        "question": "893 × 6,617=？",
        "answer": 6.771512593532142
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 482=？",
        "answer": 4.274111645265349
    },
    {
        "question": "161,335,329 ÷ 84,275,397=？",
        "answer": 0.28202867199360415
    },
    {
        "question": "106,410 ÷ 2,143=？",
        "answer": 1.6959602721497766
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 589,218=？",
        "answer": 6.247397260339794
    },
    {
        "question": "2,398,567 ÷ 1,159,245=？",
        "answer": 0.3157766228753078
    },
    {
        "question": "37,181,638 ÷ 1,095=？",
        "answer": 4.530914399091687
    },
    {
        "question": "688,952 ÷ 2,547=？",
        "answer": 2.432160020251267
    },
    {
        "question": "4,881,718 ÷ 2,077=？",
        "answer": 3.3711361915773708
    },
    {
        "question": "20,950,955 ÷ 835,819=？",
        "answer": 1.3990915846594485
    },
    {
        "question": "1,833,601 ÷ 12,909=？",
        "answer": 2.1524122363384612
    },
    {
        "question": "205,705 ÷ 141,387=？",
        "answer": 0.1628353685069616
    },
    {
        "question": "2,449 × 277=？",
        "answer": 5.831468554189163
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 53,836=？",
        "answer": 5.685315293893322
    },
    {
        "question": "3,647,234 ÷ 309=？",
        "answer": 4.072005148338812
    },
    {
        "question": "64,362 × 2,572=？",
        "answer": 8.218900495258236
    },
    {
        "question": "5,794,258 ÷ 25,392=？",
        "answer": 2.3583009196485
    },
    {
        "question": "552,757,972 ÷ 5,688,877=？",
        "answer": 1.9875084708608277
    },
    {
        "question": "184,298,976 ÷ 1,421=？",
        "answer": 5.112928844275951
    },
    {
        "question": "97,633 × 1,258=？",
        "answer": 8.089277275328874
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 13,532=？",
        "answer": 5.64987592899383
    },
    {
        "question": "1,107,828 ÷ 7,923=？",
        "answer": 2.14558268167756
    },
    {
        "question": "16,438,812 ÷ 1,603=？",
        "answer": 4.010936906392034
    },
    {
        "question": "1,834,635 ÷ 18,195=？",
        "answer": 2.0035976145223398
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 80,601,904=？",
        "answer": 7.906345300948104
    },
    {
        "question": "407,955 ÷ 4,559=？",
        "answer": 1.9517426681194918
    },
    {
        "question": "38,112,791 ÷ 363,762=？",
        "answer": 2.020253424326922
    },
    {
        "question": "306,389,257 ÷ 24,887,694=？",
        "answer": 1.090288875074383
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 42,840=？",
        "answer": 5.1089707168794805
    },
    {
        "question": "188,548,080 ÷ 121,441=？",
        "answer": 3.1910567795662343
    },
    {
        "question": "61,455 ÷ 1,468=？",
        "answer": 1.6218311674287718
    },
    {
        "question": "157,168,381 ÷ 129,501=？",
        "answer": 3.0840920574700195
    },
    {
        "question": "4,129 ÷ 2,690=？",
        "answer": 0.18609260287229418
    },
    {
        "question": "1,359,530 ÷ 13,659=？",
        "answer": 1.997969890338628
    },
    {
        "question": "150 × 7,442=？",
        "answer": 6.047780924741197
    },
    {
        "question": "24,031,813 ÷ 2,835,438=？",
        "answer": 0.9281663805441129
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 222=？",
        "answer": 3.5224442335063197
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 55,918,083=？",
        "answer": 8.224673529102631
    },
    {
        "question": "50,164,399 ÷ 13,250=？",
        "answer": 3.578179735228814
    },
    {
        "question": "737,001,239 ÷ 23,812,166=？",
        "answer": 1.4906693165127354
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 278=？",
        "answer": 3.143014800254095
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 5,997,904=？",
        "answer": 7.777999510339161
    },
    {
        "question": "3,499,970 ÷ 71,362=？",
        "answer": 1.6905973086821455
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 44,732,555=？",
        "answer": 7.65062370458248
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 136,370=？",
        "answer": 6.725783447526894
    },
    {
        "question": "5,339 × 769=？",
        "answer": 6.61338626065934
    },
    {
        "question": "3,948,077 ÷ 1,575,984=？",
        "answer": 0.3988338101473277
    },
    {
        "question": "357 × 2,799,512=？",
        "answer": 8.9997505495337
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 40,221=？",
        "answer": 5.206512855427646
    },
    {
        "question": "65,644,249 ÷ 386=？",
        "answer": 5.2306093794937425
    },
    {
        "question": "3,980 × 443=？",
        "answer": 6.246286798296757
    },
    {
        "question": "335,485,998 ÷ 837=？",
        "answer": 5.602948940973052
    },
    {
        "question": "4,958,148 ÷ 106,266=？",
        "answer": 1.6689251528144358
    },
    {
        "question": "88,315,375 ÷ 19,865=？",
        "answer": 3.647947747961897
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 252=？",
        "answer": 2.401400540781544
    },
    {
        "question": "32,103,645 ÷ 215,088=？",
        "answer": 2.1739381630638186
    },
    {
        "question": "1,120 × 169,994=？",
        "answer": 8.279651615737416
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 184,133=？",
        "answer": 7.043282879374204
    },
    {
        "question": "4,212 × 21,987=？",
        "answer": 7.966654338926211
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 565,720,769=？",
        "answer": 8.752602123051037
    },
    {
        "question": "6,555 × 1,059=？",
        "answer": 6.841468656133588
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 5,419,873=？",
        "answer": 7.432959114482265
    },
    {
        "question": "17,692 ÷ 1,454=？",
        "answer": 1.0852125241745472
    },
    {
        "question": "520,841,568 ÷ 2,134,539=？",
        "answer": 2.3874015435071736
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 393,072=？",
        "answer": 6.770563367544829
    },
    {
        "question": "49,102,233 ÷ 12,184,784=？",
        "answer": 0.6052834079466317
    },
    {
        "question": "7,199 × 17,880=？",
        "answer": 8.10963968802394
    },
    {
        "question": "112,632,254 ÷ 205,483=？",
        "answer": 2.738886877625734
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 14,482=？",
        "answer": 5.762888534472509
    },
    {
        "question": "45,801 ÷ 41,691=？",
        "answer": 0.04083264807734233
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 1,627,929=？",
        "answer": 7.591846701490454
    },
    {
        "question": "41,306 × 991=？",
        "answer": 7.61208679518838
    },
    {
        "question": "273,111 ÷ 20,290=？",
        "answer": 1.129057145391609
    },
    {
        "question": "202 × 526=？",
        "answer": 5.026337113600363
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,398,962=？",
        "answer": 6.857144623437381
    },
    {
        "question": "858 × 8,087=？",
        "answer": 6.841274730959322
    },
    {
        "question": "65,388,612 ÷ 157,141=？",
        "answer": 2.6192126061761605
    },
    {
        "question": "26,494,321 ÷ 420,345=？",
        "answer": 1.7995469079809918
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 124,644,027=？",
        "answer": 8.095671471743978
    },
    {
        "question": "260 × 201=？",
        "answer": 4.718169405391307
    },
    {
        "question": "106,441,422 ÷ 904,871=？",
        "answer": 2.0705239980247203
    },
    {
        "question": "380,381 ÷ 14,104=？",
        "answer": 1.4308765165418396
    },
    {
        "question": "3,277,181 ÷ 142,586=？",
        "answer": 1.3614235424846386
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 617,658=？",
        "answer": 6.790748070840062
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 138,587=？",
        "answer": 6.604120491572603
    },
    {
        "question": "89,768,487 ÷ 113,722=？",
        "answer": 2.897279416530542
    },
    {
        "question": "120,869 × 1,672=？",
        "answer": 8.305551202125256
    },
    {
        "question": "2,665 × 37,589=？",
        "answer": 8.000757985464839
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 267=？",
        "answer": 3.271609301378832
    },
    {
        "question": "1,209 × 7,710=？",
        "answer": 6.9694806789117285
    },
    {
        "question": "160,981 × 3,575=？",
        "answer": 8.760050667000689
    },
    {
        "question": "4,755,843 ÷ 293=？",
        "answer": 4.210359888889623
    },
    {
        "question": "6,504,036 ÷ 71,484=？",
        "answer": 1.9589740902768853
    },
    {
        "question": "98 × 48,913=？",
        "answer": 6.680650376082572
    },
    {
        "question": "532,442,581 ÷ 7,460=？",
        "answer": 4.8535339525265435
    },
    {
        "question": "262 × 983=？",
        "answer": 5.410854809151881
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 1,047=？",
        "answer": 4.45131044583783
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 834=？",
        "answer": 3.398287305357401
    },
    {
        "question": "287,324,496 ÷ 12,713=？",
        "answer": 4.354124606582851
    },
    {
        "question": "433,387 × 459=？",
        "answer": 8.298688565495354
    },
    {
        "question": "101,513,667 ÷ 26,454,995=？",
        "answer": 0.5840168323851848
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,939=？",
        "answer": 3.9973426906016223
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 204,238=？",
        "answer": 5.787257803709273
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 112,735,170=？",
        "answer": 8.897157464082936
    },
    {
        "question": "37,109 ÷ 35,763=？",
        "answer": 0.016045308598275812
    },
    {
        "question": "7,469 × 684=？",
        "answer": 6.708318561158843
    },
    {
        "question": "15,325,509 ÷ 199=？",
        "answer": 4.886561831069185
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 13,502=？",
        "answer": 5.635548081972708
    },
    {
        "question": "264,406 ÷ 7,356=？",
        "answer": 1.5556295855324556
    },
    {
        "question": "517,066,279 ÷ 1,526,949=？",
        "answer": 2.5297216838515575
    },
    {
        "question": "515,154 × 1,446=？",
        "answer": 8.872105369286054
    },
    {
        "question": "137 × 1,817,066=？",
        "answer": 8.396091269321479
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 20,486,874=？",
        "answer": 7.9135356877418195
    },
    {
        "question": "149 × 1,517,244=？",
        "answer": 8.354241697143872
    },
    {
        "question": "280,303 ÷ 4,464=？",
        "answer": 1.7979035599808655
    },
    {
        "question": "4,182 ÷ 3,124=？",
        "answer": 0.12667300327639033
    },
    {
        "question": "113,861,379 ÷ 418=？",
        "answer": 5.435200157567557
    },
    {
        "question": "13,530 ÷ 1,681=？",
        "answer": 0.905730083158152
    },
    {
        "question": "640,087,737 ÷ 125,923=？",
        "answer": 3.706134445120684
    },
    {
        "question": "1,715,197 ÷ 6,123=？",
        "answer": 2.4473497489660607
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 363,226=？",
        "answer": 5.861206923762993
    },
    {
        "question": "183 × 235=？",
        "answer": 4.633518952002166
    },
    {
        "question": "5,479,172 ÷ 2,846=？",
        "answer": 3.2844800381010124
    },
    {
        "question": "11,118 × 8,785=？",
        "answer": 7.989768435533855
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 371,843=？",
        "answer": 6.570359610241983
    },
    {
        "question": "406,286 ÷ 25,477=？",
        "answer": 1.2026835703747567
    },
    {
        "question": "117,524,970 ÷ 1,276=？",
        "answer": 4.964279474615022
    },
    {
        "question": "3,958,122 ÷ 1,739,319=？",
        "answer": 0.3571099350674671
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 22,720,625=？",
        "answer": 7.65745026945991
    },
    {
        "question": "7,190 × 320=？",
        "answer": 6.361878868702789
    },
    {
        "question": "24,623,272 ÷ 7,519=？",
        "answer": 3.5151856777065857
    },
    {
        "question": "171,144 ÷ 33,550=？",
        "answer": 0.7076691536544378
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 23,500,126=？",
        "answer": 7.672100186487123
    },
    {
        "question": "230 × 2,003,737=？",
        "answer": 8.66356855373958
    },
    {
        "question": "25,131,357 ÷ 90,915=？",
        "answer": 2.4415803964501093
    },
    {
        "question": "17,723 ÷ 4,224=？",
        "answer": 0.6228133279558024
    },
    {
        "question": "665,207,199 ÷ 183,253,236=？",
        "answer": 0.5599052881673033
    },
    {
        "question": "9,522,134 ÷ 378=？",
        "answer": 4.401242488942843
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 818=？",
        "answer": 3.2137832993353044
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,576=？",
        "answer": 3.674677467873199
    },
    {
        "question": "265,030,334 ÷ 420,087=？",
        "answer": 2.799956341798122
    },
    {
        "question": "712,654,866 ÷ 6,435=？",
        "answer": 5.044330703602802
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 235,646=？",
        "answer": 5.673290067840809
    },
    {
        "question": "34,209,235 ÷ 70,947=？",
        "answer": 2.683209326432096
    },
    {
        "question": "61,926,195 ÷ 36,536,235=？",
        "answer": 0.22915060401360018
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 1,588=？",
        "answer": 4.7571529988583645
    },
    {
        "question": "529,290 × 276=？",
        "answer": 8.16460277090658
    },
    {
        "question": "597 ÷ 440=？",
        "answer": 0.1325216546431817
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 73,738=？",
        "answer": 5.469751345363681
    },
    {
        "question": "8,269 × 276=？",
        "answer": 6.358362073994881
    },
    {
        "question": "901 × 270,540=？",
        "answer": 8.386956276669277
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 12,569=？",
        "answer": 4.576421980953126
    },
    {
        "question": "623,706 × 212=？",
        "answer": 8.12131578287688
    },
    {
        "question": "18,923,199 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 4.93260228283143
    },
    {
        "question": "286,052 ÷ 341=？",
        "answer": 2.9236906095920676
    },
    {
        "question": "867,080,551 ÷ 204,603=？",
        "answer": 3.6271474476317174
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 100,982=？",
        "answer": 6.71181414396624
    },
    {
        "question": "1,561,585 ÷ 133,610=？",
        "answer": 1.0677266646776917
    },
    {
        "question": "63,762 × 568=？",
        "answer": 7.558910266673436
    },
    {
        "question": "3,907,625 ÷ 326,428=？",
        "answer": 1.0781254753086564
    },
    {
        "question": "7,195 × 392=？",
        "answer": 6.450316865293082
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 18,026,239=？",
        "answer": 7.255905124840583
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 12,096=？",
        "answer": 5.258733037212813
    },
    {
        "question": "1,112,269 ÷ 959=？",
        "answer": 3.0643912260173916
    },
    {
        "question": "13,357 × 1,854=？",
        "answer": 7.393818655781131
    },
    {
        "question": "111,267,896 ÷ 15,003,702=？",
        "answer": 0.870171446204063
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 608,821,323=？",
        "answer": 8.784489854503432
    },
    {
        "question": "196,523 ÷ 541=？",
        "answer": 2.5602161200809306
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 29,340=？",
        "answer": 5.72273261461057
    },
    {
        "question": "5,382 ÷ 4,671=？",
        "answer": 0.061533826139953014
    },
    {
        "question": "2,014,326 ÷ 248=？",
        "answer": 3.909678077617687
    },
    {
        "question": "775,053,539 ÷ 2,175=？",
        "answer": 5.551872442362957
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 68,383=？",
        "answer": 6.803431098171372
    },
    {
        "question": "405,125 ÷ 399=？",
        "answer": 3.006616148353518
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 18,471,505=？",
        "answer": 8.266502281827213
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 3,515,077=？",
        "answer": 8.064448782835106
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 30,580=？",
        "answer": 6.016916398118556
    },
    {
        "question": "10,166 ÷ 1,026=？",
        "answer": 0.9960027445908872
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 14,488,288=？",
        "answer": 8.161017070351807
    },
    {
        "question": "15,748 ÷ 1,609=？",
        "answer": 0.9906693620191623
    },
    {
        "question": "83,586,250 ÷ 542,940=？",
        "answer": 2.187383002953902
    },
    {
        "question": "10,935 ÷ 1,701=？",
        "answer": 0.8081144737610869
    },
    {
        "question": "279 × 4,233=？",
        "answer": 6.072252471747608
    },
    {
        "question": "149,462,087 ÷ 141,243,210=？",
        "answer": 0.02456346308520521
    },
    {
        "question": "3,287,034 ÷ 18,312=？",
        "answer": 2.2540684166378386
    },
    {
        "question": "430,280,678 ÷ 7,159=？",
        "answer": 4.778899481860428
    },
    {
        "question": "350,243,818 ÷ 206,317,664=？",
        "answer": 0.22983406655878022
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 10,339=？",
        "answer": 5.128421887633043
    },
    {
        "question": "38,147 ÷ 3,091=？",
        "answer": 1.0913613842872065
    },
    {
        "question": "2,821 × 5,728=？",
        "answer": 7.208406095455166
    },
    {
        "question": "3,209,295 ÷ 224,742=？",
        "answer": 1.1547253981240024
    },
    {
        "question": "202 × 1,437=？",
        "answer": 5.46280813758085
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 88,517=？",
        "answer": 6.362000034455998
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 172,358=？",
        "answer": 6.277824131157038
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 294,244=？",
        "answer": 6.699156537181057
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,140,183=？",
        "answer": 6.330450910027803
    },
    {
        "question": "8,064 × 6,433=？",
        "answer": 7.714964070501818
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 592,207=？",
        "answer": 7.152684778239061
    },
    {
        "question": "652,228 ÷ 243=？",
        "answer": 3.428793165435366
    },
    {
        "question": "141,448,832 ÷ 3,132=？",
        "answer": 4.654777612277382
    },
    {
        "question": "134,000 ÷ 831=？",
        "answer": 2.2075037745806965
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 63,880=？",
        "answer": 5.504334911802464
    },
    {
        "question": "258,026 × 533=？",
        "answer": 8.138390678895261
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,040,007=？",
        "answer": 6.795187512808522
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 685,928=？",
        "answer": 6.137308527050381
    },
    {
        "question": "1,127 × 4,317=？",
        "answer": 6.687105964702374
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 24,673=？",
        "answer": 6.0256904143207795
    },
    {
        "question": "631,529 ÷ 323,294=？",
        "answer": 0.29079565364838367
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 7,103=？",
        "answer": 4.89283449983028
    },
    {
        "question": "4,258,232 ÷ 1,307,689=？",
        "answer": 0.5127248487247806
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,812,751=？",
        "answer": 7.103436193391245
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 824,718=？",
        "answer": 5.916305473422552
    },
    {
        "question": "67,199 ÷ 793=？",
        "answer": 1.9280896229726308
    },
    {
        "question": "99,466 × 2,140=？",
        "answer": 8.32808842659948
    },
    {
        "question": "694,241,036 ÷ 26,206,984=？",
        "answer": 1.4230932373217995
    },
    {
        "question": "387,867 ÷ 102,652=？",
        "answer": 0.5773154158087427
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 343=？",
        "answer": 3.9332341287148083
    },
    {
        "question": "675,713,713 ÷ 13,562=？",
        "answer": 4.697438992587994
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 4,425=？",
        "answer": 4.1230345297535065
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 692=？",
        "answer": 3.31722734917642
    },
    {
        "question": "955 × 216,841=？",
        "answer": 8.316144773021488
    },
    {
        "question": "967 × 2,707=？",
        "answer": 6.417914729853508
    },
    {
        "question": "62,963 ÷ 26,938=？",
        "answer": 0.3687200641060833
    },
    {
        "question": "7,912,336 ÷ 116,421=？",
        "answer": 1.8322733960973148
    },
    {
        "question": "3,528,420 ÷ 2,589,152=？",
        "answer": 0.13442272802299188
    },
    {
        "question": "548,109 ÷ 524=？",
        "answer": 3.019535646302206
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 25,391,296=？",
        "answer": 8.35892737775236
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 12,187=？",
        "answer": 4.085896811131588
    },
    {
        "question": "295,185 ÷ 460=？",
        "answer": 2.807336453099705
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 108,155=？",
        "answer": 5.636106592978387
    },
    {
        "question": "101,368,739 ÷ 1,098,484=？",
        "answer": 1.96511030844702
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 288,443=？",
        "answer": 6.460060003865277
    },
    {
        "question": "136,940 ÷ 64,000=？",
        "answer": 0.33035034954741277
    },
    {
        "question": "139 × 1,473=？",
        "answer": 5.311217547096726
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 3,400,783=？",
        "answer": 8.434668907983989
    },
    {
        "question": "41,269,477 ÷ 1,129=？",
        "answer": 4.562935023258403
    },
    {
        "question": "16,134,740 ÷ 14,962,849=？",
        "answer": 0.03274767823978906
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 3,166,655=？",
        "answer": 8.313514107176792
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 4,722=？",
        "answer": 5.035853818760301
    },
    {
        "question": "406,933,745 ÷ 17,773,228=？",
        "answer": 1.3597573930607256
    },
    {
        "question": "641 × 891,404=？",
        "answer": 8.756932608084355
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 3,938,667=？",
        "answer": 8.373500514722652
    },
    {
        "question": "1,098 × 428,259=？",
        "answer": 8.672308838685108
    },
    {
        "question": "90,313 ÷ 407=？",
        "answer": 2.346155859603282
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 2,574,169=？",
        "answer": 7.711667051580481
    },
    {
        "question": "7,795,215 ÷ 940=？",
        "answer": 3.9187002443762116
    },
    {
        "question": "347,479 ÷ 1,438=？",
        "answer": 2.3831696769520603
    },
    {
        "question": "48,811,248 ÷ 6,831,627=？",
        "answer": 0.853995765502506
    },
    {
        "question": "17,362,654 ÷ 8,869=？",
        "answer": 3.2917414558884985
    },
    {
        "question": "6,034 × 2,827=？",
        "answer": 7.231931114328489
    },
    {
        "question": "293 × 35,864=？",
        "answer": 7.021526346211845
    },
    {
        "question": "955,140 × 390=？",
        "answer": 8.57113164015084
    },
    {
        "question": "3,829 × 29,187=？",
        "answer": 8.048274824459986
    },
    {
        "question": "45,221 ÷ 2,058=？",
        "answer": 1.3418947915121606
    },
    {
        "question": "612,253,113 ÷ 159,962,117=？",
        "answer": 0.5829138588527447
    },
    {
        "question": "367,400,695 ÷ 55,279=？",
        "answer": 3.8225797954840575
    },
    {
        "question": "3,319 ÷ 647=？",
        "answer": 0.7101029717399036
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 80,837=？",
        "answer": 6.764942684158979
    },
    {
        "question": "117 × 130,691=？",
        "answer": 7.184431542785634
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 3,432=？",
        "answer": 4.649490631483505
    },
    {
        "question": "853,493 ÷ 58,024=？",
        "answer": 1.167592299106213
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 19,971,070=？",
        "answer": 8.953613847681941
    },
    {
        "question": "105,982,681 ÷ 6,316=？",
        "answer": 4.2247927801487055
    },
    {
        "question": "201,515 ÷ 393=？",
        "answer": 2.709914828512463
    },
    {
        "question": "10,321,647 ÷ 223,534=？",
        "answer": 1.6644054125176775
    },
    {
        "question": "2,819 ÷ 2,504=？",
        "answer": 0.05146075133321029
    },
    {
        "question": "194,099 ÷ 4,276=？",
        "answer": 1.656985601367848
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 154,191=？",
        "answer": 6.091149012040169
    },
    {
        "question": "8,939,279 ÷ 85,816=？",
        "answer": 2.017734224453517
    },
    {
        "question": "7,618 × 20,356=？",
        "answer": 8.190533410526184
    },
    {
        "question": "67,590 × 1,520=？",
        "answer": 8.011726034388266
    },
    {
        "question": "6,367,604 ÷ 176,504=？",
        "answer": 1.557221494903575
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 14,757,392=？",
        "answer": 8.61616764492099
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 196,789=？",
        "answer": 6.498120801482873
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 106,038=？",
        "answer": 5.502582782558962
    },
    {
        "question": "34,439,181 ÷ 11,373,166=？",
        "answer": 0.481171436873853
    },
    {
        "question": "145 × 4,706,114=？",
        "answer": 8.834030445468365
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 49,322,807=？",
        "answer": 7.693047784669863
    },
    {
        "question": "96,186 × 9,808=？",
        "answer": 8.974692321673587
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 5,078=？",
        "answer": 5.137056460696691
    },
    {
        "question": "19,858,857 ÷ 746,778=？",
        "answer": 1.4247627333496589
    },
    {
        "question": "202,966,451 ÷ 334,970=？",
        "answer": 2.7824183446133723
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 579=？",
        "answer": 4.671163582606086
    },
    {
        "question": "32,787 × 7,745=？",
        "answer": 8.404723102776465
    },
    {
        "question": "143,884,853 ÷ 113,261=？",
        "answer": 3.1039346856689156
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 25,738=？",
        "answer": 4.410574796542328
    },
    {
        "question": "7,766,482 ÷ 1,190=？",
        "answer": 3.814677378647587
    },
    {
        "question": "6,028,025 ÷ 1,146,344=？",
        "answer": 0.7208600825868469
    },
    {
        "question": "1,694 × 512,847=？",
        "answer": 8.938901225362892
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 20,073,695=？",
        "answer": 8.302627321187533
    },
    {
        "question": "391 × 34,729=？",
        "answer": 7.1328690356466105
    },
    {
        "question": "6,144,003 ÷ 837=？",
        "answer": 3.865725961087996
    },
    {
        "question": "14,621 ÷ 588=？",
        "answer": 1.3955997510347475
    },
    {
        "question": "59,880,338 ÷ 78,903=？",
        "answer": 2.880190727098872
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 91,979=？",
        "answer": 5.2647186792577
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 35,614=？",
        "answer": 6.042982448198447
    },
    {
        "question": "1,949 × 1,395=？",
        "answer": 6.434386046727238
    },
    {
        "question": "242 × 4,407=？",
        "answer": 6.027958416490351
    },
    {
        "question": "86,481,943 ÷ 6,424=？",
        "answer": 4.129119906129521
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 867=？",
        "answer": 4.385177128818429
    },
    {
        "question": "372,840 ÷ 8,083=？",
        "answer": 1.6639499205040482
    },
    {
        "question": "4,110,460 ÷ 2,504,492=？",
        "answer": 0.21517077754643688
    },
    {
        "question": "17,757 ÷ 348=？",
        "answer": 1.7077903507449352
    },
    {
        "question": "617,906 ÷ 270=？",
        "answer": 3.359558648168781
    },
    {
        "question": "37,838,993 ÷ 31,432=？",
        "answer": 3.0805675543054303
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 61,131=？",
        "answer": 5.087291495836711
    },
    {
        "question": "558,536 × 239=？",
        "answer": 8.125449071412262
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 45,188=？",
        "answer": 5.500121160097723
    },
    {
        "question": "12,760,975 ÷ 1,149=？",
        "answer": 4.045563829156351
    },
    {
        "question": "286,849 × 608=？",
        "answer": 8.241556919476068
    },
    {
        "question": "713,890,617 ÷ 21,625=？",
        "answer": 4.5186755577227045
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 11,811=？",
        "answer": 4.373316665173873
    },
    {
        "question": "86 × 505=？",
        "answer": 4.637789829362229
    },
    {
        "question": "28,985 × 1,064=？",
        "answer": 7.48911493266582
    },
    {
        "question": "88,159 ÷ 993=？",
        "answer": 1.9483174067765638
    },
    {
        "question": "10,149 × 1,656=？",
        "answer": 7.225483584956504
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 368=？",
        "answer": 3.866877814337499
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 287,253=？",
        "answer": 7.257605122502825
    },
    {
        "question": "604,419,799 ÷ 955,597=？",
        "answer": 2.801063904442735
    },
    {
        "question": "14,858 × 1,495=？",
        "answer": 7.346601546673125
    },
    {
        "question": "122 × 597,654=？",
        "answer": 7.8628096611864295
    },
    {
        "question": "290,268,611 ÷ 2,720,708=？",
        "answer": 2.0281181411110722
    },
    {
        "question": "1,629 ÷ 250=？",
        "answer": 0.8139810756364718
    },
    {
        "question": "43,459,000 ÷ 6,147=？",
        "answer": 3.849416515778548
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 6,755=？",
        "answer": 5.70468661674975
    },
    {
        "question": "150,031,003 ÷ 54,858=？",
        "answer": 3.436941042507841
    },
    {
        "question": "95,958,115 ÷ 94,222=？",
        "answer": 3.007929389567522
    },
    {
        "question": "152,087,173 ÷ 525=？",
        "answer": 5.461933283886829
    },
    {
        "question": "19,452 ÷ 5,321=？",
        "answer": 0.5629710019714174
    },
    {
        "question": "1,719 ÷ 393=？",
        "answer": 0.6408833263116257
    },
    {
        "question": "320 × 192,266=？",
        "answer": 7.789052469433548
    },
    {
        "question": "685 × 243=？",
        "answer": 5.2212968450907375
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 24,394=？",
        "answer": 6.172612854491909
    },
    {
        "question": "74 × 361=？",
        "answer": 4.426738921636634
    },
    {
        "question": "587,295,982 ÷ 260=？",
        "answer": 6.353883681645853
    },
    {
        "question": "299 × 1,794=？",
        "answer": 5.729493627032503
    },
    {
        "question": "42,944 ÷ 483=？",
        "answer": 1.948955363401367
    },
    {
        "question": "4,790,431 ÷ 1,594,452=？",
        "answer": 0.4777631394866422
    },
    {
        "question": "11,724 ÷ 2,797=？",
        "answer": 0.6223833433948707
    },
    {
        "question": "984,960 × 985=？",
        "answer": 8.986854824312978
    },
    {
        "question": "43,198,770 ÷ 30,385,008=？",
        "answer": 0.15281202628211427
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 20,878=？",
        "answer": 6.278730285570592
    },
    {
        "question": "52,351,834 ÷ 135,645=？",
        "answer": 2.586528110676307
    },
    {
        "question": "8,217 ÷ 2,728=？",
        "answer": 0.47886892098918254
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 2,133=？",
        "answer": 5.288032247770523
    },
    {
        "question": "4,198,843 ÷ 1,353=？",
        "answer": 3.4918318395291497
    },
    {
        "question": "5,153,394 ÷ 16,781=？",
        "answer": 2.487275510089237
    },
    {
        "question": "2,603 × 482=？",
        "answer": 6.098521206348085
    },
    {
        "question": "350 × 467,462=？",
        "answer": 8.2138143571822
    },
    {
        "question": "171,389 ÷ 790=？",
        "answer": 2.33635585352776
    },
    {
        "question": "666 × 1,001=？",
        "answer": 5.82390830664962
    },
    {
        "question": "57,611 ÷ 32,708=？",
        "answer": 0.2458514246070155
    },
    {
        "question": "405 × 790,709=？",
        "answer": 8.505471705262572
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 22,724=？",
        "answer": 5.771458128576039
    },
    {
        "question": "56,153 × 2,478=？",
        "answer": 8.143474265640933
    },
    {
        "question": "14,812 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 1.8262214296922943
    },
    {
        "question": "205,706,448 ÷ 418,232=？",
        "answer": 2.691830646411504
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 27,269=？",
        "answer": 6.404152160479981
    },
    {
        "question": "2,735 × 31,956=？",
        "answer": 7.941509743156016
    },
    {
        "question": "5,559 × 161,794=？",
        "answer": 8.95395908615284
    },
    {
        "question": "3,437 × 34,273=？",
        "answer": 8.071131653095302
    },
    {
        "question": "338 × 545=？",
        "answer": 5.265313202554297
    },
    {
        "question": "74 × 2,538=？",
        "answer": 5.273723337489662
    },
    {
        "question": "262,856,997 ÷ 25,368=？",
        "answer": 4.015433312989949
    },
    {
        "question": "365,275,873 ÷ 2,028=？",
        "answer": 5.2555530367189505
    },
    {
        "question": "204,075 × 1,014=？",
        "answer": 8.315827760168775
    },
    {
        "question": "2,008,605 ÷ 4,994=？",
        "answer": 2.604446001427359
    },
    {
        "question": "614 × 655,156=？",
        "answer": 8.604513093839097
    },
    {
        "question": "102 × 14,112=？",
        "answer": 6.158188739549662
    },
    {
        "question": "25,527 × 18,713=？",
        "answer": 8.679143195967496
    },
    {
        "question": "24,479,063 ÷ 17,422,459=？",
        "answer": 0.14768533886261107
    },
    {
        "question": "253,469,486 ÷ 2,362,059=？",
        "answer": 2.0306349428341406
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 4,064,526=？",
        "answer": 8.394339741007947
    },
    {
        "question": "427,026,062 ÷ 2,029=？",
        "answer": 5.323172334402417
    },
    {
        "question": "136 × 11,457=？",
        "answer": 6.192609821463198
    },
    {
        "question": "38,108 × 9,622=？",
        "answer": 8.5642815091121
    },
    {
        "question": "1,384 × 263=？",
        "answer": 5.561091838610497
    },
    {
        "question": "27,921,994 ÷ 936=？",
        "answer": 4.4746705806956415
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,554,342=？",
        "answer": 7.218911923146178
    },
    {
        "question": "2,258,467 × 255=？",
        "answer": 8.760353929605175
    },
    {
        "question": "72,129,862 ÷ 289,369=？",
        "answer": 2.3966630978330654
    },
    {
        "question": "676,862,971 ÷ 24,351,154=？",
        "answer": 1.4439812086577175
    },
    {
        "question": "55,196,285 ÷ 9,943=？",
        "answer": 3.7443924089975478
    },
    {
        "question": "1,201,866 ÷ 11,550=？",
        "answer": 2.01727406521505
    },
    {
        "question": "267,155,668 ÷ 1,261,046=？",
        "answer": 2.326033463743614
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 4,186=？",
        "answer": 4.466897264016924
    },
    {
        "question": "8,172,041 ÷ 15,975=？",
        "answer": 2.708889670037105
    },
    {
        "question": "1,212,253 ÷ 40,545=？",
        "answer": 1.4756559627964745
    },
    {
        "question": "41,805,850 ÷ 28,106=？",
        "answer": 3.1724380160459527
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 24,359,377=？",
        "answer": 8.617115098240504
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 619,838=？",
        "answer": 7.982609895895477
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 30,203,996=？",
        "answer": 8.480064404081153
    },
    {
        "question": "51,777,866 ÷ 9,399,512=？",
        "answer": 0.7410388405655903
    },
    {
        "question": "442 × 628,825=？",
        "answer": 8.443952068834353
    },
    {
        "question": "67 × 2,034,040=？",
        "answer": 8.13443429190135
    },
    {
        "question": "22,334 ÷ 1,141=？",
        "answer": 1.2916808673838456
    },
    {
        "question": "82,256,263 ÷ 12,062=？",
        "answer": 3.833749650970817
    },
    {
        "question": "219 × 1,578,205=？",
        "answer": 8.53860752980114
    },
    {
        "question": "1,173 × 1,083=？",
        "answer": 6.103926468740849
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 4,044=？",
        "answer": 5.197875753945462
    },
    {
        "question": "344 × 1,669,868=？",
        "answer": 8.759240584894357
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 250,794=？",
        "answer": 7.06207497389583
    },
    {
        "question": "12,864,464 ÷ 10,745=？",
        "answer": 3.078185276145123
    },
    {
        "question": "744,868,252 ÷ 18,038=？",
        "answer": 4.615891081448118
    },
    {
        "question": "2,269,758 ÷ 2,376=？",
        "answer": 2.980133119180343
    },
    {
        "question": "991 × 822=？",
        "answer": 5.910945472025325
    },
    {
        "question": "301,458,045 ÷ 3,868=？",
        "answer": 4.891740412946273
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 196,833=？",
        "answer": 6.37327915780781
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,230,853=？",
        "answer": 6.567327443231036
    },
    {
        "question": "740,907 ÷ 38,874=？",
        "answer": 1.2801044676347226
    },
    {
        "question": "8,997,622 ÷ 752,491=？",
        "answer": 1.0776264340086614
    },
    {
        "question": "2,344 × 196,220=？",
        "answer": 8.662700878723124
    },
    {
        "question": "1,352,252 ÷ 12,541=？",
        "answer": 2.032725464594627
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 935,787=？",
        "answer": 5.971177007657315
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,326,385=？",
        "answer": 6.122669601826476
    },
    {
        "question": "11,534 ÷ 407=？",
        "answer": 1.4523855378496584
    },
    {
        "question": "915,554,117 ÷ 511=？",
        "answer": 6.253263119742608
    },
    {
        "question": "592,680,743 ÷ 3,899,281=？",
        "answer": 2.1818362830924887
    },
    {
        "question": "879 × 168,324=？",
        "answer": 8.170134918111144
    },
    {
        "question": "9,986 ÷ 693=？",
        "answer": 1.1586583271072841
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 788=？",
        "answer": 4.674677467873199
    },
    {
        "question": "17,098 ÷ 9,785=？",
        "answer": 0.24238448275120736
    },
    {
        "question": "75,314,287 ÷ 5,563=？",
        "answer": 4.131568309044849
    },
    {
        "question": "9,207,114 ÷ 651=？",
        "answer": 4.150542531933617
    },
    {
        "question": "37,377,095 ÷ 389,420=？",
        "answer": 1.9821872919413022
    },
    {
        "question": "139 × 1,201,990=？",
        "answer": 8.222915654806934
    },
    {
        "question": "806 × 1,571=？",
        "answer": 6.102511226845064
    },
    {
        "question": "1,370 × 168,601=？",
        "answer": 8.363580713324097
    },
    {
        "question": "17,188 ÷ 674=？",
        "answer": 1.4065654484765457
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 80,515,961=？",
        "answer": 8.383003235548694
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,363,485=？",
        "answer": 6.979748404548553
    },
    {
        "question": "321 × 14,959=？",
        "answer": 6.681407594583198
    },
    {
        "question": "679 × 238,030=？",
        "answer": 8.208501470889034
    },
    {
        "question": "54,035 ÷ 528=？",
        "answer": 2.0100412332700586
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 833=？",
        "answer": 4.6366483450415865
    },
    {
        "question": "76,133 ÷ 1,561=？",
        "answer": 1.6881700403231112
    },
    {
        "question": "3,066,878 ÷ 2,612,334=？",
        "answer": 0.06966779726915578
    },
    {
        "question": "1,156 × 13,474=？",
        "answer": 7.1924543771011695
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,699=？",
        "answer": 3.973035440686933
    },
    {
        "question": "86,825 ÷ 235=？",
        "answer": 2.5675769297110635
    },
    {
        "question": "448,760,597 ÷ 20,872=？",
        "answer": 4.332450651013511
    },
    {
        "question": "43,170,170 ÷ 20,586=？",
        "answer": 3.321611790429945
    },
    {
        "question": "24,347,120 ÷ 687,862=？",
        "answer": 1.5489462781613
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 13,376,873=？",
        "answer": 8.029444590890023
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 21,225,242=？",
        "answer": 7.3268526505610065
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 14,972=？",
        "answer": 4.175279818442385
    },
    {
        "question": "1,576,470 ÷ 10,759=？",
        "answer": 2.165913803086303
    },
    {
        "question": "600,251,099 ÷ 130,539=？",
        "answer": 3.6625926824398576
    },
    {
        "question": "272,590,972 ÷ 890,649=？",
        "answer": 2.4858048836186053
    },
    {
        "question": "603,343 ÷ 10,403=？",
        "answer": 1.763405679915343
    },
    {
        "question": "3,271,331 × 282=？",
        "answer": 8.964973597476666
    },
    {
        "question": "70,744 ÷ 9,373=？",
        "answer": 0.8778109949808105
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 6,150,186=？",
        "answer": 8.320367167378993
    },
    {
        "question": "9,016,133 ÷ 316=？",
        "answer": 4.455333226890372
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 17,507,417=？",
        "answer": 8.674585840259843
    },
    {
        "question": "1,421 × 2,020=？",
        "answer": 6.457945447374094
    },
    {
        "question": "1,495 × 2,400=？",
        "answer": 6.554852434372054
    },
    {
        "question": "2,073 × 74,880=？",
        "answer": 8.190965137823909
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,880=？",
        "answer": 4.228400358703005
    },
    {
        "question": "1,268,915 ÷ 126,938=？",
        "answer": 0.9998408798533314
    },
    {
        "question": "18,259 × 383=？",
        "answer": 6.844675762589997
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 115,810,682=？",
        "answer": 8.06374861914703
    },
    {
        "question": "11,013,702 ÷ 20,840=？",
        "answer": 2.7230356068816355
    },
    {
        "question": "3,669,323 ÷ 7,381=？",
        "answer": 2.696470737811499
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 35,279=？",
        "answer": 6.1038187671183115
    },
    {
        "question": "615 × 227=？",
        "answer": 5.144900972968539
    },
    {
        "question": "1,217 × 266,435=？",
        "answer": 8.510881853189423
    },
    {
        "question": "151,171 × 5,964=？",
        "answer": 8.955006120734906
    },
    {
        "question": "5,703,195 ÷ 407,333=？",
        "answer": 1.1461686251681857
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 29,341,024=？",
        "answer": 8.768505262287437
    },
    {
        "question": "13,481,709 ÷ 111,255=？",
        "answer": 2.083425410676688
    },
    {
        "question": "49,280 ÷ 4,243=？",
        "answer": 1.0649976673897532
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,345,907=？",
        "answer": 6.970621455097478
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 488,076=？",
        "answer": 6.466638703146032
    },
    {
        "question": "51,618,250 ÷ 249,423=？",
        "answer": 2.315866778174345
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 21,743=？",
        "answer": 5.8687983828991825
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 773=？",
        "answer": 2.888179493918325
    },
    {
        "question": "173 × 49,188=？",
        "answer": 6.929905267492922
    },
    {
        "question": "1,705 × 56,815=？",
        "answer": 7.986187394342381
    },
    {
        "question": "83,763,635 ÷ 393=？",
        "answer": 5.32866296531288
    },
    {
        "question": "85,032 ÷ 245=？",
        "answer": 2.540416309680251
    },
    {
        "question": "191,528 ÷ 135,034=？",
        "answer": 0.15178914104593919
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 348,951=？",
        "answer": 6.584157132393475
    },
    {
        "question": "918,999,730 ÷ 115,904=？",
        "answer": 3.899216959493468
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 109,052=？",
        "answer": 5.037633634894076
    },
    {
        "question": "190 × 200,036=？",
        "answer": 7.579861762588826
    },
    {
        "question": "42,578,060 ÷ 817=？",
        "answer": 4.716963813099506
    },
    {
        "question": "2,791,033 ÷ 184,634=？",
        "answer": 1.1794532928768717
    },
    {
        "question": "191,861,890 ÷ 54,715,010=？",
        "answer": 0.5448822353866729
    },
    {
        "question": "1,748 × 859=？",
        "answer": 6.176534592129626
    },
    {
        "question": "372 × 843,927=？",
        "answer": 8.496847821497694
    },
    {
        "question": "2,736,375 ÷ 422,057=？",
        "answer": 0.811804506350961
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 149,052=？",
        "answer": 6.018435847844405
    },
    {
        "question": "74,384,573 ÷ 211=？",
        "answer": 5.547200419015879
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 2,189,920=？",
        "answer": 7.702156085929331
    },
    {
        "question": "8,602,293 ÷ 256=？",
        "answer": 4.52637426552609
    },
    {
        "question": "7,246,472 ÷ 322=？",
        "answer": 4.352270746757777
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 100,483,826=？",
        "answer": 8.780247413192507
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 859,209=？",
        "answer": 5.934098817505697
    },
    {
        "question": "247,079,829 ÷ 12,000=？",
        "answer": 4.313656046049867
    },
    {
        "question": "203,027,703 ÷ 2,928,267=？",
        "answer": 1.8409446279064843
    },
    {
        "question": "1,763,505 × 216=？",
        "answer": 8.580830446495144
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 1,362,236=？",
        "answer": 8.037342340250792
    },
    {
        "question": "60 × 7,382,777=？",
        "answer": 8.646371000949937
    },
    {
        "question": "1,720,658 ÷ 107,068=？",
        "answer": 1.206034867772171
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,353=？",
        "answer": 4.07059193151204
    },
    {
        "question": "11,432 × 2,297=？",
        "answer": 7.41928321097794
    },
    {
        "question": "46,762 ÷ 3,053=？",
        "answer": 1.1851662732636143
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 6,780=？",
        "answer": 4.433289685195025
    },
    {
        "question": "565 × 4,113=？",
        "answer": 6.366207157328613
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 6,290,708=？",
        "answer": 7.57685077709911
    },
    {
        "question": "178,942,777 ÷ 24,043,000=？",
        "answer": 0.8717255164120935
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 313,097,419=？",
        "answer": 8.796709483214855
    },
    {
        "question": "40,915,443 ÷ 8,797=？",
        "answer": 3.6675526657633535
    },
    {
        "question": "562,358,042 ÷ 129,047,284=？",
        "answer": 0.639264041573035
    },
    {
        "question": "513,709 × 782=？",
        "answer": 8.603923927536565
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 115,886,353=？",
        "answer": 8.064032295620564
    },
    {
        "question": "35,663 ÷ 7,563=？",
        "answer": 0.673523773178067
    },
    {
        "question": "21,375 × 8,012=？",
        "answer": 8.23364706402175
    },
    {
        "question": "166,557 × 820=？",
        "answer": 8.135376742172781
    },
    {
        "question": "38,338,010 ÷ 262=？",
        "answer": 5.165328275009239
    },
    {
        "question": "2,198 × 12,920=？",
        "answer": 7.453290201746537
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 51,853,534=？",
        "answer": 8.66902086986346
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 350=？",
        "answer": 3.975431808509263
    },
    {
        "question": "541 × 669=？",
        "answer": 5.5586233828743925
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 3,230,009=？",
        "answer": 7.208173736773899
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 4,931,343=？",
        "answer": 8.295025202300918
    },
    {
        "question": "3,320,167 ÷ 153,507=？",
        "answer": 1.3350317443685855
    },
    {
        "question": "3,039,999 ÷ 8,171=？",
        "answer": 2.570598230249891
    },
    {
        "question": "150 × 497=？",
        "answer": 4.872447647789014
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 26,524=？",
        "answer": 4.724669014903952
    },
    {
        "question": "3,900,708 ÷ 337,583=？",
        "answer": 1.0627628727143006
    },
    {
        "question": "6,355,497 ÷ 223,293=？",
        "answer": 1.4542744094447244
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 168,243,614=？",
        "answer": 8.225938588752207
    },
    {
        "question": "1,046,722 ÷ 413,194=？",
        "answer": 0.4036773457711127
    },
    {
        "question": "233,666 ÷ 3,666=？",
        "answer": 1.8044030635477557
    },
    {
        "question": "911,700,138 ÷ 1,740=？",
        "answer": 5.719302772254237
    },
    {
        "question": "23,280,067 ÷ 1,190,046=？",
        "answer": 1.2914204769565658
    },
    {
        "question": "356,321 × 1,332=？",
        "answer": 8.676345643355274
    },
    {
        "question": "229,330,840 ÷ 1,429,941=？",
        "answer": 2.205144343148428
    },
    {
        "question": "10,419,082 ÷ 7,269=？",
        "answer": 3.1563547871603355
    },
    {
        "question": "30,141 ÷ 432=？",
        "answer": 1.8436739101642796
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 2,137=？",
        "answer": 4.9830170359394135
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 32,972=？",
        "answer": 6.363243331185922
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 21,427=？",
        "answer": 4.330961369611591
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 15,033=？",
        "answer": 5.432318162565445
    },
    {
        "question": "984,819,096 ÷ 212,441,675=？",
        "answer": 0.6661167441698355
    },
    {
        "question": "8,829 × 608=？",
        "answer": 6.7298150960920085
    },
    {
        "question": "82,136,126 ÷ 1,353,228=？",
        "answer": 1.783163239927697
    },
    {
        "question": "26,464,133 ÷ 17,491=？",
        "answer": 3.1798430307131675
    },
    {
        "question": "14,480 × 1,361=？",
        "answer": 7.294626687064463
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 385=？",
        "answer": 4.293030905606437
    },
    {
        "question": "601,580,756 ÷ 1,216=？",
        "answer": 5.6943603601989246
    },
    {
        "question": "17,317 × 9,326=？",
        "answer": 8.20816806806683
    },
    {
        "question": "1,959 × 324,576=？",
        "answer": 8.803350839800073
    },
    {
        "question": "482 ÷ 238=？",
        "answer": 0.3064700811823376
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 559=？",
        "answer": 3.0484418035504044
    },
    {
        "question": "224,184,928 ÷ 5,105,699=？",
        "answer": 1.6425512035874583
    },
    {
        "question": "7,784 × 55,356=？",
        "answer": 8.634367527916186
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 1,624=？",
        "answer": 4.465858530008463
    },
    {
        "question": "1,266,810 ÷ 1,026,607=？",
        "answer": 0.0913072617604383
    },
    {
        "question": "8,431 × 558=？",
        "answer": 6.672513288239079
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 628,164,513=？",
        "answer": 8.798073398086679
    },
    {
        "question": "77,195 ÷ 2,318=？",
        "answer": 1.5224757399162903
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 441,541=？",
        "answer": 6.5480610238908685
    },
    {
        "question": "546,635 × 565=？",
        "answer": 8.489745883116498
    },
    {
        "question": "132,025,131 ÷ 41,384=？",
        "answer": 3.5038241416820504
    },
    {
        "question": "768,353,708 ÷ 206=？",
        "answer": 6.57169397110711
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 26,654=？",
        "answer": 5.124732397720029
    },
    {
        "question": "353,297 ÷ 1,384=？",
        "answer": 2.4070038595445697
    },
    {
        "question": "8,717,971 ÷ 1,753,694=？",
        "answer": 0.696461603911843
    },
    {
        "question": "1,502,607 × 282=？",
        "answer": 8.627094516019088
    },
    {
        "question": "124,265 ÷ 4,881=？",
        "answer": 1.4058400165016518
    },
    {
        "question": "723,618 ÷ 30,256=？",
        "answer": 1.378697849897765
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 43,793=？",
        "answer": 5.340374701499331
    },
    {
        "question": "164,226,193 ÷ 788,792=？",
        "answer": 2.318479928126042
    },
    {
        "question": "98,334,712 ÷ 37,971,372=？",
        "answer": 0.4132505606098504
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,148=？",
        "answer": 3.662001879389917
    },
    {
        "question": "817,721 × 514=？",
        "answer": 8.623568270064014
    },
    {
        "question": "20,846 × 16,365=？",
        "answer": 8.532938743074437
    },
    {
        "question": "20,943 ÷ 641=？",
        "answer": 1.5141808632072373
    },
    {
        "question": "15,312,706 ÷ 2,529=？",
        "answer": 3.7821031149151576
    },
    {
        "question": "2,210,972 ÷ 1,485,850=？",
        "answer": 0.17260827405570806
    },
    {
        "question": "826,410,929 ÷ 4,257,117=？",
        "answer": 2.2880804657194487
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 2,511=？",
        "answer": 4.302936699704866
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 6,129=？",
        "answer": 4.486359625688129
    },
    {
        "question": "332,805,475 ÷ 2,334=？",
        "answer": 5.15408961056898
    },
    {
        "question": "7,615,230 ÷ 78,426=？",
        "answer": 1.9872229596681146
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 28,128=？",
        "answer": 5.227290103777322
    },
    {
        "question": "198 × 3,880,924=？",
        "answer": 8.885600328311053
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 106,656=？",
        "answer": 5.027985291980436
    },
    {
        "question": "118 × 67,019=？",
        "answer": 6.898079950684191
    },
    {
        "question": "94,036,595 ÷ 277=？",
        "answer": 5.530817126170639
    },
    {
        "question": "306,536,549 ÷ 1,299,179=？",
        "answer": 2.3728132717955996
    },
    {
        "question": "633 ÷ 511=？",
        "answer": 0.0929828098826424
    },
    {
        "question": "5,473 × 20,724=？",
        "answer": 8.054699031757588
    },
    {
        "question": "12,063,807 ÷ 85,236=？",
        "answer": 2.150861319902713
    },
    {
        "question": "19,490 × 1,268=？",
        "answer": 7.392931092663336
    },
    {
        "question": "201 × 454,158=？",
        "answer": 7.960403026116099
    },
    {
        "question": "10,056,955 ÷ 254=？",
        "answer": 4.597632790255395
    },
    {
        "question": "2,818,226 ÷ 1,072=？",
        "answer": 3.4197810318826427
    },
    {
        "question": "347 × 304=？",
        "answer": 5.023203058399628
    },
    {
        "question": "398 × 2,617=？",
        "answer": 6.017686794713569
    },
    {
        "question": "840,851 ÷ 43,280=？",
        "answer": 1.2884317929136602
    },
    {
        "question": "513 × 4,960=？",
        "answer": 6.405599041602014
    },
    {
        "question": "98,169,195 ÷ 333,765=？",
        "answer": 2.468534436951549
    },
    {
        "question": "65,825,862 ÷ 31,082,238=？",
        "answer": 0.32588427341046383
    },
    {
        "question": "3,705 ÷ 254=？",
        "answer": 1.1639544956954089
    },
    {
        "question": "3,309,741 ÷ 3,096=？",
        "answer": 3.0289930578761073
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,597,308=？",
        "answer": 6.805448658125957
    },
    {
        "question": "5,033 ÷ 3,069=？",
        "answer": 0.21483004196531685
    },
    {
        "question": "1,841 × 151,338=？",
        "answer": 8.445001778775822
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 103,741,586=？",
        "answer": 8.015952883196636
    },
    {
        "question": "1,326,961 ÷ 5,216=？",
        "answer": 2.4055205762116403
    },
    {
        "question": "582 × 1,152=？",
        "answer": 5.826375463737082
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 7,534,774=？",
        "answer": 7.354191485222354
    },
    {
        "question": "633,084 ÷ 155,034=？",
        "answer": 0.611034385369557
    },
    {
        "question": "129 × 1,565=？",
        "answer": 5.305104052181716
    },
    {
        "question": "20,154 × 10,434=？",
        "answer": 8.322812086611664
    },
    {
        "question": "983 ÷ 851=？",
        "answer": 0.06262395774754773
    },
    {
        "question": "16,801,414 ÷ 1,863=？",
        "answer": 3.955132978410323
    },
    {
        "question": "18,598,281 ÷ 93,573=？",
        "answer": 2.298322251735847
    },
    {
        "question": "89,111,365 ÷ 1,690,437=？",
        "answer": 1.7219341062906153
    },
    {
        "question": "79,833,569 ÷ 308,636=？",
        "answer": 2.4127389632882563
    },
    {
        "question": "1,232 × 295,660=？",
        "answer": 8.561403280395302
    },
    {
        "question": "2,576 ÷ 929=？",
        "answer": 0.4429301446941327
    },
    {
        "question": "73,105 × 7,934=？",
        "answer": 8.763439277585036
    },
    {
        "question": "3,884 ÷ 1,018=？",
        "answer": 0.5815314432352273
    },
    {
        "question": "191 × 541=？",
        "answer": 5.014230632354297
    },
    {
        "question": "20,813,184 ÷ 1,173=？",
        "answer": 4.24904051152979
    },
    {
        "question": "337,991,879 ÷ 2,472=？",
        "answer": 5.1358577991039
    },
    {
        "question": "412 × 143,329=？",
        "answer": 7.771231286861407
    },
    {
        "question": "173,840,687 ÷ 226,614=？",
        "answer": 2.8848646929404675
    },
    {
        "question": "5,544 × 2,954=？",
        "answer": 7.214233712579681
    },
    {
        "question": "928,954,440 ÷ 1,579=？",
        "answer": 5.769612284801499
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 48,610=？",
        "answer": 6.457577632716687
    },
    {
        "question": "1,376,481 ÷ 2,762=？",
        "answer": 2.6975465468248365
    },
    {
        "question": "20,866,491 ÷ 2,427=？",
        "answer": 3.9343796460221654
    },
    {
        "question": "594,701,503 ÷ 31,280=？",
        "answer": 4.279032291713252
    },
    {
        "question": "184,531,675 ÷ 12,929,336=？",
        "answer": 1.1544947020750003
    },
    {
        "question": "238,144,463 ÷ 21,578,270=？",
        "answer": 1.0428238654175017
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 1,239=？",
        "answer": 4.134463991534289
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,672=？",
        "answer": 3.82529626443096
    },
    {
        "question": "16,148 × 5,840=？",
        "answer": 7.974531587850676
    },
    {
        "question": "9,681,619 ÷ 5,541,164=？",
        "answer": 0.24234698386375492
    },
    {
        "question": "492,715,856 ÷ 6,786,757=？",
        "answer": 1.860934238906781
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 214,621,123=？",
        "answer": 8.632702458638246
    },
    {
        "question": "4,376 × 7,001=？",
        "answer": 7.48623739097732
    },
    {
        "question": "1,331 ÷ 825=？",
        "answer": 0.20772410692475002
    },
    {
        "question": "6,668,453 ÷ 4,524,055=？",
        "answer": 0.1684972184573567
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 302,477=？",
        "answer": 6.258843607379267
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 4,387,010=？",
        "answer": 7.818259883417287
    },
    {
        "question": "556,092,645 ÷ 248,207,749=？",
        "answer": 0.35033181507564953
    },
    {
        "question": "611,228 ÷ 195,321=？",
        "answer": 0.49545430169277876
    },
    {
        "question": "53,366,360 ÷ 908=？",
        "answer": 4.769181733037882
    },
    {
        "question": "34,488,217 ÷ 556,871=？",
        "answer": 1.791916140578738
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 5,708,697=？",
        "answer": 7.659626979600977
    },
    {
        "question": "60,927,427 ÷ 1,166,102=？",
        "answer": 1.7180762977910882
    },
    {
        "question": "1,089,791 × 794=？",
        "answer": 8.937163719404548
    },
    {
        "question": "174,581 × 672=？",
        "answer": 8.069366249856602
    },
    {
        "question": "253 × 8,410=？",
        "answer": 6.32791651697373
    },
    {
        "question": "2,324 × 1,588=？",
        "answer": 6.567086621809371
    },
    {
        "question": "9,581 × 11,592=？",
        "answer": 8.045569212629006
    },
    {
        "question": "188,156,249 ÷ 5,537=？",
        "answer": 4.53124412306715
    },
    {
        "question": "199 × 3,053,163=？",
        "answer": 8.783603067118744
    },
    {
        "question": "78,888,753 ÷ 60,186=？",
        "answer": 3.117519610396324
    },
    {
        "question": "302 × 242=？",
        "answer": 4.863822308937582
    },
    {
        "question": "309,725 ÷ 2,204=？",
        "answer": 2.147764671437453
    },
    {
        "question": "831,716,110 ÷ 50,099,703=？",
        "answer": 1.2201399623713747
    },
    {
        "question": "105 × 1,898,632=？",
        "answer": 8.299630095372605
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 63,713=？",
        "answer": 5.980319313875148
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 243=？",
        "answer": 2.6866362692622934
    },
    {
        "question": "375 × 669=？",
        "answer": 5.399457385495542
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 2,399=？",
        "answer": 4.225128287982088
    },
    {
        "question": "738,009,086 ÷ 339,485,972=？",
        "answer": 0.3372398752962677
    },
    {
        "question": "5,367 ÷ 1,452=？",
        "answer": 0.5677649789229605
    },
    {
        "question": "2,647,205 ÷ 367,000=？",
        "answer": 0.8581215101892052
    },
    {
        "question": "293 × 147,023=？",
        "answer": 7.634252900624262
    },
    {
        "question": "118,783,280 ÷ 42,399=？",
        "answer": 3.4473996997388867
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 38,131=？",
        "answer": 5.695221547268078
    },
    {
        "question": "1,075 × 841,145=？",
        "answer": 8.956279331954196
    },
    {
        "question": "26,402,364 ÷ 1,024,702=？",
        "answer": 1.4110452303678944
    },
    {
        "question": "189,953,029 ÷ 8,843=？",
        "answer": 4.332046598211207
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 36,994=？",
        "answer": 6.59751506990916
    },
    {
        "question": "4,984 × 66,961=？",
        "answer": 8.523399964467245
    },
    {
        "question": "74,664 ÷ 13,418=？",
        "answer": 0.7454234652804589
    },
    {
        "question": "8,462 ÷ 5,048=？",
        "answer": 0.22435367475919799
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 10,167=？",
        "answer": 5.6199766802767765
    },
    {
        "question": "356 × 3,879=？",
        "answer": 6.140169777572932
    },
    {
        "question": "384,720 ÷ 535=？",
        "answer": 2.8567909820445223
    },
    {
        "question": "650,870 ÷ 1,290=？",
        "answer": 2.702904544135988
    },
    {
        "question": "352,540 ÷ 478=？",
        "answer": 2.867780503562725
    },
    {
        "question": "33,183,692 ÷ 1,691=？",
        "answer": 4.292781096152876
    },
    {
        "question": "163,145 ÷ 112,537=？",
        "answer": 0.1612784346577071
    },
    {
        "question": "30,244,989 ÷ 11,052=？",
        "answer": 3.4372125546474934
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 119,766=？",
        "answer": 6.308782466408818
    },
    {
        "question": "3,417 ÷ 343=？",
        "answer": 0.9983508587559923
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,596=？",
        "answer": 3.4143046881283317
    },
    {
        "question": "724 × 1,214=？",
        "answer": 5.943957252936386
    },
    {
        "question": "127 × 799=？",
        "answer": 5.006350500269948
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,757=？",
        "answer": 3.875871190727366
    },
    {
        "question": "241,538 ÷ 1,565=？",
        "answer": 2.1884711240210506
    },
    {
        "question": "7,591,579 ÷ 6,123,208=？",
        "answer": 0.09335310348385796
    },
    {
        "question": "13,856,983 ÷ 40,352=？",
        "answer": 2.535803619273141
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 184,907=？",
        "answer": 6.346134598547138
    },
    {
        "question": "1,134 × 34,079=？",
        "answer": 7.587099897081899
    },
    {
        "question": "1,611 × 235=？",
        "answer": 5.578163402690954
    },
    {
        "question": "26,363,942 ÷ 12,234=？",
        "answer": 3.333441871370619
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,197,259=？",
        "answer": 6.819002506743121
    },
    {
        "question": "534,155,312 ÷ 343,425,856=？",
        "answer": 0.191834562254371
    },
    {
        "question": "4,018,326 ÷ 124,248=？",
        "answer": 1.509755760725705
    },
    {
        "question": "9,137 ÷ 439=？",
        "answer": 1.3183391046696484
    },
    {
        "question": "1,396 × 450=？",
        "answer": 5.798097932062486
    },
    {
        "question": "764 × 1,196=？",
        "answer": 5.960824538228082
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,333,044=？",
        "answer": 6.8652842908731335
    },
    {
        "question": "357,709 ÷ 2,934=？",
        "answer": 2.086069757678792
    },
    {
        "question": "442,292 ÷ 14,263=？",
        "answer": 1.491498201889565
    },
    {
        "question": "19,504,450 ÷ 158,071=？",
        "answer": 2.091281507517883
    },
    {
        "question": "334,450,501 ÷ 4,026=？",
        "answer": 4.919458080300742
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 681=？",
        "answer": 2.833147111912785
    },
    {
        "question": "4,477,392 ÷ 677,622=？",
        "answer": 0.820037621385997
    },
    {
        "question": "3,696 × 3,202=？",
        "answer": 7.07315329013135
    },
    {
        "question": "54,284 ÷ 23,446=？",
        "answer": 0.36460308117336476
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,969=？",
        "answer": 3.7759015788916743
    },
    {
        "question": "266,364,734 ÷ 960=？",
        "answer": 5.44320549180163
    },
    {
        "question": "5,136,802 ÷ 113,480=？",
        "answer": 1.6557734988760413
    },
    {
        "question": "256,903 ÷ 13,613=？",
        "answer": 1.2758153312775382
    },
    {
        "question": "3,807 × 154,056=？",
        "answer": 8.76826149421025
    },
    {
        "question": "3,062,173 ÷ 775=？",
        "answer": 3.5967280203755205
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,020,549=？",
        "answer": 6.700751210099996
    },
    {
        "question": "942,248,687 ÷ 622,577=？",
        "answer": 3.1799724685379367
    },
    {
        "question": "426 × 77,078=？",
        "answer": 7.516340036271491
    },
    {
        "question": "35,525,446 ÷ 9,785,920=？",
        "answer": 0.5599378778558906
    },
    {
        "question": "3,031 × 6,858=？",
        "answer": 7.317783417146548
    },
    {
        "question": "152 × 1,228,530=？",
        "answer": 8.271229354113235
    },
    {
        "question": "119,229 ÷ 4,340=？",
        "answer": 1.4388921719333991
    },
    {
        "question": "1,450 ÷ 1,144=？",
        "answer": 0.1029419777779695
    },
    {
        "question": "873,783,369 ÷ 12,962,881=？",
        "answer": 1.8287022401849666
    },
    {
        "question": "5,920 × 17,097=？",
        "answer": 8.005241618416413
    },
    {
        "question": "132,684,234 ÷ 2,192=？",
        "answer": 4.781978771744019
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 14,787=？",
        "answer": 5.448633673827215
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,626=？",
        "answer": 3.882296800937652
    },
    {
        "question": "962,759,657 ÷ 299,334=？",
        "answer": 3.5073618343302733
    },
    {
        "question": "337,977 ÷ 257=？",
        "answer": 3.1189540233577393
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 534=？",
        "answer": 2.727541257028556
    },
    {
        "question": "18,095 ÷ 4,443=？",
        "answer": 0.6098822742033473
    },
    {
        "question": "783,733,313 ÷ 78,577=？",
        "answer": 3.998872863262372
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 3,579=？",
        "answer": 5.324613710032149
    },
    {
        "question": "10,351,925 ÷ 908,426=？",
        "answer": 1.0567315612207744
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 27,617=？",
        "answer": 5.783599180763282
    },
    {
        "question": "51,707 × 233=？",
        "answer": 7.0809052621003294
    },
    {
        "question": "102 × 1,795,762=？",
        "answer": 8.262848949006399
    },
    {
        "question": "305,042 ÷ 69,616=？",
        "answer": 0.6416505737668687
    },
    {
        "question": "231,754,279 ÷ 526,327=？",
        "answer": 2.643772112074734
    },
    {
        "question": "83,108,785 ÷ 384,324=？",
        "answer": 2.334949427401647
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 25,719,411=？",
        "answer": 8.313351005583986
    },
    {
        "question": "311 × 414=？",
        "answer": 5.109760730147737
    },
    {
        "question": "79,088,162 ÷ 797,910=？",
        "answer": 1.9961575746956222
    },
    {
        "question": "2,775 ÷ 2,021=？",
        "answer": 0.13769667394339102
    },
    {
        "question": "834,174 ÷ 970=？",
        "answer": 2.934484915122134
    },
    {
        "question": "15,675,640 ÷ 1,461=？",
        "answer": 4.0305750651661825
    },
    {
        "question": "5,692,517 ÷ 800=？",
        "answer": 3.852214349264085
    },
    {
        "question": "296,502,228 ÷ 108,575,257=？",
        "answer": 0.4362970951017776
    },
    {
        "question": "60,999,003 ÷ 14,514,465=？",
        "answer": 0.6235217042665778
    },
    {
        "question": "294,001,324 ÷ 1,765=？",
        "answer": 5.221604576486273
    },
    {
        "question": "188,521 ÷ 79,882=？",
        "answer": 0.37291080505147084
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 8,647=？",
        "answer": 4.237895454639604
    },
    {
        "question": "15,693,730 ÷ 537=？",
        "answer": 4.465751890895384
    },
    {
        "question": "524 × 186,954=？",
        "answer": 7.9910660485806435
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,707=？",
        "answer": 4.347173836413207
    },
    {
        "question": "8,784,858 ÷ 164,092=？",
        "answer": 1.7286473375249676
    },
    {
        "question": "12,721,158 ÷ 28,532=？",
        "answer": 2.649194431350495
    },
    {
        "question": "272,794,454 ÷ 1,402=？",
        "answer": 5.289087523095443
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 137,089=？",
        "answer": 6.040092595457909
    },
    {
        "question": "3,695 × 708=？",
        "answer": 6.417647700420614
    },
    {
        "question": "88,975 ÷ 39,556=？",
        "answer": 0.3520556284564673
    },
    {
        "question": "867 × 17,512=？",
        "answer": 7.181354846036085
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 5,068,757=？",
        "answer": 8.490231306331083
    },
    {
        "question": "366,636,864 ÷ 842=？",
        "answer": 5.638924038048776
    },
    {
        "question": "46,177 ÷ 557=？",
        "answer": 1.9185705193371108
    },
    {
        "question": "156,947,560 ÷ 350=？",
        "answer": 5.651686523938268
    },
    {
        "question": "702,971 ÷ 314=？",
        "answer": 3.3500077611574826
    },
    {
        "question": "382 × 534=？",
        "answer": 5.309604619940266
    },
    {
        "question": "658,044 × 711=？",
        "answer": 8.670124534341186
    },
    {
        "question": "124 × 819=？",
        "answer": 5.006705586922654
    },
    {
        "question": "257,616,788 ÷ 5,933,644=？",
        "answer": 1.6376526746297755
    },
    {
        "question": "6,210 ÷ 1,877=？",
        "answer": 0.5196273275552339
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 142,553,640=？",
        "answer": 8.153978311170075
    },
    {
        "question": "7,411 × 32,370=？",
        "answer": 8.380019512669339
    },
    {
        "question": "107,108,332 ÷ 87,515,707=？",
        "answer": 0.08773725047949443
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 6,273=？",
        "answer": 5.420724577935235
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 6,606=？",
        "answer": 4.996029828411077
    },
    {
        "question": "13,694 × 432=？",
        "answer": 6.772014070346212
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 439=？",
        "answer": 3.4875625602563782
    },
    {
        "question": "3,104 × 773=？",
        "answer": 6.3801012065044755
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 46,400,897=？",
        "answer": 8.143647630929388
    },
    {
        "question": "7,529 ÷ 270=？",
        "answer": 1.4453735329816773
    },
    {
        "question": "401,128 × 237=？",
        "answer": 7.978031324174926
    },
    {
        "question": "856,994,077 ÷ 2,413,511=？",
        "answer": 2.550328537832766
    },
    {
        "question": "53,234,424 ÷ 623=？",
        "answer": 4.931704512674415
    },
    {
        "question": "160 × 204=？",
        "answer": 4.513750150081823
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 24,466=？",
        "answer": 5.990622962726038
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 139,664=？",
        "answer": 5.145084476148725
    },
    {
        "question": "254,274 ÷ 6,822=？",
        "answer": 1.571390239937966
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 51,169=？",
        "answer": 5.663249439041389
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 516=？",
        "answer": 3.5577477416414682
    },
    {
        "question": "1,161 ÷ 364=？",
        "answer": 0.5037308360895179
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 708=？",
        "answer": 3.3271545124094315
    },
    {
        "question": "8,768,639 ÷ 626=？",
        "answer": 4.146357857571972
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 315,601,789=？",
        "answer": 8.499139456358124
    },
    {
        "question": "178 × 308=？",
        "answer": 4.738970718809338
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 903,172=？",
        "answer": 6.557830456522568
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 166,009,963=？",
        "answer": 8.521164148439476
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 6,409=？",
        "answer": 4.283911526303729
    },
    {
        "question": "340,246,375 ÷ 4,641,494=？",
        "answer": 1.8651357135245443
    },
    {
        "question": "4,167,095 ÷ 1,157,822=？",
        "answer": 0.556191604043789
    },
    {
        "question": "915,981,331 ÷ 63,254,846=？",
        "answer": 1.160792819479728
    },
    {
        "question": "147,020 ÷ 1,352=？",
        "answer": 2.0363997268079657
    },
    {
        "question": "61,749,339 ÷ 3,245,769=？",
        "answer": 1.2793147049853895
    },
    {
        "question": "21,589 × 843=？",
        "answer": 7.260060100954342
    },
    {
        "question": "67 × 4,972=？",
        "answer": 5.522605922670434
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,395=？",
        "answer": 3.9813655090785445
    },
    {
        "question": "889 ÷ 673=？",
        "answer": 0.12088669674623684
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 617=？",
        "answer": 4.112504458767161
    },
    {
        "question": "875 × 214=？",
        "answer": 5.272421826371504
    },
    {
        "question": "293,648,865 ÷ 531=？",
        "answer": 5.742733805482865
    },
    {
        "question": "420,926 × 386=？",
        "answer": 8.210793057000409
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 12,759=？",
        "answer": 6.035235563147978
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 2,897,705=？",
        "answer": 8.030255894231347
    },
    {
        "question": "390,203,510 ÷ 8,092=？",
        "answer": 4.68323529758909
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 3,048=？",
        "answer": 5.513398740352772
    },
    {
        "question": "20,188 × 5,407=？",
        "answer": 8.038049665637272
    },
    {
        "question": "17,823 × 32,591=？",
        "answer": 8.764078493361403
    },
    {
        "question": "2,563 × 1,200=？",
        "answer": 6.4879298522318685
    },
    {
        "question": "5,175,779 ÷ 2,245=？",
        "answer": 3.362759378826408
    },
    {
        "question": "183 × 54,544=？",
        "answer": 6.999198073615245
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 260,705=？",
        "answer": 5.416149360480129
    },
    {
        "question": "212,618 ÷ 37,978=？",
        "answer": 0.7480679384666808
    },
    {
        "question": "649,050 × 945=？",
        "answer": 8.78770996276367
    },
    {
        "question": "3,292 × 158,953=？",
        "answer": 8.718728555526795
    },
    {
        "question": "339,258,325 ÷ 11,995,737=？",
        "answer": 1.4515035780160706
    },
    {
        "question": "70,376,093 ÷ 8,291,530=？",
        "answer": 0.9287904764523767
    },
    {
        "question": "938,370,236 ÷ 15,884=？",
        "answer": 4.771414345624024
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 5,149=？",
        "answer": 5.073450727844827
    },
    {
        "question": "51,993 ÷ 564=？",
        "answer": 1.9646657729973953
    },
    {
        "question": "29,867,072 ÷ 547,623=？",
        "answer": 1.7367109688174098
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 231=？",
        "answer": 4.0796153235269434
    },
    {
        "question": "3,793,438 ÷ 200=？",
        "answer": 4.278002994679451
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 46,612=？",
        "answer": 5.270557729109917
    },
    {
        "question": "722 × 243=？",
        "answer": 5.244143471167951
    },
    {
        "question": "131 × 5,496,257=？",
        "answer": 8.85733832739873
    },
    {
        "question": "33,299 × 422=？",
        "answer": 7.147743642395833
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,136=？",
        "answer": 3.7878853509409245
    },
    {
        "question": "542,862,846 ÷ 247,676=？",
        "answer": 3.3408061940385934
    },
    {
        "question": "91,146,290 ÷ 1,566,816=？",
        "answer": 1.7647209980930927
    },
    {
        "question": "43,166,800 ÷ 415=？",
        "answer": 5.017101758433581
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 231,053=？",
        "answer": 5.363711611785637
    },
    {
        "question": "2,409 ÷ 457=？",
        "answer": 0.7219205999284932
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 108,384=？",
        "answer": 5.034965174964536
    },
    {
        "question": "258 × 718,436=？",
        "answer": 8.268007792163717
    },
    {
        "question": "400,410 ÷ 5,603=？",
        "answer": 1.854084292719801
    },
    {
        "question": "52,088 ÷ 13,682=？",
        "answer": 0.5805880962503094
    },
    {
        "question": "98,082,950 ÷ 4,302,685=？",
        "answer": 1.3578539669610579
    },
    {
        "question": "611,529 ÷ 69,010=？",
        "answer": 0.9475050296185389
    },
    {
        "question": "397,302 ÷ 7,999=？",
        "answer": 1.6960850544908213
    },
    {
        "question": "941 × 829,265=？",
        "answer": 8.892282959341793
    },
    {
        "question": "143,957,833 ÷ 899,449=？",
        "answer": 2.204258757303966
    },
    {
        "question": "168,538,907 ÷ 4,168,827=？",
        "answer": 1.6066863001920428
    },
    {
        "question": "101,583,035 ÷ 5,068=？",
        "answer": 4.30198457790691
    },
    {
        "question": "2,206,713 ÷ 698,819=？",
        "answer": 0.49938114911021997
    },
    {
        "question": "133,532,524 ÷ 37,387=？",
        "answer": 3.5528664400273477
    },
    {
        "question": "460,267 ÷ 10,070=？",
        "answer": 1.6599803676215537
    },
    {
        "question": "326 × 1,116=？",
        "answer": 5.560881794669499
    },
    {
        "question": "29,281 × 369=？",
        "answer": 7.033612270753947
    },
    {
        "question": "267 × 459=？",
        "answer": 5.088323946901837
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 998=？",
        "answer": 4.850388890006446
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 521,600=？",
        "answer": 7.079065418741457
    },
    {
        "question": "850,388,055 ÷ 45,315,814=？",
        "answer": 1.2733673656738387
    },
    {
        "question": "2,086,265 × 269=？",
        "answer": 8.749121752227188
    },
    {
        "question": "1,103 × 221=？",
        "answer": 5.386967786125301
    },
    {
        "question": "384,612 × 1,636=？",
        "answer": 8.79880612955623
    },
    {
        "question": "161,734,488 ÷ 438,714=？",
        "answer": 2.5666211444399707
    },
    {
        "question": "400,839 ÷ 74,557=？",
        "answer": 0.7304815452976712
    },
    {
        "question": "48,455,383 ÷ 132,401=？",
        "answer": 2.5634507653998995
    },
    {
        "question": "12,334,542 ÷ 1,832,527=？",
        "answer": 0.8280726459733261
    },
    {
        "question": "4,808 × 34,353=？",
        "answer": 8.217929128383107
    },
    {
        "question": "1,516 × 1,443=？",
        "answer": 6.339965532389529
    },
    {
        "question": "985,541,194 ÷ 365,833=？",
        "answer": 3.43039190330767
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,577,682=？",
        "answer": 7.262705611374206
    },
    {
        "question": "3,377,014 ÷ 15,681=？",
        "answer": 2.3331591062651835
    },
    {
        "question": "16,021 ÷ 13,718=？",
        "answer": 0.06739882189789234
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 235=？",
        "answer": 2.3710678622717363
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 3,435,994=？",
        "answer": 8.328444086284593
    },
    {
        "question": "1,218 × 8,954=？",
        "answer": 7.0376643783442825
    },
    {
        "question": "562,006,465 ÷ 10,930,652=？",
        "answer": 1.711095243616296
    },
    {
        "question": "84,624 ÷ 252=？",
        "answer": 2.526093008893365
    },
    {
        "question": "3,350,174 ÷ 2,896=？",
        "answer": 3.0632688063109677
    },
    {
        "question": "134,907,540 ÷ 2,974=？",
        "answer": 4.656695258939516
    },
    {
        "question": "4,794,197 ÷ 1,786=？",
        "answer": 3.4288344212558926
    },
    {
        "question": "141 × 250,861=？",
        "answer": 7.54865226180851
    },
    {
        "question": "4,277 × 171,529=？",
        "answer": 8.86547680597817
    },
    {
        "question": "109,277 ÷ 16,306=？",
        "answer": 0.8261813257530906
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 1,774=？",
        "answer": 5.094051655509965
    },
    {
        "question": "43,891,361 ÷ 397,723=？",
        "answer": 2.0427983412106205
    },
    {
        "question": "143,078 ÷ 2,865=？",
        "answer": 1.6984482344785656
    },
    {
        "question": "1,885,258 ÷ 937=？",
        "answer": 3.303631201483755
    },
    {
        "question": "74 × 2,729,444=？",
        "answer": 8.305305908044883
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 637,284=？",
        "answer": 7.2356967791413815
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,261,788=？",
        "answer": 6.79995639714876
    },
    {
        "question": "7,803 × 1,995=？",
        "answer": 7.192204506938302
    },
    {
        "question": "15,448 ÷ 14,790=？",
        "answer": 0.01890408677444586
    },
    {
        "question": "353,319,776 ÷ 283=？",
        "answer": 6.096381510903788
    },
    {
        "question": "34,940 × 210=？",
        "answer": 6.865542195380831
    },
    {
        "question": "575 × 24,931=？",
        "answer": 7.156407543400859
    },
    {
        "question": "25,136,363 ÷ 3,290,640=？",
        "answer": 0.8830220669366804
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 1,789,820=？",
        "answer": 7.796877401063413
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 528,664=？",
        "answer": 7.740213076914664
    },
    {
        "question": "507 × 5,409=？",
        "answer": 6.4381249407754
    },
    {
        "question": "284,706,746 ÷ 5,637,511=？",
        "answer": 1.7033103553948317
    },
    {
        "question": "200,069 × 4,833=？",
        "answer": 8.985396596559111
    },
    {
        "question": "301,188,200 ÷ 595=？",
        "answer": 5.7043209872739755
    },
    {
        "question": "910,749,936 ÷ 1,311,092=？",
        "answer": 2.841765981968797
    },
    {
        "question": "247 × 1,924,250=？",
        "answer": 8.676958448491183
    },
    {
        "question": "183 × 3,699,741=？",
        "answer": 8.83062241211962
    },
    {
        "question": "554,205,827 ÷ 20,433,965=？",
        "answer": 1.4333184425339758
    },
    {
        "question": "45,614,643 ÷ 8,549=？",
        "answer": 3.7271889631547013
    },
    {
        "question": "2,783 ÷ 1,916=？",
        "answer": 0.16211770159151734
    },
    {
        "question": "415,352,138 ÷ 10,224=？",
        "answer": 4.608795609497253
    },
    {
        "question": "256 × 51,908=？",
        "answer": 7.123474261274174
    },
    {
        "question": "4,194 ÷ 417=？",
        "answer": 1.0024923711555676
    },
    {
        "question": "327,858 ÷ 37,974=？",
        "answer": 0.936199439209759
    },
    {
        "question": "261,743 × 1,018=？",
        "answer": 8.425622853826216
    },
    {
        "question": "781,869,672 ÷ 18,289=？",
        "answer": 4.630944407663088
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 646,200=？",
        "answer": 6.713456940673569
    },
    {
        "question": "1,067,133 ÷ 602,438=？",
        "answer": 0.2483061921643038
    },
    {
        "question": "1,280,980 ÷ 13,880=？",
        "answer": 1.965152883018946
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 1,768,742=？",
        "answer": 7.627875730275399
    },
    {
        "question": "1,030,794 ÷ 7,245=？",
        "answer": 2.1531334921569716
    },
    {
        "question": "1,384 × 112,975=？",
        "answer": 8.194118440123978
    },
    {
        "question": "146,209,720 ÷ 311=？",
        "answer": 5.672215856386002
    },
    {
        "question": "341,454,622 ÷ 659=？",
        "answer": 5.714447581199643
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 248=？",
        "answer": 3.9742352774430265
    },
    {
        "question": "1,342 × 70,148=？",
        "answer": 7.973767809139677
    },
    {
        "question": "24,421,624 ÷ 540,100=？",
        "answer": 1.6553003631953034
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 535,866=？",
        "answer": 6.507207452881973
    },
    {
        "question": "200 × 353=？",
        "answer": 4.848804701051804
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,201,505=？",
        "answer": 7.041689680490839
    },
    {
        "question": "471 × 1,729=？",
        "answer": 5.9108159004028185
    },
    {
        "question": "213,097,570 ÷ 147,870=？",
        "answer": 3.158698424509416
    },
    {
        "question": "1,544 × 44,767=？",
        "answer": 7.839605287700557
    },
    {
        "question": "42,512 ÷ 6,743=？",
        "answer": 0.7996583773895622
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 75,246=？",
        "answer": 5.177513413895309
    },
    {
        "question": "260,623 ÷ 235,647=？",
        "answer": 0.043750824421330596
    },
    {
        "question": "37,483 × 308=？",
        "answer": 7.062385059423371
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 7,591,245=？",
        "answer": 7.658464258464782
    },
    {
        "question": "206,788,882 ÷ 1,095,401=？",
        "answer": 2.27595405215195
    },
    {
        "question": "438,482,664 ÷ 7,112=？",
        "answer": 4.789960679664715
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 226,779=？",
        "answer": 6.935386432523848
    },
    {
        "question": "46,203 ÷ 45,145=？",
        "answer": 0.010060518221662743
    },
    {
        "question": "16,985,963 ÷ 10,101,609=？",
        "answer": 0.22569961934624178
    },
    {
        "question": "65,864 ÷ 13,456=？",
        "answer": 0.689732123949627
    },
    {
        "question": "451,288 × 582=？",
        "answer": 8.419376770190706
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 9,588=？",
        "answer": 5.911146951075909
    },
    {
        "question": "9,133 × 11,512=？",
        "answer": 8.021764238576457
    },
    {
        "question": "8,483 ÷ 313=？",
        "answer": 1.4330051294552153
    },
    {
        "question": "1,046,539 ÷ 49,874=？",
        "answer": 1.3218812163119318
    },
    {
        "question": "5,689 × 23,734=？",
        "answer": 8.13040687179683
    },
    {
        "question": "14,296 ÷ 3,912=？",
        "answer": 0.562815693382024
    },
    {
        "question": "1,442,621 ÷ 44,085=？",
        "answer": 1.5148614047261273
    },
    {
        "question": "87,654,505 ÷ 3,188,676=？",
        "answer": 1.4391638485432312
    },
    {
        "question": "139,620 ÷ 8,813=？",
        "answer": 1.199823863548254
    },
    {
        "question": "279,632 × 333=？",
        "answer": 7.969031102397585
    },
    {
        "question": "1,102 × 125,564=？",
        "answer": 8.141046736764043
    },
    {
        "question": "3,982 ÷ 302=？",
        "answer": 1.1200943127342402
    },
    {
        "question": "939 × 2,403=？",
        "answer": 6.353419363070011
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 14,466=？",
        "answer": 5.607506492103316
    },
    {
        "question": "2,572 × 250,898=？",
        "answer": 8.809768163659957
    },
    {
        "question": "41,774 × 4,529=？",
        "answer": 8.276908383086088
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 45,485=？",
        "answer": 5.436019449430434
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 68,162,489=？",
        "answer": 8.532515444944856
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 2,552,625=？",
        "answer": 7.912136996652223
    },
    {
        "question": "2,762 × 291,189=？",
        "answer": 8.905398639219008
    },
    {
        "question": "57,107 ÷ 42,229=？",
        "answer": 0.1310785487118124
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 3,972=？",
        "answer": 4.71295259213018
    },
    {
        "question": "16,743,206 ÷ 106,578=？",
        "answer": 2.1961710544251374
    },
    {
        "question": "4,190 × 347=？",
        "answer": 6.162543497757169
    },
    {
        "question": "610 × 401=？",
        "answer": 5.388474207630949
    },
    {
        "question": "914,722 ÷ 765,696=？",
        "answer": 0.07723274609412584
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 17,285=？",
        "answer": 5.669033148037413
    },
    {
        "question": "1,808,993 ÷ 5,801=？",
        "answer": 2.493934020868582
    },
    {
        "question": "1,063,245 × 367=？",
        "answer": 8.591299413336232
    },
    {
        "question": "940,177,514 ÷ 5,486=？",
        "answer": 5.2339540567910205
    },
    {
        "question": "12,623 ÷ 597=？",
        "answer": 1.3251882510854724
    },
    {
        "question": "24,669 ÷ 7,053=？",
        "answer": 0.5437776611342214
    },
    {
        "question": "1,426 × 945=？",
        "answer": 6.12955133402511
    },
    {
        "question": "319 × 1,469,567=？",
        "answer": 8.67098007412384
    },
    {
        "question": "2,610,942 ÷ 1,065=？",
        "answer": 3.389447616648829
    },
    {
        "question": "510,241 ÷ 30,685=？",
        "answer": 1.2208492254353622
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 2,013=？",
        "answer": 4.766241772787611
    },
    {
        "question": "2,194 × 2,765=？",
        "answer": 6.78293175887941
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 5,266,021=？",
        "answer": 8.911814284836645
    },
    {
        "question": "105,437,457 ÷ 63,773,868=？",
        "answer": 0.2183521642882967
    },
    {
        "question": "211 × 1,157,539=？",
        "answer": 8.387818087557411
    },
    {
        "question": "76,209 ÷ 383=？",
        "answer": 2.298807488965853
    },
    {
        "question": "687,496 ÷ 3,404=？",
        "answer": 2.305280624278141
    },
    {
        "question": "379,888,670 ÷ 7,358=？",
        "answer": 4.7128965576251405
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 1,056,886=？",
        "answer": 7.592229869140748
    },
    {
        "question": "14,121 ÷ 964=？",
        "answer": 1.165788419123431
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 18,870,774=？",
        "answer": 8.656000955179945
    },
    {
        "question": "657,920,400 ÷ 982,730=？",
        "answer": 2.8257391386329753
    },
    {
        "question": "3,892,988 ÷ 589,287=？",
        "answer": 0.8199562046003517
    },
    {
        "question": "833,911,064 ÷ 8,791,179=？",
        "answer": 1.9770726129682588
    },
    {
        "question": "551 × 560=？",
        "answer": 5.489339625857985
    },
    {
        "question": "13,544,975 ÷ 3,338=？",
        "answer": 3.6082918754481024
    },
    {
        "question": "929 × 83,279=？",
        "answer": 7.888551215593512
    },
    {
        "question": "104,351 × 1,077=？",
        "answer": 8.05071231858159
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 153,496=？",
        "answer": 5.186097062545699
    },
    {
        "question": "8,459,430 ÷ 592=？",
        "answer": 4.155019394354587
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 1,973,450=？",
        "answer": 7.637648808260516
    },
    {
        "question": "17,559,670 ÷ 2,199=？",
        "answer": 3.902291120562044
    },
    {
        "question": "5,634 × 91,551=？",
        "answer": 8.712479935057104
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 6,133=？",
        "answer": 5.600586321330349
    },
    {
        "question": "71,281 × 2,282=？",
        "answer": 8.211289423864038
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 1,189=？",
        "answer": 4.279301837274616
    },
    {
        "question": "254 × 32,351=？",
        "answer": 6.914721426285232
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 54,679,956=？",
        "answer": 7.737828156426785
    },
    {
        "question": "141 × 418,416=？",
        "answer": 7.7708273960166325
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 336=？",
        "answer": 4.117403884416343
    },
    {
        "question": "594,493 ÷ 26,418=？",
        "answer": 1.3522468094374094
    },
    {
        "question": "786,876,902 ÷ 1,980=？",
        "answer": 5.5992416069468565
    },
    {
        "question": "1,978,799 ÷ 619,216=？",
        "answer": 0.50455951260894
    },
    {
        "question": "689,376 ÷ 52,286=？",
        "answer": 1.1200707411991784
    },
    {
        "question": "125 × 1,600,699=？",
        "answer": 8.301219686633157
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 4,112=？",
        "answer": 4.091174360706882
    },
    {
        "question": "109,363,536 ÷ 4,160,089=？",
        "answer": 1.4197699217031792
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 56,343=？",
        "answer": 5.5959380074201155
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 286=？",
        "answer": 2.456366033129043
    },
    {
        "question": "789,071,581 ÷ 15,952,699=？",
        "answer": 1.6942822313430885
    },
    {
        "question": "8,507,574 ÷ 65,332=？",
        "answer": 2.1146797819412417
    },
    {
        "question": "801 × 2,101=？",
        "answer": 6.22605856849019
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 579,489,451=？",
        "answer": 8.763045534494285
    },
    {
        "question": "1,444,817 ÷ 1,357,566=？",
        "answer": 0.02705189037603741
    },
    {
        "question": "212,523,414 ÷ 15,984,702=？",
        "answer": 1.1237022396418797
    },
    {
        "question": "289,605 × 379=？",
        "answer": 8.040445265606664
    },
    {
        "question": "2,201 ÷ 322=？",
        "answer": 0.8347641708575171
    },
    {
        "question": "12,026,238 ÷ 175,010=？",
        "answer": 1.8370669295046003
    },
    {
        "question": "31,734 × 26,135=？",
        "answer": 8.918747321836397
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 47,604=？",
        "answer": 5.853734705577456
    },
    {
        "question": "38,517,973 ÷ 2,600=？",
        "answer": 4.17069007642982
    },
    {
        "question": "2,513,409 × 201=？",
        "answer": 8.703459223287235
    },
    {
        "question": "552 × 338,917=？",
        "answer": 8.27203243122584
    },
    {
        "question": "167,381,167 ÷ 5,960=？",
        "answer": 4.448460331741993
    },
    {
        "question": "601 × 2,124=？",
        "answer": 6.106028984412171
    },
    {
        "question": "259,917,464 ÷ 679,892=？",
        "answer": 2.5823955299251784
    },
    {
        "question": "943,287 ÷ 788=？",
        "answer": 3.0781176317194743
    },
    {
        "question": "701,225,535 ÷ 79,981,738=？",
        "answer": 0.942866885362146
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 517,265=？",
        "answer": 6.491864343868874
    },
    {
        "question": "19,308 × 291=？",
        "answer": 6.749630279132561
    },
    {
        "question": "520 × 330,243=？",
        "answer": 8.23483696449035
    },
    {
        "question": "313,994,692 ÷ 24,655=？",
        "answer": 4.105017299630917
    },
    {
        "question": "2,127,424 ÷ 211,950=？",
        "answer": 1.0016206334128195
    },
    {
        "question": "3,002 ÷ 251=？",
        "answer": 1.0777369664262135
    },
    {
        "question": "13,758,926 ÷ 4,032=？",
        "answer": 3.533064011444758
    },
    {
        "question": "1,404 × 516,778=？",
        "answer": 8.8606711246191
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 22,174,268=？",
        "answer": 8.521940551198323
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 222,493=？",
        "answer": 6.192414391919092
    },
    {
        "question": "700,800,695 ÷ 395,344=？",
        "answer": 3.2486193718145007
    },
    {
        "question": "50,699 ÷ 7,000=？",
        "answer": 0.8599013532684885
    },
    {
        "question": "880,517,256 ÷ 3,322=？",
        "answer": 5.42333824338854
    },
    {
        "question": "380,421,169 ÷ 55,181,710=？",
        "answer": 0.8384695212853313
    },
    {
        "question": "631,936,141 ÷ 276,759,323=？",
        "answer": 0.3585709341936731
    },
    {
        "question": "79,363,988 ÷ 785,906=？",
        "answer": 2.0042528783635
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,513=？",
        "answer": 3.179838928023187
    },
    {
        "question": "9,352,694 ÷ 365,273=？",
        "answer": 1.408319153882412
    },
    {
        "question": "497,969 ÷ 8,773=？",
        "answer": 1.7540541781642278
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,183,357=？",
        "answer": 6.922554923719224
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 220,064=？",
        "answer": 5.819670257381591
    },
    {
        "question": "233,845 ÷ 7,949=？",
        "answer": 1.4686155914124994
    },
    {
        "question": "7,237,071 ÷ 363,732=？",
        "answer": 1.2987813227346192
    },
    {
        "question": "474,223 ÷ 61,840=？",
        "answer": 0.8847131326940479
    },
    {
        "question": "102,421,257 ÷ 23,197=？",
        "answer": 3.6449582790686272
    },
    {
        "question": "879,285,531 ÷ 263=？",
        "answer": 6.524174178235314
    },
    {
        "question": "24,803,955 ÷ 1,105,670=？",
        "answer": 1.3508954086700808
    },
    {
        "question": "14,909 × 2,055=？",
        "answer": 7.486260340956402
    },
    {
        "question": "122,737,903 ÷ 29,639,127=？",
        "answer": 0.6171132913570668
    },
    {
        "question": "285 × 460=？",
        "answer": 5.1176026916900845
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 430=？",
        "answer": 3.53655844257153
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 229,967,991=？",
        "answer": 8.662697386901216
    },
    {
        "question": "426,243,758 ÷ 1,284=？",
        "answer": 5.521093008417854
    },
    {
        "question": "270 × 784=？",
        "answer": 5.325679826843426
    },
    {
        "question": "1,042 × 526=？",
        "answer": 5.738853463117245
    },
    {
        "question": "424,139,050 ÷ 8,526=？",
        "answer": 4.696762930988463
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 664,603=？",
        "answer": 6.901743543388308
    },
    {
        "question": "3,554,577 ÷ 210,072=？",
        "answer": 1.228419756266129
    },
    {
        "question": "478,772,433 ÷ 171,128,641=？",
        "answer": 0.44680643496822886
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 619,014,073=？",
        "answer": 8.791700522617482
    },
    {
        "question": "620,880,405 ÷ 297=？",
        "answer": 6.320251504401118
    },
    {
        "question": "75,604 ÷ 6,286=？",
        "answer": 1.0801703967557847
    },
    {
        "question": "335,402,615 ÷ 72,534=？",
        "answer": 3.665024816338229
    },
    {
        "question": "37,651 × 26,080=？",
        "answer": 8.992084102489416
    },
    {
        "question": "4,615 ÷ 549=？",
        "answer": 0.9245993609118389
    },
    {
        "question": "25,423 × 25,546=？",
        "answer": 8.812549705299578
    },
    {
        "question": "889,693,754 ÷ 741,860=？",
        "answer": 3.0789185864683626
    },
    {
        "question": "1,957 × 35,253=？",
        "answer": 7.838786906645192
    },
    {
        "question": "29,291,177 ÷ 173,012=？",
        "answer": 2.2286605966213893
    },
    {
        "question": "12,705 × 9,909=？",
        "answer": 8.100004497797466
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 80,707=？",
        "answer": 5.384032458952661
    },
    {
        "question": "3,554 × 236=？",
        "answer": 5.92362942643939
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 6,371,928=？",
        "answer": 8.758513369258413
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 150,507=？",
        "answer": 6.381676681859385
    },
    {
        "question": "230,477 × 3,814=？",
        "answer": 8.944008281032303
    },
    {
        "question": "442,312 × 205=？",
        "answer": 7.957482583068558
    },
    {
        "question": "6,609,002 ÷ 10,843=？",
        "answer": 2.7849864255221197
    },
    {
        "question": "151,857 ÷ 1,145=？",
        "answer": 2.1226293292774545
    },
    {
        "question": "300 × 405=？",
        "answer": 5.084576277934331
    },
    {
        "question": "19,063 ÷ 469=？",
        "answer": 1.6090184051570589
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,227,783=？",
        "answer": 6.089121615803275
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 225,620=？",
        "answer": 5.654407590552626
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 9,355=？",
        "answer": 4.27207378750001
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 857=？",
        "answer": 4.294708657940791
    },
    {
        "question": "2,299,434 ÷ 481=？",
        "answer": 3.679475872284143
    },
    {
        "question": "1,170,078 ÷ 59,066=？",
        "answer": 1.296877252686447
    },
    {
        "question": "3,733,355 ÷ 1,821,186=？",
        "answer": 0.31174498530449024
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 22,301=？",
        "answer": 4.825445592420049
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,482,006=？",
        "answer": 7.015948001931261
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 640=？",
        "answer": 3.2833012287035497
    },
    {
        "question": "606 × 378,592=？",
        "answer": 8.360644056845931
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 7,184,842=？",
        "answer": 8.303575253459977
    },
    {
        "question": "64,020 ÷ 40,416=？",
        "answer": 0.19976234093287681
    },
    {
        "question": "4,827 ÷ 1,188=？",
        "answer": 0.6088608581735172
    },
    {
        "question": "228 × 405,181=？",
        "answer": 7.965583918958631
    },
    {
        "question": "150,182 ÷ 9,266=？",
        "answer": 1.2097255877389281
    },
    {
        "question": "589 × 17,214=？",
        "answer": 7.0059970934167435
    },
    {
        "question": "17,762,586 ÷ 4,954,917=？",
        "answer": 0.5544698096378918
    },
    {
        "question": "25,929 ÷ 269=？",
        "answer": 1.9840334877173298
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 364=？",
        "answer": 4.573938608354228
    },
    {
        "question": "15,429,834 ÷ 517=？",
        "answer": 4.474870710689763
    },
    {
        "question": "4,748,615 ÷ 656=？",
        "answer": 3.85966312065625
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 28,003=？",
        "answer": 5.04926455172923
    },
    {
        "question": "1,987,548 ÷ 1,263,549=？",
        "answer": 0.1967255374486659
    },
    {
        "question": "83,751,483 ÷ 9,837,065=？",
        "answer": 0.9301269648245022
    },
    {
        "question": "76,881,377 ÷ 25,285=？",
        "answer": 3.4829581952838358
    },
    {
        "question": "333 × 4,858=？",
        "answer": 6.2089017439754315
    },
    {
        "question": "462,399,674 ÷ 1,620,832=？",
        "answer": 2.455279516873529
    },
    {
        "question": "879 × 219,151=？",
        "answer": 8.28473233178171
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 57,216,967=？",
        "answer": 8.711767342110335
    },
    {
        "question": "502,608,295 ÷ 74,859,218=？",
        "answer": 0.8269843658285821
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 8,798,143=？",
        "answer": 8.993609039143283
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 664=？",
        "answer": 3.1231980750319988
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 673,837=？",
        "answer": 6.606706104542333
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 8,233=？",
        "answer": 5.888685969011219
    },
    {
        "question": "723 × 289,439=？",
        "answer": 8.320695346343049
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 28,815,205=？",
        "answer": 7.936742968349066
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 216=？",
        "answer": 2.635483746814912
    },
    {
        "question": "63,516 ÷ 18,438=？",
        "answer": 0.5371693293988709
    },
    {
        "question": "1,819 × 435=？",
        "answer": 5.898321956018121
    },
    {
        "question": "59,038,767 ÷ 49,868=？",
        "answer": 3.0733153280452976
    },
    {
        "question": "218 × 251,871=？",
        "answer": 7.739634660050696
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 35,499,776=？",
        "answer": 7.550225612709436
    },
    {
        "question": "651 × 284,789=？",
        "answer": 8.268104199194667
    },
    {
        "question": "732 × 41,203=？",
        "answer": 7.47943991932485
    },
    {
        "question": "188,946,063 ÷ 45,944=？",
        "answer": 3.6141090438389414
    },
    {
        "question": "410,355,790 ÷ 8,285,743=？",
        "answer": 1.6948291069693395
    },
    {
        "question": "677,513,056 ÷ 117,331=？",
        "answer": 3.7615048965544586
    },
    {
        "question": "451,090,329 ÷ 3,884=？",
        "answer": 5.064984295050488
    },
    {
        "question": "686,355,849 ÷ 162,822=？",
        "answer": 3.624836253980993
    },
    {
        "question": "3,416,339 ÷ 4,265=？",
        "answer": 2.9036419232712083
    },
    {
        "question": "11,086,469 ÷ 204,343=？",
        "answer": 1.7344334819060965
    },
    {
        "question": "470,139,844 ÷ 6,489,282=？",
        "answer": 1.8600304114926456
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 99,730=？",
        "answer": 6.413799167011104
    },
    {
        "question": "8,823 × 720=？",
        "answer": 6.802948775658
    },
    {
        "question": "2,690,859 ÷ 18,229=？",
        "answer": 2.1691280965562076
    },
    {
        "question": "17,919 ÷ 2,988=？",
        "answer": 0.7779331763233733
    },
    {
        "question": "4,979,072 ÷ 753=？",
        "answer": 3.820353430246804
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 2,197,102=？",
        "answer": 7.860364159296748
    },
    {
        "question": "33,325 ÷ 1,898=？",
        "answer": 1.244473949994623
    },
    {
        "question": "157 × 379=？",
        "answer": 4.774538862377306
    },
    {
        "question": "48,906,617 ÷ 6,264,493=？",
        "answer": 0.8924816942736145
    },
    {
        "question": "2,401 ÷ 314=？",
        "answer": 0.8834625119838124
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 55,685,899=？",
        "answer": 8.745745235356965
    },
    {
        "question": "116 × 1,046,435=？",
        "answer": 8.084170246251322
    },
    {
        "question": "778,955,226 ÷ 819=？",
        "answer": 5.978228593575856
    },
    {
        "question": "672,796 ÷ 748=？",
        "answer": 2.9539818029053415
    },
    {
        "question": "27,774,866 ÷ 3,288=？",
        "answer": 3.9267201634937328
    },
    {
        "question": "291,199 ÷ 24,580=？",
        "answer": 1.0736080006921178
    },
    {
        "question": "49,645,503 ÷ 4,107,123=？",
        "answer": 1.0823422059667072
    },
    {
        "question": "151,019 ÷ 3,775=？",
        "answer": 1.6021146342157744
    },
    {
        "question": "1,124,286 ÷ 99,469=？",
        "answer": 1.0531890508771695
    },
    {
        "question": "461,590,106 ÷ 38,705,533=？",
        "answer": 1.0764834389709865
    },
    {
        "question": "200 × 24,860=？",
        "answer": 6.696531119969607
    },
    {
        "question": "69,812 × 373=？",
        "answer": 7.415638911822269
    },
    {
        "question": "604 × 13,015=？",
        "answer": 6.8954811110663865
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,020,553=？",
        "answer": 6.485956818411485
    },
    {
        "question": "1,873 × 222,447=？",
        "answer": 8.619764330447698
    },
    {
        "question": "12,680,763 ÷ 1,510,061=？",
        "answer": 0.9241508944937533
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 3,532=？",
        "answer": 4.752140677561456
    },
    {
        "question": "117 × 1,997,644=？",
        "answer": 8.368703956941854
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 88,490=？",
        "answer": 5.7250454454859705
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 323=？",
        "answer": 2.8102325179950842
    },
    {
        "question": "14,767,637 ÷ 1,828=？",
        "answer": 3.907334817119176
    },
    {
        "question": "8,369,865 ÷ 580=？",
        "answer": 4.159290459624124
    },
    {
        "question": "143,766,454 ÷ 11,207,005=？",
        "answer": 1.108167995302352
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 722,127=？",
        "answer": 6.335734838091026
    },
    {
        "question": "3,632 ÷ 1,498=？",
        "answer": 0.38463402648559986
    },
    {
        "question": "11,380,368 ÷ 10,289=？",
        "answer": 3.043783138578681
    },
    {
        "question": "645,848,177 ÷ 19,685=？",
        "answer": 4.515995018930027
    },
    {
        "question": "43,295,835 ÷ 92,066=？",
        "answer": 2.672346845099768
    },
    {
        "question": "409 × 837,664=？",
        "answer": 8.53479315932499
    },
    {
        "question": "40,798,823 ÷ 514,965=？",
        "answer": 1.8988699214856806
    },
    {
        "question": "4,136,249 ÷ 3,644,168=？",
        "answer": 0.05500828497320239
    },
    {
        "question": "1,016 × 1,294=？",
        "answer": 6.118827984280582
    },
    {
        "question": "6,146,651 ÷ 6,622=？",
        "answer": 2.967649378647698
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 58,547,778=？",
        "answer": 8.545661667799704
    },
    {
        "question": "101,261,757 ÷ 260,962=？",
        "answer": 2.588868186470249
    },
    {
        "question": "184 × 831,361=？",
        "answer": 8.184607470456536
    },
    {
        "question": "1,049,018 ÷ 534=？",
        "answer": 3.2932416832466083
    },
    {
        "question": "721,549 ÷ 9,519=？",
        "answer": 1.8796745023128696
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,003,035=？",
        "answer": 6.778590389540714
    },
    {
        "question": "2,658,763 ÷ 31,791=？",
        "answer": 1.9223754373401918
    },
    {
        "question": "47,404,024 ÷ 271=？",
        "answer": 5.242845918454078
    },
    {
        "question": "1,564 × 2,549=？",
        "answer": 6.6006065841930965
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 271=？",
        "answer": 3.2780673308886628
    },
    {
        "question": "480,781 × 443=？",
        "answer": 8.328351022659097
    },
    {
        "question": "9,196 × 26,529=？",
        "answer": 8.387319842332037
    },
    {
        "question": "574,331 ÷ 2,727=？",
        "answer": 2.3234771203830515
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 123,298=？",
        "answer": 6.090956032021454
    },
    {
        "question": "86,633,635 ÷ 1,918,125=？",
        "answer": 1.6548096312633278
    },
    {
        "question": "13,813,134 ÷ 16,022=？",
        "answer": 2.935575497484452
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 1,282,837=？",
        "answer": 7.761383991274416
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 21,329=？",
        "answer": 4.3289704942369305
    },
    {
        "question": "746,384,775 ÷ 546=？",
        "answer": 6.135770129243614
    },
    {
        "question": "3,667,888 ÷ 151,435=？",
        "answer": 1.3841898040062475
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 2,655,471=？",
        "answer": 8.332626581794887
    },
    {
        "question": "134 × 327,277=？",
        "answer": 7.642020283892594
    },
    {
        "question": "51,826,513 ÷ 141,676=？",
        "answer": 2.5632557028189873
    },
    {
        "question": "61,505 ÷ 10,556=？",
        "answer": 0.7654110412866415
    },
    {
        "question": "860 × 16,239=？",
        "answer": 7.1450577330542915
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 31,747=？",
        "answer": 6.692034390160392
    },
    {
        "question": "114 × 8,258,384=？",
        "answer": 8.973799924256816
    },
    {
        "question": "23,459,170 ÷ 612,930=？",
        "answer": 1.5829017639271488
    },
    {
        "question": "17,955,785 ÷ 787,471=？",
        "answer": 1.3579698274802519
    },
    {
        "question": "23,984,403 ÷ 885,171=？",
        "answer": 1.4329017357171157
    },
    {
        "question": "862,086 × 274=？",
        "answer": 8.373301155167646
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 401=？",
        "answer": 4.108294350940088
    },
    {
        "question": "7,759 × 39,791=？",
        "answer": 8.489590605541357
    },
    {
        "question": "7,139 ÷ 597=？",
        "answer": 1.077663050829225
    },
    {
        "question": "268,337 ÷ 535=？",
        "answer": 2.700326778045191
    },
    {
        "question": "279,615,265 ÷ 7,110,770=？",
        "answer": 1.5946442456218715
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 16,341=？",
        "answer": 5.41739861264872
    },
    {
        "question": "233,685 × 466=？",
        "answer": 8.0370167530604
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 6,999,840=？",
        "answer": 7.959031465476628
    },
    {
        "question": "87,807 ÷ 2,476=？",
        "answer": 1.5497784990226329
    },
    {
        "question": "11,717 ÷ 1,137=？",
        "answer": 1.013055965234485
    },
    {
        "question": "147,075,656 ÷ 1,284=？",
        "answer": 5.058975770410075
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 118,602=？",
        "answer": 6.375122008314824
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 25,774=？",
        "answer": 6.08327968211797
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 274,695=？",
        "answer": 6.970329671504055
    },
    {
        "question": "943,666,896 ÷ 843,042=？",
        "answer": 3.048969508656019
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 1,893=？",
        "answer": 4.724308645306016
    },
    {
        "question": "247,378,884 ÷ 1,057=？",
        "answer": 5.36928763864993
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,592=？",
        "answer": 3.413634997198556
    },
    {
        "question": "46,907 ÷ 9,290=？",
        "answer": 0.7032219439565298
    },
    {
        "question": "402,471,954 ÷ 3,458,149=？",
        "answer": 2.0658919205974424
    },
    {
        "question": "493,120,466 ÷ 22,170=？",
        "answer": 4.347187334333338
    },
    {
        "question": "573 × 132,728=？",
        "answer": 7.881117172282874
    },
    {
        "question": "7,208 × 266=？",
        "answer": 6.282696414602073
    },
    {
        "question": "380 × 1,978,469=？",
        "answer": 8.87611284645039
    },
    {
        "question": "134,074 ÷ 99,319=？",
        "answer": 0.1303122282509324
    },
    {
        "question": "367,067,310 ÷ 403=？",
        "answer": 5.959440663018907
    },
    {
        "question": "1,631 × 6,547=？",
        "answer": 7.028496301962273
    },
    {
        "question": "1,189,008 ÷ 37,461=？",
        "answer": 1.501605410254046
    },
    {
        "question": "57,679,881 ÷ 239,612=？",
        "answer": 2.38151579156622
    },
    {
        "question": "622,980 ÷ 6,933=？",
        "answer": 1.953552904198662
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 10,562=？",
        "answer": 5.614810770178975
    },
    {
        "question": "37,164 × 1,393=？",
        "answer": 7.714073567828375
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 13,433=？",
        "answer": 5.844176358384527
    },
    {
        "question": "98,417,982 ÷ 2,116=？",
        "answer": 4.667558792485803
    },
    {
        "question": "1,888,988 ÷ 434,920=？",
        "answer": 0.6378198196682605
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 14,044,722=？",
        "answer": 8.101755656674975
    },
    {
        "question": "1,238 × 245=？",
        "answer": 5.4818867290486315
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 41,683=？",
        "answer": 6.051322732525291
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 1,146,021=？",
        "answer": 7.337946176787131
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 15,324=？",
        "answer": 4.963523393694683
    },
    {
        "question": "20,454,829 ÷ 864,556=？",
        "answer": 1.3740027240631452
    },
    {
        "question": "99 × 1,851,793=？",
        "answer": 8.26322763267663
    },
    {
        "question": "105,202,005 ÷ 175,240=？",
        "answer": 2.7783907724231645
    },
    {
        "question": "6,554,907 ÷ 2,489=？",
        "answer": 3.420541637758725
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 110,582=？",
        "answer": 6.043684440378527
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 125,772=？",
        "answer": 6.712367823751238
    },
    {
        "question": "39,493 ÷ 1,000=？",
        "answer": 1.5965201252270254
    },
    {
        "question": "308 × 54,900=？",
        "answer": 7.228123060950536
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 5,108=？",
        "answer": 5.276452612658373
    },
    {
        "question": "4,943 ÷ 972=？",
        "answer": 0.7063243455345022
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 2,303,904=？",
        "answer": 7.953528985797258
    },
    {
        "question": "12,278 ÷ 816=？",
        "answer": 1.1774374702904173
    },
    {
        "question": "2,949 × 3,044=？",
        "answer": 6.953119420650333
    },
    {
        "question": "12,168 ÷ 3,041=？",
        "answer": 0.6022027809008098
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 5,173,338=？",
        "answer": 7.412740858298836
    },
    {
        "question": "126,134,393 ÷ 1,231=？",
        "answer": 5.010575468642092
    },
    {
        "question": "496,400,269 ÷ 1,049=？",
        "answer": 5.675056519977986
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 192,135,531=？",
        "answer": 8.760728939676898
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 389,674=？",
        "answer": 6.435799469586201
    },
    {
        "question": "841,413,183 ÷ 64,793,553=？",
        "answer": 1.1134775166837878
    },
    {
        "question": "1,176 ÷ 386=？",
        "answer": 0.48382001706836475
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 1,551,992=？",
        "answer": 7.491919473949031
    },
    {
        "question": "1,532 × 35,654=？",
        "answer": 7.737367025444568
    },
    {
        "question": "211,759 ÷ 1,033=？",
        "answer": 2.3117415558882004
    },
    {
        "question": "5,692 ÷ 2,863=？",
        "answer": 0.2984435433906481
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 6,655=？",
        "answer": 5.594000071452838
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 5,799,513=？",
        "answer": 7.240512780990772
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 9,468=？",
        "answer": 5.090201601563882
    },
    {
        "question": "57,456,142 ÷ 510,312=？",
        "answer": 2.0515006802221722
    },
    {
        "question": "40,505 ÷ 382=？",
        "answer": 2.0254452735962696
    },
    {
        "question": "482,312,340 ÷ 148,573,612=？",
        "answer": 0.5113866918271227
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 57,962=？",
        "answer": 6.406596039033739
    },
    {
        "question": "8,598 × 96,787=？",
        "answer": 8.920214469500445
    },
    {
        "question": "188,581,982 ÷ 2,926,683=？",
        "answer": 1.809124510949161
    },
    {
        "question": "62,367 × 1,812=？",
        "answer": 8.053113047304045
    },
    {
        "question": "969,701,499 ÷ 257,998=？",
        "answer": 3.5750217276326572
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 155,133=？",
        "answer": 5.19070419106614
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 8,757,065=？",
        "answer": 8.866637859366287
    },
    {
        "question": "783 × 327,847=？",
        "answer": 8.40943297601928
    },
    {
        "question": "16,135,978 ÷ 15,835,261=？",
        "answer": 0.008170067185319865
    },
    {
        "question": "272 × 75,816=？",
        "answer": 7.314329771650954
    },
    {
        "question": "573,716,665 ÷ 200,187,891=？",
        "answer": 0.4572596609507174
    },
    {
        "question": "36,128,387 ÷ 4,691=？",
        "answer": 3.8865831393975916
    },
    {
        "question": "244 × 41,721=？",
        "answer": 7.007744535711562
    },
    {
        "question": "109,934,825 ÷ 1,612,732=？",
        "answer": 1.8335730860645403
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 14,715,398=？",
        "answer": 8.313900048418066
    },
    {
        "question": "521 × 17,901=？",
        "answer": 6.969715015863285
    },
    {
        "question": "70,917 ÷ 53,338=？",
        "answer": 0.1237136283283385
    },
    {
        "question": "212 × 5,328=？",
        "answer": 6.052900077090996
    },
    {
        "question": "718,226,893 ÷ 5,536=？",
        "answer": 5.1130655811943715
    },
    {
        "question": "225 × 891,114=？",
        "answer": 8.302115784891143
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 4,385,014=？",
        "answer": 7.340940988608897
    },
    {
        "question": "779 × 6,349=？",
        "answer": 6.694242784746916
    },
    {
        "question": "111 × 222,654=？",
        "answer": 7.392953480465097
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 8,548=？",
        "answer": 5.3298045221640695
    },
    {
        "question": "170,278,920 ÷ 26,072=？",
        "answer": 3.8149865395288196
    },
    {
        "question": "2,083 × 4,442=？",
        "answer": 6.966267824160201
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 948,034=？",
        "answer": 7.122951948699426
    },
    {
        "question": "327,945,360 ÷ 18,566,147=？",
        "answer": 1.2470797058631946
    },
    {
        "question": "13,578 × 1,239=？",
        "answer": 7.225907110714435
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 2,096,816=？",
        "answer": 7.525680304542007
    },
    {
        "question": "3,625 × 2,142=？",
        "answer": 6.890127477402849
    },
    {
        "question": "1,398 × 570,318=？",
        "answer": 8.901624250126648
    },
    {
        "question": "124 × 91,486=？",
        "answer": 7.054776324715677
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 4,690=？",
        "answer": 4.574262829707027
    },
    {
        "question": "7,610,655 ÷ 1,288=？",
        "answer": 3.77150617228086
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 80,062=？",
        "answer": 6.225645729592623
    },
    {
        "question": "549 × 1,382=？",
        "answer": 5.880080387488271
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 35,242=？",
        "answer": 6.170309837252466
    },
    {
        "question": "39,339,717 ÷ 231=？",
        "answer": 5.231219251497466
    },
    {
        "question": "235 × 24,553=？",
        "answer": 6.761172426097171
    },
    {
        "question": "79,838,029 ÷ 4,356,349=？",
        "answer": 1.2630871416813059
    },
    {
        "question": "35,861 × 1,268=？",
        "answer": 7.6577416494363115
    },
    {
        "question": "9,743,257 ÷ 708=？",
        "answer": 4.138670900490737
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 251,026=？",
        "answer": 7.012502562550347
    },
    {
        "question": "2,498 × 42,544=？",
        "answer": 8.026430754025608
    },
    {
        "question": "69,635,580 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 5.498438923531438
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 12,719=？",
        "answer": 5.660755468089579
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 6,084=？",
        "answer": 4.4831592097169795
    },
    {
        "question": "520,213 × 257=？",
        "answer": 8.126114324243282
    },
    {
        "question": "107,797 ÷ 1,015=？",
        "answer": 2.026140632316004
    },
    {
        "question": "220,927,039 ÷ 4,943,527=？",
        "answer": 1.6502119614348805
    },
    {
        "question": "157,469,719 ÷ 55,534,324=？",
        "answer": 0.45263556278281136
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 446,581=？",
        "answer": 7.558385260742847
    },
    {
        "question": "118,621,890 ÷ 85,312=？",
        "answer": 3.1431547159592537
    },
    {
        "question": "173 × 4,978,558=？",
        "answer": 8.93514967413576
    },
    {
        "question": "1,468 ÷ 1,395=？",
        "answer": 0.022151847970435398
    },
    {
        "question": "6,020 × 35,118=？",
        "answer": 8.32512626575565
    },
    {
        "question": "3,158,755 ÷ 1,152,569=？",
        "answer": 0.43784900794611215
    },
    {
        "question": "95,165,473 ÷ 717,009=？",
        "answer": 2.122954803483909
    },
    {
        "question": "265,873,848 ÷ 1,428,735=？",
        "answer": 2.2697239373108515
    },
    {
        "question": "209,632,279 ÷ 5,506,493=？",
        "answer": 1.580583064282234
    },
    {
        "question": "6,434 × 686=？",
        "answer": 6.644805172272703
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 180,758=？",
        "answer": 6.900550203913171
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 1,093=？",
        "answer": 4.339650157613684
    },
    {
        "question": "149 × 399,511=？",
        "answer": 7.774715009943468
    },
    {
        "question": "26,438 × 13,606=？",
        "answer": 8.55595906487322
    },
    {
        "question": "190 × 49,593=？",
        "answer": 6.974173981557664
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 538=？",
        "answer": 3.844725627973226
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 8,709=？",
        "answer": 5.508170014618331
    },
    {
        "question": "42,470 ÷ 14,999=？",
        "answer": 0.4520199558656002
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 67,452=？",
        "answer": 6.084267336443869
    },
    {
        "question": "221,063,668 ÷ 67,812=？",
        "answer": 3.5132108184341226
    },
    {
        "question": "214 × 68,711=？",
        "answer": 7.167440042532242
    },
    {
        "question": "154,812 ÷ 452=？",
        "answer": 2.534666186469573
    },
    {
        "question": "70,070,059 ÷ 54,353=？",
        "answer": 3.1103089633186936
    },
    {
        "question": "108,045 × 651=？",
        "answer": 7.847185662400563
    },
    {
        "question": "658,730 ÷ 214=？",
        "answer": 3.488293669260035
    },
    {
        "question": "17,034,112 ÷ 6,321=？",
        "answer": 3.430533708095538
    },
    {
        "question": "197 × 426,662=？",
        "answer": 7.924550190967926
    },
    {
        "question": "802,445,451 ÷ 537=？",
        "answer": 6.174441233713939
    },
    {
        "question": "144,190,798 ÷ 814,019=？",
        "answer": 2.248303003501497
    },
    {
        "question": "89,862 × 330=？",
        "answer": 7.472090020051853
    },
    {
        "question": "583 × 5,393=？",
        "answer": 6.4974989750471766
    },
    {
        "question": "279,539,379 ÷ 66,211,641=？",
        "answer": 0.6255086444034081
    },
    {
        "question": "7,099 × 7,371=？",
        "answer": 7.718723587373904
    },
    {
        "question": "147,962 ÷ 1,123=？",
        "answer": 2.1197704367731762
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 57,789=？",
        "answer": 6.159785188027857
    },
    {
        "question": "88,436 × 7,570=？",
        "answer": 8.825724970516498
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 18,371,505=？",
        "answer": 8.10924277533054
    },
    {
        "question": "3,316,688 ÷ 669=？",
        "answer": 3.6952785017011998
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 8,945,011=？",
        "answer": 8.127672138026862
    },
    {
        "question": "2,121,334 ÷ 712,141=？",
        "answer": 0.4740430626710144
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 138,783=？",
        "answer": 5.841306275509908
    },
    {
        "question": "317 × 933,775=？",
        "answer": 8.471301504582524
    },
    {
        "question": "437,848,034 ÷ 185,383=？",
        "answer": 3.373253498061248
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 5,421,896=？",
        "answer": 8.346935039632351
    },
    {
        "question": "31,427,359 ÷ 1,762,005=？",
        "answer": 1.2513007501231306
    },
    {
        "question": "255 × 33,376=？",
        "answer": 6.929974467180392
    },
    {
        "question": "300 × 8,048=？",
        "answer": 6.382809222431515
    },
    {
        "question": "1,378 ÷ 1,291=？",
        "answer": 0.02832297530518669
    },
    {
        "question": "452,742,947 ÷ 347=？",
        "answer": 6.115522218645052
    },
    {
        "question": "148 × 314,599=？",
        "answer": 7.668019053214418
    },
    {
        "question": "883,747 ÷ 4,125=？",
        "answer": 2.3309039996495273
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 10,108,930=？",
        "answer": 7.305735184915906
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 472=？",
        "answer": 4.7231600213042695
    },
    {
        "question": "521 × 102,137=？",
        "answer": 7.72602082077264
    },
    {
        "question": "8,165,898 ÷ 4,115,373=？",
        "answer": 0.29759474691389126
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 190,896=？",
        "answer": 6.280796828361567
    },
    {
        "question": "42,942 ÷ 596=？",
        "answer": 1.8576360078573495
    },
    {
        "question": "77,945 × 4,345=？",
        "answer": 8.529778042169
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 56,233=？",
        "answer": 4.74999125350213
    },
    {
        "question": "740,747,138 ÷ 90,750,318=？",
        "answer": 0.9118218266554562
    },
    {
        "question": "226,208 ÷ 3,543=？",
        "answer": 1.8051368076480276
    },
    {
        "question": "182,654,177 ÷ 17,673=？",
        "answer": 4.0143193308048915
    },
    {
        "question": "632 × 362,116=？",
        "answer": 8.35956479271054
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 416=？",
        "answer": 4.5922211842264415
    },
    {
        "question": "1,585 ÷ 1,566=？",
        "answer": 0.005237508831845685
    },
    {
        "question": "306 × 28,407=？",
        "answer": 6.939146797753245
    },
    {
        "question": "335,281,642 ÷ 57,145,937=？",
        "answer": 0.7684244166642563
    },
    {
        "question": "332,857,405 ÷ 75,256=？",
        "answer": 3.645717092024953
    },
    {
        "question": "153 × 2,155,420=？",
        "answer": 8.518223339147236
    },
    {
        "question": "50,181 × 3,754=？",
        "answer": 8.275033579910284
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 3,364,387=？",
        "answer": 7.805659547144578
    },
    {
        "question": "524 × 572=？",
        "answer": 5.476727315776751
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,324=？",
        "answer": 4.212826586101233
    },
    {
        "question": "573,413 ÷ 40,669=？",
        "answer": 1.1492040409527375
    },
    {
        "question": "29,293 ÷ 2,310=？",
        "answer": 1.103151871705022
    },
    {
        "question": "862,553,809 ÷ 776,588,976=？",
        "answer": 0.04559497607206782
    },
    {
        "question": "3,032 × 59,921=？",
        "answer": 8.259308249496186
    },
    {
        "question": "476,354,336 ÷ 39,978=？",
        "answer": 4.076109059071355
    },
    {
        "question": "711 × 182,500=？",
        "answer": 8.11313246952226
    },
    {
        "question": "247,387,495 ÷ 42,934,079=？",
        "answer": 0.7605755919599696
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,449,699=？",
        "answer": 7.0149024575199155
    },
    {
        "question": "135,856,471 ÷ 1,471,115=？",
        "answer": 1.9654337054700788
    },
    {
        "question": "28,388,514 ÷ 1,054,025=？",
        "answer": 1.4302917480698074
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 2,148,505=？",
        "answer": 7.177234408725305
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,354=？",
        "answer": 3.9097699147327694
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 325=？",
        "answer": 3.591064607026499
    },
    {
        "question": "3,173 × 1,653=？",
        "answer": 6.71974292567186
    },
    {
        "question": "1,689 × 2,151=？",
        "answer": 6.560270059958471
    },
    {
        "question": "89,676 ÷ 3,205=？",
        "answer": 1.4468481944489575
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,028,576=？",
        "answer": 6.01223638661042
    },
    {
        "question": "53,470,271 ÷ 6,301,059=？",
        "answer": 0.928698839060339
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,665,502=？",
        "answer": 7.270958371264807
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 71,747=？",
        "answer": 6.814845138693194
    },
    {
        "question": "180,298,557 ÷ 96,236=？",
        "answer": 3.2726546874279534
    },
    {
        "question": "3,311,287 ÷ 961,515=？",
        "answer": 0.5370407603102694
    },
    {
        "question": "626,067 ÷ 5,162=？",
        "answer": 2.0838028125125665
    },
    {
        "question": "5,316 ÷ 300=？",
        "answer": 1.248463717551032
    },
    {
        "question": "24,727,200 ÷ 49,256=？",
        "answer": 2.7007158009539585
    },
    {
        "question": "742,342,029 ÷ 1,414=？",
        "answer": 5.720154640134049
    },
    {
        "question": "362 × 331=？",
        "answer": 5.078536564308885
    },
    {
        "question": "294,780 ÷ 9,042=？",
        "answer": 1.51323351182019
    },
    {
        "question": "390,778 × 1,335=？",
        "answer": 8.717411371546854
    },
    {
        "question": "170,267,297 ÷ 960=？",
        "answer": 5.248860008602987
    },
    {
        "question": "330,571,156 ÷ 3,729,244=？",
        "answer": 1.9476441568430283
    },
    {
        "question": "36,491,830 ÷ 30,038,569=？",
        "answer": 0.08451640342526384
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 592,034=？",
        "answer": 6.0733766442591595
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 5,997,035=？",
        "answer": 7.7779365834821865
    },
    {
        "question": "24,074 ÷ 4,895=？",
        "answer": 0.6917955600519422
    },
    {
        "question": "518 × 1,165,006=？",
        "answer": 8.780657921811288
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 151,210=？",
        "answer": 6.258761759443034
    },
    {
        "question": "200,716 ÷ 13,759=？",
        "answer": 1.1639951228341325
    },
    {
        "question": "12,372 × 42,023=？",
        "answer": 8.715926964563819
    },
    {
        "question": "3,218 × 137,047=？",
        "answer": 8.644455572905906
    },
    {
        "question": "3,666 × 7,991=？",
        "answer": 7.4667935912927295
    },
    {
        "question": "182,408 ÷ 16,602=？",
        "answer": 1.0408834720536868
    },
    {
        "question": "241,773,862 ÷ 13,132,655=？",
        "answer": 1.2650568124685775
    },
    {
        "question": "25,474 × 721=？",
        "answer": 7.2640324091935335
    },
    {
        "question": "191,537 ÷ 301=？",
        "answer": 2.803686185288776
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 15,079=？",
        "answer": 4.780432532537962
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 641=？",
        "answer": 4.037306950897091
    },
    {
        "question": "61,170,236 ÷ 10,162=？",
        "answer": 3.7795609654719975
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 5,187,419=？",
        "answer": 7.192072583113994
    },
    {
        "question": "248,552,798 ÷ 3,925,018=？",
        "answer": 1.8015770036817589
    },
    {
        "question": "651,801 ÷ 5,737=？",
        "answer": 2.055430172546391
    },
    {
        "question": "855,062,877 ÷ 938,874=？",
        "answer": 2.959390739303436
    },
    {
        "question": "94,385,891 ÷ 2,110=？",
        "answer": 4.650624624606359
    },
    {
        "question": "701,356,011 ÷ 7,749,193=？",
        "answer": 1.9566820459925676
    },
    {
        "question": "450 ÷ 363=？",
        "answer": 0.0933058887392312
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 9,966,135=？",
        "answer": 8.144654801451061
    },
    {
        "question": "945,401 ÷ 113,621=？",
        "answer": 0.9201574500768103
    },
    {
        "question": "69,611 × 377=？",
        "answer": 7.41901922288861
    },
    {
        "question": "315,485,814 ÷ 59,487=？",
        "answer": 3.7245577682283697
    },
    {
        "question": "29,999 × 9,065=？",
        "answer": 8.43447458642718
    },
    {
        "question": "71,657,738 ÷ 117,723=？",
        "answer": 2.784401773858752
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 10,219=？",
        "answer": 5.213528381807792
    },
    {
        "question": "76,720 ÷ 237=？",
        "answer": 2.5101602481525034
    },
    {
        "question": "4,194,169 ÷ 676,843=？",
        "answer": 0.7921579842184987
    },
    {
        "question": "932,680 ÷ 23,945=？",
        "answer": 1.5905178226547696
    },
    {
        "question": "27,221,329 ÷ 3,840=？",
        "answer": 3.8505781001469837
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 967=？",
        "answer": 2.9854264740830017
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 1,326,817=？",
        "answer": 7.90814086234336
    },
    {
        "question": "27,491 ÷ 894=？",
        "answer": 1.4878530190316526
    },
    {
        "question": "961 × 312=？",
        "answer": 5.476877981686989
    },
    {
        "question": "910 × 1,666=？",
        "answer": 6.180716389391862
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 414,578=？",
        "answer": 7.634639591393076
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 292,785=？",
        "answer": 6.420791332563044
    },
    {
        "question": "334,053 ÷ 33,511=？",
        "answer": 0.9986279885493908
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 17,808=？",
        "answer": 4.9495851513266516
    },
    {
        "question": "549 × 34,522=？",
        "answer": 7.277668292669477
    },
    {
        "question": "10,363 × 433=？",
        "answer": 6.65197339450782
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 22,429,682=？",
        "answer": 8.049793120690977
    },
    {
        "question": "726,561,174 ÷ 9,612=？",
        "answer": 4.878458424172042
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 158,187=？",
        "answer": 7.04426882979381
    },
    {
        "question": "472 × 523,874=？",
        "answer": 8.393168843471175
    },
    {
        "question": "182,922,782 ÷ 87,053=？",
        "answer": 3.3224840555058237
    },
    {
        "question": "42,314 ÷ 22,658=？",
        "answer": 0.27126250925982354
    },
    {
        "question": "448 × 7,515=？",
        "answer": 6.527206998921071
    },
    {
        "question": "48,053,542 ÷ 2,103=？",
        "answer": 4.358886132104111
    },
    {
        "question": "188,319,099 ÷ 83,333,994=？",
        "answer": 0.35407217062635765
    },
    {
        "question": "135,070,597 ÷ 3,526,828=？",
        "answer": 1.5831765393502315
    },
    {
        "question": "51,549 ÷ 567=？",
        "answer": 1.9586371859216953
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 6,125,005=？",
        "answer": 7.389166438890496
    },
    {
        "question": "242,854 × 1,162=？",
        "answer": 8.450551389100431
    },
    {
        "question": "293,761,897 ÷ 238,292,193=？",
        "answer": 0.09088564994094321
    },
    {
        "question": "92,984 ÷ 26,823=？",
        "answer": 0.5399008751957255
    },
    {
        "question": "449 × 89,854=？",
        "answer": 7.605783756218604
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 4,985,011=？",
        "answer": 8.746884143639628
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,174,490=？",
        "answer": 6.802703959000117
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 270=？",
        "answer": 2.4313637641589874
    },
    {
        "question": "16,031 × 27,044=？",
        "answer": 8.637031541379683
    },
    {
        "question": "86,734 ÷ 1,858=？",
        "answer": 1.669143665994422
    },
    {
        "question": "12,477 ÷ 1,381=？",
        "answer": 0.9559164965059648
    },
    {
        "question": "236,714 × 208=？",
        "answer": 7.692287279173823
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 263=？",
        "answer": 2.419955748489758
    },
    {
        "question": "18,220,832 ÷ 313=？",
        "answer": 4.765023866306734
    },
    {
        "question": "650 × 97,631=？",
        "answer": 7.802501094302296
    },
    {
        "question": "539 × 1,696,749=？",
        "answer": 8.961206367093496
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 186,934=？",
        "answer": 5.572718294739253
    },
    {
        "question": "4,761,449 ÷ 25,023=？",
        "answer": 2.279399761037322
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 6,340,086=？",
        "answer": 8.682908741183365
    },
    {
        "question": "96,340 ÷ 3,038=？",
        "answer": 1.5012188724516478
    },
    {
        "question": "4,665 ÷ 2,921=？",
        "answer": 0.20332009110896904
    },
    {
        "question": "31,960 ÷ 2,024=？",
        "answer": 1.1983962624741924
    },
    {
        "question": "147,366 ÷ 5,817=？",
        "answer": 1.4036982316944973
    },
    {
        "question": "4,233 × 453=？",
        "answer": 6.282746470486842
    },
    {
        "question": "3,159,148 ÷ 306,409=？",
        "answer": 1.0132684547769535
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,076,456=？",
        "answer": 6.333026278455408
    },
    {
        "question": "10,836,761 ÷ 21,561=？",
        "answer": 2.7012305957230756
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,408=？",
        "answer": 3.94527158150771
    },
    {
        "question": "255,292,192 ÷ 702=？",
        "answer": 5.560700420170842
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,960=？",
        "answer": 3.77232170672292
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 310,079=？",
        "answer": 5.491472354779914
    },
    {
        "question": "533,144,428 ÷ 21,993,369=？",
        "answer": 1.384553113881685
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 9,122=？",
        "answer": 5.164210050560844
    },
    {
        "question": "3,223,622 ÷ 671,362=？",
        "answer": 0.6813873550549008
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 183,982=？",
        "answer": 6.808843379951838
    },
    {
        "question": "31,296,430 ÷ 21,404=？",
        "answer": 3.1649998578727847
    },
    {
        "question": "1,051,220 ÷ 45,806=？",
        "answer": 1.360771246218617
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 305,092=？",
        "answer": 5.484430819896073
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,370=？",
        "answer": 3.941511432634403
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 27,122=？",
        "answer": 4.734351707294765
    },
    {
        "question": "79,002,891 ÷ 109,576=？",
        "answer": 2.8579275412258505
    },
    {
        "question": "3,186 × 1,804=？",
        "answer": 6.759482304671035
    },
    {
        "question": "73,369,856 ÷ 47,139,833=？",
        "answer": 0.19212962706665218
    },
    {
        "question": "101 × 716,878=？",
        "answer": 7.859766626472756
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 357,870=？",
        "answer": 7.072239233181161
    },
    {
        "question": "104,769,878 ÷ 88,483,560=？",
        "answer": 0.07337385071100555
    },
    {
        "question": "400,959 ÷ 32,719=？",
        "answer": 1.088299944438313
    },
    {
        "question": "1,020,387 × 216=？",
        "answer": 8.343218668097474
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,085,850=？",
        "answer": 6.035769835684129
    },
    {
        "question": "11,913,983 ÷ 91,170=？",
        "answer": 2.116205021271139
    },
    {
        "question": "255,992,430 ÷ 304=？",
        "answer": 5.925353539289671
    },
    {
        "question": "347,005,851 ÷ 62,306,652=？",
        "answer": 0.7458023822580817
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 779=？",
        "answer": 3.794627444664508
    },
    {
        "question": "790,853 ÷ 284,320=？",
        "answer": 0.4442883559419749
    },
    {
        "question": "991,138 ÷ 1,501=？",
        "answer": 2.819753434962471
    },
    {
        "question": "108,517 × 3,504=？",
        "answer": 8.580061876490367
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 61,231,422=？",
        "answer": 8.088004340998493
    },
    {
        "question": "111 × 5,113,343=？",
        "answer": 8.754027904705255
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 152,411,096=？",
        "answer": 8.66013784085809
    },
    {
        "question": "346 × 1,594,706=？",
        "answer": 8.741756727034417
    },
    {
        "question": "60,284 ÷ 266=？",
        "answer": 2.3553204245346393
    },
    {
        "question": "102,286 ÷ 18,730=？",
        "answer": 0.737278418029745
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 329,666=？",
        "answer": 5.518074158626918
    },
    {
        "question": "18,053,037 ÷ 1,874=？",
        "answer": 3.9837806856951206
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 259=？",
        "answer": 3.8112397727532894
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 201=？",
        "answer": 3.1482940974347455
    },
    {
        "question": "2,945,140 ÷ 507=？",
        "answer": 3.7640979848771603
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 653,978,031=？",
        "answer": 8.815563159370557
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 224,871=？",
        "answer": 6.2550234381943435
    },
    {
        "question": "322,996 ÷ 88,619=？",
        "answer": 0.5616702990073691
    },
    {
        "question": "152,565 ÷ 209=？",
        "answer": 2.8633086272569055
    },
    {
        "question": "739,390,818 ÷ 523=？",
        "answer": 6.150372364190624
    },
    {
        "question": "343,942 ÷ 7,965=？",
        "answer": 1.6352994321911032
    },
    {
        "question": "5,770,074 ÷ 14,446=？",
        "answer": 2.6014337724036563
    },
    {
        "question": "29,703 × 5,050=？",
        "answer": 8.176091693349946
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 18,547,089=？",
        "answer": 8.171365742967625
    },
    {
        "question": "174,972 ÷ 4,885=？",
        "answer": 1.5541039879548357
    },
    {
        "question": "4,838 × 13,973=？",
        "answer": 7.829955523080008
    },
    {
        "question": "198,645,616 ÷ 10,339,022=？",
        "answer": 1.2835995254102663
    },
    {
        "question": "21,251,817 ÷ 126,103=？",
        "answer": 2.226670648936806
    },
    {
        "question": "267,005,690 ÷ 11,387,645=？",
        "answer": 1.3700865965250104
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 218,613=？",
        "answer": 7.080038673550721
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 29,672,491=？",
        "answer": 8.472354006786796
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 331=？",
        "answer": 2.519827993775719
    },
    {
        "question": "809 × 349=？",
        "answer": 5.450773948571452
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 67,679=？",
        "answer": 6.361932850145173
    },
    {
        "question": "114,921,025 ÷ 232=？",
        "answer": 5.694911505992
    },
    {
        "question": "11,734 × 272=？",
        "answer": 6.504014987914512
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 164,962=？",
        "answer": 6.933387256994332
    },
    {
        "question": "39,003 ÷ 316=？",
        "answer": 2.0914109303911053
    },
    {
        "question": "2,803 × 330=？",
        "answer": 5.966137037638173
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 22,650=？",
        "answer": 5.63382180730168
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 5,820=？",
        "answer": 4.878866336956725
    },
    {
        "question": "160 × 9,279=？",
        "answer": 6.171621157378766
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 223=？",
        "answer": 4.0385009430766745
    },
    {
        "question": "30,894 ÷ 966=？",
        "answer": 1.504897015795385
    },
    {
        "question": "28,932,733 ÷ 271,289=？",
        "answer": 2.0279572745448537
    },
    {
        "question": "1,616,849 ÷ 118,704=？",
        "answer": 1.134204108637724
    },
    {
        "question": "3,968,791 ÷ 1,775=？",
        "answer": 3.349459871791529
    },
    {
        "question": "16,152 × 3,155=？",
        "answer": 7.707225669515736
    },
    {
        "question": "26,671,762 ÷ 104,184=？",
        "answer": 2.4082506796131438
    },
    {
        "question": "43,060 ÷ 419=？",
        "answer": 2.011860002521173
    },
    {
        "question": "849,983 × 364=？",
        "answer": 8.490511623386851
    },
    {
        "question": "210,750,421 ÷ 32,192=？",
        "answer": 3.816020491814708
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 1,520,544=？",
        "answer": 7.967328826857392
    },
    {
        "question": "541,883 × 266=？",
        "answer": 8.158787163133399
    },
    {
        "question": "854 × 242,831=？",
        "answer": 8.316761999012924
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 111,392,447=？",
        "answer": 8.745825748697717
    },
    {
        "question": "4,058,588 ÷ 3,687,754=？",
        "answer": 0.04161302421077491
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 244,041=？",
        "answer": 6.165614046304027
    },
    {
        "question": "10,189 ÷ 5,668=？",
        "answer": 0.25470172066523966
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 20,780=？",
        "answer": 5.162743583235415
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 26,925,800=？",
        "answer": 8.948682555484828
    },
    {
        "question": "333,749 ÷ 84,358=？",
        "answer": 0.5972936983865696
    },
    {
        "question": "10,384 × 7,092=？",
        "answer": 7.867133406385174
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 93,348=？",
        "answer": 6.669075021872658
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 3,072=？",
        "answer": 4.4416637207987995
    },
    {
        "question": "7,020 × 1,616=？",
        "answer": 7.054778468568372
    },
    {
        "question": "671,937,619 ÷ 175,838,864=？",
        "answer": 0.5822140867707
    },
    {
        "question": "310,864,926 ÷ 3,046=？",
        "answer": 5.008841825603661
    },
    {
        "question": "535 × 1,076,233=？",
        "answer": 8.760260086492693
    },
    {
        "question": "178,962,239 ÷ 559,416=？",
        "answer": 2.5050265210085185
    },
    {
        "question": "22,444 × 21,418=？",
        "answer": 8.681879174262237
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,896=？",
        "answer": 4.139627248480638
    },
    {
        "question": "9,059,038 ÷ 10,125=？",
        "answer": 2.9516870495126333
    },
    {
        "question": "577,723,109 ÷ 20,722,901=？",
        "answer": 1.4452691874885792
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 14,551,667=？",
        "answer": 7.764972739112554
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 4,778=？",
        "answer": 4.524344185428116
    },
    {
        "question": "2,954,012 ÷ 286,772=？",
        "answer": 1.0128755100161013
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 83,044=？",
        "answer": 4.919308259773282
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 5,758=？",
        "answer": 5.061301656206044
    },
    {
        "question": "7,778,223 ÷ 15,019=？",
        "answer": 2.7142393728277416
    },
    {
        "question": "2,703,842 ÷ 10,829=？",
        "answer": 2.3973929561399325
    },
    {
        "question": "530 × 369,838=？",
        "answer": 8.292287401471134
    },
    {
        "question": "95,304,626 ÷ 26,076=？",
        "answer": 3.5628730090415712
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 286=？",
        "answer": 2.9334872878487053
    },
    {
        "question": "273,378,655 ÷ 211=？",
        "answer": 6.112482147188678
    },
    {
        "question": "904,225 ÷ 787=？",
        "answer": 3.0603017778728914
    },
    {
        "question": "95,609 ÷ 5,082=？",
        "answer": 1.274464115101123
    },
    {
        "question": "288 × 4,093=？",
        "answer": 6.0714342324045
    },
    {
        "question": "316,682 ÷ 34,982=？",
        "answer": 0.9567787436065333
    },
    {
        "question": "3,346,421 ÷ 524,717=？",
        "answer": 0.8046554420559446
    },
    {
        "question": "161,428 ÷ 5,890=？",
        "answer": 1.4378635713537407
    },
    {
        "question": "43,593 ÷ 199=？",
        "answer": 2.340563681082708
    },
    {
        "question": "12,054 × 3,788=？",
        "answer": 7.659541157463129
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 811,596=？",
        "answer": 7.4891234945367575
    },
    {
        "question": "43,814 × 3,010=？",
        "answer": 8.120179399505352
    },
    {
        "question": "293,146,676 ÷ 67,295=？",
        "answer": 3.639102176606972
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 118,478=？",
        "answer": 5.073637714349285
    },
    {
        "question": "2,224,938 ÷ 100,138=？",
        "answer": 1.3467190002295257
    },
    {
        "question": "623,748 ÷ 1,297=？",
        "answer": 2.682069190017737
    },
    {
        "question": "575,258,187 ÷ 280=？",
        "answer": 6.312704776865254
    },
    {
        "question": "282,083,382 ÷ 146,326=？",
        "answer": 3.2850560011116188
    },
    {
        "question": "688,336 ÷ 11,930=？",
        "answer": 1.7611600400959386
    },
    {
        "question": "373,820 ÷ 6,062=？",
        "answer": 1.7900466011195004
    },
    {
        "question": "3,987 × 818=？",
        "answer": 6.513399539333718
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 8,970,451=？",
        "answer": 7.9942069634183195
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 24,366=？",
        "answer": 5.784724248545718
    },
    {
        "question": "81 × 1,702,715=？",
        "answer": 8.139626980825168
    },
    {
        "question": "164 × 528=？",
        "answer": 4.93747777058151
    },
    {
        "question": "300 × 22,459=？",
        "answer": 6.828511669861915
    },
    {
        "question": "122,801 × 278=？",
        "answer": 7.533246699308841
    },
    {
        "question": "1,052 × 13,062=？",
        "answer": 7.138025419242458
    },
    {
        "question": "335,038,029 ÷ 26,437=？",
        "answer": 4.102881934054837
    },
    {
        "question": "11,244,134 ÷ 119,243=？",
        "answer": 1.9744931188079997
    },
    {
        "question": "198,693 × 276=？",
        "answer": 7.739091649150253
    },
    {
        "question": "133,021,218 ÷ 807=？",
        "answer": 5.217047385383017
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 404=？",
        "answer": 3.5094713521025485
    },
    {
        "question": "34,770,296 ÷ 274=？",
        "answer": 5.103457825033404
    },
    {
        "question": "119,084 × 2,606=？",
        "answer": 8.491827825432809
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 2,955,104=？",
        "answer": 8.14267062769828
    },
    {
        "question": "26,210 × 25,671=？",
        "answer": 8.827909807655557
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 15,247,909=？",
        "answer": 8.525632972241079
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 1,411,417=？",
        "answer": 7.492078024869541
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 11,811=？",
        "answer": 4.6743466608378546
    },
    {
        "question": "4,867,208 ÷ 50,173=？",
        "answer": 1.9868098365784401
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 143,971=？",
        "answer": 7.24106039152041
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,476,024=？",
        "answer": 6.169093419128504
    },
    {
        "question": "1,277,589 ÷ 2,799=？",
        "answer": 2.659388265418908
    },
    {
        "question": "122 × 6,089,157=？",
        "answer": 8.87091700252113
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 892,793=？",
        "answer": 7.413148774392447
    },
    {
        "question": "19,510,448 ÷ 24,343=？",
        "answer": 2.903893142717753
    },
    {
        "question": "864,115,961 ÷ 278,557=？",
        "answer": 3.4916579504808603
    },
    {
        "question": "138,326 ÷ 76,238=？",
        "answer": 0.25873232388614037
    },
    {
        "question": "73,985 × 10,264=？",
        "answer": 8.880460321509162
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 10,928,081=？",
        "answer": 8.214635164438038
    },
    {
        "question": "250 × 3,018=？",
        "answer": 5.877659244111609
    },
    {
        "question": "845,859 × 1,009=？",
        "answer": 8.931189140829746
    },
    {
        "question": "1,800,888 ÷ 2,911=？",
        "answer": 2.7914444987774627
    },
    {
        "question": "15,574,762 ÷ 682,387=？",
        "answer": 1.3583906742778604
    },
    {
        "question": "859 × 54,204=？",
        "answer": 7.668024500440262
    },
    {
        "question": "110,598,126 ÷ 348,320=？",
        "answer": 2.501769356548747
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 1,748,367=？",
        "answer": 7.761146540570613
    },
    {
        "question": "95,304,251 ÷ 9,986=？",
        "answer": 3.979720710846495
    },
    {
        "question": "192,870 ÷ 271=？",
        "answer": 2.852295389606748
    },
    {
        "question": "605,705 ÷ 1,147=？",
        "answer": 2.7226977408098247
    },
    {
        "question": "246,937,475 ÷ 1,648,526=？",
        "answer": 2.175491201977147
    },
    {
        "question": "506 × 46,503=？",
        "answer": 7.371631487824786
    },
    {
        "question": "2,276,760 ÷ 10,142=？",
        "answer": 2.3511936465512484
    },
    {
        "question": "760,472,576 ÷ 165,097,036=？",
        "answer": 0.6633442808263487
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 38,913,090=？",
        "answer": 8.669276964558032
    },
    {
        "question": "338 × 9,474=？",
        "answer": 6.5054500806695925
    },
    {
        "question": "4,490,585 ÷ 64,366=？",
        "answer": 1.8436464004362925
    },
    {
        "question": "1,803,806 ÷ 102,883=？",
        "answer": 1.243846207682288
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 2,094,918=？",
        "answer": 8.16626506834546
    },
    {
        "question": "287 × 1,555=？",
        "answer": 5.649612290096849
    },
    {
        "question": "83,729 ÷ 1,374=？",
        "answer": 1.7848891716093844
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,185=？",
        "answer": 3.374748346010104
    },
    {
        "question": "76,339 ÷ 474=？",
        "answer": 2.2069681249512243
    },
    {
        "question": "596,069 × 1,028=？",
        "answer": 8.787289650548416
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 121,250=？",
        "answer": 6.928779787288558
    },
    {
        "question": "20,247,013 ÷ 82,918=？",
        "answer": 2.3877121434367954
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 17,141,566=？",
        "answer": 8.012201745572431
    },
    {
        "question": "9,488 ÷ 355=？",
        "answer": 1.4269463229650934
    },
    {
        "question": "1,976,993 ÷ 13,888=？",
        "answer": 2.153365423764131
    },
    {
        "question": "10,749 × 7,290=？",
        "answer": 7.894095591203747
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 161,697=？",
        "answer": 6.487455563372947
    },
    {
        "question": "54,321,194 ÷ 2,103,563=？",
        "answer": 1.4120137840171154
    },
    {
        "question": "573,319 ÷ 81,079=？",
        "answer": 0.8494879510722086
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 175,438=？",
        "answer": 6.7212449224434225
    },
    {
        "question": "10,767,575 ÷ 9,133,795=？",
        "answer": 0.07146664543865307
    },
    {
        "question": "210,138,495 ÷ 57,287,444=？",
        "answer": 0.5644461718215186
    },
    {
        "question": "669,184,803 ÷ 445,259,757=？",
        "answer": 0.1769326247390271
    },
    {
        "question": "331,161 ÷ 181,886=？",
        "answer": 0.26023991320934786
    },
    {
        "question": "790 × 128,363=？",
        "answer": 8.006066949824694
    },
    {
        "question": "124,686,477 ÷ 694=？",
        "answer": 5.254459883723396
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 88,336,504=？",
        "answer": 8.24717020331499
    },
    {
        "question": "11,313,605 ÷ 3,233,041=？",
        "answer": 0.5439897996570191
    },
    {
        "question": "4,308 × 41,188=？",
        "answer": 8.249046398695693
    },
    {
        "question": "708 × 11,604=？",
        "answer": 6.914640977820396
    },
    {
        "question": "68,935,892 ÷ 54,666=？",
        "answer": 3.100728102519044
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 73,340,733=？",
        "answer": 7.865345246179048
    },
    {
        "question": "2,956 ÷ 2,818=？",
        "answer": 0.02076344094945048
    },
    {
        "question": "1,217 × 456=？",
        "answer": 5.7442554208945
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 11,881=？",
        "answer": 5.074852995881248
    },
    {
        "question": "4,660,367 ÷ 611=？",
        "answer": 3.8823789081210367
    },
    {
        "question": "1,111,045 × 579=？",
        "answer": 8.808410212997652
    },
    {
        "question": "2,511 × 1,836=？",
        "answer": 6.663719389578146
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 167,814=？",
        "answer": 7.237665414029322
    },
    {
        "question": "101 × 2,707=？",
        "answer": 5.436809629553149
    },
    {
        "question": "405,458 × 786=？",
        "answer": 8.503368419844447
    },
    {
        "question": "2,685,043 ÷ 343,533=？",
        "answer": 0.8929827831559921
    },
    {
        "question": "350 × 703,040=？",
        "answer": 8.391048079590693
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 413,326=？",
        "answer": 6.61629272514954
    },
    {
        "question": "29,464,077 ÷ 681,351=？",
        "answer": 1.6359219431551664
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 7,941,251=？",
        "answer": 8.261616759049335
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 20,123=？",
        "answer": 5.206782714187061
    },
    {
        "question": "26,264,467 ÷ 17,082=？",
        "answer": 3.1868298743091716
    },
    {
        "question": "542 × 244=？",
        "answer": 5.121389112877116
    },
    {
        "question": "162 × 536,207=？",
        "answer": 7.93884749379324
    },
    {
        "question": "454,217,623 ÷ 18,996,998=？",
        "answer": 1.3785790032177125
    },
    {
        "question": "120,406 ÷ 3,697=？",
        "answer": 1.5127986783916045
    },
    {
        "question": "272,070 × 1,962=？",
        "answer": 8.727379659661072
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 776,855=？",
        "answer": 6.589309969628004
    },
    {
        "question": "335,189 ÷ 6,967=？",
        "answer": 1.6822439472825952
    },
    {
        "question": "41,495,252 ÷ 6,961,929=？",
        "answer": 0.7752688164993216
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 3,653=？",
        "answer": 4.2616196765479355
    },
    {
        "question": "250,346,220 ÷ 194,742=？",
        "answer": 3.1090814124363915
    },
    {
        "question": "3,903,148 ÷ 210,101=？",
        "answer": 1.2689868997342686
    },
    {
        "question": "680,091,966 ÷ 135,354=？",
        "answer": 3.7010965498824113
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 248=？",
        "answer": 2.6954816764901977
    },
    {
        "question": "26,016 ÷ 17,325=？",
        "answer": 0.1765672806301298
    },
    {
        "question": "3,981,095 ÷ 94,985=？",
        "answer": 1.6223475141203636
    },
    {
        "question": "15,859,389 ÷ 194,588=？",
        "answer": 1.9111703972849319
    },
    {
        "question": "557,362 ÷ 399=？",
        "answer": 3.145164460235425
    },
    {
        "question": "173,748,001 ÷ 1,354=？",
        "answer": 5.108301152310647
    },
    {
        "question": "111 × 8,656=？",
        "answer": 5.982640226549152
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,761,614=？",
        "answer": 6.9448807574274705
    },
    {
        "question": "514,201,593 ÷ 2,131,832=？",
        "answer": 2.38238044082928
    },
    {
        "question": "973,489,225 ÷ 497=？",
        "answer": 6.2919747601900635
    },
    {
        "question": "105,308,741 ÷ 59,420,455=？",
        "answer": 0.24852844766636673
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 2,571,041=？",
        "answer": 7.255207042340424
    },
    {
        "question": "2,031 × 34,378=？",
        "answer": 7.843990530653189
    },
    {
        "question": "30,386 × 3,742=？",
        "answer": 8.05577731666732
    },
    {
        "question": "356,558,507 ÷ 780,015=？",
        "answer": 2.660027848154746
    },
    {
        "question": "126 × 250=？",
        "answer": 4.498310553789601
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 203,784=？",
        "answer": 6.485261341648117
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,313=？",
        "answer": 4.072507235528804
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 215,884=？",
        "answer": 5.811341710999229
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 12,390=？",
        "answer": 4.695131297704026
    },
    {
        "question": "684,947 ÷ 1,093=？",
        "answer": 2.797036805895936
    },
    {
        "question": "320 ÷ 200=？",
        "answer": 0.2041199826559248
    },
    {
        "question": "2,774,918 ÷ 14,230=？",
        "answer": 2.2900452539784872
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 339=？",
        "answer": 3.308350948586726
    },
    {
        "question": "179 × 302,149=？",
        "answer": 7.733074192214706
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 241=？",
        "answer": 4.268507767747351
    },
    {
        "question": "772 × 139,143=？",
        "answer": 8.031078663087424
    },
    {
        "question": "1,562 × 211=？",
        "answer": 5.517963484838974
    },
    {
        "question": "82,319 × 1,026=？",
        "answer": 7.926647446812003
    },
    {
        "question": "202 × 837,618=？",
        "answer": 8.2283973709931
    },
    {
        "question": "1,783,144 ÷ 696=？",
        "answer": 3.4085771769692474
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 5,103,466=？",
        "answer": 7.963137730889686
    },
    {
        "question": "561,213 ÷ 11,579=？",
        "answer": 1.6854566685875325
    },
    {
        "question": "832,726 ÷ 1,185=？",
        "answer": 2.8467837743941367
    },
    {
        "question": "9,949 × 63,122=？",
        "answer": 8.797960181764104
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 110,491,439=？",
        "answer": 8.742298634039564
    },
    {
        "question": "2,286 × 910=？",
        "answer": 6.318117618380357
    },
    {
        "question": "89,923,470 ÷ 1,095=？",
        "answer": 4.914458938087722
    },
    {
        "question": "24,971,792 ÷ 20,253,649=？",
        "answer": 0.09094642956880922
    },
    {
        "question": "505,411,745 ÷ 24,513=？",
        "answer": 4.314248864825695
    },
    {
        "question": "17,176,106 ÷ 613=？",
        "answer": 4.447464237107322
    },
    {
        "question": "507,461,687 ÷ 249=？",
        "answer": 6.309203911799681
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 230,717=？",
        "answer": 5.363079595969656
    },
    {
        "question": "107,409,874 ÷ 668,229=？",
        "answer": 2.20611888777173
    },
    {
        "question": "1,475 × 4,127=？",
        "answer": 6.784426489191598
    },
    {
        "question": "1,001,685 × 909=？",
        "answer": 8.959295053585794
    },
    {
        "question": "3,408 × 202=？",
        "answer": 5.8378509555412865
    },
    {
        "question": "865,544,371 ÷ 8,087=？",
        "answer": 5.029501893210005
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 244,413=？",
        "answer": 6.166275552110114
    },
    {
        "question": "3,520 ÷ 685=？",
        "answer": 0.7108520919857054
    },
    {
        "question": "8,032 × 3,119=？",
        "answer": 7.398839074558088
    },
    {
        "question": "10,086,596 ÷ 4,691,379=？",
        "answer": 0.3324441068247904
    },
    {
        "question": "74,515 × 731=？",
        "answer": 7.736161082746459
    },
    {
        "question": "421,098,795 ÷ 4,502,006=？",
        "answer": 1.9709779291955973
    },
    {
        "question": "385 × 1,174,419=？",
        "answer": 8.655283798245692
    },
    {
        "question": "33,497 ÷ 32,474=？",
        "answer": 0.013470126907197481
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,638=？",
        "answer": 3.2143138974244
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,206=？",
        "answer": 3.3823773034681137
    },
    {
        "question": "52,703,010 ÷ 581,940=？",
        "answer": 1.9569572098441805
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 15,667,345=？",
        "answer": 7.194995406836015
    },
    {
        "question": "254,698,393 ÷ 10,191,329=？",
        "answer": 1.3977953829641507
    },
    {
        "question": "905,655,588 ÷ 7,792=？",
        "answer": 5.065314127240373
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 253,353=？",
        "answer": 6.658998556322188
    },
    {
        "question": "693,449,875 ÷ 170,295,140=？",
        "answer": 0.609812820264245
    },
    {
        "question": "11,688,791 ÷ 98,504=？",
        "answer": 2.0743157268896324
    },
    {
        "question": "73,914 × 681=？",
        "answer": 7.7018738175186305
    },
    {
        "question": "118,519 ÷ 88,964=？",
        "answer": 0.12457367705011071
    },
    {
        "question": "1,816,705 ÷ 26,705=？",
        "answer": 1.8326918291671441
    },
    {
        "question": "1,244,155 ÷ 343=？",
        "answer": 3.559580369195746
    },
    {
        "question": "545,749 ÷ 24,647=？",
        "answer": 1.3452288835205015
    },
    {
        "question": "4,058 ÷ 281=？",
        "answer": 1.1596057227922474
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 10,681=？",
        "answer": 5.662080370645817
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 353,413,820=？",
        "answer": 8.548283528284461
    },
    {
        "question": "32,407 ÷ 18,222=？",
        "answer": 0.25004278682504044
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 8,070=？",
        "answer": 3.90687353472207
    },
    {
        "question": "91,581,583 ÷ 5,790=？",
        "answer": 4.199129582367749
    },
    {
        "question": "5,313 × 368=？",
        "answer": 6.291187634583255
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 271=？",
        "answer": 3.688241795977712
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 507,687=？",
        "answer": 7.196957736694169
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,374=？",
        "answer": 3.9719249491841913
    },
    {
        "question": "1,257 × 841=？",
        "answer": 6.02413127348387
    },
    {
        "question": "306,828 ÷ 2,734=？",
        "answer": 2.050096478978082
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 72,654=？",
        "answer": 5.338380784298041
    },
    {
        "question": "3,108 ÷ 208=？",
        "answer": 1.174417675166115
    },
    {
        "question": "3,570,984 ÷ 60,368=？",
        "answer": 1.7719811164587187
    },
    {
        "question": "51,974 × 1,467=？",
        "answer": 7.882216255932217
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 9,671,832=？",
        "answer": 8.476870438044864
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 17,925=？",
        "answer": 5.684822928498825
    },
    {
        "question": "462,865,177 ÷ 48,345=？",
        "answer": 3.9811029439192147
    },
    {
        "question": "785 × 201=？",
        "answer": 5.198065714165741
    },
    {
        "question": "564,660 ÷ 7,995=？",
        "answer": 1.8489685557187976
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 10,403,471=？",
        "answer": 8.415118269571707
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 40,179=？",
        "answer": 5.9464218043771355
    },
    {
        "question": "103,608,666 ÷ 4,144,582=？",
        "answer": 1.3979153455210498
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 100,848=？",
        "answer": 5.00366728978154
    },
    {
        "question": "3,041,331 ÷ 112,942=？",
        "answer": 1.430208214646568
    },
    {
        "question": "186,267 × 679=？",
        "answer": 8.102005694193558
    },
    {
        "question": "9,353,496 ÷ 1,185=？",
        "answer": 3.8972556145083903
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 635,012=？",
        "answer": 6.705871919346188
    },
    {
        "question": "5,136 × 41,276=？",
        "answer": 8.32632261884229
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 30,298,702=？",
        "answer": 7.782454019337503
    },
    {
        "question": "10,356,443 ÷ 307=？",
        "answer": 4.5280722437615655
    },
    {
        "question": "5,013,579 ÷ 367,488=？",
        "answer": 1.1349047004548283
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,250=？",
        "answer": 3.6283889300503116
    },
    {
        "question": "653,922 ÷ 249,672=？",
        "answer": 0.4181561084462286
    },
    {
        "question": "1,332 × 41,197=？",
        "answer": 7.739369816331419
    },
    {
        "question": "4,355 ÷ 724=？",
        "answer": 0.7792495931465351
    },
    {
        "question": "29,252,816 ÷ 1,146=？",
        "answer": 4.406983061825969
    },
    {
        "question": "27,145,705 ÷ 50,610=？",
        "answer": 2.7294647878736953
    },
    {
        "question": "68,103 × 5,014=？",
        "answer": 8.53335057302909
    },
    {
        "question": "951,820,718 ÷ 149,760=？",
        "answer": 3.803159322331106
    },
    {
        "question": "35,299,365 ÷ 1,606,195=？",
        "answer": 1.3419686233011134
    },
    {
        "question": "1,849,285 ÷ 546=？",
        "answer": 3.5298112043058305
    },
    {
        "question": "13,032 × 29,555=？",
        "answer": 8.585642034985359
    },
    {
        "question": "83,001,441 ÷ 903,627=？",
        "answer": 1.9630964333095227
    },
    {
        "question": "58,585 × 695=？",
        "answer": 7.609771238848353
    },
    {
        "question": "250 × 21,485=？",
        "answer": 6.73007536669196
    },
    {
        "question": "17,915 ÷ 9,043=？",
        "answer": 0.29690428166093485
    },
    {
        "question": "149 × 781,380=？",
        "answer": 8.06604855935428
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 25,806,623=？",
        "answer": 7.7127611730703025
    },
    {
        "question": "363,683 ÷ 206=？",
        "answer": 3.246855780496542
    },
    {
        "question": "8,546 ÷ 1,006=？",
        "answer": 0.9291649077612691
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 60,397=？",
        "answer": 6.2581366218870995
    },
    {
        "question": "55,513 × 836=？",
        "answer": 7.666600975285023
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 525,680=？",
        "answer": 6.623811441174403
    },
    {
        "question": "14,068 ÷ 6,194=？",
        "answer": 0.356261158624137
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 18,549,247=？",
        "answer": 7.26832628428085
    },
    {
        "question": "1,116 × 254=？",
        "answer": 5.452497911221498
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 304,272=？",
        "answer": 6.182231993483581
    },
    {
        "question": "1,393 × 78,343=？",
        "answer": 8.037951314456587
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 78,267=？",
        "answer": 5.592548691823778
    },
    {
        "question": "58,993,157 ÷ 223,090=？",
        "answer": 2.422321534433872
    },
    {
        "question": "30,251 × 14,544=？",
        "answer": 8.64342360147146
    },
    {
        "question": "19,274,409 ÷ 750,488=？",
        "answer": 1.4096373179664312
    },
    {
        "question": "378 × 329,111=？",
        "answer": 8.094834197961026
    },
    {
        "question": "1,550,717 ÷ 11,128=？",
        "answer": 2.144115430956903
    },
    {
        "question": "36,906 × 1,999=？",
        "answer": 7.867909771525508
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 264,130=？",
        "answer": 6.26691577137839
    },
    {
        "question": "624,771,316 ÷ 8,494,794=？",
        "answer": 1.8665682307188116
    },
    {
        "question": "119 × 252,073=？",
        "answer": 7.477073291483959
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 953=？",
        "answer": 3.2801228963023075
    },
    {
        "question": "655,301 ÷ 503=？",
        "answer": 3.1148728456411705
    },
    {
        "question": "215,935,540 ÷ 834=？",
        "answer": 5.413158076437751
    },
    {
        "question": "9,629,199 ÷ 4,324=？",
        "answer": 3.347704476781134
    },
    {
        "question": "179,677,626 ÷ 10,447,654=？",
        "answer": 1.235475219387621
    },
    {
        "question": "513,900 ÷ 47,741=？",
        "answer": 1.0319871060321701
    },
    {
        "question": "552 × 258,105=？",
        "answer": 8.153735495490334
    },
    {
        "question": "6,009 × 62,108=？",
        "answer": 8.571949748345752
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 74,128=？",
        "answer": 5.86998228285908
    },
    {
        "question": "63,405,798 ÷ 4,285=？",
        "answer": 4.170178146516433
    },
    {
        "question": "455 × 2,223=？",
        "answer": 6.004950859356103
    },
    {
        "question": "21,573,529 ÷ 18,194,953=？",
        "answer": 0.07397025476495168
    },
    {
        "question": "105,070 ÷ 1,817=？",
        "answer": 1.762123804949493
    },
    {
        "question": "526,026,048 ÷ 589,879=？",
        "answer": 2.9502443149459716
    },
    {
        "question": "1,458 × 3,523=？",
        "answer": 6.710670167163198
    },
    {
        "question": "1,192 ÷ 303=？",
        "answer": 0.5948336269019127
    },
    {
        "question": "32,669 × 9,415=？",
        "answer": 8.487956165252097
    },
    {
        "question": "3,050 × 4,695=？",
        "answer": 7.155935435948916
    },
    {
        "question": "376,646,870 ÷ 55,047,967=？",
        "answer": 0.835193078233288
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 404,306=？",
        "answer": 6.208770177745872
    },
    {
        "question": "2,872,716 ÷ 532,809=？",
        "answer": 0.7317211411075756
    },
    {
        "question": "2,472,058 ÷ 55,027=？",
        "answer": 1.65248281976453
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,332=？",
        "answer": 4.238447577141119
    },
    {
        "question": "206,818 × 794=？",
        "answer": 8.215408836464487
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,240=？",
        "answer": 3.9876662649262746
    },
    {
        "question": "23,133,919 ÷ 3,679,470=？",
        "answer": 0.7984639443082823
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 798=？",
        "answer": 3.6009728956867484
    },
    {
        "question": "20,144,099 ÷ 1,160=？",
        "answer": 4.239689857921701
    },
    {
        "question": "745,734,794 ÷ 723,656=？",
        "answer": 3.01305223929267
    },
    {
        "question": "137 × 744,657=？",
        "answer": 8.008676843516369
    },
    {
        "question": "203,246,229 ÷ 9,180=？",
        "answer": 4.345179815305039
    },
    {
        "question": "2,760,915 ÷ 495=？",
        "answer": 3.746447837332929
    },
    {
        "question": "2,426 ÷ 242=？",
        "answer": 1.0010754305501228
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 212=？",
        "answer": 2.326335860928751
    },
    {
        "question": "91,889 ÷ 14,076=？",
        "answer": 0.8147842670942265
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 263,345=？",
        "answer": 5.420525077039337
    },
    {
        "question": "18,486,183 ÷ 881,836=？",
        "answer": 1.3214594234725994
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 348=？",
        "answer": 3.3197304943302246
    },
    {
        "question": "20,409 ÷ 9,313=？",
        "answer": 0.3407321227253083
    },
    {
        "question": "30,182,258 ÷ 9,668,971=？",
        "answer": 0.4943714695034585
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 3,232=？",
        "answer": 4.68556261115823
    },
    {
        "question": "10,911,906 ÷ 935=？",
        "answer": 4.067089005250632
    },
    {
        "question": "1,288,278 ÷ 13,198=？",
        "answer": 1.989501466356645
    },
    {
        "question": "252,629,524 ÷ 11,021,335=？",
        "answer": 1.3602499005558832
    },
    {
        "question": "419,685,197 ÷ 983,866=？",
        "answer": 2.6299876985118584
    },
    {
        "question": "36,303 × 6,072=？",
        "answer": 8.343274278546415
    },
    {
        "question": "133 × 31,497=？",
        "answer": 6.622120831407742
    },
    {
        "question": "62,741 ÷ 913=？",
        "answer": 1.837080658902991
    },
    {
        "question": "50,778,983 ÷ 2,921=？",
        "answer": 4.240152441613956
    },
    {
        "question": "25,905,132 ÷ 17,465=？",
        "answer": 3.1712172196093493
    },
    {
        "question": "88,563,450 ÷ 142,954=？",
        "answer": 2.7920582143242685
    },
    {
        "question": "4,278,374 ÷ 4,629=？",
        "answer": 2.9657915655669274
    },
    {
        "question": "344 × 2,119=？",
        "answer": 5.862689399282325
    },
    {
        "question": "180 × 20,515=？",
        "answer": 6.5673440264062375
    },
    {
        "question": "888,927,210 ÷ 2,619=？",
        "answer": 5.5307307017017955
    },
    {
        "question": "110,129 × 396=？",
        "answer": 7.63959688166007
    },
    {
        "question": "21,988,886 ÷ 310,759=？",
        "answer": 1.8497795124595988
    },
    {
        "question": "1,428,667 ÷ 7,655=？",
        "answer": 2.2709858182804794
    },
    {
        "question": "963 × 77,010=？",
        "answer": 7.8701734105156405
    },
    {
        "question": "123,166,783 ÷ 89,771=？",
        "answer": 3.1373575351964913
    },
    {
        "question": "49,508 × 375=？",
        "answer": 7.268706649997236
    },
    {
        "question": "29,584,803 ÷ 603,616=？",
        "answer": 1.690307938667606
    },
    {
        "question": "859,242,516 ÷ 10,279=？",
        "answer": 4.92216489206257
    },
    {
        "question": "15,565 ÷ 1,906=？",
        "answer": 0.9120262287162265
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 149,769,767=？",
        "answer": 8.17542415414972
    },
    {
        "question": "921,802 ÷ 63,638=？",
        "answer": 1.1609211237774941
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 5,061,761=？",
        "answer": 8.11927498329491
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 7,723=？",
        "answer": 5.693966008822259
    },
    {
        "question": "458,495 ÷ 790=？",
        "answer": 2.763707512653985
    },
    {
        "question": "191 × 1,258=？",
        "answer": 5.3807140083569776
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 752=？",
        "answer": 3.1772478362556233
    },
    {
        "question": "979,165,929 ÷ 577=？",
        "answer": 6.229680480223445
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 23,770=？",
        "answer": 4.677059177392161
    },
    {
        "question": "225,548 ÷ 267=？",
        "answer": 2.926727719070197
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 8,610=？",
        "answer": 4.236033147117636
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 646,697,024=？",
        "answer": 8.810700862395468
    },
    {
        "question": "593,773,327 ÷ 67,804,974=？",
        "answer": 0.9423591309050421
    },
    {
        "question": "20,820 ÷ 2,536=？",
        "answer": 0.9143314759648222
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 24,612=？",
        "answer": 5.692176902079972
    },
    {
        "question": "242,122,318 ÷ 50,764,807=？",
        "answer": 0.6784720836515835
    },
    {
        "question": "2,252,140 ÷ 216=？",
        "answer": 4.018141632958054
    },
    {
        "question": "3,314 × 442=？",
        "answer": 6.1657747734324095
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 28,134=？",
        "answer": 5.051291474450456
    },
    {
        "question": "9,122 × 102,747=？",
        "answer": 8.971859218137054
    },
    {
        "question": "479,743,947 ÷ 627=？",
        "answer": 5.883741963053952
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 289=？",
        "answer": 2.4608978427565478
    },
    {
        "question": "15,999,266 ÷ 68,297=？",
        "answer": 2.3696984315693106
    },
    {
        "question": "5,166 × 2,030=？",
        "answer": 7.020650439750511
    },
    {
        "question": "850,083,263 ÷ 612,679,095=？",
        "answer": 0.14222840340434792
    },
    {
        "question": "14,279 ÷ 417=？",
        "answer": 1.5345617386226305
    },
    {
        "question": "60,040 ÷ 27,178=？",
        "answer": 0.3442231892660851
    },
    {
        "question": "328,833 ÷ 940=？",
        "answer": 2.543847541030935
    },
    {
        "question": "254,775 ÷ 6,645=？",
        "answer": 1.5836618249829773
    },
    {
        "question": "2,176,330 ÷ 8,253=？",
        "answer": 2.4211129035973045
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 939=？",
        "answer": 3.4497868469857735
    },
    {
        "question": "16,344,525 ÷ 28,674=？",
        "answer": 2.7558840228509562
    },
    {
        "question": "1,902,149 ÷ 4,409=？",
        "answer": 2.6349044344602963
    },
    {
        "question": "2,491,606 × 273=？",
        "answer": 8.832642015062314
    },
    {
        "question": "25,646 ÷ 1,852=？",
        "answer": 1.1413786555855778
    },
    {
        "question": "9,898,582 ÷ 771,924=？",
        "answer": 1.1079984412825703
    },
    {
        "question": "11,498,628 ÷ 6,530=？",
        "answer": 3.245732842767593
    },
    {
        "question": "2,311 ÷ 352=？",
        "answer": 0.8172572820009784
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 24,598=？",
        "answer": 5.1690510475571765
    },
    {
        "question": "1,199,321 ÷ 388,480=？",
        "answer": 0.48956677314444047
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 852,790=？",
        "answer": 6.407963353800985
    },
    {
        "question": "238 × 4,575=？",
        "answer": 6.036968055458979
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 15,209,113=？",
        "answer": 8.687253864927916
    },
    {
        "question": "139,378,092 ÷ 4,360,250=？",
        "answer": 1.5046831242401286
    },
    {
        "question": "5,108 × 70,720=？",
        "answer": 8.557793140596395
    },
    {
        "question": "12,861 ÷ 207=？",
        "answer": 1.7933043927733774
    },
    {
        "question": "2,273,824 ÷ 51,984=？",
        "answer": 1.6408871521085453
    },
    {
        "question": "20,470 × 291=？",
        "answer": 6.775010831648413
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 5,696=？",
        "answer": 5.575113916170668
    },
    {
        "question": "427,792 ÷ 57,026=？",
        "answer": 0.8751597489675771
    },
    {
        "question": "234,780 ÷ 11,114=？",
        "answer": 1.3247907058349635
    },
    {
        "question": "24,400,588 ÷ 401=？",
        "answer": 4.784255919377501
    },
    {
        "question": "2,830,372 ÷ 1,254=？",
        "answer": 3.3535459827504153
    },
    {
        "question": "143,176,705 ÷ 37,791=？",
        "answer": 3.5784839794747008
    },
    {
        "question": "2,758,785 × 300=？",
        "answer": 8.917839110707387
    },
    {
        "question": "52,019 × 9,205=？",
        "answer": 8.680185792013685
    },
    {
        "question": "197,857,568 ÷ 54,710,142=？",
        "answer": 0.5582848245807144
    },
    {
        "question": "392,728 ÷ 373,250=？",
        "answer": 0.022092049507919962
    },
    {
        "question": "22,616 × 538=？",
        "answer": 7.085198071147852
    },
    {
        "question": "987,111 ÷ 225=？",
        "answer": 3.6421834734407303
    },
    {
        "question": "434,416,286 ÷ 2,872,353=？",
        "answer": 2.1796682865197687
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 4,768,698=？",
        "answer": 8.140797817483902
    },
    {
        "question": "17,104 × 32,566=？",
        "answer": 8.745862106404712
    },
    {
        "question": "15,522,842 ÷ 5,206=？",
        "answer": 3.4744670732470815
    },
    {
        "question": "804,480 ÷ 685=？",
        "answer": 3.0698246801774194
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 943,644=？",
        "answer": 5.974808182861812
    },
    {
        "question": "104,964,305 ÷ 1,763=？",
        "answer": 4.77478932222658
    },
    {
        "question": "2,327,512 ÷ 66,915=？",
        "answer": 1.5413684464625692
    },
    {
        "question": "602,233,033 ÷ 30,204,039=？",
        "answer": 1.2996995508908424
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 452,614=？",
        "answer": 7.685111760862718
    },
    {
        "question": "157,494,334 ÷ 42,705,178=？",
        "answer": 0.5667843978781317
    },
    {
        "question": "439 × 8,507=？",
        "answer": 6.572240953047023
    },
    {
        "question": "381,082,378 ÷ 30,562,394=？",
        "answer": 1.0958314964035785
    },
    {
        "question": "429,754,395 ÷ 55,086=？",
        "answer": 3.8921790890367975
    },
    {
        "question": "217,062 ÷ 74,203=？",
        "answer": 0.46616233626313
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,271=？",
        "answer": 3.4051755462179893
    },
    {
        "question": "1,064,516 ÷ 5,383=？",
        "answer": 2.2961278135861685
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 567=？",
        "answer": 3.230704313612569
    },
    {
        "question": "24,610,041 ÷ 548=？",
        "answer": 4.6523317787478495
    },
    {
        "question": "375 ÷ 367=？",
        "answer": 0.009365203475629556
    },
    {
        "question": "86,756 × 1,424=？",
        "answer": 8.09180950938372
    },
    {
        "question": "24,088,355 ÷ 522=？",
        "answer": 4.664136639926096
    },
    {
        "question": "724,378,431 ÷ 5,811,316=？",
        "answer": 2.0956910187696405
    },
    {
        "question": "14,370,683 ÷ 2,096,848=？",
        "answer": 0.8359104597707632
    },
    {
        "question": "105,833,411 ÷ 18,312=？",
        "answer": 3.761887013952325
    },
    {
        "question": "709 ÷ 304=？",
        "answer": 0.3677726515743128
    },
    {
        "question": "516,023,052 ÷ 650,177=？",
        "answer": 2.899637500775185
    },
    {
        "question": "36,738 × 1,687=？",
        "answer": 7.792230592408502
    },
    {
        "question": "8,140,557 ÷ 257,191=？",
        "answer": 1.500398354509637
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 10,365,059=？",
        "answer": 7.492693033248095
    },
    {
        "question": "634 ÷ 246=？",
        "answer": 0.41115415077835354
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,830=？",
        "answer": 3.739572344450092
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 85,572=？",
        "answer": 5.8354216694874115
    },
    {
        "question": "439,561 ÷ 36,402=？",
        "answer": 1.0818939074042884
    },
    {
        "question": "70,532,172 ÷ 4,192,829=？",
        "answer": 1.225880107380059
    },
    {
        "question": "2,604 × 2,002=？",
        "answer": 6.717105053039454
    },
    {
        "question": "200,476 ÷ 712=？",
        "answer": 2.4495823948333597
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 1,446=？",
        "answer": 4.691647210000768
    },
    {
        "question": "1,341 × 10,829=？",
        "answer": 7.162017131565223
    },
    {
        "question": "536,581 ÷ 9,209=？",
        "answer": 1.765422817540446
    },
    {
        "question": "76,186,578 ÷ 3,547=？",
        "answer": 4.332017278747312
    },
    {
        "question": "378,960,960 ÷ 520=？",
        "answer": 5.862591128259723
    },
    {
        "question": "19,847 ÷ 8,288=？",
        "answer": 0.3792451272919156
    },
    {
        "question": "43,376 ÷ 7,424=？",
        "answer": 0.7666115370256047
    },
    {
        "question": "67,696 ÷ 1,942=？",
        "answer": 1.5423137824152333
    },
    {
        "question": "6,681,862 ÷ 1,421,529=？",
        "answer": 0.6721417779717878
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 1,551,124=？",
        "answer": 7.83409919406972
    },
    {
        "question": "56,687,750 ÷ 1,624,807=？",
        "answer": 1.5426874382708593
    },
    {
        "question": "446,202,430 ÷ 4,164,701=？",
        "answer": 2.029948103923406
    },
    {
        "question": "333,833,777 ÷ 34,984,129=？",
        "answer": 0.9796592103384335
    },
    {
        "question": "2,051 ÷ 1,394=？",
        "answer": 0.16770288660637564
    },
    {
        "question": "694,429,037 ÷ 59,671,571=？",
        "answer": 1.0658604003691174
    },
    {
        "question": "1,176,935 ÷ 84,848=？",
        "answer": 1.1421108684293282
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 236,737=？",
        "answer": 5.374266139805079
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 41,385,530=？",
        "answer": 8.461946561337248
    },
    {
        "question": "876,457,494 ÷ 531,098=？",
        "answer": 3.2175561927792704
    },
    {
        "question": "123 × 4,778=？",
        "answer": 5.769151256853257
    },
    {
        "question": "3,944,701 ÷ 595=？",
        "answer": 3.821497124460414
    },
    {
        "question": "620,333 ÷ 38,078=？",
        "answer": 1.2119507555155595
    },
    {
        "question": "27,797,068 ÷ 8,705=？",
        "answer": 3.504230214041189
    },
    {
        "question": "499 × 4,379=？",
        "answer": 6.3394754908155155
    },
    {
        "question": "16,463,980 ÷ 3,497=？",
        "answer": 3.67283919754018
    },
    {
        "question": "48,415 × 1,221=？",
        "answer": 7.771695600134162
    },
    {
        "question": "404 × 59,828=？",
        "answer": 7.383285850094023
    },
    {
        "question": "69,734,161 ÷ 390=？",
        "answer": 5.252380973070486
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 3,073=？",
        "answer": 5.110811850654279
    },
    {
        "question": "422,636 ÷ 1,236=？",
        "answer": 2.533948016604895
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 551,549=？",
        "answer": 6.5866821415308126
    },
    {
        "question": "451,541,359 ÷ 29,938,271=？",
        "answer": 1.1784708204568806
    },
    {
        "question": "131 × 430,020=？",
        "answer": 7.750759950508948
    },
    {
        "question": "189,244,717 ÷ 141,028,784=？",
        "answer": 0.1277160031908969
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 930,857=？",
        "answer": 7.739734980613881
    },
    {
        "question": "1,331 × 12,676=？",
        "answer": 7.227160285992938
    },
    {
        "question": "246 × 782=？",
        "answer": 5.284141860163227
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 162,084=？",
        "answer": 6.054838185925896
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 48,096=？",
        "answer": 5.983138954570795
    },
    {
        "question": "1,803 × 56,540=？",
        "answer": 8.008351530875903
    },
    {
        "question": "215,491,479 ÷ 32,031,568=？",
        "answer": 0.8278519032500978
    },
    {
        "question": "414,248,788 ÷ 193,296,119=？",
        "answer": 0.33103811209367495
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 982=？",
        "answer": 4.837209527801207
    },
    {
        "question": "5,513,647 ÷ 3,321=？",
        "answer": 3.2201700822432673
    },
    {
        "question": "655,377,328 ÷ 38,837,392=？",
        "answer": 1.227241354836955
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 53,723=？",
        "answer": 5.633250243540133
    },
    {
        "question": "843 × 4,988=？",
        "answer": 6.623754019431248
    },
    {
        "question": "139,811,764 ÷ 3,142=？",
        "answer": 4.648337534520711
    },
    {
        "question": "199,900 × 462=？",
        "answer": 7.965454769674243
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 264=？",
        "answer": 2.4216039268698313
    },
    {
        "question": "7,420,355 ÷ 4,825=？",
        "answer": 3.186927365342215
    },
    {
        "question": "209,512,282 ÷ 22,595=？",
        "answer": 3.967197141532368
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 164,144,314=？",
        "answer": 8.215225843256684
    },
    {
        "question": "868 × 1,678=？",
        "answer": 6.163311681669174
    },
    {
        "question": "141,295 × 1,923=？",
        "answer": 8.43410607799907
    },
    {
        "question": "3,271 × 11,879=？",
        "answer": 7.589460426456914
    },
    {
        "question": "6,217,147 ÷ 342,959=？",
        "answer": 1.258348931883984
    },
    {
        "question": "9,686,442 ÷ 568,797=？",
        "answer": 1.231206985229981
    },
    {
        "question": "91,550 × 354=？",
        "answer": 7.510661610663503
    },
    {
        "question": "8,958 ÷ 234=？",
        "answer": 1.5829952006985262
    },
    {
        "question": "93,396,752 ÷ 1,138,280=？",
        "answer": 1.914082668104402
    },
    {
        "question": "247 × 149,089=？",
        "answer": 7.566142555025656
    },
    {
        "question": "184 × 9,976=？",
        "answer": 6.263774263480022
    },
    {
        "question": "334,532 ÷ 36,544=？",
        "answer": 0.9616215847432057
    },
    {
        "question": "12,107,447 ÷ 897=？",
        "answer": 4.130260133567079
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 276,188=？",
        "answer": 5.441204805136898
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 5,609=？",
        "answer": 4.862828792316353
    },
    {
        "question": "385 × 132,717=？",
        "answer": 7.708387285630809
    },
    {
        "question": "176 × 57,345=？",
        "answer": 7.004008224888859
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 946,347=？",
        "answer": 7.453171664433284
    },
    {
        "question": "905,290,801 ÷ 292,203,578=？",
        "answer": 0.49110257784549627
    },
    {
        "question": "523,423,225 ÷ 266,805,951=？",
        "answer": 0.2926574768506914
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 81,611,273=？",
        "answer": 7.911750152179711
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 877,111=？",
        "answer": 5.943054557604399
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 12,392=？",
        "answer": 5.1345340899093745
    },
    {
        "question": "4,934,089 ÷ 2,590=？",
        "answer": 3.2799072148503914
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,952,579=？",
        "answer": 7.193698601152035
    },
    {
        "question": "272,334 ÷ 14,956=？",
        "answer": 1.2602864084736562
    },
    {
        "question": "830 × 683,402=？",
        "answer": 8.75375433781876
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 211,185=？",
        "answer": 5.62569306365182
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 42,673=？",
        "answer": 4.630153175731282
    },
    {
        "question": "56,832 × 7,638=？",
        "answer": 8.637572593799787
    },
    {
        "question": "777,137,494 ÷ 724,763,451=？",
        "answer": 0.03030157832055635
    },
    {
        "question": "90,823 ÷ 39,822=？",
        "answer": 0.35807277507909313
    },
    {
        "question": "160,670 × 1,352=？",
        "answer": 8.3369114852903
    },
    {
        "question": "9,832 × 5,414=？",
        "answer": 7.726160121312885
    },
    {
        "question": "13,121 × 21,634=？",
        "answer": 8.453103760863392
    },
    {
        "question": "725,940 ÷ 433=？",
        "answer": 3.2244128307575592
    },
    {
        "question": "6,069 × 17,030=？",
        "answer": 8.014331785453068
    },
    {
        "question": "1,680 ÷ 1,452=？",
        "answer": 0.06334266536178791
    },
    {
        "question": "85 × 950=？",
        "answer": 4.9071425310031405
    },
    {
        "question": "8,643,189 ÷ 3,875,455=？",
        "answer": 0.3483513113639363
    },
    {
        "question": "1,249,768 ÷ 18,399=？",
        "answer": 1.832035181063985
    },
    {
        "question": "523 × 490,567=？",
        "answer": 8.409200019121798
    },
    {
        "question": "925,556,714 ÷ 54,549,724=？",
        "answer": 1.2296104779672279
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 7,242,530=？",
        "answer": 7.160920298477643
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,727=？",
        "answer": 3.839352328895421
    },
    {
        "question": "703,271 ÷ 18,658=？",
        "answer": 1.5762576205268266
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 2,738=？",
        "answer": 4.7384634394619525
    },
    {
        "question": "13,228,351 ÷ 379,553=？",
        "answer": 1.542233281475456
    },
    {
        "question": "13,573 ÷ 405=？",
        "answer": 1.5252208258782936
    },
    {
        "question": "229,697,134 ÷ 9,131=？",
        "answer": 4.400637233625679
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 51,758,597=？",
        "answer": 8.492133745953556
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 364,620,887=？",
        "answer": 8.561841543224672
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,507,770=？",
        "answer": 6.875510959572531
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 38,002,943=？",
        "answer": 7.579817230279151
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 656,194=？",
        "answer": 6.662130295051173
    },
    {
        "question": "18,796,894 ÷ 18,674=？",
        "answer": 3.002848737872506
    },
    {
        "question": "9,173 × 533=？",
        "answer": 6.689238602534169
    },
    {
        "question": "3,324,312 ÷ 715,276=？",
        "answer": 0.6672281241050175
    },
    {
        "question": "48 × 23,288=？",
        "answer": 6.048373429806341
    },
    {
        "question": "9,898,690 ÷ 606=？",
        "answer": 4.2131050993791765
    },
    {
        "question": "17,572,045 ÷ 722=？",
        "answer": 4.386285109203627
    },
    {
        "question": "16,402,597 ÷ 107,206=？",
        "answer": 2.184693522519705
    },
    {
        "question": "546,324,362 ÷ 94,403,353=？",
        "answer": 0.7624631474883616
    },
    {
        "question": "156,231,682 ÷ 59,064,671=？",
        "answer": 0.42244131921689226
    },
    {
        "question": "904 × 3,387=？",
        "answer": 6.485983627119993
    },
    {
        "question": "267,512,658 ÷ 61,746,283=？",
        "answer": 0.6367335174449213
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 95,685=？",
        "answer": 4.980843861206142
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 36,326,080=？",
        "answer": 8.674161887350342
    },
    {
        "question": "226,276 ÷ 282=？",
        "answer": 2.9043893845646283
    },
    {
        "question": "326 × 26,810=？",
        "answer": 6.941514414050818
    },
    {
        "question": "36,709 ÷ 750=？",
        "answer": 1.6897112905375873
    },
    {
        "question": "229 × 35,899=？",
        "answer": 6.914917833410389
    },
    {
        "question": "18,725 ÷ 1,002=？",
        "answer": 1.2715541048402772
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 7,929=？",
        "answer": 5.376339672571035
    },
    {
        "question": "3,502,910 ÷ 13,488=？",
        "answer": 2.414481421885301
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 4,458,665=？",
        "answer": 8.44854539248789
    },
    {
        "question": "729 × 946,192=？",
        "answer": 8.83870680011069
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 12,688=？",
        "answer": 5.942242260710784
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 63,737,617=？",
        "answer": 8.503365826525242
    },
    {
        "question": "466,848,354 ÷ 30,041,285=？",
        "answer": 1.191457326477946
    },
    {
        "question": "18,599 × 43,800=？",
        "answer": 8.910963704928633
    },
    {
        "question": "118,381,354 ÷ 309=？",
        "answer": 5.583324823531203
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 63,068=？",
        "answer": 4.799809058950575
    },
    {
        "question": "133,543 × 429=？",
        "answer": 7.7580784204758615
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 8,480,372=？",
        "answer": 7.882657412875729
    },
    {
        "question": "136 × 295,403=？",
        "answer": 7.603953809897367
    },
    {
        "question": "336,429 ÷ 208=？",
        "answer": 3.2088300897289224
    },
    {
        "question": "14,146 × 6,754=？",
        "answer": 7.980194710045821
    },
    {
        "question": "4,255,116 ÷ 396,081=？",
        "answer": 1.0311273942110109
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 1,133,745=？",
        "answer": 7.28496430614129
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 60,471,499=？",
        "answer": 8.38361072559224
    },
    {
        "question": "5,734,577 ÷ 91,014=？",
        "answer": 1.7993931868070905
    },
    {
        "question": "318,730 ÷ 966=？",
        "answer": 2.5184458163217402
    },
    {
        "question": "422,618,111 ÷ 4,679,843=？",
        "answer": 1.9557168209486604
    },
    {
        "question": "23,636,755 ÷ 68,266=？",
        "answer": 2.5393833972610915
    },
    {
        "question": "443,845 ÷ 45,224=？",
        "answer": 0.9918623593802472
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 197,254=？",
        "answer": 7.263508767331788
    },
    {
        "question": "905 × 426,844=？",
        "answer": 8.586917760276927
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 84,874,806=？",
        "answer": 8.928778794614322
    },
    {
        "question": "584,931,438 ÷ 73,773=？",
        "answer": 3.899207519260024
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 7,606=？",
        "answer": 5.673548010573818
    },
    {
        "question": "192 × 1,061=？",
        "answer": 5.30901661260489
    },
    {
        "question": "561,382,793 ÷ 13,404=？",
        "answer": 4.622024677735694
    },
    {
        "question": "161,162,699 ÷ 98,295=？",
        "answer": 3.2147331049174235
    },
    {
        "question": "43,258,996 ÷ 3,146,588=？",
        "answer": 1.1382365535790735
    },
    {
        "question": "194,008,697 ÷ 11,153=？",
        "answer": 4.240429496670242
    },
    {
        "question": "2,692,158 ÷ 268=？",
        "answer": 4.001965750570151
    },
    {
        "question": "7,907 × 2,669=？",
        "answer": 7.324360312585009
    },
    {
        "question": "506,688,351 ÷ 1,953,867=？",
        "answer": 2.4138459218713075
    },
    {
        "question": "3,207 × 782=？",
        "answer": 6.399305712988289
    },
    {
        "question": "22,967,743 ÷ 80,002=？",
        "answer": 2.458017475713124
    },
    {
        "question": "378,864,643 ÷ 5,383=？",
        "answer": 4.847459697440086
    },
    {
        "question": "663,452,858 ÷ 34,232=？",
        "answer": 4.287377795792661
    },
    {
        "question": "157 × 3,039=？",
        "answer": 5.678630352489177
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 260,695=？",
        "answer": 7.329946554080495
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 46,031,812=？",
        "answer": 8.508156110848105
    },
    {
        "question": "296,909 × 751=？",
        "answer": 8.348263299272144
    },
    {
        "question": "10,223,295 ÷ 14,805=？",
        "answer": 2.839182481107148
    },
    {
        "question": "820 ÷ 639=？",
        "answer": 0.10831299422531657
    },
    {
        "question": "407,913,740 ÷ 5,212,860=？",
        "answer": 1.8934922727764993
    },
    {
        "question": "17,895 ÷ 651=？",
        "answer": 1.4391507141578312
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 32,897,301=？",
        "answer": 8.517160268500453
    },
    {
        "question": "700 × 530=？",
        "answer": 5.569373909615046
    },
    {
        "question": "15,270 ÷ 5,033=？",
        "answer": 0.48201210665928174
    },
    {
        "question": "863,570,213 ÷ 2,394=？",
        "answer": 5.557173507794632
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 53,814=？",
        "answer": 6.569744365135797
    },
    {
        "question": "2,104,146 ÷ 219=？",
        "answer": 3.982631756000187
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 92,975,022=？",
        "answer": 8.269396285458933
    },
    {
        "question": "8,667,530 ÷ 364,451=？",
        "answer": 1.376256207301854
    },
    {
        "question": "17,582 ÷ 1,192=？",
        "answer": 1.1687920203141817
    },
    {
        "question": "579 × 1,159=？",
        "answer": 5.8267619996910325
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 189,324,346=？",
        "answer": 8.277206465277018
    },
    {
        "question": "895,535 ÷ 731=？",
        "answer": 3.0881651869958415
    },
    {
        "question": "370,063 ÷ 74,805=？",
        "answer": 0.6943450379369506
    },
    {
        "question": "2,605,667 ÷ 721,527=？",
        "answer": 0.5576663254853648
    },
    {
        "question": "179,595 ÷ 124,893=？",
        "answer": 0.1577561438302785
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 145,420,100=？",
        "answer": 8.46365443462011
    },
    {
        "question": "780,848,140 ÷ 2,549=？",
        "answer": 5.486196744665648
    },
    {
        "question": "40,514 × 2,850=？",
        "answer": 8.062449983768941
    },
    {
        "question": "1,045,682 ÷ 861,001=？",
        "answer": 0.08439597643123577
    },
    {
        "question": "15,775 ÷ 412=？",
        "answer": 1.5830721518830373
    },
    {
        "question": "501,786 ÷ 369,103=？",
        "answer": 0.13337096510977553
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 11,397,742=？",
        "answer": 7.533940076751711
    },
    {
        "question": "630 × 3,226=？",
        "answer": 6.308004912506524
    },
    {
        "question": "3,220 × 241,031=？",
        "answer": 8.889928774283677
    },
    {
        "question": "385,974 ÷ 4,243=？",
        "answer": 1.9588850189237
    },
    {
        "question": "10,845 ÷ 8,839=？",
        "answer": 0.0888264224511575
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 22,867=？",
        "answer": 4.83633044648396
    },
    {
        "question": "141,006,387 ÷ 246=？",
        "answer": 5.758303677722449
    },
    {
        "question": "91,078,289 ÷ 654,722=？",
        "answer": 2.1433579289968807
    },
    {
        "question": "611,829 ÷ 314,604=？",
        "answer": 0.28886581808730705
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 564,295=？",
        "answer": 6.981955123549733
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 10,112,921=？",
        "answer": 7.907966601629188
    },
    {
        "question": "9,671,719 ÷ 1,152,176=？",
        "answer": 0.9239848455743896
    },
    {
        "question": "26,356 × 8,499=？",
        "answer": 8.350247328115598
    },
    {
        "question": "1,275,950 × 245=？",
        "answer": 8.494999740607394
    },
    {
        "question": "1,177,887 ÷ 2,154=？",
        "answer": 2.737857929663665
    },
    {
        "question": "145,344,445 ÷ 35,459=？",
        "answer": 3.6126719542369408
    },
    {
        "question": "33,514,695 ÷ 7,813=？",
        "answer": 3.6324174471474637
    },
    {
        "question": "118 × 1,486,232=？",
        "answer": 8.243968615152882
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 50,793,755=？",
        "answer": 8.961082824950989
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 841=？",
        "answer": 3.623766000133931
    },
    {
        "question": "146,217 ÷ 2,251=？",
        "answer": 1.812622374043901
    },
    {
        "question": "2,256,385 × 261=？",
        "answer": 8.770053711297646
    },
    {
        "question": "7,055 ÷ 6,930=？",
        "answer": 0.007763783478559907
    },
    {
        "question": "714 ÷ 245=？",
        "answer": 0.4645321274116419
    },
    {
        "question": "124,911,569 ÷ 860=？",
        "answer": 5.162104212272141
    },
    {
        "question": "216 × 1,949,319=？",
        "answer": 8.624336667027553
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 62,086=？",
        "answer": 6.372777277176486
    },
    {
        "question": "2,783,320 ÷ 2,724,847=？",
        "answer": 0.009221018618896683
    },
    {
        "question": "52,659,361 ÷ 976=？",
        "answer": 4.732025767147837
    },
    {
        "question": "58,757,102 ÷ 1,442,138=？",
        "answer": 1.610053546948056
    },
    {
        "question": "297,580,014 ÷ 137,549,074=？",
        "answer": 0.33514608886474473
    },
    {
        "question": "61,368,752 ÷ 202,750=？",
        "answer": 2.4809864286421517
    },
    {
        "question": "53,282 ÷ 600=？",
        "answer": 1.9484292678180506
    },
    {
        "question": "157,868,127 ÷ 893=？",
        "answer": 5.247442997495432
    },
    {
        "question": "2,234 × 318,672=？",
        "answer": 8.852427074802097
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,265=？",
        "answer": 3.403120521175818
    },
    {
        "question": "28,203,686 ÷ 4,159=？",
        "answer": 3.83131695053773
    },
    {
        "question": "15,019,951 ÷ 4,407=？",
        "answer": 3.532525465349687
    },
    {
        "question": "129,915 × 290=？",
        "answer": 7.57605729555502
    },
    {
        "question": "625,287,104 ÷ 6,939,603=？",
        "answer": 1.9547448457315624
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 135,204=？",
        "answer": 6.3070807994203975
    },
    {
        "question": "2,428,585 ÷ 665,212=？",
        "answer": 0.5623932332835166
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 132,470,225=？",
        "answer": 8.821088278296866
    },
    {
        "question": "3,866 × 21,805=？",
        "answer": 7.92581794070198
    },
    {
        "question": "8,233,343 ÷ 40,954=？",
        "answer": 2.3032798824880105
    },
    {
        "question": "304,470,976 ÷ 6,726=？",
        "answer": 4.655789036407965
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,038,847=？",
        "answer": 6.618611581283015
    },
    {
        "question": "17,484 ÷ 487=？",
        "answer": 1.5551118366029806
    },
    {
        "question": "232 × 4,766=？",
        "answer": 6.043642022901337
    },
    {
        "question": "3,637 ÷ 233=？",
        "answer": 1.193387380028693
    },
    {
        "question": "139,154,678 ÷ 14,060,916=？",
        "answer": 0.99548419693946
    },
    {
        "question": "356,506,620 ÷ 297=？",
        "answer": 6.07931114939459
    },
    {
        "question": "4,146,566 ÷ 4,528=？",
        "answer": 2.961782164165085
    },
    {
        "question": "432,136 ÷ 380,884=？",
        "answer": 0.05482771823406773
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 742=？",
        "answer": 3.949585151326652
    },
    {
        "question": "87,498,583 ÷ 14,376=？",
        "answer": 3.7843629557755234
    },
    {
        "question": "156,657 ÷ 105,723=？",
        "answer": 0.17078032730394685
    },
    {
        "question": "8,096 × 18,060=？",
        "answer": 8.16498824547321
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,814,279=？",
        "answer": 6.7358253284268415
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 89,398=？",
        "answer": 5.42844905764668
    },
    {
        "question": "5,685,581 ÷ 712=？",
        "answer": 3.9022948574803373
    },
    {
        "question": "34,038,078 ÷ 434=？",
        "answer": 4.894475299645036
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,649=？",
        "answer": 4.269419537511049
    },
    {
        "question": "67,076,062 ÷ 5,400,870=？",
        "answer": 1.0941038336302904
    },
    {
        "question": "186,362,130 ÷ 29,688,514=？",
        "answer": 0.7977692051263094
    },
    {
        "question": "301 × 141,186=？",
        "answer": 7.628358129815371
    },
    {
        "question": "8,657 ÷ 832=？",
        "answer": 1.0172440912265657
    },
    {
        "question": "19,327,789 ÷ 65,300=？",
        "answer": 2.4712689945320716
    },
    {
        "question": "1,384,680 ÷ 20,853=？",
        "answer": 1.8221808761701073
    },
    {
        "question": "7,181,024 ÷ 8,516=？",
        "answer": 2.925950725437023
    },
    {
        "question": "6,361,629 ÷ 1,091,394=？",
        "answer": 0.765586776256903
    },
    {
        "question": "304 × 2,119=？",
        "answer": 5.809004540319548
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 15,223=？",
        "answer": 6.063313839659991
    },
    {
        "question": "909,712,925 ÷ 4,667,654=？",
        "answer": 2.289805709570677
    },
    {
        "question": "14,485 × 724=？",
        "answer": 7.020657065736928
    },
    {
        "question": "38,546 × 457=？",
        "answer": 7.245895517137505
    },
    {
        "question": "79,719 × 232=？",
        "answer": 7.267049827137039
    },
    {
        "question": "539 × 134,578=？",
        "answer": 7.8605628350337335
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,650,687=？",
        "answer": 6.863404594979093
    },
    {
        "question": "3,529,316 ÷ 802,024=？",
        "answer": 0.6435031805552504
    },
    {
        "question": "10,262 × 991=？",
        "answer": 7.007305664804641
    },
    {
        "question": "1,086 × 913,362=？",
        "answer": 8.99647276428031
    },
    {
        "question": "2,827,199 ÷ 60,778=？",
        "answer": 1.667609973744516
    },
    {
        "question": "4,497,171 ÷ 60,407=？",
        "answer": 1.8718521336070477
    },
    {
        "question": "7,603,419 ÷ 985=？",
        "answer": 3.887572693222596
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,146,121=？",
        "answer": 7.047123753357457
    },
    {
        "question": "33,958 × 4,222=？",
        "answer": 8.156460332965766
    },
    {
        "question": "927,830,842 ÷ 10,621,596=？",
        "answer": 1.9412790260977963
    },
    {
        "question": "54,649 × 2,489=？",
        "answer": 8.133607115987537
    },
    {
        "question": "232 × 252,697=？",
        "answer": 7.768088070929613
    },
    {
        "question": "104,607 × 738=？",
        "answer": 7.887617109066103
    },
    {
        "question": "23,575 × 15,676=？",
        "answer": 8.56768695621543
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 241,292=？",
        "answer": 6.336785432618519
    },
    {
        "question": "91,849,902 ÷ 19,698,145=？",
        "answer": 0.668653367258518
    },
    {
        "question": "191,259 × 717=？",
        "answer": 8.137141036399974
    },
    {
        "question": "342,108,098 ÷ 7,432,599=？",
        "answer": 1.663022651851277
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 2,815=？",
        "answer": 4.896636430529584
    },
    {
        "question": "109 × 231=？",
        "answer": 4.401038477832768
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 1,397,398=？",
        "answer": 7.186712802501062
    },
    {
        "question": "1,867,813 ÷ 271,092=？",
        "answer": 0.8382166921521303
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 138,440=？",
        "answer": 5.618382845341753
    },
    {
        "question": "893,317 ÷ 368=？",
        "answer": 3.385157780104207
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 441=？",
        "answer": 2.94546858513182
    },
    {
        "question": "7,956,022 ÷ 19,141=？",
        "answer": 2.6187313521056947
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 17,698,422=？",
        "answer": 7.548964541842561
    },
    {
        "question": "2,130,900 ÷ 706,929=？",
        "answer": 0.4791872715164677
    },
    {
        "question": "2,868,938 ÷ 83,652=？",
        "answer": 1.5352448341189509
    },
    {
        "question": "5,612,944 ÷ 55,058=？",
        "answer": 2.0083702778581096
    },
    {
        "question": "4,026 ÷ 401=？",
        "answer": 1.0017293979324533
    },
    {
        "question": "1,558,548 ÷ 138,572=？",
        "answer": 1.0510446970219596
    },
    {
        "question": "162,472 ÷ 462=？",
        "answer": 2.5461365510309797
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 674,716=？",
        "answer": 7.107874609951047
    },
    {
        "question": "828,688 × 596=？",
        "answer": 8.693637309732102
    },
    {
        "question": "317,363,050 ÷ 173,780,222=？",
        "answer": 0.26155601356134844
    },
    {
        "question": "5,015,120 ÷ 302,350=？",
        "answer": 1.2197713561820387
    },
    {
        "question": "7,190 ÷ 5,532=？",
        "answer": 0.11384671894560966
    },
    {
        "question": "36,738,243 ÷ 212=？",
        "answer": 5.238782521480589
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 254,482=？",
        "answer": 7.435040846962568
    },
    {
        "question": "2,985 ÷ 2,341=？",
        "answer": 0.10554292176876354
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,624=？",
        "answer": 4.1648285343444815
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 27,815=？",
        "answer": 4.745309059940828
    },
    {
        "question": "2,063 × 392,841=？",
        "answer": 8.908716035867428
    },
    {
        "question": "2,428 × 2,818=？",
        "answer": 6.835189671176558
    },
    {
        "question": "35,353,974 ÷ 12,231,781=？",
        "answer": 0.46094854140945557
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,458,171=？",
        "answer": 6.810109540119546
    },
    {
        "question": "825 × 62,868=？",
        "answer": 7.714883593045496
    },
    {
        "question": "171,297,883 ÷ 645=？",
        "answer": 5.424192281096738
    },
    {
        "question": "164 × 12,859=？",
        "answer": 6.324051044367763
    },
    {
        "question": "96 × 233=？",
        "answer": 4.349627154065588
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 8,729,015=？",
        "answer": 7.639935244124113
    },
    {
        "question": "310,896,770 ÷ 3,029=？",
        "answer": 5.011316936717852
    },
    {
        "question": "48,155 × 764=？",
        "answer": 7.5657347457719055
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 128,952=？",
        "answer": 5.587549336999962
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,077,458=？",
        "answer": 6.3334303457508145
    },
    {
        "question": "95 × 10,340,143=？",
        "answer": 8.992250150205521
    },
    {
        "question": "169 × 49,583=？",
        "answer": 6.923219504658015
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 195,218=？",
        "answer": 5.290519859131225
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 40,984,818=？",
        "answer": 8.390774261252636
    },
    {
        "question": "877,992 × 291=？",
        "answer": 8.407383547748863
    },
    {
        "question": "30,146,195 ÷ 167,485=？",
        "answer": 2.2552565864572713
    },
    {
        "question": "46,400 ÷ 5,336=？",
        "answer": 0.9393021596463883
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,050=？",
        "answer": 3.322219294733919
    },
    {
        "question": "1,155 × 114,528=？",
        "answer": 8.121493660938073
    },
    {
        "question": "1,538 × 32,412=？",
        "answer": 7.697662165700488
    },
    {
        "question": "71,342,827 ÷ 253,323=？",
        "answer": 2.4496756919520783
    },
    {
        "question": "582,749 ÷ 5,869=？",
        "answer": 1.9969174274283252
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 79,978,779=？",
        "answer": 8.204004765333826
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 78,694=？",
        "answer": 5.498001612299138
    },
    {
        "question": "2,053 ÷ 588=？",
        "answer": 0.5430116232944534
    },
    {
        "question": "422 × 1,851,974=？",
        "answer": 8.892947336258025
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 20,758,383=？",
        "answer": 7.317193520586439
    },
    {
        "question": "153,999 × 251=？",
        "answer": 7.5871916222143065
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 397=？",
        "answer": 3.2008504980910772
    },
    {
        "question": "2,528,508 ÷ 242,378=？",
        "answer": 1.0183711345046405
    },
    {
        "question": "227,158,738 ÷ 435=？",
        "answer": 5.717840190302961
    },
    {
        "question": "180 × 760,457=？",
        "answer": 8.136347167028562
    },
    {
        "question": "8,921 ÷ 1,036=？",
        "answer": 0.9350537839601668
    },
    {
        "question": "198 × 25,706=？",
        "answer": 6.706699693466897
    },
    {
        "question": "56,565,475 ÷ 475=？",
        "answer": 5.075857828773812
    },
    {
        "question": "44,102 × 765=？",
        "answer": 7.528119720069721
    },
    {
        "question": "4,316 × 593=？",
        "answer": 6.408136129375135
    },
    {
        "question": "811 × 590=？",
        "answer": 5.679872865853301
    },
    {
        "question": "1,055 × 570=？",
        "answer": 5.779127315306203
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 11,043=？",
        "answer": 4.888185112180586
    },
    {
        "question": "37,354 ÷ 22,013=？",
        "answer": 0.22965788086146902
    },
    {
        "question": "27,295 × 576=？",
        "answer": 7.196505582065192
    },
    {
        "question": "1,335,029 ÷ 1,892=？",
        "answer": 2.8485695676446947
    },
    {
        "question": "5,195 × 188,742=？",
        "answer": 8.991454104620987
    },
    {
        "question": "12,678 ÷ 888=？",
        "answer": 1.1546377816573559
    },
    {
        "question": "781,655 ÷ 138,200=？",
        "answer": 0.7525070672376938
    },
    {
        "question": "2,640,003 ÷ 456=？",
        "answer": 3.7626395777215724
    },
    {
        "question": "2,227,090 ÷ 24,105=？",
        "answer": 1.9656306320518282
    },
    {
        "question": "284,043,668 ÷ 6,549=？",
        "answer": 4.63721012184911
    },
    {
        "question": "14,185 ÷ 2,202=？",
        "answer": 0.8090120254961382
    },
    {
        "question": "100 × 91,293=？",
        "answer": 6.960437478761895
    },
    {
        "question": "401,834,149 ÷ 933=？",
        "answer": 5.63416519780477
    },
    {
        "question": "774,146,892 ÷ 8,086,669=？",
        "answer": 1.981053707426305
    },
    {
        "question": "45,823 ÷ 40,552=？",
        "answer": 0.05307124052706309
    },
    {
        "question": "19,158,290 ÷ 2,868=？",
        "answer": 3.824777595914513
    },
    {
        "question": "146 × 277=？",
        "answer": 4.606832624848885
    },
    {
        "question": "24,020 ÷ 208=？",
        "answer": 2.0625096681041257
    },
    {
        "question": "48,409 ÷ 4,818=？",
        "answer": 1.002059315712968
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 23,942=？",
        "answer": 4.379160426466545
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 309,929=？",
        "answer": 6.19023221933207
    },
    {
        "question": "695,065 ÷ 24,921=？",
        "answer": 1.4454599549754854
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 301,706=？",
        "answer": 6.324681987050302
    },
    {
        "question": "382,479 ÷ 321,773=？",
        "answer": 0.07505799561181715
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 427=？",
        "answer": 4.198629599092019
    },
    {
        "question": "9,609 × 4,386=？",
        "answer": 7.624746820724988
    },
    {
        "question": "6,184 ÷ 2,861=？",
        "answer": 0.33475162310500584
    },
    {
        "question": "392 × 169,701=？",
        "answer": 7.822970468520233
    },
    {
        "question": "5,278,564 ÷ 1,185=？",
        "answer": 3.648797441184296
    },
    {
        "question": "188 × 480,908=？",
        "answer": 7.956219850972457
    },
    {
        "question": "114,893 ÷ 17,206=？",
        "answer": 0.8246136509940786
    },
    {
        "question": "7,949,834 ÷ 3,339,479=？",
        "answer": 0.376679343485213
    },
    {
        "question": "1,067,727 ÷ 13,981=？",
        "answer": 1.8829219893122502
    },
    {
        "question": "356 × 2,482,391=？",
        "answer": 8.946320186001198
    },
    {
        "question": "3,921,471 ÷ 2,242,536=？",
        "answer": 0.24270958405861914
    },
    {
        "question": "42,829,045 ÷ 9,531,622=？",
        "answer": 0.6525715796307677
    },
    {
        "question": "52,904 ÷ 27,258=？",
        "answer": 0.28799452249765556
    },
    {
        "question": "1,782 ÷ 655=？",
        "answer": 0.4346663997090729
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 15,477=？",
        "answer": 5.6668080373126335
    },
    {
        "question": "67,339 ÷ 1,796=？",
        "answer": 1.5739603303933922
    },
    {
        "question": "445,592,304 ÷ 105,265=？",
        "answer": 3.6266536865614927
    },
    {
        "question": "58,970 ÷ 7,406=？",
        "answer": 0.9010474200643828
    },
    {
        "question": "8,439,242 ÷ 1,255,325=？",
        "answer": 0.8275472627457454
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 121,280,537=？",
        "answer": 8.685851102567957
    },
    {
        "question": "18,169 ÷ 1,391=？",
        "answer": 1.1160038949256077
    },
    {
        "question": "175 × 85,363=？",
        "answer": 7.1743077182300645
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 8,012,700=？",
        "answer": 6.903778882815468
    },
    {
        "question": "19,719,206 ÷ 245,020=？",
        "answer": 1.9056878884256987
    },
    {
        "question": "153,172,417 ÷ 173,994=？",
        "answer": 2.944646293053509
    },
    {
        "question": "1,115 × 586,652=？",
        "answer": 8.8156554229809
    },
    {
        "question": "30,705,574 ÷ 121,779=？",
        "answer": 2.401644816871537
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 10,357,886=？",
        "answer": 7.316301122480691
    },
    {
        "question": "59,492,315 ÷ 1,523,831=？",
        "answer": 1.5915240643957298
    },
    {
        "question": "10,594,631 ÷ 219,449=？",
        "answer": 1.68375222912111
    },
    {
        "question": "2,573 × 3,059=？",
        "answer": 6.896019263195026
    },
    {
        "question": "11,875 ÷ 668=？",
        "answer": 1.2498571558213585
    },
    {
        "question": "90,160 × 1,899=？",
        "answer": 8.233538867775067
    },
    {
        "question": "256,274,210 ÷ 6,813=？",
        "answer": 4.575366514481503
    },
    {
        "question": "3,751,131 ÷ 130,264=？",
        "answer": 1.459337821327192
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 321=？",
        "answer": 2.506505032404872
    },
    {
        "question": "1,871,246 ÷ 15,695=？",
        "answer": 2.0763695649624574
    },
    {
        "question": "138,729 ÷ 2,044=？",
        "answer": 1.831686364300574
    },
    {
        "question": "231,847,587 ÷ 483=？",
        "answer": 5.681255449497399
    },
    {
        "question": "36,905,154 ÷ 73,012=？",
        "answer": 2.703692776789514
    },
    {
        "question": "28,720 ÷ 340=？",
        "answer": 1.9267055185280075
    },
    {
        "question": "7,940 × 1,264=？",
        "answer": 7.001567576373462
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 7,372,164=？",
        "answer": 8.781408840284904
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 83,497,446=？",
        "answer": 8.398794446310205
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,888,248=？",
        "answer": 6.57708902903614
    },
    {
        "question": "21,139 ÷ 6,721=？",
        "answer": 0.49765054335331066
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,348=？",
        "answer": 3.5247854493212225
    },
    {
        "question": "364,828 × 481=？",
        "answer": 8.244233238757296
    },
    {
        "question": "129,589 ÷ 3,820=？",
        "answer": 1.5305047756440835
    },
    {
        "question": "4,918,795 ÷ 3,294=？",
        "answer": 3.174135128066312
    },
    {
        "question": "207,990,651 ÷ 397=？",
        "answer": 5.719253307476754
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 8,392,781=？",
        "answer": 8.536689747563996
    },
    {
        "question": "1,303 × 185,046=？",
        "answer": 8.382224117428485
    },
    {
        "question": "9,553,818 ÷ 40,257=？",
        "answer": 2.375335556114862
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,915=？",
        "answer": 4.076094046682475
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 54,425,898=？",
        "answer": 8.911896862468902
    },
    {
        "question": "262,250,502 ÷ 639,406=？",
        "answer": 2.6129396209450966
    },
    {
        "question": "48,744,362 ÷ 10,205,987=？",
        "answer": 0.6790693796076303
    },
    {
        "question": "347,816,209 ÷ 83,690,976=？",
        "answer": 0.6186711846072012
    },
    {
        "question": "412 × 279=？",
        "answer": 5.060501419306732
    },
    {
        "question": "16,050 × 278=？",
        "answer": 6.649519832658967
    },
    {
        "question": "34,635,493 ÷ 210=？",
        "answer": 5.217302079010435
    },
    {
        "question": "297 × 53,573=？",
        "answer": 7.201702416148637
    },
    {
        "question": "3,091,527 ÷ 45,611=？",
        "answer": 1.8311034497330256
    },
    {
        "question": "185,591,103 ÷ 79,185,608=？",
        "answer": 0.36991089720687453
    },
    {
        "question": "60,702 × 3,414=？",
        "answer": 8.316466517156353
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 441=？",
        "answer": 3.8997110945711446
    },
    {
        "question": "861 × 4,823=？",
        "answer": 6.618320413375537
    },
    {
        "question": "1,337,114 ÷ 1,649=？",
        "answer": 2.9089477803836044
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 546,451=？",
        "answer": 6.038581220716972
    },
    {
        "question": "99 × 103,426=？",
        "answer": 7.010264923269594
    },
    {
        "question": "1,070 × 41,368=？",
        "answer": 7.646048302449223
    },
    {
        "question": "121,803,030 ÷ 1,601,175=？",
        "answer": 1.8812192914255546
    },
    {
        "question": "68 × 1,238,870=？",
        "answer": 7.925534649070395
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 20,024,399=？",
        "answer": 8.301559490304316
    },
    {
        "question": "15,301 ÷ 6,297=？",
        "answer": 0.38558612184820856
    },
    {
        "question": "948,033,102 ÷ 56,042=？",
        "answer": 4.228309875863749
    },
    {
        "question": "459,260,238 ÷ 565=？",
        "answer": 5.910010398720402
    },
    {
        "question": "88,132,122 ÷ 9,811=？",
        "answer": 3.953420951254553
    },
    {
        "question": "234,921,407 ÷ 66,542=？",
        "answer": 3.547826743298324
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 1,750=？",
        "answer": 4.565257343420214
    },
    {
        "question": "2,139 × 200,300=？",
        "answer": 8.631891733865105
    },
    {
        "question": "159,105 × 2,178=？",
        "answer": 8.539741703327111
    },
    {
        "question": "473 × 155,110=？",
        "answer": 7.865500938582496
    },
    {
        "question": "5,028,835 ÷ 50,574=？",
        "answer": 1.9975400820935003
    },
    {
        "question": "81,326 ÷ 678=？",
        "answer": 2.0789997182874034
    },
    {
        "question": "545 × 346=？",
        "answer": 5.275472601069419
    },
    {
        "question": "657,400 × 540=？",
        "answer": 8.550223459568574
    },
    {
        "question": "23,881 × 694=？",
        "answer": 7.2194119790675
    },
    {
        "question": "87 × 10,674=？",
        "answer": 5.967846451086187
    },
    {
        "question": "628,300,081 ÷ 423,996,503=？",
        "answer": 0.1708048410321137
    },
    {
        "question": "2,632 × 18,935=？",
        "answer": 7.697551194398763
    },
    {
        "question": "659,856 ÷ 3,202=？",
        "answer": 2.3140278424604697
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 19,196=？",
        "answer": 6.089390715244271
    },
    {
        "question": "422,940 ÷ 15,952=？",
        "answer": 1.4234636199839379
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 775=？",
        "answer": 4.168055303459139
    },
    {
        "question": "24,634,754 ÷ 2,866,836=？",
        "answer": 0.9341453803743593
    },
    {
        "question": "13,070,047 ÷ 5,179,652=？",
        "answer": 0.40197656708535245
    },
    {
        "question": "2,975 × 1,448=？",
        "answer": 6.634255531925697
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 136,970=？",
        "answer": 7.185843478431114
    },
    {
        "question": "1,338 × 9,625=？",
        "answer": 7.109856851612342
    },
    {
        "question": "461,431 ÷ 9,351=？",
        "answer": 1.6932487110747596
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 919,793=？",
        "answer": 5.963690100092399
    },
    {
        "question": "92,676,344 ÷ 11,140=？",
        "answer": 3.920083702084029
    },
    {
        "question": "1,774,013 ÷ 326,982=？",
        "answer": 0.7344329521413204
    },
    {
        "question": "154 × 869,294=？",
        "answer": 8.12668740290512
    },
    {
        "question": "6,598 ÷ 3,567=？",
        "answer": 0.2671092018709711
    },
    {
        "question": "63,922 × 2,213=？",
        "answer": 8.150631768709028
    },
    {
        "question": "68,755,589 ÷ 33,705=？",
        "answer": 3.309613675364984
    },
    {
        "question": "2,738 × 34,221=？",
        "answer": 7.9717261400648995
    },
    {
        "question": "325 × 333=？",
        "answer": 5.034327594485195
    },
    {
        "question": "940,750 × 335=？",
        "answer": 8.498519034028748
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 162,141=？",
        "answer": 5.2098928471883665
    },
    {
        "question": "522,348 ÷ 4,809=？",
        "answer": 2.035905159116044
    },
    {
        "question": "2,412,532 ÷ 3,668=？",
        "answer": 2.818043755569661
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 578,337=？",
        "answer": 7.017453482953854
    },
    {
        "question": "28,783 × 534=？",
        "answer": 7.186677314716174
    },
    {
        "question": "1,199 × 911=？",
        "answer": 6.038337560071847
    },
    {
        "question": "128,479,891 ÷ 43,204=？",
        "answer": 3.4733112020818644
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 10,931=？",
        "answer": 4.339689889966477
    },
    {
        "question": "10,680,256 ÷ 4,969,206=？",
        "answer": 0.3322946616895044
    },
    {
        "question": "13,160 × 5,378=？",
        "answer": 7.84987668716522
    },
    {
        "question": "2,395 × 1,385=？",
        "answer": 6.520755291151049
    },
    {
        "question": "1,467,367 ÷ 1,601=？",
        "answer": 2.9621474159671615
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 14,158=？",
        "answer": 4.452031903656812
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 289=？",
        "answer": 3.691346764134822
    },
    {
        "question": "528,915 ÷ 42,180=？",
        "answer": 1.098279308357535
    },
    {
        "question": "15,761 × 6,103=？",
        "answer": 7.98312713899237
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 194,409=？",
        "answer": 6.735874397693082
    },
    {
        "question": "876,929,105 ÷ 10,088,028=？",
        "answer": 1.9391582054327448
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 139,007=？",
        "answer": 5.143036670648538
    },
    {
        "question": "6,123,462 ÷ 4,893=？",
        "answer": 3.0974218113519996
    },
    {
        "question": "1,171 × 252=？",
        "answer": 5.469957435853908
    },
    {
        "question": "127 × 78,776=？",
        "answer": 7.000197645867375
    },
    {
        "question": "3,625 × 35,990=？",
        "answer": 8.115489857559924
    },
    {
        "question": "208 × 4,684=？",
        "answer": 5.988680221363087
    },
    {
        "question": "733,136 ÷ 1,723=？",
        "answer": 2.6288992682311316
    },
    {
        "question": "24,969,786 ÷ 14,819,301=？",
        "answer": 0.22658710107799568
    },
    {
        "question": "187 × 4,420=？",
        "answer": 5.917263875885591
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 4,143,105=？",
        "answer": 8.43686987543991
    },
    {
        "question": "348 × 274,294=？",
        "answer": 7.979795551750196
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 3,414=？",
        "answer": 4.894991352796308
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 55,642=？",
        "answer": 5.046432727576249
    },
    {
        "question": "13,537,164 ÷ 7,830,128=？",
        "answer": 0.23775882875697354
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,408=？",
        "answer": 3.5324995860946626
    },
    {
        "question": "941 × 350,612=？",
        "answer": 8.518416399544979
    },
    {
        "question": "186 × 41,673=？",
        "answer": 6.889367710251098
    },
    {
        "question": "228,200 ÷ 85,578=？",
        "answer": 0.425953507491578
    },
    {
        "question": "853,122 ÷ 239=？",
        "answer": 3.5526132405806403
    },
    {
        "question": "331,365 ÷ 55,828=？",
        "answer": 0.773454564886504
    },
    {
        "question": "686,116 ÷ 17,858=？",
        "answer": 1.5845647284206819
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 2,651,796=？",
        "answer": 8.095637969115653
    },
    {
        "question": "10,576,995 ÷ 9,248,780=？",
        "answer": 0.05827785001141533
    },
    {
        "question": "602 × 350,987=？",
        "answer": 8.32488752244496
    },
    {
        "question": "506,908,650 ÷ 440,498,952=？",
        "answer": 0.06098482267212058
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 88,566,136=？",
        "answer": 8.248297693175873
    },
    {
        "question": "676 × 62,964=？",
        "answer": 7.6290390061875994
    },
    {
        "question": "2,081,519 ÷ 1,939=？",
        "answer": 3.030802570380217
    },
    {
        "question": "65,262,141 ÷ 717=？",
        "answer": 4.959142161550431
    },
    {
        "question": "597,869,414 ÷ 11,172,917=？",
        "answer": 1.7284397636643427
    },
    {
        "question": "120,196,396 ÷ 568,781=？",
        "answer": 2.324946365407664
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 25,331,723=？",
        "answer": 7.403664730412078
    },
    {
        "question": "13,454,447 ÷ 8,961,917=？",
        "answer": 0.17646493483009196
    },
    {
        "question": "171,186 ÷ 255=？",
        "answer": 2.826928063719309
    },
    {
        "question": "21,657,627 ÷ 20,556=？",
        "answer": 3.0226722607617047
    },
    {
        "question": "5,824,122 ÷ 9,765=？",
        "answer": 2.775558216100725
    },
    {
        "question": "51,913,327 ÷ 795,627=？",
        "answer": 1.8145693499544846
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,894=？",
        "answer": 4.1604685311190375
    },
    {
        "question": "190,032 ÷ 59,953=？",
        "answer": 0.5010158194018894
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,360=？",
        "answer": 4.030194785356751
    },
    {
        "question": "707,805,522 ÷ 369,964=？",
        "answer": 3.2817544801651355
    },
    {
        "question": "667,074 ÷ 768=？",
        "answer": 2.93881279380863
    },
    {
        "question": "23,882 ÷ 1,261=？",
        "answer": 1.2773556074333605
    },
    {
        "question": "22,084,800 ÷ 258=？",
        "answer": 4.9324737646771535
    },
    {
        "question": "154,301,884 ÷ 34,466,637=？",
        "answer": 0.6509723185323203
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 103,507=？",
        "answer": 5.969212230812686
    },
    {
        "question": "883,272 ÷ 563,579=？",
        "answer": 0.195139661263536
    },
    {
        "question": "44,143,500 ÷ 232,553=？",
        "answer": 2.2783448176351406
    },
    {
        "question": "424,842 × 230=？",
        "answer": 7.989955280688431
    },
    {
        "question": "343,702 ÷ 21,374=？",
        "answer": 1.2062962542472944
    },
    {
        "question": "280,108,572 ÷ 8,954=？",
        "answer": 4.495309309441388
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,200,180=？",
        "answer": 7.225327893947686
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 17,037,671=？",
        "answer": 7.231410227697241
    },
    {
        "question": "130 × 1,026,951=？",
        "answer": 8.125493074446187
    },
    {
        "question": "18,099,706 ÷ 29,223=？",
        "answer": 2.7919467224605063
    },
    {
        "question": "169,819 ÷ 4,486=？",
        "answer": 1.578127009909094
    },
    {
        "question": "2,990,159 ÷ 6,679=？",
        "answer": 2.6509828388351697
    },
    {
        "question": "36,134,529 ÷ 543=？",
        "answer": 4.823122568636781
    },
    {
        "question": "17,471 ÷ 3,242=？",
        "answer": 0.7315047532026989
    },
    {
        "question": "89,218 ÷ 9,934=？",
        "answer": 0.9533283277756546
    },
    {
        "question": "95,844,918 ÷ 48,479,330=？",
        "answer": 0.2960124810509894
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 20,132=？",
        "answer": 5.345279606883327
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 118,962=？",
        "answer": 5.97849824396568
    },
    {
        "question": "1,663,245 ÷ 12,048=？",
        "answer": 2.140041267699656
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 21,726=？",
        "answer": 5.814101029920318
    },
    {
        "question": "1,597 × 5,057=？",
        "answer": 6.907197869771028
    },
    {
        "question": "170,055 × 5,309=？",
        "answer": 8.955602131033515
    },
    {
        "question": "315,989 ÷ 13,247=？",
        "answer": 1.3775544281961185
    },
    {
        "question": "5,450 ÷ 1,091=？",
        "answer": 0.6985717516883005
    },
    {
        "question": "3,570,349 ÷ 969,999=？",
        "answer": 0.5659393837366097
    },
    {
        "question": "153,614,102 ÷ 421=？",
        "answer": 5.562148990560735
    },
    {
        "question": "313,483,117 ÷ 1,431,777=？",
        "answer": 2.340338774707926
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 697,085=？",
        "answer": 6.9572290899173685
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 836,504=？",
        "answer": 6.223498017679399
    },
    {
        "question": "364 × 426=？",
        "answer": 5.190510982751775
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 448,418=？",
        "answer": 6.651683037339025
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 21,946,047=？",
        "answer": 8.517447564012286
    },
    {
        "question": "310,701 ÷ 243,471=？",
        "answer": 0.10589541153273868
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 13,605,983=？",
        "answer": 7.434759919659483
    },
    {
        "question": "20,218 ÷ 630=？",
        "answer": 1.5063976427547359
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,455,466=？",
        "answer": 6.163002064680462
    },
    {
        "question": "130,405,807 ÷ 7,183,798=？",
        "answer": 1.2589428190798326
    },
    {
        "question": "8,147,256 ÷ 250,006=？",
        "answer": 1.5130609311476462
    },
    {
        "question": "20,115 ÷ 2,434=？",
        "answer": 0.917199463013234
    },
    {
        "question": "307,845,645 ÷ 1,718=？",
        "answer": 5.253309854641968
    },
    {
        "question": "144,009,553 ÷ 9,497=？",
        "answer": 4.180804864352336
    },
    {
        "question": "161,877,734 ÷ 882=？",
        "answer": 5.263718531280915
    },
    {
        "question": "102,171,895 ÷ 31,338,797=？",
        "answer": 0.5132491271678689
    },
    {
        "question": "680,404 ÷ 5,350=？",
        "answer": 2.1044130760833553
    },
    {
        "question": "22,819 × 995=？",
        "answer": 7.356119689101461
    },
    {
        "question": "2,367,544 ÷ 271,801=？",
        "answer": 0.9400470087262358
    },
    {
        "question": "106,972 ÷ 1,287=？",
        "answer": 1.9196915687543643
    },
    {
        "question": "2,744,598 ÷ 108,685=？",
        "answer": 1.4023091328226331
    },
    {
        "question": "7,715 × 447=？",
        "answer": 6.537643453531103
    },
    {
        "question": "197,738,839 ÷ 20,292=？",
        "answer": 3.988767126274009
    },
    {
        "question": "175,228 × 439=？",
        "answer": 7.886068024322401
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 391,093=？",
        "answer": 6.06940129749721
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 85,481=？",
        "answer": 4.931869594118396
    },
    {
        "question": "309,467 ÷ 269,415=？",
        "answer": 0.06019257293104784
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 3,172=？",
        "answer": 5.27218519028771
    },
    {
        "question": "1,519 × 2,172=？",
        "answer": 6.518417594779596
    },
    {
        "question": "35,913,141 ÷ 2,382,521=？",
        "answer": 1.1782166533436453
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 40,670,333=？",
        "answer": 7.609277728329604
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 2,545,560=？",
        "answer": 8.153971365017474
    },
    {
        "question": "8,008,898 ÷ 3,239=？",
        "answer": 3.3931618145854237
    },
    {
        "question": "12,045,649 ÷ 147,598=？",
        "answer": 1.9117497313478364
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 15,195,769=？",
        "answer": 8.026820722976181
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 33,757,079=？",
        "answer": 7.829394855742453
    },
    {
        "question": "37,401 ÷ 464=？",
        "answer": 1.9063652336422818
    },
    {
        "question": "98 × 20,780=？",
        "answer": 6.308871618913654
    },
    {
        "question": "130,165,864 ÷ 17,211,175=？",
        "answer": 0.8786865849793664
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 287,627,006=？",
        "answer": 8.458829660591755
    },
    {
        "question": "16,615,294 ÷ 529=？",
        "answer": 4.497052358289025
    },
    {
        "question": "107 × 37,727=？",
        "answer": 6.606036049749547
    },
    {
        "question": "135 × 292=？",
        "answer": 4.595716619943424
    },
    {
        "question": "137,579 ÷ 276=？",
        "answer": 2.697643066368177
    },
    {
        "question": "89 × 9,130=？",
        "answer": 5.9098607841792115
    },
    {
        "question": "230,094,071 ÷ 1,686,032=？",
        "answer": 2.1350396149858075
    },
    {
        "question": "110,612,047 ÷ 2,456=？",
        "answer": 4.653574067037541
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 15,377=？",
        "answer": 4.885841618700554
    },
    {
        "question": "2,859,077 ÷ 775=？",
        "answer": 3.5669241493276473
    },
    {
        "question": "2,886 × 96,400=？",
        "answer": 8.444373360660306
    },
    {
        "question": "2,713 × 8,043=？",
        "answer": 7.338867862464138
    },
    {
        "question": "132 × 3,088=？",
        "answer": 5.6102512228695485
    },
    {
        "question": "206,683,151 ÷ 1,627=？",
        "answer": 5.103917521049021
    },
    {
        "question": "568,775,824 ÷ 9,885=？",
        "answer": 4.759964454637185
    },
    {
        "question": "2,238 × 56,163=？",
        "answer": 8.099310380186012
    },
    {
        "question": "33,507,206 ÷ 396=？",
        "answer": 4.927443029753044
    },
    {
        "question": "23,724 × 1,226=？",
        "answer": 7.463678385543694
    },
    {
        "question": "234,878 × 940=？",
        "answer": 8.343970193808333
    },
    {
        "question": "3,644 × 322=？",
        "answer": 6.0694342399967915
    },
    {
        "question": "519 ÷ 200=？",
        "answer": 0.41413736218447667
    },
    {
        "question": "26,631,998 ÷ 6,718=？",
        "answer": 3.5981637500284793
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 3,113=？",
        "answer": 4.192149125018534
    },
    {
        "question": "55,815,483 ÷ 2,161=？",
        "answer": 4.4120999203831195
    },
    {
        "question": "77,283 × 595=？",
        "answer": 7.662600938066595
    },
    {
        "question": "851,354,425 ÷ 13,546=？",
        "answer": 4.798299326390383
    },
    {
        "question": "201,337 ÷ 96,463=？",
        "answer": 0.3195628288086051
    },
    {
        "question": "11,024,544 ÷ 360,097=？",
        "answer": 1.4859411318717075
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 4,114=？",
        "answer": 5.406655976856959
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 241=？",
        "answer": 2.984077033902831
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 120,234=？",
        "answer": 7.048510244210734
    },
    {
        "question": "200,613,534 ÷ 30,205,215=？",
        "answer": 0.8222782971269393
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 511=？",
        "answer": 3.7498135852929377
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 2,707,409=？",
        "answer": 8.356833154328022
    },
    {
        "question": "28,618 × 2,881=？",
        "answer": 7.9161825376233095
    },
    {
        "question": "440,164,664 ÷ 99,284=？",
        "answer": 3.6467359089679756
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 7,829,598=？",
        "answer": 8.693080013827796
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 841,017=？",
        "answer": 6.225834770215251
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 3,535,822=？",
        "answer": 7.849520389345636
    },
    {
        "question": "10,419 ÷ 613=？",
        "answer": 1.2303655635120097
    },
    {
        "question": "99 × 8,368=？",
        "answer": 5.918256866120749
    },
    {
        "question": "852 ÷ 302=？",
        "answer": 0.4504326518095495
    },
    {
        "question": "260,153 ÷ 101,901=？",
        "answer": 0.40705039245105623
    },
    {
        "question": "29,121 × 728=？",
        "answer": 7.326337663656822
    },
    {
        "question": "39,085,810 ÷ 182,171=？",
        "answer": 2.331539874218576
    },
    {
        "question": "604,803,352 ÷ 2,680=？",
        "answer": 5.353479395460177
    },
    {
        "question": "12,840,309 ÷ 454=？",
        "answer": 4.451519622229327
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 211,177=？",
        "answer": 5.32464661595922
    },
    {
        "question": "33,418,173 ÷ 408,748=？",
        "answer": 1.9125270622820556
    },
    {
        "question": "7,641,687 ÷ 2,144,828=？",
        "answer": 0.5517967746350202
    },
    {
        "question": "1,333 × 704=？",
        "answer": 5.972402808555971
    },
    {
        "question": "985,088 × 220=？",
        "answer": 8.33589770949983
    },
    {
        "question": "767,773 ÷ 409,065=？",
        "answer": 0.2734405129414615
    },
    {
        "question": "11,245 ÷ 4,610=？",
        "answer": 0.38725853438200286
    },
    {
        "question": "603,847,217 ÷ 62,230,185=？",
        "answer": 0.9869259770009283
    },
    {
        "question": "25,384,414 ÷ 5,723,486=？",
        "answer": 0.6469065173090528
    },
    {
        "question": "32,052,252 ÷ 2,103=？",
        "answer": 4.183019275889703
    },
    {
        "question": "138,477,753 ÷ 5,086,617=？",
        "answer": 1.4349509694856684
    },
    {
        "question": "227,138,924 ÷ 6,698,674=？",
        "answer": 1.5303027213390303
    },
    {
        "question": "371,496,307 ÷ 1,287=？",
        "answer": 5.46037595394458
    },
    {
        "question": "364,775,001 ÷ 73,344=？",
        "answer": 3.69666047570622
    },
    {
        "question": "60,662,647 ÷ 788,197=？",
        "answer": 1.886286579182694
    },
    {
        "question": "81,853 ÷ 15,109=？",
        "answer": 0.7337988801984642
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 301,038=？",
        "answer": 5.7796513156720115
    },
    {
        "question": "4,102,650 ÷ 1,853=？",
        "answer": 3.345189049256051
    },
    {
        "question": "151,935 ÷ 381=？",
        "answer": 2.6007328545133563
    },
    {
        "question": "130,250 × 1,416=？",
        "answer": 8.265840985325312
    },
    {
        "question": "100,687,418 ÷ 92,394,167=？",
        "answer": 0.03733064973278596
    },
    {
        "question": "15,202,411 ÷ 293,553=？",
        "answer": 1.7142259465261875
    },
    {
        "question": "220,988,903 ÷ 2,854=？",
        "answer": 4.888916497273603
    },
    {
        "question": "915,254 ÷ 5,580=？",
        "answer": 2.214907436648365
    },
    {
        "question": "402,702 ÷ 18,253=？",
        "answer": 1.3436495327161897
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 1,192=？",
        "answer": 4.222404291082456
    },
    {
        "question": "2,375,863 × 202=？",
        "answer": 8.681172763643229
    },
    {
        "question": "270,472 × 562=？",
        "answer": 8.18185862798798
    },
    {
        "question": "5,921 × 4,724=？",
        "answer": 7.446704950023477
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,368,022=？",
        "answer": 6.867350913940196
    },
    {
        "question": "14,888,135 ÷ 14,658,259=？",
        "answer": 0.006757907089804554
    },
    {
        "question": "41,121 ÷ 15,340=？",
        "answer": 0.42823830788206774
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 409,259=？",
        "answer": 6.457096278757636
    },
    {
        "question": "2,080 × 17,123=？",
        "answer": 7.551643191641777
    },
    {
        "question": "615,521 ÷ 3,626=？",
        "answer": 2.2298150747759844
    },
    {
        "question": "27,251 × 27,705=？",
        "answer": 8.877940598228342
    },
    {
        "question": "5,050 × 8,085=？",
        "answer": 7.6109714023610815
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 2,177=？",
        "answer": 5.195190925472363
    },
    {
        "question": "124,657,738 ÷ 1,276=？",
        "answer": 4.989868567671631
    },
    {
        "question": "4,245,497 ÷ 2,937,452=？",
        "answer": 0.15995775966582032
    },
    {
        "question": "631,160 ÷ 199,790=？",
        "answer": 0.49956572061355964
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 27,766=？",
        "answer": 6.133709399351999
    },
    {
        "question": "323,444 ÷ 167,661=？",
        "answer": 0.2853670470922831
    },
    {
        "question": "166,455,547 ÷ 542=？",
        "answer": 5.487298985716998
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 23,003,665=？",
        "answer": 8.139948284769652
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 19,185,967=？",
        "answer": 7.282983693144993
    },
    {
        "question": "581,246 ÷ 274=？",
        "answer": 3.32660941437413
    },
    {
        "question": "15,691,645 ÷ 109,435=？",
        "answer": 2.156512232053143
    },
    {
        "question": "18,712,912 ÷ 18,703,051=？",
        "answer": 0.00022891715951307303
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 8,301,754=？",
        "answer": 8.396291114811858
    },
    {
        "question": "1,216 × 630,299=？",
        "answer": 8.884480193033573
    },
    {
        "question": "309,580,002 ÷ 696=？",
        "answer": 5.64816365910069
    },
    {
        "question": "580,685,227 ÷ 555,942,107=？",
        "answer": 0.018911208741903753
    },
    {
        "question": "123,404 ÷ 21,893=？",
        "answer": 0.7510239600235558
    },
    {
        "question": "212,673 × 350=？",
        "answer": 7.871780401693923
    },
    {
        "question": "1,917 × 369=？",
        "answer": 5.849648479037123
    },
    {
        "question": "71,719,172 ÷ 583,467=？",
        "answer": 2.0896189689310516
    },
    {
        "question": "18,759 ÷ 1,493=？",
        "answer": 1.0991498756753055
    },
    {
        "question": "5,073 × 482=？",
        "answer": 6.388311900556253
    },
    {
        "question": "6,458,103 ÷ 75,323=？",
        "answer": 1.933177358305191
    },
    {
        "question": "3,718,918 ÷ 5,932=？",
        "answer": 2.7972154601650034
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 291,051,735=？",
        "answer": 8.463970192518616
    },
    {
        "question": "890,420 ÷ 1,444=？",
        "answer": 2.7900277130257463
    },
    {
        "question": "148,906,578 ÷ 467,376=？",
        "answer": 2.503247475904209
    },
    {
        "question": "150,843,680 ÷ 1,176,029=？",
        "answer": 2.1081090877107185
    },
    {
        "question": "8,698 × 107,963=？",
        "answer": 8.972694347251437
    },
    {
        "question": "12,045 × 327=？",
        "answer": 6.595354556994648
    },
    {
        "question": "921 × 179,495=？",
        "answer": 8.218311985603368
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 2,363=？",
        "answer": 4.964528328658869
    },
    {
        "question": "37,460 × 8,775=？",
        "answer": 8.51681489817708
    },
    {
        "question": "559,333,339 ÷ 2,687,059=？",
        "answer": 2.31839350379142
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 380=？",
        "answer": 2.57978359661681
    },
    {
        "question": "188,276 × 1,867=？",
        "answer": 8.545939280919198
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 298,714,349=？",
        "answer": 8.475256084813187
    },
    {
        "question": "185 × 64,028=？",
        "answer": 7.073541664671513
    },
    {
        "question": "12,699 ÷ 924=？",
        "answer": 1.138097551973566
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 2,937=？",
        "answer": 5.1013724021023865
    },
    {
        "question": "581,188,020 ÷ 1,401=？",
        "answer": 5.617878518341731
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 6,720,309=？",
        "answer": 7.827389242385621
    },
    {
        "question": "6,089 × 100,512=？",
        "answer": 8.786763888772933
    },
    {
        "question": "1,899,631 × 327=？",
        "answer": 8.793217000861848
    },
    {
        "question": "441,435,650 ÷ 12,136,858=？",
        "answer": 1.5607611327574886
    },
    {
        "question": "605 × 338=？",
        "answer": 5.310672074930124
    },
    {
        "question": "340,268,706 ÷ 2,303=？",
        "answer": 5.169528071559258
    },
    {
        "question": "2,076,797 × 200=？",
        "answer": 8.618424043432375
    },
    {
        "question": "1,483 × 132,118=？",
        "answer": 8.29210314175516
    },
    {
        "question": "342,616,308 ÷ 1,831,972=？",
        "answer": 2.271889199266544
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 176,097,676=？",
        "answer": 8.546783620188693
    },
    {
        "question": "273,199,189 ÷ 68,379=？",
        "answer": 3.6015566605726614
    },
    {
        "question": "59,579,863 ÷ 1,195,798=？",
        "answer": 1.6974416775312986
    },
    {
        "question": "1,309,891 ÷ 805=？",
        "answer": 3.211439277831372
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,272,341=？",
        "answer": 6.657503500214336
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 89,499=？",
        "answer": 5.65078818717251
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,010=？",
        "answer": 3.303196057420489
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 2,085=？",
        "answer": 4.9525745148893625
    },
    {
        "question": "38,949,312 ÷ 390,340=？",
        "answer": 1.9990567329189095
    },
    {
        "question": "26,959 ÷ 3,324=？",
        "answer": 0.9090427636066789
    },
    {
        "question": "225,009 ÷ 10,907=？",
        "answer": 1.3144945764076752
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 17,825=？",
        "answer": 5.573248833257822
    },
    {
        "question": "57,158,060 ÷ 7,078,852=？",
        "answer": 0.9071146475138324
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 39,620=？",
        "answer": 6.338277160696772
    },
    {
        "question": "29,485,597 ÷ 172,143=？",
        "answer": 2.233720558131758
    },
    {
        "question": "9,742,251 ÷ 85,005=？",
        "answer": 2.0592148428745114
    },
    {
        "question": "260,711,793 ÷ 15,419=？",
        "answer": 4.228104467988831
    },
    {
        "question": "278,680 ÷ 281=？",
        "answer": 2.996399481957452
    },
    {
        "question": "1,159,310 × 332=？",
        "answer": 8.585337665731094
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 191,645,237=？",
        "answer": 8.282498030110997
    },
    {
        "question": "474,710,993 ÷ 18,928=？",
        "answer": 4.399324561615799
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 557,449,566=？",
        "answer": 8.746205581677701
    },
    {
        "question": "981,790,058 ÷ 30,763=？",
        "answer": 4.5039899444630205
    },
    {
        "question": "358,722 ÷ 3,656=？",
        "answer": 1.9917518252027242
    },
    {
        "question": "40,817 ÷ 313=？",
        "answer": 2.1152967438888526
    },
    {
        "question": "4,667 ÷ 1,996=？",
        "answer": 0.36887726393380366
    },
    {
        "question": "330,346,284 ÷ 4,377=？",
        "answer": 4.877792879265984
    },
    {
        "question": "1,172,988 ÷ 595,179=？",
        "answer": 0.2946459698049861
    },
    {
        "question": "5,440,677 ÷ 92,771=？",
        "answer": 1.7682407056619462
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,964,063=？",
        "answer": 6.594185409926288
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,257,013=？",
        "answer": 6.099339769172887
    },
    {
        "question": "598 × 9,881=？",
        "answer": 6.771502083283015
    },
    {
        "question": "316,350,395 ÷ 3,333=？",
        "answer": 4.977333067401789
    },
    {
        "question": "374,897,299 ÷ 156,437=？",
        "answer": 3.3795728326240844
    },
    {
        "question": "1,516 × 235=？",
        "answer": 5.551767063567771
    },
    {
        "question": "14,006,936 ÷ 32,876=？",
        "answer": 2.629464172516473
    },
    {
        "question": "8,820 × 9,353=？",
        "answer": 7.916419519477244
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 13,773,632=？",
        "answer": 8.57041223960629
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,756,439=？",
        "answer": 6.57477634081893
    },
    {
        "question": "25,893 ÷ 5,218=？",
        "answer": 0.6956782965654489
    },
    {
        "question": "27,908,940 ÷ 2,625,640=？",
        "answer": 1.0265081620432046
    },
    {
        "question": "105,290 ÷ 4,942=？",
        "answer": 1.3284843846203775
    },
    {
        "question": "7,158,316 ÷ 1,395=？",
        "answer": 3.7102366585632724
    },
    {
        "question": "2,489,733 ÷ 19,915=？",
        "answer": 2.0969724649270707
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 58,188=？",
        "answer": 5.06586342582713
    },
    {
        "question": "185,318 ÷ 4,917=？",
        "answer": 1.5762173962473731
    },
    {
        "question": "9,023 ÷ 581=？",
        "answer": 1.191174824977329
    },
    {
        "question": "395,265 × 469=？",
        "answer": 8.26806120277061
    },
    {
        "question": "9,967 × 861=？",
        "answer": 6.933567609714596
    },
    {
        "question": "10,038 × 428=？",
        "answer": 6.63309096035921
    },
    {
        "question": "550 × 960=？",
        "answer": 5.722633922533812
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 35,296=？",
        "answer": 6.50676688308119
    },
    {
        "question": "7,159 × 1,354=？",
        "answer": 6.986471026766959
    },
    {
        "question": "88,281,355 ÷ 497,342=？",
        "answer": 2.2492138538911965
    },
    {
        "question": "3,957 × 32,903=？",
        "answer": 8.11460154773112
    },
    {
        "question": "42,069 ÷ 3,647=？",
        "answer": 1.0620264254409484
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 202=？",
        "answer": 3.76774936734558
    },
    {
        "question": "241,467 × 1,006=？",
        "answer": 8.385455767164881
    },
    {
        "question": "428 × 651=？",
        "answer": 5.445024757581364
    },
    {
        "question": "12,936,298 ÷ 1,322=？",
        "answer": 3.990578556252816
    },
    {
        "question": "258,662,758 ÷ 709,204=？",
        "answer": 2.561962727529704
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 676=？",
        "answer": 4.244920043912454
    },
    {
        "question": "11,535 × 1,374=？",
        "answer": 7.200004331580644
    },
    {
        "question": "342 × 249,302=？",
        "answer": 7.9307518686573
    },
    {
        "question": "64,591 ÷ 2,211=？",
        "answer": 1.4655832657780292
    },
    {
        "question": "7,984,168 ÷ 4,464=？",
        "answer": 3.2525054807146896
    },
    {
        "question": "37,078 ÷ 11,482=？",
        "answer": 0.5090987575797646
    },
    {
        "question": "791 × 429=？",
        "answer": 5.530633775682401
    },
    {
        "question": "2,924,063 ÷ 992,468=？",
        "answer": 0.46927021265138696
    },
    {
        "question": "22,441,889 ÷ 14,265,606=？",
        "answer": 0.19676918484545847
    },
    {
        "question": "299 × 8,447=？",
        "answer": 6.402373682507075
    },
    {
        "question": "337,932 × 313=？",
        "answer": 8.024373656179591
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,820=？",
        "answer": 3.2600713879850747
    },
    {
        "question": "751,324 × 1,068=？",
        "answer": 8.904398514686946
    },
    {
        "question": "1,044,200 ÷ 921=？",
        "answer": 3.0545240586778477
    },
    {
        "question": "42,491,048 ÷ 15,523=？",
        "answer": 3.437321785183564
    },
    {
        "question": "10,245 ÷ 9,654=？",
        "answer": 0.025804668254540607
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 21,721,853=？",
        "answer": 8.814018125054021
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 3,931=？",
        "answer": 4.196563035148052
    },
    {
        "question": "1,132,025 ÷ 49,415=？",
        "answer": 1.359997218354643
    },
    {
        "question": "432,881 ÷ 6,145=？",
        "answer": 1.847846636968501
    },
    {
        "question": "599,767,294 ÷ 796=？",
        "answer": 5.877069711754197
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,244,667=？",
        "answer": 6.6521819174891785
    },
    {
        "question": "665,080 ÷ 606,037=？",
        "answer": 0.040374748426872706
    },
    {
        "question": "32,318,524 ÷ 13,067=？",
        "answer": 3.3932756270513065
    },
    {
        "question": "309 × 17,421=？",
        "answer": 6.731031560177821
    },
    {
        "question": "209,845,828 ÷ 421=？",
        "answer": 5.697618243475055
    },
    {
        "question": "9,384,085 ÷ 6,670=？",
        "answer": 3.1482660989999367
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 14,210,818=？",
        "answer": 8.567592425381855
    },
    {
        "question": "141,465 × 206=？",
        "answer": 7.464516224278414
    },
    {
        "question": "119,541,096 ÷ 1,593=？",
        "answer": 4.875301457498189
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 9,150,007=？",
        "answer": 8.075364778620303
    },
    {
        "question": "3,298 × 396=？",
        "answer": 6.115945837234012
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,654,601=？",
        "answer": 6.218693282468299
    },
    {
        "question": "297,968,642 ÷ 72,860=？",
        "answer": 3.61168139474437
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,421,850=？",
        "answer": 6.384147241123452
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 34,819=？",
        "answer": 5.444906281035798
    },
    {
        "question": "7,426 × 15,948=？",
        "answer": 8.073461171880497
    },
    {
        "question": "515 × 725=？",
        "answer": 5.572145235612185
    },
    {
        "question": "940,897,683 ÷ 547,753,230=？",
        "answer": 0.23495745187049832
    },
    {
        "question": "277,621,335 ÷ 447,040=？",
        "answer": 2.793106453849926
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 955=？",
        "answer": 4.093946723890583
    },
    {
        "question": "2,979,195 ÷ 768=？",
        "answer": 3.5887377103914364
    },
    {
        "question": "65,468,076 ÷ 319,737=？",
        "answer": 2.311236682119006
    },
    {
        "question": "434,716 ÷ 696=？",
        "answer": 2.795596385360199
    },
    {
        "question": "46,929,309 ÷ 4,269,878=？",
        "answer": 1.041028693154676
    },
    {
        "question": "532,772,185 ÷ 234,592=？",
        "answer": 3.356228345257531
    },
    {
        "question": "390,242,291 ÷ 18,179,837=？",
        "answer": 1.3317443475657753
    },
    {
        "question": "42,526,093 ÷ 9,231=？",
        "answer": 3.663406733640085
    },
    {
        "question": "49,200,749 ÷ 9,721=？",
        "answer": 3.7042607711023177
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 74,785=？",
        "answer": 5.174844493655455
    },
    {
        "question": "42,814,600 ÷ 492,402=？",
        "answer": 1.9392720826876209
    },
    {
        "question": "8,936,543 ÷ 22,572=？",
        "answer": 2.5975995078044294
    },
    {
        "question": "36,708 × 5,412=？",
        "answer": 8.298118510957888
    },
    {
        "question": "50,589 ÷ 310=？",
        "answer": 2.21269440089799
    },
    {
        "question": "1,977,956 ÷ 674=？",
        "answer": 3.467556729871572
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 1,811,369=？",
        "answer": 7.404134966577447
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 490=？",
        "answer": 3.6444385894678386
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 268=？",
        "answer": 3.9466487339066765
    },
    {
        "question": "30,468 ÷ 209=？",
        "answer": 2.163697660810293
    },
    {
        "question": "74,013 × 11,286=？",
        "answer": 8.921848053940748
    },
    {
        "question": "4,128 × 19,801=？",
        "answer": 7.912426812391557
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 175,961=？",
        "answer": 7.126230013721829
    },
    {
        "question": "271,742,786 ÷ 23,091=？",
        "answer": 4.070715282345875
    },
    {
        "question": "14,706,569 ÷ 5,678=？",
        "answer": 3.413315976708477
    },
    {
        "question": "13,706 ÷ 2,928=？",
        "answer": 0.6703396550950216
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 1,070=？",
        "answer": 4.9978667262391445
    },
    {
        "question": "79,077,929 ÷ 486,623=？",
        "answer": 2.2108626551000747
    },
    {
        "question": "14,659,801 ÷ 9,150,477=？",
        "answer": 0.20468434125288754
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 3,735=？",
        "answer": 4.4753805931433615
    },
    {
        "question": "11,394,259 ÷ 1,225=？",
        "answer": 3.968549998369592
    },
    {
        "question": "3,132,456 ÷ 1,432=？",
        "answer": 3.3399419614257444
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 402=？",
        "answer": 3.60422605308447
    },
    {
        "question": "221,181 ÷ 119,863=？",
        "answer": 0.26606267398669303
    },
    {
        "question": "8,785 × 21,720=？",
        "answer": 8.280601586748123
    },
    {
        "question": "24,765 ÷ 4,874=？",
        "answer": 0.7059528074697694
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 199=？",
        "answer": 3.4127964287165433
    },
    {
        "question": "704,348 ÷ 11,927=？",
        "answer": 1.7712560665044184
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 945,704=？",
        "answer": 7.355966467666846
    },
    {
        "question": "613,489 ÷ 202,824=？",
        "answer": 0.4806874367150453
    },
    {
        "question": "891,286,611 ÷ 2,557=？",
        "answer": 5.542286654529199
    },
    {
        "question": "968 × 268=？",
        "answer": 5.414010151337182
    },
    {
        "question": "160 × 850=？",
        "answer": 5.133538908370218
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 66,149=？",
        "answer": 6.218463291847642
    },
    {
        "question": "459,546 ÷ 101,037=？",
        "answer": 0.6578485476249857
    },
    {
        "question": "13,709 ÷ 4,534=？",
        "answer": 0.48052426063860004
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 65,743,336=？",
        "answer": 7.817851737616502
    },
    {
        "question": "260 × 441=？",
        "answer": 5.059411937438656
    },
    {
        "question": "154 × 27,640=？",
        "answer": 6.629058759538624
    },
    {
        "question": "579,864,962 ÷ 25,911=？",
        "answer": 4.349842693234428
    },
    {
        "question": "17,100,062 ÷ 547=？",
        "answer": 4.495010358690832
    },
    {
        "question": "624,460 ÷ 855=？",
        "answer": 2.8635385099905615
    },
    {
        "question": "3,151 ÷ 2,870=？",
        "answer": 0.0405665064400073
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 190,795=？",
        "answer": 6.058718239719948
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 2,744,043=？",
        "answer": 7.5523342649233305
    },
    {
        "question": "190,015,885 ÷ 130,912,791=？",
        "answer": 0.16180782682340983
    },
    {
        "question": "37,893,210 ÷ 1,340=？",
        "answer": 4.4514565983126015
    },
    {
        "question": "87 × 261,877=？",
        "answer": 7.357616609723823
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 605,816=？",
        "answer": 7.124763419974126
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 17,319=？",
        "answer": 4.539552807882274
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 134,059=？",
        "answer": 5.127295975492575
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 190,478=？",
        "answer": 5.978814826708042
    },
    {
        "question": "6,983 × 1,412=？",
        "answer": 6.993876738756802
    },
    {
        "question": "131,152 × 236=？",
        "answer": 7.490686920712651
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 9,260=？",
        "answer": 5.30903366750414
    },
    {
        "question": "989,048 ÷ 74,152=？",
        "answer": 1.1250944999281067
    },
    {
        "question": "12,938 × 36,844=？",
        "answer": 8.678233920436368
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 135,684=？",
        "answer": 7.322860336387183
    },
    {
        "question": "2,287,316 ÷ 2,469=？",
        "answer": 2.9668050779874426
    },
    {
        "question": "2,994,529 ÷ 397=？",
        "answer": 3.8775380165275384
    },
    {
        "question": "14,358 × 16,776=？",
        "answer": 8.381782366454368
    },
    {
        "question": "2,017 × 3,236=？",
        "answer": 6.814714411153
    },
    {
        "question": "209,813 ÷ 1,113=？",
        "answer": 2.275337229214697
    },
    {
        "question": "8,432,804 ÷ 380=？",
        "answer": 4.346188409709621
    },
    {
        "question": "6,361 ÷ 950=？",
        "answer": 0.8258017902876846
    },
    {
        "question": "23,126 ÷ 2,551=？",
        "answer": 0.9573900626971514
    },
    {
        "question": "373,358 ÷ 1,260=？",
        "answer": 2.4717549163418964
    },
    {
        "question": "1,207 × 384,138=？",
        "answer": 8.66619454100638
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 10,795=？",
        "answer": 4.033222646670249
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,898=？",
        "answer": 3.7554174628109362
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 39,221,708=？",
        "answer": 8.593526502101366
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 109,312=？",
        "answer": 5.038667840336873
    },
    {
        "question": "2,239,825 ÷ 46,095=？",
        "answer": 1.686560268440274
    },
    {
        "question": "112,698 × 4,650=？",
        "answer": 8.719369161778376
    },
    {
        "question": "1,956 ÷ 283=？",
        "answer": 0.8395824149272925
    },
    {
        "question": "1,970,562 × 356=？",
        "answer": 8.846040101642542
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 3,930,372=？",
        "answer": 7.548676166659921
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 575=？",
        "answer": 3.873611196996467
    },
    {
        "question": "4,953 ÷ 2,577=？",
        "answer": 0.2837539094315513
    },
    {
        "question": "35,177,947 ÷ 250=？",
        "answer": 5.1483304815776565
    },
    {
        "question": "47,716,534 ÷ 722=？",
        "answer": 4.820131692597522
    },
    {
        "question": "748,593,643 ÷ 16,152,533=？",
        "answer": 1.6660054978116914
    },
    {
        "question": "23,962,137 ÷ 2,286=？",
        "answer": 4.020449320793324
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 6,794,333=？",
        "answer": 8.522342908479272
    },
    {
        "question": "127,106,440 ÷ 3,265,472=？",
        "answer": 1.5902215909347446
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 2,920=？",
        "answer": 4.368472838440362
    },
    {
        "question": "500,171 ÷ 46,701=？",
        "answer": 1.0297923275219572
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 19,472=？",
        "answer": 5.465501819941671
    },
    {
        "question": "36,992,513 ÷ 15,064=？",
        "answer": 3.3901735280905636
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 4,363,394=？",
        "answer": 7.7859524657863535
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 34,839=？",
        "answer": 6.232261760786794
    },
    {
        "question": "52,740 ÷ 49,739=？",
        "answer": 0.025443075903627196
    },
    {
        "question": "985,867,994 ÷ 3,466=？",
        "answer": 5.453990209184647
    },
    {
        "question": "11,160,207 ÷ 3,747,585=？",
        "answer": 0.47392075800510614
    },
    {
        "question": "24,041,507 ÷ 3,527,835=？",
        "answer": 0.8334534225840478
    },
    {
        "question": "7,057 × 42,382=？",
        "answer": 8.47580156458166
    },
    {
        "question": "823,326 ÷ 1,688=？",
        "answer": 2.68819938802318
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 1,028=？",
        "answer": 4.053385799817482
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 888,161=？",
        "answer": 6.42561295368943
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 182,968,457=？",
        "answer": 8.262376225623349
    },
    {
        "question": "3,497,086 ÷ 3,311,675=？",
        "answer": 0.023658603003920434
    },
    {
        "question": "473,389,417 ÷ 1,581=？",
        "answer": 5.4762866747680015
    },
    {
        "question": "192 × 14,907=？",
        "answer": 6.456691480168745
    },
    {
        "question": "135,705,766 ÷ 6,613=？",
        "answer": 4.312199778078694
    },
    {
        "question": "403,510 ÷ 14,216=？",
        "answer": 1.4530768873116595
    },
    {
        "question": "557,307,502 ÷ 107,033,173=？",
        "answer": 0.7165764889150378
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 1,645,665=？",
        "answer": 7.5965526743748315
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 108,796=？",
        "answer": 5.3376429240237355
    },
    {
        "question": "495,797,702 ÷ 490=？",
        "answer": 6.005108429472607
    },
    {
        "question": "97 × 6,905=？",
        "answer": 5.825935417180895
    },
    {
        "question": "76,309,264 ÷ 1,211,032=？",
        "answer": 1.7994216458395564
    },
    {
        "question": "443,319,222 ÷ 447,276=？",
        "answer": 2.9961409670393913
    },
    {
        "question": "176,567 × 658=？",
        "answer": 8.065135431716755
    },
    {
        "question": "301 × 1,510=？",
        "answer": 5.657543442887013
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 19,967,030=？",
        "answer": 7.300313470452258
    },
    {
        "question": "294,672,803 ÷ 586,569=？",
        "answer": 2.7010209473196984
    },
    {
        "question": "271 × 6,551=？",
        "answer": 6.249276890306345
    },
    {
        "question": "501 × 776=？",
        "answer": 5.589699447125434
    },
    {
        "question": "802 ÷ 456=？",
        "answer": 0.24520952561972853
    },
    {
        "question": "9,067 × 624=？",
        "answer": 6.752648205412355
    },
    {
        "question": "3,121,265 ÷ 979,835=？",
        "answer": 0.5031776939459435
    },
    {
        "question": "2,401,470 ÷ 15,156=？",
        "answer": 2.199892569047921
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 54,292,942=？",
        "answer": 7.7347433756351895
    },
    {
        "question": "109 × 2,270,111=？",
        "answer": 8.393473591040754
    },
    {
        "question": "157,610,881 ÷ 2,102,872=？",
        "answer": 1.874773358263891
    },
    {
        "question": "2,646 × 2,262=？",
        "answer": 6.7770824404409185
    },
    {
        "question": "3,882,927 ÷ 245=？",
        "answer": 4.199993141413245
    },
    {
        "question": "470,990,752 ÷ 72,023,041=？",
        "answer": 0.8155409252871221
    },
    {
        "question": "503,801,393 ÷ 270,732,382=？",
        "answer": 0.26971915961991955
    },
    {
        "question": "341,138,316 ÷ 5,924,445=？",
        "answer": 1.7602828292407193
    },
    {
        "question": "2,388 × 9,586=？",
        "answer": 7.359671747113101
    },
    {
        "question": "5,852 ÷ 2,233=？",
        "answer": 0.41841559438183523
    },
    {
        "question": "811,900 × 349=？",
        "answer": 8.452327968364596
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 837,735=？",
        "answer": 5.923106660350282
    },
    {
        "question": "7,633 ÷ 2,154=？",
        "answer": 0.5494495634196344
    },
    {
        "question": "126,837 ÷ 650=？",
        "answer": 2.290332604725017
    },
    {
        "question": "309 × 254,005=？",
        "answer": 7.894800745064604
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 139,186=？",
        "answer": 5.143595554035172
    },
    {
        "question": "2,321,964 ÷ 343=？",
        "answer": 3.830561362059807
    },
    {
        "question": "1,223,653 ÷ 131,727=？",
        "answer": 0.967983478136076
    },
    {
        "question": "514,175 ÷ 106,582=？",
        "answer": 0.683427091265486
    },
    {
        "question": "2,036,745 ÷ 39,555=？",
        "answer": 1.71173526998648
    },
    {
        "question": "2,372 ÷ 691=？",
        "answer": 0.5356366373180266
    },
    {
        "question": "83,230,592 ÷ 40,302=？",
        "answer": 3.314956384998058
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 15,233=？",
        "answer": 5.1827854420846835
    },
    {
        "question": "52,997 × 2,103=？",
        "answer": 8.047090558884824
    },
    {
        "question": "8,110 × 757=？",
        "answer": 6.788116733711229
    },
    {
        "question": "19,376,041 ÷ 3,942=？",
        "answer": 3.691548424830311
    },
    {
        "question": "54,249,267 ÷ 43,726=？",
        "answer": 3.093654124058212
    },
    {
        "question": "2,012 × 6,933=？",
        "answer": 7.144549176582662
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 1,236,457=？",
        "answer": 7.046421527033171
    },
    {
        "question": "4,446,031 ÷ 1,133,953=？",
        "answer": 0.5933774321721904
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,497,069=？",
        "answer": 6.476271813127051
    },
    {
        "question": "230,687,443 ÷ 9,707,977=？",
        "answer": 1.3758952164941243
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 227=？",
        "answer": 3.87453979707101
    },
    {
        "question": "6,039,090 ÷ 2,052,774=？",
        "answer": 0.4686303635231481
    },
    {
        "question": "239,168,544 ÷ 1,524=？",
        "answer": 5.195719092654106
    },
    {
        "question": "394,666,291 ÷ 14,652=？",
        "answer": 4.43033312428781
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 21,208=？",
        "answer": 5.530619697380962
    },
    {
        "question": "155,731 × 239=？",
        "answer": 7.570772973303392
    },
    {
        "question": "47,951 × 18,696=？",
        "answer": 8.952546368032737
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 41,181=？",
        "answer": 5.568939397841028
    },
    {
        "question": "549,264 × 900=？",
        "answer": 8.694023644754694
    },
    {
        "question": "106,967,750 ÷ 453=？",
        "answer": 5.373154658773476
    },
    {
        "question": "20,473 ÷ 874=？",
        "answer": 1.3696700537986148
    },
    {
        "question": "60,917 × 5,135=？",
        "answer": 8.495278955277424
    },
    {
        "question": "5,925,582 ÷ 4,109=？",
        "answer": 3.158994871137616
    },
    {
        "question": "207 × 380,677=？",
        "answer": 7.89652698356671
    },
    {
        "question": "122,488,213 ÷ 82,485,137=？",
        "answer": 0.17171859863752198
    },
    {
        "question": "417 ÷ 209=？",
        "answer": 0.2999897688627035
    },
    {
        "question": "862,704,344 ÷ 222,927=？",
        "answer": 3.587699313234262
    },
    {
        "question": "596 × 489=？",
        "answer": 5.464555118863856
    },
    {
        "question": "20,642 × 2,252=？",
        "answer": 7.667320159894353
    },
    {
        "question": "5,675,561 ÷ 2,864=？",
        "answer": 3.2970357821258554
    },
    {
        "question": "42,520,411 ÷ 38,345,389=？",
        "answer": 0.04488430585131324
    },
    {
        "question": "182 × 717,267=？",
        "answer": 8.11575223827181
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 1,040,603=？",
        "answer": 7.193376332664101
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 46,139,813=？",
        "answer": 8.141197084756651
    },
    {
        "question": "15,798,750 ÷ 858,720=？",
        "answer": 1.2647711489116065
    },
    {
        "question": "291,159 ÷ 3,999=？",
        "answer": 1.8621788149710976
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 2,393,012=？",
        "answer": 8.3331873858717
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,182=？",
        "answer": 3.9177155165594932
    },
    {
        "question": "8,188,974 ÷ 1,305,147=？",
        "answer": 0.7975700627833099
    },
    {
        "question": "2,179 × 2,095=？",
        "answer": 6.659441257548569
    },
    {
        "question": "166,480,930 ÷ 609,919=？",
        "answer": 2.4360923307071345
    },
    {
        "question": "354,609,472 ÷ 300,020,220=？",
        "answer": 0.0725998067107235
    },
    {
        "question": "277,119,279 ÷ 18,131=？",
        "answer": 4.184244982503713
    },
    {
        "question": "273,477,375 ÷ 200,479,797=？",
        "answer": 0.13485078873252285
    },
    {
        "question": "2,490 ÷ 473=？",
        "answer": 0.7213382063579248
    },
    {
        "question": "445,354,287 ÷ 553=？",
        "answer": 5.905980505904977
    },
    {
        "question": "972,918 ÷ 853=？",
        "answer": 3.057127207201327
    },
    {
        "question": "10,013 × 7,019=？",
        "answer": 7.8468394585775885
    },
    {
        "question": "170 × 24,438=？",
        "answer": 6.618514581847915
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 53,668=？",
        "answer": 5.843658763410006
    },
    {
        "question": "684,828,630 ÷ 17,520=？",
        "answer": 4.592047806366106
    },
    {
        "question": "528,687 ÷ 240=？",
        "answer": 3.3429873898630205
    },
    {
        "question": "96,525 × 349=？",
        "answer": 7.527465237255266
    },
    {
        "question": "34,676,028 ÷ 1,190,237=？",
        "answer": 1.4643958982375151
    },
    {
        "question": "1,726 × 8,274=？",
        "answer": 7.154756307938684
    },
    {
        "question": "1,141 × 1,504=？",
        "answer": 6.234533480673838
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 3,255=？",
        "answer": 4.854973673726417
    },
    {
        "question": "884,397,653 ÷ 5,291,755=？",
        "answer": 2.2230478525606125
    },
    {
        "question": "9,838 ÷ 790=？",
        "answer": 1.0952797269328711
    },
    {
        "question": "276,329 ÷ 281=？",
        "answer": 2.992720145464092
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,520,909=？",
        "answer": 6.784163221173107
    },
    {
        "question": "149,723,350 ÷ 2,864=？",
        "answer": 4.718316522080397
    },
    {
        "question": "30,705 × 499=？",
        "answer": 7.185309647341577
    },
    {
        "question": "7,471,149 ÷ 204,333=？",
        "answer": 1.5630488864732084
    },
    {
        "question": "653,411,431 ÷ 1,472,543=？",
        "answer": 2.647118742342401
    },
    {
        "question": "54,984 ÷ 770=？",
        "answer": 1.8537456057285218
    },
    {
        "question": "25,755 ÷ 3,484=？",
        "answer": 0.8687834078809722
    },
    {
        "question": "28,622 × 1,056=？",
        "answer": 7.480363895581586
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 19,296,717=？",
        "answer": 8.829551472007596
    },
    {
        "question": "514,625 ÷ 6,153=？",
        "answer": 1.9224039649175138
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 1,427,582=？",
        "answer": 7.3007290990933
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 242,857=？",
        "answer": 6.3395931353359245
    },
    {
        "question": "1,669 ÷ 690=？",
        "answer": 0.3836072459419914
    },
    {
        "question": "475,739 ÷ 792=？",
        "answer": 2.778643573762565
    },
    {
        "question": "784 ÷ 231=？",
        "answer": 0.5307040827922942
    },
    {
        "question": "13,657,766 ÷ 245,677=？",
        "answer": 1.7450151674011987
    },
    {
        "question": "5,269,734 ÷ 1,559,983=？",
        "answer": 0.5286688282807674
    },
    {
        "question": "604,751,038 ÷ 15,343,769=？",
        "answer": 1.5956445708765266
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 2,313,660=？",
        "answer": 8.332782486846032
    },
    {
        "question": "186,214 ÷ 87,028=？",
        "answer": 0.33035332607029466
    },
    {
        "question": "248 × 69,566=？",
        "answer": 7.236848713249987
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 46,606=？",
        "answer": 5.367411835170924
    },
    {
        "question": "361,622 × 878=？",
        "answer": 8.501749359689414
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 337,498=？",
        "answer": 5.82930119922647
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 22,340,174=？",
        "answer": 8.67130584609836
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 688,650=？",
        "answer": 7.450782408541437
    },
    {
        "question": "449 × 19,464=？",
        "answer": 6.941478436926086
    },
    {
        "question": "131,784,460 ÷ 56,715=？",
        "answer": 3.366166264931202
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,533,765=？",
        "answer": 6.4037663327510685
    },
    {
        "question": "24,559 × 1,290=？",
        "answer": 7.500800389408296
    },
    {
        "question": "18,185,316 ÷ 6,788=？",
        "answer": 3.4279790183969436
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,407,313=？",
        "answer": 6.926541949847656
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 230,048=？",
        "answer": 5.361818461931441
    },
    {
        "question": "13,703,831 ÷ 431=？",
        "answer": 4.502364723972145
    },
    {
        "question": "2,225 × 357=？",
        "answer": 5.8999982314291435
    },
    {
        "question": "89,675,882 ÷ 1,125=？",
        "answer": 4.901523134390439
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,934,461=？",
        "answer": 6.286559978484491
    },
    {
        "question": "57,814 × 1,195=？",
        "answer": 7.839400923402237
    },
    {
        "question": "141,793,232 ÷ 146,408=？",
        "answer": 2.9860906938129985
    },
    {
        "question": "81,014,616 ÷ 5,357,980=？",
        "answer": 1.1795622896731797
    },
    {
        "question": "58,873 ÷ 50,865=？",
        "answer": 0.06349711794917665
    },
    {
        "question": "18,074 ÷ 4,362=？",
        "answer": 0.6173686167019768
    },
    {
        "question": "3,086,138 ÷ 21,239=？",
        "answer": 2.1622812771904396
    },
    {
        "question": "14,459 ÷ 2,746=？",
        "answer": 0.7214377248226654
    },
    {
        "question": "23,164,442 ÷ 75,023=？",
        "answer": 2.489627416484449
    },
    {
        "question": "1,449 × 13,456=？",
        "answer": 7.2899843639250115
    },
    {
        "question": "108,446 ÷ 1,153=？",
        "answer": 1.9733842305219502
    },
    {
        "question": "62,250,277 ÷ 1,487,497=？",
        "answer": 1.621685189775038
    },
    {
        "question": "10,778 × 8,038=？",
        "answer": 7.937686181116023
    },
    {
        "question": "151,227,526 ÷ 6,939,745=？",
        "answer": 1.3382873347391246
    },
    {
        "question": "1,841 × 229,913=？",
        "answer": 8.626617316835691
    },
    {
        "question": "476,851 ÷ 5,696=？",
        "answer": 1.9228127170977127
    },
    {
        "question": "1,257 ÷ 240=？",
        "answer": 0.7191240359743517
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,477=？",
        "answer": 4.112403892717874
    },
    {
        "question": "911 × 2,429=？",
        "answer": 6.344945891778129
    },
    {
        "question": "37,979,110 ÷ 128,878=？",
        "answer": 2.469365995449759
    },
    {
        "question": "75,136 ÷ 61,314=？",
        "answer": 0.08828842135997238
    },
    {
        "question": "176 × 3,665,629=？",
        "answer": 8.809661175519947
    },
    {
        "question": "9,795 × 43,618=？",
        "answer": 8.63067018848593
    },
    {
        "question": "8,931,728 ÷ 952,013=？",
        "answer": 0.972292610093575
    },
    {
        "question": "864 × 421,306=？",
        "answer": 8.561111386624342
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 29,020=？",
        "answer": 5.717969913205023
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 348=？",
        "answer": 2.5415792439465807
    },
    {
        "question": "60,411,023 ÷ 128,089=？",
        "answer": 2.6736043550360344
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 7,096=？",
        "answer": 4.453073598151632
    },
    {
        "question": "16,504 × 2,723=？",
        "answer": 7.65263685630506
    },
    {
        "question": "8,581 × 2,761=？",
        "answer": 7.374604308610968
    },
    {
        "question": "280,078,989 ÷ 218,377=？",
        "answer": 3.1080736346049918
    },
    {
        "question": "5,663 × 552=？",
        "answer": 6.494985639355728
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,415=？",
        "answer": 3.5333907080175515
    },
    {
        "question": "7,266 × 28,737=？",
        "answer": 8.319736821505465
    },
    {
        "question": "1,642 × 993=？",
        "answer": 6.212322401278803
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 17,160=？",
        "answer": 6.109578546904387
    },
    {
        "question": "4,204 ÷ 4,023=？",
        "answer": 0.019112674784943214
    },
    {
        "question": "857 × 448=？",
        "answer": 5.584258835921342
    },
    {
        "question": "66,995,854 ÷ 4,545,629=？",
        "answer": 1.1684539403873155
    },
    {
        "question": "68 × 5,575=？",
        "answer": 5.578753784426435
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 202=？",
        "answer": 3.346744054604849
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,019,185=？",
        "answer": 6.907236102643278
    },
    {
        "question": "2,189,346 ÷ 212=？",
        "answer": 4.0139785411217055
    },
    {
        "question": "15,803 × 33,651=？",
        "answer": 8.725737514697961
    },
    {
        "question": "50,480,114 ÷ 225,179=？",
        "answer": 2.3505924408732697
    },
    {
        "question": "58,772 ÷ 28,777=？",
        "answer": 0.3101249531300131
    },
    {
        "question": "285,370,569 ÷ 3,980,113=？",
        "answer": 1.8555137788122227
    },
    {
        "question": "695 × 18,060=？",
        "answer": 7.098702550567601
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 20,177=？",
        "answer": 5.583610194949857
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,524=？",
        "answer": 3.8480658954039915
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 15,202=？",
        "answer": 5.026998768210661
    },
    {
        "question": "278,092 ÷ 2,023=？",
        "answer": 2.138192612724678
    },
    {
        "question": "3,832,528 ÷ 118,239=？",
        "answer": 1.5107245883985458
    },
    {
        "question": "3,675 × 4,313=？",
        "answer": 7.200036801566165
    },
    {
        "question": "19,197,234 ÷ 15,544,897=？",
        "answer": 0.09165080988051542
    },
    {
        "question": "108,763,168 ÷ 17,457=？",
        "answer": 3.794512237102435
    },
    {
        "question": "339,832 × 537=？",
        "answer": 8.261238557139825
    },
    {
        "question": "5,948 ÷ 304=？",
        "answer": 1.2914973762411628
    },
    {
        "question": "38,568 ÷ 1,956=？",
        "answer": 1.294858268023368
    },
    {
        "question": "75,024,537 ÷ 1,108,287=？",
        "answer": 1.830551084866009
    },
    {
        "question": "22,259 × 2,809=？",
        "answer": 7.796057388677481
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 327=？",
        "answer": 3.894758994371892
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 102,308,454=？",
        "answer": 8.00991152201961
    },
    {
        "question": "666,313 ÷ 403,460=？",
        "answer": 0.21787780240100524
    },
    {
        "question": "581,300,999 ÷ 216=？",
        "answer": 6.429947318166741
    },
    {
        "question": "536,010,622 ÷ 251=？",
        "answer": 6.329499674611505
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 10,823=？",
        "answer": 5.075740343605073
    },
    {
        "question": "191,905 ÷ 6,515=？",
        "answer": 1.469171870185153
    },
    {
        "question": "51,994 × 2,919=？",
        "answer": 8.18118732482982
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 184,118=？",
        "answer": 6.043247499064404
    },
    {
        "question": "241,185 ÷ 397=？",
        "answer": 2.783559787501849
    },
    {
        "question": "280,655 ÷ 232=？",
        "answer": 3.0826847988928923
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 1,077=？",
        "answer": 4.463579467456969
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 49,586,103=？",
        "answer": 8.925808899560504
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 1,362,313=？",
        "answer": 7.874639590430609
    },
    {
        "question": "10,144,449 ÷ 9,172,973=？",
        "answer": 0.04371834792886358
    },
    {
        "question": "2,333 × 374=？",
        "answer": 5.940786340994233
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 10,394=？",
        "answer": 4.794933962870484
    },
    {
        "question": "7,292,762 ÷ 4,326,815=？",
        "answer": 0.22672371392141433
    },
    {
        "question": "296,277,203 ÷ 231,197=？",
        "answer": 3.1077160416461784
    },
    {
        "question": "2,275,375 × 213=？",
        "answer": 8.685432585535
    },
    {
        "question": "87,980 ÷ 334=？",
        "answer": 2.4206374908292796
    },
    {
        "question": "853,175,456 ÷ 4,897,132=？",
        "answer": 2.241096542861308
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 6,237,479=？",
        "answer": 8.607922453118073
    },
    {
        "question": "258 × 1,292,186=？",
        "answer": 8.5229447373929
    },
    {
        "question": "3,325 × 1,196=？",
        "answer": 6.599522829291516
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 277,000=？",
        "answer": 7.174873528887417
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 3,879,879=？",
        "answer": 7.543060691102676
    },
    {
        "question": "1,861 × 1,045=？",
        "answer": 6.28886266357784
    },
    {
        "question": "58,697 ÷ 24,708=？",
        "answer": 0.3757783123853605
    },
    {
        "question": "48,031,683 ÷ 3,054,817=？",
        "answer": 1.196542605533375
    },
    {
        "question": "911,461,020 ÷ 1,166=？",
        "answer": 5.893039549709094
    },
    {
        "question": "489 × 101,752=？",
        "answer": 7.696851813437855
    },
    {
        "question": "10,215 × 14,275=？",
        "answer": 8.163814487886352
    },
    {
        "question": "115,017 ÷ 947=？",
        "answer": 2.084412056659431
    },
    {
        "question": "33,043,007 ÷ 205=？",
        "answer": 5.207325701323948
    },
    {
        "question": "622,251 × 228=？",
        "answer": 8.15190045022264
    },
    {
        "question": "17,757,149 ÷ 124,916=？",
        "answer": 2.1527551698539553
    },
    {
        "question": "3,944 × 1,150=？",
        "answer": 6.656634746622785
    },
    {
        "question": "89 × 331=？",
        "answer": 4.469218000420631
    },
    {
        "question": "15,226 ÷ 1,704=？",
        "answer": 0.9511162350266116
    },
    {
        "question": "22,489,007 ÷ 5,469,072=？",
        "answer": 0.6140566387540719
    },
    {
        "question": "170,980,687 ÷ 1,955=？",
        "answer": 4.941800296011059
    },
    {
        "question": "9,253,109 ÷ 61,225=？",
        "answer": 2.1793588843136176
    },
    {
        "question": "456,211,380 ÷ 11,906=？",
        "answer": 4.583400236152256
    },
    {
        "question": "4,952,468 ÷ 3,025=？",
        "answer": 3.214096299069988
    },
    {
        "question": "16,418,627 ÷ 7,053,201=？",
        "answer": 0.3669505762146011
    },
    {
        "question": "53,082 × 4,529=？",
        "answer": 8.380949598338061
    },
    {
        "question": "99 × 4,099,207=？",
        "answer": 8.6083350442846
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 41,691,427=？",
        "answer": 8.398198010648331
    },
    {
        "question": "205 × 62,949=？",
        "answer": 7.110742696406205
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,014=？",
        "answer": 3.4831592097169795
    },
    {
        "question": "12,434 × 3,343=？",
        "answer": 7.618747239624706
    },
    {
        "question": "1,635,991 ÷ 17,262=？",
        "answer": 1.97668979790419
    },
    {
        "question": "1,908 × 73,396=？",
        "answer": 8.146250762365021
    },
    {
        "question": "19,265 × 37,620=？",
        "answer": 8.86018780456338
    },
    {
        "question": "143 × 13,578=？",
        "answer": 6.288171841803434
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 41,386=？",
        "answer": 5.461951493429393
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 49,388,018=？",
        "answer": 7.99465159342029
    },
    {
        "question": "11,429,721 ÷ 680=？",
        "answer": 4.225526716670734
    },
    {
        "question": "12,278 × 4,924=？",
        "answer": 7.7814456733035575
    },
    {
        "question": "2,336 × 75,986=？",
        "answer": 8.249206421736591
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 538=？",
        "answer": 3.934902258322314
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 243,042,439=？",
        "answer": 8.686712110473206
    },
    {
        "question": "694 × 19,442=？",
        "answer": 7.130100409249142
    },
    {
        "question": "358,710,793 ÷ 115,302=？",
        "answer": 3.4929076035328936
    },
    {
        "question": "188,067,325 ÷ 43,463=？",
        "answer": 3.6361936474983967
    },
    {
        "question": "661 × 1,078=？",
        "answer": 5.85282022033636
    },
    {
        "question": "325,077,370 ÷ 8,458,800=？",
        "answer": 1.584677980871385
    },
    {
        "question": "170,072 ÷ 3,241=？",
        "answer": 1.7199537878922557
    },
    {
        "question": "374,553,746 ÷ 300,305,741=？",
        "answer": 0.09595051014417441
    },
    {
        "question": "698 × 28,659=？",
        "answer": 7.301116455088578
    },
    {
        "question": "558,297,009 ÷ 30,746,609=？",
        "answer": 1.2590680761546231
    },
    {
        "question": "157 × 1,481,731=？",
        "answer": 8.366669019467203
    },
    {
        "question": "372,144,445 ÷ 179,070,651=？",
        "answer": 0.31768712819842987
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 25,438,113=？",
        "answer": 8.635933813571539
    },
    {
        "question": "5,674,092 ÷ 290=？",
        "answer": 4.291498375289537
    },
    {
        "question": "451,325 ÷ 996=？",
        "answer": 2.656230052400533
    },
    {
        "question": "110,078,717 ÷ 724,014=？",
        "answer": 2.1819563950147676
    },
    {
        "question": "8,890 × 99,968=？",
        "answer": 8.948762764495383
    },
    {
        "question": "64,313 × 6,492=？",
        "answer": 8.620677279686698
    },
    {
        "question": "364 × 4,190=？",
        "answer": 6.1833154066153515
    },
    {
        "question": "47,027 ÷ 1,571=？",
        "answer": 1.4761710895810298
    },
    {
        "question": "34,890,313 ÷ 18,218,542=？",
        "answer": 0.28219124735557066
    },
    {
        "question": "35,902,809 ÷ 1,389=？",
        "answer": 4.412426182937507
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 477,060=？",
        "answer": 5.979602999505363
    },
    {
        "question": "167 × 64,030=？",
        "answer": 7.029099972971751
    },
    {
        "question": "176 × 41,672=？",
        "answer": 6.865357012238791
    },
    {
        "question": "591,999,029 ÷ 27,989,117=？",
        "answer": 1.3253317968210994
    },
    {
        "question": "424,730 × 2,175=？",
        "answer": 8.965572198933826
    },
    {
        "question": "229,579,743 ÷ 7,703=？",
        "answer": 4.474273667522255
    },
    {
        "question": "167 × 47,258=？",
        "answer": 6.897191809109543
    },
    {
        "question": "606,260,380 ÷ 362,762,118=？",
        "answer": 0.22303725850736808
    },
    {
        "question": "19,249,266 ÷ 7,111,208=？",
        "answer": 0.4324707921700435
    },
    {
        "question": "76,854,875 ÷ 311,455=？",
        "answer": 2.3922761132545998
    },
    {
        "question": "347,004,956 ÷ 342=？",
        "answer": 6.006309571466963
    },
    {
        "question": "105,799,335 ÷ 19,463=？",
        "answer": 3.735273155311855
    },
    {
        "question": "6,179,638 ÷ 2,375=？",
        "answer": 3.415299421126776
    },
    {
        "question": "671,660,791 ÷ 3,129=？",
        "answer": 5.331744433433944
    },
    {
        "question": "157,865,423 ÷ 16,650=？",
        "answer": 3.976872779786531
    },
    {
        "question": "42,003 × 404=？",
        "answer": 7.229661675435086
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 8,462,145=？",
        "answer": 7.881722972193091
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 197,665=？",
        "answer": 6.141027816801245
    },
    {
        "question": "179,313,224 ÷ 6,488,799=？",
        "answer": 1.4414479976499646
    },
    {
        "question": "58,704,776 ÷ 1,782,527=？",
        "answer": 1.5176373184044785
    },
    {
        "question": "197,978 ÷ 61,795=？",
        "answer": 0.5056635960647381
    },
    {
        "question": "640,168,931 ÷ 9,395,233=？",
        "answer": 1.8333870379306598
    },
    {
        "question": "15,032 × 8,448=？",
        "answer": 8.103770672282206
    },
    {
        "question": "44,340,876 ÷ 48,956=？",
        "answer": 2.956998342688509
    },
    {
        "question": "2,463 × 401,123=？",
        "answer": 8.994741976554993
    },
    {
        "question": "102 × 19,309=？",
        "answer": 6.29435995430736
    },
    {
        "question": "31,572 × 3,850=？",
        "answer": 8.084762823641828
    },
    {
        "question": "346,306 ÷ 166,688=？",
        "answer": 0.31755568032564163
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 19,772=？",
        "answer": 5.8871152088152385
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,826=？",
        "answer": 3.7386220279179425
    },
    {
        "question": "185,537,208 ÷ 1,387,140=？",
        "answer": 2.1263107216002926
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 268,611=？",
        "answer": 6.947637733547451
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 13,434=？",
        "answer": 5.169598029120899
    },
    {
        "question": "9,113,736 ÷ 1,171,492=？",
        "answer": 0.8909571169154111
    },
    {
        "question": "1,203,510 ÷ 117,432=？",
        "answer": 1.0106632457201246
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 19,199,308=？",
        "answer": 7.5843155713884975
    },
    {
        "question": "235 × 359,183=？",
        "answer": 7.926383635754456
    },
    {
        "question": "15,317,341 ÷ 10,702,196=？",
        "answer": 0.1557104805010385
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 13,302,316=？",
        "answer": 8.300018519455499
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 969,874=？",
        "answer": 7.742590172764428
    },
    {
        "question": "359,068 ÷ 1,030=？",
        "answer": 2.542339477990745
    },
    {
        "question": "849,956,738 ÷ 3,668,507=？",
        "answer": 2.3649074689921368
    },
    {
        "question": "675 × 507=？",
        "answer": 5.534311732164361
    },
    {
        "question": "18,950,665 ÷ 19,733=？",
        "answer": 2.9824313385640444
    },
    {
        "question": "14,277 ÷ 2,403=？",
        "answer": 0.7738831887145198
    },
    {
        "question": "55,533,299 ÷ 33,322=？",
        "answer": 3.2218224138010547
    },
    {
        "question": "403,379,442 ÷ 200,373,163=？",
        "answer": 0.3038742070591066
    },
    {
        "question": "360 ÷ 226=？",
        "answer": 0.20219406161988634
    },
    {
        "question": "653,878 × 1,121=？",
        "answer": 8.865102338183258
    },
    {
        "question": "15,312,932 ÷ 327=？",
        "answer": 4.670510601297772
    },
    {
        "question": "28,435 ÷ 210=？",
        "answer": 2.131633937854267
    },
    {
        "question": "418,316,800 ÷ 825=？",
        "answer": 5.7050513580598325
    },
    {
        "question": "63,267,027 ÷ 1,942,928=？",
        "answer": 1.5127207198329273
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,826=？",
        "answer": 3.8635607645262424
    },
    {
        "question": "161,387,701 ÷ 1,383,947=？",
        "answer": 2.066750976441529
    },
    {
        "question": "60,232 ÷ 25,121=？",
        "answer": 0.3797903606184951
    },
    {
        "question": "110,377,840 ÷ 32,953=？",
        "answer": 3.524986932682968
    },
    {
        "question": "28,241,827 ÷ 76,441=？",
        "answer": 2.5675664285014923
    },
    {
        "question": "37,821,984 ÷ 3,020=？",
        "answer": 4.097737363615659
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 45,628=？",
        "answer": 5.9602614285392095
    },
    {
        "question": "9,444,283 ÷ 628=？",
        "answer": 4.177209348593352
    },
    {
        "question": "5,251 × 2,356=？",
        "answer": 7.092417304402121
    },
    {
        "question": "384,007,569 ÷ 697=？",
        "answer": 5.741107006536546
    },
    {
        "question": "483,984,001 ÷ 16,002,393=？",
        "answer": 1.4806460734945546
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 85,230,179=？",
        "answer": 8.231623396210658
    },
    {
        "question": "166,896,670 ÷ 490,021=？",
        "answer": 2.5322329792698195
    },
    {
        "question": "7,388,292 ÷ 625,499=？",
        "answer": 1.0723174315762503
    },
    {
        "question": "26,514 × 1,347=？",
        "answer": 7.552842847668923
    },
    {
        "question": "15,540,845 ÷ 25,994=？",
        "answer": 2.7766015143331946
    },
    {
        "question": "814 × 1,218=？",
        "answer": 5.996271693186058
    },
    {
        "question": "27,206,697 ÷ 2,036=？",
        "answer": 4.125898046257424
    },
    {
        "question": "4,920,192 ÷ 106,629=？",
        "answer": 1.6641067142367392
    },
    {
        "question": "49,599 ÷ 3,350=？",
        "answer": 1.1704281134279504
    },
    {
        "question": "58,790 × 543=？",
        "answer": 7.5041032897779285
    },
    {
        "question": "29,406 ÷ 206=？",
        "answer": 2.1545687325271197
    },
    {
        "question": "4,786 × 9,699=？",
        "answer": 7.666699653608637
    },
    {
        "question": "297,044,015 ÷ 4,818=？",
        "answer": 4.789954010743498
    },
    {
        "question": "15,998,815 ÷ 5,020=？",
        "answer": 3.503384099384673
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 136,672=？",
        "answer": 5.913830800130373
    },
    {
        "question": "2,913 × 1,096=？",
        "answer": 6.504151038776017
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 90,544,015=？",
        "answer": 8.859949735530721
    },
    {
        "question": "20,072,845 ÷ 6,097=？",
        "answer": 3.5174927360224184
    },
    {
        "question": "19,700 ÷ 3,893=？",
        "answer": 0.704181822443431
    },
    {
        "question": "68,165,398 ÷ 286=？",
        "answer": 5.37719794165759
    },
    {
        "question": "285,777 ÷ 56,665=？",
        "answer": 0.7027123797241751
    },
    {
        "question": "33,302 × 1,497=？",
        "answer": 7.697692116818774
    },
    {
        "question": "952,221,611 ÷ 65,950=？",
        "answer": 4.159523233831978
    },
    {
        "question": "79,339,941 ÷ 16,124,507=？",
        "answer": 0.6920054280417411
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,315,257=？",
        "answer": 6.9976384554410185
    },
    {
        "question": "97,873,148 ÷ 537=？",
        "answer": 5.260689271527464
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 113,206=？",
        "answer": 5.3548994410483575
    },
    {
        "question": "669,889,101 ÷ 43,068=？",
        "answer": 4.191848207558521
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 410,259=？",
        "answer": 6.868330622207996
    },
    {
        "question": "623,296,054 ÷ 10,018=？",
        "answer": 4.793913350089682
    },
    {
        "question": "72,787 ÷ 744=？",
        "answer": 1.9904808842559418
    },
    {
        "question": "269,210,953 ÷ 4,840=？",
        "answer": 4.745247363783797
    },
    {
        "question": "295 × 42,780=？",
        "answer": 7.1010627962136725
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 77,731=？",
        "answer": 5.668745505271535
    },
    {
        "question": "263,586 ÷ 17,534=？",
        "answer": 1.1770413373750785
    },
    {
        "question": "23,135 × 4,846=？",
        "answer": 8.049652913637404
    },
    {
        "question": "978 × 5,128=？",
        "answer": 6.7002868712983625
    },
    {
        "question": "29,313,778 ÷ 6,909=？",
        "answer": 3.6276566018315153
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,358=？",
        "answer": 3.610021024664145
    },
    {
        "question": "201,471 ÷ 848=？",
        "answer": 2.3758166898017095
    },
    {
        "question": "168,874 × 4,018=？",
        "answer": 8.831572722742731
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 13,152,482=？",
        "answer": 8.232951068417089
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 261=？",
        "answer": 2.717670503002262
    },
    {
        "question": "3,678 × 248,888=？",
        "answer": 8.961615682742405
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 6,912=？",
        "answer": 4.538573733806856
    },
    {
        "question": "212,707,665 ÷ 387=？",
        "answer": 5.740072175129349
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 13,904=？",
        "answer": 5.906567752667528
    },
    {
        "question": "727 × 10,859=？",
        "answer": 6.897324243986795
    },
    {
        "question": "21,883,430 ÷ 3,670,926=？",
        "answer": 0.7753397642290493
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 5,746=？",
        "answer": 5.776398960954709
    },
    {
        "question": "1,322 ÷ 1,185=？",
        "answer": 0.0475131048034988
    },
    {
        "question": "876,609,893 ÷ 8,655,974=？",
        "answer": 2.005490424313847
    },
    {
        "question": "480,338,873 ÷ 29,462,182=？",
        "answer": 1.2122828267666383
    },
    {
        "question": "86,821 × 593=？",
        "answer": 7.711679477078195
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 96,849,840=？",
        "answer": 7.986098907583013
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,550=？",
        "answer": 3.8512583487190755
    },
    {
        "question": "1,852 × 32,753=？",
        "answer": 7.7828920675523525
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 205,939=？",
        "answer": 6.45986663523902
    },
    {
        "question": "5,938 × 2,707=？",
        "answer": 7.206128449030532
    },
    {
        "question": "130,113 ÷ 754=？",
        "answer": 2.2369493445904216
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 16,503,086=？",
        "answer": 7.694686417567187
    },
    {
        "question": "343 × 2,109=？",
        "answer": 5.859370699782257
    },
    {
        "question": "33,017,105 ÷ 504,477=？",
        "answer": 1.8158976200940713
    },
    {
        "question": "133,336,776 ÷ 14,820=？",
        "answer": 3.95410174630375
    },
    {
        "question": "234,558,151 ÷ 11,859,453=？",
        "answer": 1.296185871182061
    },
    {
        "question": "972,534,335 ÷ 86,885=？",
        "answer": 4.048960137437139
    },
    {
        "question": "4,160,618 ÷ 239,821=？",
        "answer": 1.239270634062421
    },
    {
        "question": "448,698 × 437=？",
        "answer": 8.292435570709202
    },
    {
        "question": "60,222,613 ÷ 371=？",
        "answer": 5.2103856855813175
    },
    {
        "question": "12,504,671 ÷ 16,259=？",
        "answer": 2.885978438796909
    },
    {
        "question": "13,666,908 ÷ 798,976=？",
        "answer": 1.2331365369601774
    },
    {
        "question": "2,061 × 5,763=？",
        "answer": 7.074726611360569
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 18,974=？",
        "answer": 6.091072252887519
    },
    {
        "question": "41,973,530 ÷ 12,896=？",
        "answer": 3.512520470722685
    },
    {
        "question": "1,263,088 ÷ 205=？",
        "answer": 3.78967974807681
    },
    {
        "question": "11,236 × 32,644=？",
        "answer": 8.564415099713434
    },
    {
        "question": "350,348 × 1,814=？",
        "answer": 8.803136925343043
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 11,872,946=？",
        "answer": 8.153739738616347
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 25,786=？",
        "answer": 5.615503960983908
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 110,946,107=？",
        "answer": 8.890210107843389
    },
    {
        "question": "246 × 123,136=？",
        "answer": 7.48132014878906
    },
    {
        "question": "1,153 × 120,562=？",
        "answer": 8.143039751161322
    },
    {
        "question": "455,313,728 ÷ 5,313=？",
        "answer": 4.932970928852148
    },
    {
        "question": "7,910,071 ÷ 2,626,087=？",
        "answer": 0.4788712719048215
    },
    {
        "question": "7,304 × 12,465=？",
        "answer": 7.959253047366035
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,173=？",
        "answer": 3.638089721984506
    },
    {
        "question": "295,903,200 ÷ 668=？",
        "answer": 5.646373199321882
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 816=？",
        "answer": 4.924527383459034
    },
    {
        "question": "38,269,854 ÷ 8,395=？",
        "answer": 3.65883610491439
    },
    {
        "question": "19,784,737 ÷ 71,432=？",
        "answer": 2.442437471574537
    },
    {
        "question": "24,871 × 1,161=？",
        "answer": 7.460525467242158
    },
    {
        "question": "8,697 ÷ 669=？",
        "answer": 1.1139433523068367
    },
    {
        "question": "353,842,091 ÷ 37,651=？",
        "answer": 3.9730329773662163
    },
    {
        "question": "7,599 ÷ 285=？",
        "answer": 1.4259115845017
    },
    {
        "question": "247,232,528 ÷ 2,439,894=？",
        "answer": 2.0057346505894573
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 4,680=？",
        "answer": 4.784189205380961
    },
    {
        "question": "444,291,720 ÷ 8,210=？",
        "answer": 4.733325062509416
    },
    {
        "question": "905,040,696 ÷ 7,104,161=？",
        "answer": 2.1051553129011267
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,272,503=？",
        "answer": 7.055474469555694
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 289=？",
        "answer": 2.4608978427565478
    },
    {
        "question": "320,921,860 ÷ 504=？",
        "answer": 5.803968764177651
    },
    {
        "question": "86,476 ÷ 68,280=？",
        "answer": 0.10260208041162239
    },
    {
        "question": "3,454,975 ÷ 6,657=？",
        "answer": 2.715166352240072
    },
    {
        "question": "188,130 ÷ 44,485=？",
        "answer": 0.6262444605907285
    },
    {
        "question": "243 × 2,111,170=？",
        "answer": 8.710129479473139
    },
    {
        "question": "302,978 ÷ 26,598=？",
        "answer": 1.056562112741832
    },
    {
        "question": "1,550 ÷ 925=？",
        "answer": 0.22418996543125888
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 31,579,779=？",
        "answer": 8.453651595864725
    },
    {
        "question": "487,100,871 ÷ 1,014,798=？",
        "answer": 2.6812393035202193
    },
    {
        "question": "7,769 × 367=？",
        "answer": 6.455031185700213
    },
    {
        "question": "1,398,209 ÷ 2,322=？",
        "answer": 2.779709877868733
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,964=？",
        "answer": 3.594171479114912
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 360,537=？",
        "answer": 7.289343600504684
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 10,995=？",
        "answer": 4.342225229360791
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 33,982=？",
        "answer": 5.376346975565619
    },
    {
        "question": "3,438 ÷ 2,851=？",
        "answer": 0.08130865504157364
    },
    {
        "question": "216,646 × 1,693=？",
        "answer": 8.564407633044228
    },
    {
        "question": "1,303,112 ÷ 1,658=？",
        "answer": 2.895397217887903
    },
    {
        "question": "2,030,012 ÷ 1,231=？",
        "answer": 3.21724055223233
    },
    {
        "question": "4,259 × 413=？",
        "answer": 6.24525769173015
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 350=？",
        "answer": 4.146128035678238
    },
    {
        "question": "565,323 ÷ 213,768=？",
        "answer": 0.42235396093552247
    },
    {
        "question": "86,514 × 280=？",
        "answer": 7.384244423555781
    },
    {
        "question": "7,673,831 ÷ 1,188=？",
        "answer": 3.8101957898992143
    },
    {
        "question": "305 × 26,805=？",
        "answer": 6.912515650908111
    },
    {
        "question": "153,999,485 ÷ 257,734=？",
        "answer": 2.776347554481136
    },
    {
        "question": "1,341 × 143,501=？",
        "answer": 8.284283705353447
    },
    {
        "question": "168 × 8,460=？",
        "answer": 6.152679644764887
    },
    {
        "question": "33,323,422 ÷ 101,696=？",
        "answer": 2.515445721765794
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 79,950=？",
        "answer": 5.379939722801916
    },
    {
        "question": "7,616 × 3,200=？",
        "answer": 7.386876913696324
    },
    {
        "question": "17,309 ÷ 2,536=？",
        "answer": 0.8341227287161321
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,664=？",
        "answer": 4.124504224834283
    },
    {
        "question": "527,100,746 ÷ 49,829=？",
        "answer": 4.024411459306499
    },
    {
        "question": "512,602 × 551=？",
        "answer": 8.45093189517381
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 22,058=？",
        "answer": 5.598838637489431
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 433,341,206=？",
        "answer": 8.63682998764402
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 3,981=？",
        "answer": 5.4061721515679855
    },
    {
        "question": "38,597 ÷ 6,558=？",
        "answer": 0.769782137569535
    },
    {
        "question": "9,100 × 67,992=？",
        "answer": 8.791499208553137
    },
    {
        "question": "8,401 × 5,242=？",
        "answer": 7.64382800131926
    },
    {
        "question": "862 × 23,369=？",
        "answer": 7.304147394401198
    },
    {
        "question": "39,154,080 ÷ 78,491=？",
        "answer": 2.6979571616771443
    },
    {
        "question": "14,646,839 ÷ 4,033,462=？",
        "answer": 0.5600659380343104
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,699,771=？",
        "answer": 6.531420411080232
    },
    {
        "question": "82,737 × 3,003=？",
        "answer": 8.395255101755014
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 6,624=？",
        "answer": 4.967248359455062
    },
    {
        "question": "1,234,193 ÷ 921,265=？",
        "answer": 0.12699850679752708
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 649,004=？",
        "answer": 6.414307364819509
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 206,272,046=？",
        "answer": 8.31444037634671
    },
    {
        "question": "6,580 ÷ 4,177=？",
        "answer": 0.19736141834883436
    },
    {
        "question": "15,292,749 ÷ 93,952=？",
        "answer": 2.211579530944506
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 115,000=？",
        "answer": 6.6047658847038875
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,862=？",
        "answer": 3.4566696294237578
    },
    {
        "question": "154,396,301 ÷ 27,264=？",
        "answer": 3.7530473182853132
    },
    {
        "question": "16,701 ÷ 15,448=？",
        "answer": 0.03387021525526255
    },
    {
        "question": "1,338 × 808=？",
        "answer": 6.0338674742063905
    },
    {
        "question": "306,791,078 ÷ 1,308,071=？",
        "answer": 2.370211408010077
    },
    {
        "question": "135,295,888 ÷ 1,793,493=？",
        "answer": 1.8775849114751462
    },
    {
        "question": "14,351,249 ÷ 10,381,498=？",
        "answer": 0.14062967506100052
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 13,794=？",
        "answer": 4.440720217316904
    },
    {
        "question": "470,481 ÷ 31,108=？",
        "answer": 1.1796699991979978
    },
    {
        "question": "81,498,373 ÷ 2,592,501=？",
        "answer": 1.497430006169483
    },
    {
        "question": "853,386,869 ÷ 1,231,432=？",
        "answer": 2.840735521136611
    },
    {
        "question": "6,000,109 ÷ 1,267=？",
        "answer": 3.6753825251116266
    },
    {
        "question": "491,295,424 ÷ 1,156,165=？",
        "answer": 2.6283229010088167
    },
    {
        "question": "151,631,703 ÷ 979=？",
        "answer": 5.190007320828742
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,855=？",
        "answer": 3.745465168670727
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 403,819=？",
        "answer": 7.278284606919343
    },
    {
        "question": "46,246 ÷ 867=？",
        "answer": 1.7270550773706648
    },
    {
        "question": "471,856,308 ÷ 16,585=？",
        "answer": 4.454094289423473
    },
    {
        "question": "50,578 ÷ 243=？",
        "answer": 2.318355378493173
    },
    {
        "question": "50,569,577 ÷ 105,044=？",
        "answer": 2.6825180698810813
    },
    {
        "question": "263,524 ÷ 331=？",
        "answer": 2.9009921802051797
    },
    {
        "question": "1,419 × 1,353=？",
        "answer": 6.283280192055097
    },
    {
        "question": "1,257 ÷ 388=？",
        "answer": 0.5105035520917505
    },
    {
        "question": "102,459 × 2,370=？",
        "answer": 8.385298458856289
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,222=？",
        "answer": 4.018866863150907
    },
    {
        "question": "100,396,444 ÷ 93,006,523=？",
        "answer": 0.03320492174547707
    },
    {
        "question": "616,377 ÷ 38,848=？",
        "answer": 1.2004777596669156
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,870=？",
        "answer": 3.5728716022004803
    },
    {
        "question": "26,808 ÷ 14,323=？",
        "answer": 0.27223042290359434
    },
    {
        "question": "265,479,505 ÷ 98,071,962=？",
        "answer": 0.4324861354468683
    },
    {
        "question": "3,210 ÷ 371=？",
        "answer": 0.9371311227898261
    },
    {
        "question": "2,090,362 ÷ 353,735=？",
        "answer": 0.771543469066977
    },
    {
        "question": "598,138 ÷ 8,711=？",
        "answer": 1.836733380490299
    },
    {
        "question": "728,004 ÷ 8,655=？",
        "answer": 1.924866693328486
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 2,882,697=？",
        "answer": 8.158769000472564
    },
    {
        "question": "709,313 ÷ 43,561=？",
        "answer": 1.211740078495267
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 11,212,269=？",
        "answer": 8.280142430000433
    },
    {
        "question": "20,368,139 ÷ 4,429=？",
        "answer": 3.6626456698272074
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 728,865,360=？",
        "answer": 8.86264731047233
    },
    {
        "question": "114,889 ÷ 2,555=？",
        "answer": 1.65288754486167
    },
    {
        "question": "74,769,258 ÷ 37,849,975=？",
        "answer": 0.295657473804756
    },
    {
        "question": "243,711,742 ÷ 15,509,830=？",
        "answer": 1.1962694163116143
    },
    {
        "question": "60,591 ÷ 20,260=？",
        "answer": 0.4757686791715265
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 16,502=？",
        "answer": 4.518566578443118
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 48,942=？",
        "answer": 5.388651717026825
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 21,533,014=？",
        "answer": 7.33310482276151
    },
    {
        "question": "14,508 ÷ 6,431=？",
        "answer": 0.35332903732562887
    },
    {
        "question": "2,062 × 6,325=？",
        "answer": 7.115349190795353
    },
    {
        "question": "322,514 ÷ 83,329=？",
        "answer": 0.5877524016037423
    },
    {
        "question": "646,547,336 ÷ 815,947=？",
        "answer": 2.898938376618542
    },
    {
        "question": "1,030 × 6,096=？",
        "answer": 6.797882183036716
    },
    {
        "question": "350,533,874 ÷ 1,767,548=？",
        "answer": 2.2973587761303245
    },
    {
        "question": "89,958,299 ÷ 164,764=？",
        "answer": 2.737178908026811
    },
    {
        "question": "22,469,082 ÷ 3,510,292=？",
        "answer": 0.8062420848800509
    },
    {
        "question": "97,278,849 ÷ 1,335,435=？",
        "answer": 1.8623956690662253
    },
    {
        "question": "31,308,083 ÷ 585,327=？",
        "answer": 1.72825791875664
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 1,291,699=？",
        "answer": 7.190342569405773
    },
    {
        "question": "696,844 ÷ 354=？",
        "answer": 3.294132302984588
    },
    {
        "question": "171,347 ÷ 30,153=？",
        "answer": 0.7545459773532112
    },
    {
        "question": "325,293 ÷ 328=？",
        "answer": 2.996400874061159
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 17,326=？",
        "answer": 5.560917604796906
    },
    {
        "question": "23,163,156 ÷ 130,028=？",
        "answer": 2.2507608495003484
    },
    {
        "question": "258,630,025 ÷ 10,135,419=？",
        "answer": 1.4068372345827276
    },
    {
        "question": "683 × 36,735=？",
        "answer": 7.399500747861928
    },
    {
        "question": "665,299 × 598=？",
        "answer": 8.599718054654048
    },
    {
        "question": "237,099 ÷ 168,147=？",
        "answer": 0.14924059903993409
    },
    {
        "question": "9,101 ÷ 679=？",
        "answer": 1.1272193400868906
    },
    {
        "question": "213,709,903 ÷ 8,242=？",
        "answer": 4.413792037004073
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 3,142,116=？",
        "answer": 8.120471504593251
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 83,521,223=？",
        "answer": 7.921796845072251
    },
    {
        "question": "8,007,819 ÷ 13,940=？",
        "answer": 2.75925147450178
    },
    {
        "question": "5,016,969 ÷ 5,130=？",
        "answer": 2.990324052405763
    },
    {
        "question": "68,285 × 2,094=？",
        "answer": 8.155301991087617
    },
    {
        "question": "326,207,263 ÷ 658=？",
        "answer": 5.695267732758317
    },
    {
        "question": "38,191,444 ÷ 990=？",
        "answer": 4.5863308845502155
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 273=？",
        "answer": 3.582290682718994
    },
    {
        "question": "1,121,427 ÷ 2,226=？",
        "answer": 2.702245848166364
    },
    {
        "question": "7,696 ÷ 1,019=？",
        "answer": 0.8780908750233302
    },
    {
        "question": "282 × 204=？",
        "answer": 4.75987927574526
    },
    {
        "question": "13,105,671 ÷ 2,144,693=？",
        "answer": 0.7860941270789936
    },
    {
        "question": "160 × 2,430,495=？",
        "answer": 8.589814714639354
    },
    {
        "question": "198,544,451 ÷ 84,035=？",
        "answer": 3.373397549325733
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 391,946=？",
        "answer": 5.593226236618721
    },
    {
        "question": "166,568 ÷ 1,421=？",
        "answer": 2.068997493223261
    },
    {
        "question": "901,269,885 ÷ 912,996=？",
        "answer": 2.9943859849924066
    },
    {
        "question": "13,612,656 ÷ 1,808=？",
        "answer": 3.876744443634659
    },
    {
        "question": "994 ÷ 513=？",
        "answer": 0.28726901928549703
    },
    {
        "question": "2,509,879 ÷ 73,654=？",
        "answer": 1.5324564473924993
    },
    {
        "question": "11,934 × 26,648=？",
        "answer": 8.5024506531912
    },
    {
        "question": "9,216,342 ÷ 49,872=？",
        "answer": 2.266701797244134
    },
    {
        "question": "19,139,283 ÷ 992,668=？",
        "answer": 1.2851216420776113
    },
    {
        "question": "193 × 9,912=？",
        "answer": 6.281718602375781
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,816=？",
        "answer": 4.225722698684167
    },
    {
        "question": "77,313,788 ÷ 8,317=？",
        "answer": 3.9682902506281534
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 52,268,601=？",
        "answer": 7.718240876104806
    },
    {
        "question": "4,410,444 ÷ 101,086=？",
        "answer": 1.6397913004177078
    },
    {
        "question": "213,270,503 ÷ 19,564,738=？",
        "answer": 1.037456756788259
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,232,156=？",
        "answer": 6.391695691844803
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 97,959=？",
        "answer": 5.593104334372119
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 1,420,544=？",
        "answer": 7.3565746727819405
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 1,846,632=？",
        "answer": 8.283413696410424
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,673=？",
        "answer": 3.866050924009275
    },
    {
        "question": "30,548 ÷ 24,628=？",
        "answer": 0.09355363701111698
    },
    {
        "question": "6,576,126 ÷ 7,309=？",
        "answer": 2.954112163904177
    },
    {
        "question": "605,556,403 ÷ 38,184,957=？",
        "answer": 1.2002622947293182
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 133,334=？",
        "answer": 6.5399142560460986
    },
    {
        "question": "214,256,573 ÷ 4,615,327=？",
        "answer": 1.66673167756024
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 107,424=？",
        "answer": 5.031101319567918
    },
    {
        "question": "1,079 ÷ 247=？",
        "answer": 0.6403244914232449
    },
    {
        "question": "844,488,712 ÷ 7,432=？",
        "answer": 5.05548814789021
    },
    {
        "question": "129,273,910 ÷ 2,914,569=？",
        "answer": 1.6469365432765526
    },
    {
        "question": "7,364 ÷ 235=？",
        "answer": 1.4960459175602407
    },
    {
        "question": "298,531 ÷ 42,040=？",
        "answer": 0.8513267283768448
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 75,824=？",
        "answer": 5.356927946074989
    },
    {
        "question": "20,146,026 ÷ 1,214=？",
        "answer": 4.219970703366483
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 150,550,471=？",
        "answer": 8.654803373269079
    },
    {
        "question": "151,048,460 ÷ 1,728,482=？",
        "answer": 1.9414514405617391
    },
    {
        "question": "341,331 ÷ 241=？",
        "answer": 3.151158690525199
    },
    {
        "question": "34,104 ÷ 3,637=？",
        "answer": 0.9720620185843639
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 10,759=？",
        "answer": 4.9348618945059455
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 331,576=？",
        "answer": 6.423673075080144
    },
    {
        "question": "197 × 48,863=？",
        "answer": 6.983446353626045
    },
    {
        "question": "221,075 × 962=？",
        "answer": 8.327714705724983
    },
    {
        "question": "158,049 ÷ 491=？",
        "answer": 2.507710260214251
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 124,487=？",
        "answer": 6.417343295779752
    },
    {
        "question": "16,451 ÷ 2,793=？",
        "answer": 0.7701213666629211
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 1,022=？",
        "answer": 4.0508435809569185
    },
    {
        "question": "399,935 ÷ 233,814=？",
        "answer": 0.23311890103514862
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 1,624,864=？",
        "answer": 7.466089521789719
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 10,625=？",
        "answer": 5.669781615208537
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 25,220=？",
        "answer": 5.632194003615337
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 16,094=？",
        "answer": 4.905634001326955
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 387=？",
        "answer": 4.3280736545131555
    },
    {
        "question": "108,693,649 ÷ 629,987=？",
        "answer": 2.236872581151874
    },
    {
        "question": "10,727 × 818=？",
        "answer": 6.9432315842937316
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 66,214=？",
        "answer": 6.163372505306075
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 3,072,879=？",
        "answer": 8.078610066512649
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 16,936,525=？",
        "answer": 7.705945562241003
    },
    {
        "question": "570,855,786 ÷ 93,712,100=？",
        "answer": 0.7847307371550186
    },
    {
        "question": "33,006,255 ÷ 246,898=？",
        "answer": 2.126078678683408
    },
    {
        "question": "396,492,310 ÷ 262,253=？",
        "answer": 3.1795143036249565
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,120,217=？",
        "answer": 6.614920089678961
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 187,460=？",
        "answer": 6.272908612690247
    },
    {
        "question": "193,373,567 ÷ 317,395=？",
        "answer": 2.7847970274414737
    },
    {
        "question": "224,584,891 ÷ 28,055,484=？",
        "answer": 0.9033627702993995
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,216=？",
        "answer": 4.049838000622583
    },
    {
        "question": "52,245,141 ÷ 4,127=？",
        "answer": 4.102411436718793
    },
    {
        "question": "277,672 ÷ 45,807=？",
        "answer": 0.7826002385799848
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 7,554=？",
        "answer": 5.355298235211169
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 28,125=？",
        "answer": 6.102305044894763
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 18,685=？",
        "answer": 4.572523097849637
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 989,655=？",
        "answer": 5.99548382317397
    },
    {
        "question": "499,504,653 ÷ 5,294=？",
        "answer": 4.9747556011678675
    },
    {
        "question": "15,872,947 ÷ 16,664=？",
        "answer": 2.9788783091988837
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 224,257=？",
        "answer": 6.049716012413024
    },
    {
        "question": "436,513 ÷ 206,189=？",
        "answer": 0.3257316898227893
    },
    {
        "question": "185 × 497=？",
        "answer": 4.963528117136346
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 5,564,073=？",
        "answer": 7.222514073970872
    },
    {
        "question": "99,513,034 ÷ 75,120=？",
        "answer": 3.1221243881565632
    },
    {
        "question": "5,928 × 565=？",
        "answer": 6.52495664279071
    },
    {
        "question": "248,989,039 ÷ 211,840=？",
        "answer": 3.0701722612373605
    },
    {
        "question": "477,072 ÷ 167,673=？",
        "answer": 0.4541207931890265
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 147,675=？",
        "answer": 5.6464282342494805
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 548,542=？",
        "answer": 6.81839113168656
    },
    {
        "question": "1,802,963 ÷ 195,592=？",
        "answer": 0.9646357267876218
    },
    {
        "question": "511,888,855 ÷ 1,396=？",
        "answer": 5.564290255774352
    },
    {
        "question": "320,444,809 ÷ 224,922,968=？",
        "answer": 0.15371943502156277
    },
    {
        "question": "64,936 ÷ 15,517=？",
        "answer": 0.6216777728271471
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 10,740,678=？",
        "answer": 8.63309168818172
    },
    {
        "question": "739,460,567 ÷ 3,186=？",
        "answer": 5.365669247988933
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 7,820,095=？",
        "answer": 7.847454538423109
    },
    {
        "question": "19,591,970 ÷ 792=？",
        "answer": 4.393352925518771
    },
    {
        "question": "52,763,087 ÷ 5,133,778=？",
        "answer": 1.0118931122611934
    },
    {
        "question": "585,403,837 ÷ 1,715,780=？",
        "answer": 2.532993963504938
    },
    {
        "question": "252 × 614=？",
        "answer": 5.189568911922712
    },
    {
        "question": "43,039 ÷ 21,824=？",
        "answer": 0.29492781907954957
    },
    {
        "question": "42,293 × 261=？",
        "answer": 7.042908999702855
    },
    {
        "question": "4,434,451 ÷ 3,022=？",
        "answer": 3.166545400370143
    },
    {
        "question": "210,953 ÷ 11,439=？",
        "answer": 1.2657976459472802
    },
    {
        "question": "389 × 1,266,588=？",
        "answer": 8.692584970412183
    },
    {
        "question": "51,679 ÷ 24,740=？",
        "answer": 0.31991440608162464
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 2,027,505=？",
        "answer": 7.919745790611429
    },
    {
        "question": "2,164 ÷ 1,076=？",
        "answer": 0.3034449851041615
    },
    {
        "question": "31,933,571 ÷ 5,729,818=？",
        "answer": 0.7461066592185563
    },
    {
        "question": "186,031 × 568=？",
        "answer": 8.023933656311389
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 4,259=？",
        "answer": 5.231367631401711
    },
    {
        "question": "207,920,072 ÷ 15,008=？",
        "answer": 4.141573595848489
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 30,672=？",
        "answer": 5.440984604973313
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 12,632,413=？",
        "answer": 8.247614351593056
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 125,294,310=？",
        "answer": 8.699991340121697
    },
    {
        "question": "1,936 × 18,996=？",
        "answer": 7.565567513882356
    },
    {
        "question": "14,724,143 ÷ 289,096=？",
        "answer": 1.7069879439252487
    },
    {
        "question": "273 × 28,488=？",
        "answer": 6.8908246077069535
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 41,799,198=？",
        "answer": 8.399319199442987
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 29,555,314=？",
        "answer": 8.832363413735418
    },
    {
        "question": "19,360,440 ÷ 671,976=？",
        "answer": 1.4595614609297136
    },
    {
        "question": "495,114 ÷ 1,266=？",
        "answer": 2.5922715010718487
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 24,666,309=？",
        "answer": 7.693134163359652
    },
    {
        "question": "94,979,745 ÷ 3,730=？",
        "answer": 4.405922167452457
    },
    {
        "question": "2,665,660 ÷ 58,179=？",
        "answer": 1.6610385029755241
    },
    {
        "question": "3,211,616 ÷ 290,473=？",
        "answer": 1.043617842736419
    },
    {
        "question": "498,399 ÷ 1,956=？",
        "answer": 2.406208311821285
    },
    {
        "question": "724,188 ÷ 2,907=？",
        "answer": 2.39640629238778
    },
    {
        "question": "484,278 ÷ 21,353=？",
        "answer": 1.3556358401088053
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,518,375=？",
        "answer": 6.482409040160113
    },
    {
        "question": "41,115 ÷ 14,035=？",
        "answer": 0.4667878776247217
    },
    {
        "question": "985,089 ÷ 6,288=？",
        "answer": 2.194962936514766
    },
    {
        "question": "27,058,215 ÷ 295=？",
        "answer": 4.96247712731006
    },
    {
        "question": "50,061 ÷ 393=？",
        "answer": 2.1051069702891914
    },
    {
        "question": "4,812 ÷ 2,412=？",
        "answer": 0.2999483151996934
    },
    {
        "question": "3,144 × 325=？",
        "answer": 6.009365898346244
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 29,887,829=？",
        "answer": 8.855705611499532
    },
    {
        "question": "381,649,729 ÷ 4,816=？",
        "answer": 4.898978480086225
    },
    {
        "question": "17,057,240 ÷ 555=？",
        "answer": 4.4876157770182825
    },
    {
        "question": "22,925 ÷ 854=？",
        "answer": 1.4288514736530538
    },
    {
        "question": "120,289,537 ÷ 445=？",
        "answer": 5.431867842287574
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,659,006=？",
        "answer": 6.9979992070904515
    },
    {
        "question": "31,494 × 5,096=？",
        "answer": 8.205457242479078
    },
    {
        "question": "82,479 ÷ 3,188=？",
        "answer": 1.4128250740674542
    },
    {
        "question": "4,559 × 2,670=？",
        "answer": 7.085380853566537
    },
    {
        "question": "182 × 334=？",
        "answer": 4.78381785479664
    },
    {
        "question": "150,657 ÷ 58,545=？",
        "answer": 0.41049950483438963
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 261=？",
        "answer": 4.1242106834362176
    },
    {
        "question": "360 × 1,599,383=？",
        "answer": 8.760254976314087
    },
    {
        "question": "13,130,570 ÷ 617=？",
        "answer": 4.327998415253615
    },
    {
        "question": "32,354 ÷ 326=？",
        "answer": 1.9967103810894082
    },
    {
        "question": "2,979 ÷ 580=？",
        "answer": 0.7106425096521063
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 151,079=？",
        "answer": 6.735506602313831
    },
    {
        "question": "23,987,922 ÷ 1,012=？",
        "answer": 4.374812115496518
    },
    {
        "question": "133,559 ÷ 1,691=？",
        "answer": 1.8975295510916612
    },
    {
        "question": "13,105 × 737=？",
        "answer": 6.984904513141671
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 4,294,993=？",
        "answer": 7.11008371507229
    },
    {
        "question": "937 ÷ 320=？",
        "answer": 0.4665896125678723
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 13,884=？",
        "answer": 5.540454613671412
    },
    {
        "question": "61,013,954 ÷ 14,778=？",
        "answer": 3.6158135080694076
    },
    {
        "question": "6,571,329 ÷ 4,422=？",
        "answer": 3.172034472869248
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 77,764=？",
        "answer": 4.89077859159477
    },
    {
        "question": "3,930,882 ÷ 176,740=？",
        "answer": 1.3471551563989501
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 3,315=？",
        "answer": 4.423573519732735
    },
    {
        "question": "784,095,346 ÷ 21,524,155=？",
        "answer": 1.5614427652755563
    },
    {
        "question": "9,047 ÷ 978=？",
        "answer": 0.9661657355290961
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 28,920,533=？",
        "answer": 7.938327547381775
    },
    {
        "question": "546,806,287 ÷ 13,932,835=？",
        "answer": 1.5937940053040374
    },
    {
        "question": "1,433 × 1,402=？",
        "answer": 6.302994204027985
    },
    {
        "question": "285,498,181 ÷ 5,500,385=？",
        "answer": 1.7152102565179694
    },
    {
        "question": "128,496 ÷ 52,484=？",
        "answer": 0.38886268174279043
    },
    {
        "question": "114,863,130 ÷ 27,788=？",
        "answer": 3.6163233563519825
    },
    {
        "question": "9,215,691 ÷ 166,467=？",
        "answer": 1.7431997516018312
    },
    {
        "question": "25,446 ÷ 3,551=？",
        "answer": 0.8552688505417377
    },
    {
        "question": "10,592 × 561=？",
        "answer": 6.773940833351786
    },
    {
        "question": "345,719 ÷ 80,121=？",
        "answer": 0.634976886985367
    },
    {
        "question": "150,559,041 ÷ 50,705=？",
        "answer": 3.4726560527602497
    },
    {
        "question": "222,582 ÷ 881=？",
        "answer": 2.402514132014518
    },
    {
        "question": "29,380,915 ÷ 75,527=？",
        "answer": 2.5899630822780484
    },
    {
        "question": "36,800,639 ÷ 6,358=？",
        "answer": 3.7625348361753224
    },
    {
        "question": "52,145 ÷ 8,197=？",
        "answer": 0.8035577367073085
    },
    {
        "question": "25,446 × 1,700=？",
        "answer": 7.636068444221627
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,826,376=？",
        "answer": 6.883817639531377
    },
    {
        "question": "282,512,378 ÷ 39,231=？",
        "answer": 3.857408102297846
    },
    {
        "question": "3,351 × 4,449=？",
        "answer": 7.173436833583316
    },
    {
        "question": "71,347,700 ÷ 108,853=？",
        "answer": 2.816539574799913
    },
    {
        "question": "658,681,098 ÷ 471,754=？",
        "answer": 3.1449596095511425
    },
    {
        "question": "37,522,931 ÷ 271=？",
        "answer": 5.1413274638702005
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 24,508=？",
        "answer": 4.389307871659916
    },
    {
        "question": "1,424,335 × 209=？",
        "answer": 8.4737584323928
    },
    {
        "question": "718,727,578 ÷ 158,200=？",
        "answer": 3.6573578301495733
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 2,205=？",
        "answer": 5.229899318976339
    },
    {
        "question": "13,927 × 21,622=？",
        "answer": 8.478753438605839
    },
    {
        "question": "625,262,710 ÷ 395,624,177=？",
        "answer": 0.19877970467588876
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 27,868=？",
        "answer": 6.470411667127302
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 9,960,252=？",
        "answer": 7.952512835897657
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 3,434,762=？",
        "answer": 7.234866653834159
    },
    {
        "question": "16,513,412 ÷ 5,656=？",
        "answer": 3.465327415640255
    },
    {
        "question": "7,169 × 12,511=？",
        "answer": 7.952750604477932
    },
    {
        "question": "459 × 3,125=？",
        "answer": 6.156662707217356
    },
    {
        "question": "178,342 ÷ 37,195=？",
        "answer": 0.6807690696443833
    },
    {
        "question": "17,741,836 ÷ 1,847,554=？",
        "answer": 0.9824014197065274
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 55,581=？",
        "answer": 5.523077606617279
    },
    {
        "question": "60,012,737 ÷ 10,850=？",
        "answer": 3.742813695895177
    },
    {
        "question": "962,849 ÷ 312=？",
        "answer": 3.4894035896702547
    },
    {
        "question": "6,045,426 ÷ 3,151,763=？",
        "answer": 0.2828733566530116
    },
    {
        "question": "5,173 × 330=？",
        "answer": 6.23225641828697
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 11,027,087=？",
        "answer": 7.519582055744594
    },
    {
        "question": "6,413,046 ÷ 522=？",
        "answer": 4.089393852067716
    },
    {
        "question": "4,350 × 227=？",
        "answer": 5.99451511414776
    },
    {
        "question": "84,424,868 ÷ 63,907,772=？",
        "answer": 0.12091671316258212
    },
    {
        "question": "597 × 107,671=？",
        "answer": 7.808073077733541
    },
    {
        "question": "247,309,301 ÷ 4,650=？",
        "answer": 4.725787497062194
    },
    {
        "question": "866,730,852 ÷ 656,911=？",
        "answer": 3.1203777217030413
    },
    {
        "question": "229,018 × 1,929=？",
        "answer": 8.645201845326394
    },
    {
        "question": "124,890 × 2,126=？",
        "answer": 8.424090925793719
    },
    {
        "question": "17,577,816 ÷ 1,443,833=？",
        "answer": 1.0854479503273333
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 646,017=？",
        "answer": 5.810243946646863
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 27,988=？",
        "answer": 5.9784507822823585
    },
    {
        "question": "1,345 × 3,661=？",
        "answer": 6.6923220132199575
    },
    {
        "question": "69,638 ÷ 800=？",
        "answer": 1.9397563027158915
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 229,184=？",
        "answer": 5.36018429499579
    },
    {
        "question": "204,695 × 2,441=？",
        "answer": 8.69867501387779
    },
    {
        "question": "1,512 × 4,275=？",
        "answer": 6.810487910229379
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 34,456=？",
        "answer": 6.3823628987688
    },
    {
        "question": "433,380,043 ÷ 3,360=？",
        "answer": 5.110529630944824
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 13,836=？",
        "answer": 5.940351102795906
    },
    {
        "question": "205,938,268 ÷ 6,291,059=？",
        "answer": 1.5150132976929627
    },
    {
        "question": "1,983,975 ÷ 276,770=？",
        "answer": 0.855417181577812
    },
    {
        "question": "146 × 586,378=？",
        "answer": 7.932530523662675
    },
    {
        "question": "893 × 509=？",
        "answer": 5.657569241225305
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,764,500=？",
        "answer": 7.353858551860327
    },
    {
        "question": "14,015,521 ÷ 2,502,229=？",
        "answer": 0.748282193343991
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 218=？",
        "answer": 2.3384564936046046
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 513,137=？",
        "answer": 5.710233330805236
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 379,534=？",
        "answer": 7.110729604654437
    },
    {
        "question": "1,121 × 521=？",
        "answer": 5.766443335894498
    },
    {
        "question": "357,888 ÷ 327=？",
        "answer": 3.039199384061226
    },
    {
        "question": "720,038,049 ÷ 246=？",
        "answer": 6.466420339375296
    },
    {
        "question": "4,561 ÷ 4,116=？",
        "answer": 0.04458470615054302
    },
    {
        "question": "186,587 ÷ 1,255=？",
        "answer": 2.172237656225043
    },
    {
        "question": "26,868 × 11,497=？",
        "answer": 8.48981987098752
    },
    {
        "question": "499,202 ÷ 4,547=？",
        "answer": 2.0405513624276406
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 7,495,888=？",
        "answer": 7.351944343625884
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 6,658,557=？",
        "answer": 7.823380121837226
    },
    {
        "question": "41,681 × 9,590=？",
        "answer": 8.601756737070389
    },
    {
        "question": "75,738 ÷ 2,743=？",
        "answer": 1.441088024993956
    },
    {
        "question": "138 × 4,732=？",
        "answer": 5.814923822357129
    },
    {
        "question": "4,617 × 49,535=？",
        "answer": 8.359272041879711
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 876,351=？",
        "answer": 7.823491678850272
    },
    {
        "question": "6,852,789 ÷ 278=？",
        "answer": 4.391822564011616
    },
    {
        "question": "5,725 × 53,774=？",
        "answer": 8.48834783385534
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,469,671=？",
        "answer": 6.5402882962149285
    },
    {
        "question": "1,265,999 ÷ 883=？",
        "answer": 3.156472659059018
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,995,809=？",
        "answer": 7.07872597545766
    },
    {
        "question": "6,128,184 ÷ 456,832=？",
        "answer": 1.1275752789989884
    },
    {
        "question": "3,132,361 ÷ 2,003=？",
        "answer": 3.1941908587772816
    },
    {
        "question": "2,304,760 ÷ 216,232=？",
        "answer": 1.0277057427242793
    },
    {
        "question": "181,884,357 ÷ 2,398=？",
        "answer": 4.879946170324197
    },
    {
        "question": "272,762,175 ÷ 33,875,771=？",
        "answer": 0.9058949564652247
    },
    {
        "question": "596 × 44,877=？",
        "answer": 7.427270076638225
    },
    {
        "question": "19,247,295 ÷ 2,053=？",
        "answer": 3.971980753350807
    },
    {
        "question": "654,315 ÷ 48,407=？",
        "answer": 1.1308787082116156
    },
    {
        "question": "399,109,554 ÷ 471=？",
        "answer": 5.92807121704655
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 16,772=？",
        "answer": 5.586312689749123
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 187,875=？",
        "answer": 5.273868993594965
    },
    {
        "question": "837 × 897,219=？",
        "answer": 8.875623919858922
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 2,636,495=？",
        "answer": 8.37526946148668
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 17,221=？",
        "answer": 4.236058366738554
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 26,564,418=？",
        "answer": 8.538243657696304
    },
    {
        "question": "412,935 ÷ 66,353=？",
        "answer": 0.794021131563598
    },
    {
        "question": "8,721 × 75,184=？",
        "answer": 8.816691714168966
    },
    {
        "question": "78,756,175 ÷ 4,634,315=？",
        "answer": 1.2302990653499457
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 9,907=？",
        "answer": 4.296972158656532
    },
    {
        "question": "125,478 ÷ 1,127=？",
        "answer": 2.0466436717937064
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 6,181,600=？",
        "answer": 7.490070903572991
    },
    {
        "question": "1,893,100 ÷ 10,563=？",
        "answer": 2.2533862756959384
    },
    {
        "question": "300,713,225 ÷ 100,354=？",
        "answer": 3.476617840592283
    },
    {
        "question": "46,077 ÷ 717=？",
        "answer": 1.8079650394465934
    },
    {
        "question": "1,652,317 ÷ 72,160=？",
        "answer": 1.3597968466246126
    },
    {
        "question": "873 ÷ 379=？",
        "answer": 0.36237503373749735
    },
    {
        "question": "19,806 ÷ 240=？",
        "answer": 1.9165855330023491
    },
    {
        "question": "3,914,737 ÷ 928,752=？",
        "answer": 0.6248028285954339
    },
    {
        "question": "901,656,857 ÷ 870=？",
        "answer": 6.015522037179415
    },
    {
        "question": "16,122 × 1,360=？",
        "answer": 7.340957825187029
    },
    {
        "question": "958,347,663 ÷ 53,668=？",
        "answer": 4.251807677027479
    },
    {
        "question": "151 × 2,057,293=？",
        "answer": 8.492273095682792
    },
    {
        "question": "734 × 8,929=？",
        "answer": 6.816498882880729
    },
    {
        "question": "251 × 3,368=？",
        "answer": 5.9270458043086505
    },
    {
        "question": "204 × 162,411=？",
        "answer": 7.520245607833011
    },
    {
        "question": "1,603,667 ÷ 416,909=？",
        "answer": 0.5850729219184149
    },
    {
        "question": "328,554 ÷ 96,789=？",
        "answer": 0.5307807560439973
    },
    {
        "question": "115 × 200,496=？",
        "answer": 7.36280355299432
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 38,134,572=？",
        "answer": 8.280288880822352
    },
    {
        "question": "1,263,987 ÷ 328=？",
        "answer": 3.5858687635754323
    },
    {
        "question": "8,152,250 ÷ 135,326=？",
        "answer": 1.7798962444210105
    },
    {
        "question": "1,740 × 3,748=？",
        "answer": 6.81434883049834
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 329,379=？",
        "answer": 7.108760513715582
    },
    {
        "question": "58,823,033 ÷ 12,715,500=？",
        "answer": 0.6652139713821383
    },
    {
        "question": "738,026,178 ÷ 12,224=？",
        "answer": 4.780858425414347
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 202=？",
        "answer": 2.606381365110605
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 387=？",
        "answer": 3.064832219738574
    },
    {
        "question": "774,283,100 ÷ 104,566=？",
        "answer": 3.8695092850598525
    },
    {
        "question": "135,723 ÷ 584=？",
        "answer": 2.3662406035441927
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 2,142,693=？",
        "answer": 7.1760579908241775
    },
    {
        "question": "398,145 × 778=？",
        "answer": 8.49102086311238
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,805=？",
        "answer": 4.064832219738574
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 1,961,221=？",
        "answer": 7.690466543529317
    },
    {
        "question": "76,255 ÷ 42,165=？",
        "answer": 0.2573162207487089
    },
    {
        "question": "96 × 2,826,533=？",
        "answer": 8.433525293288294
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 13,575=？",
        "answer": 5.308831097316566
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,776,391=？",
        "answer": 6.990178562553417
    },
    {
        "question": "976,519,365 ÷ 591,010,627=？",
        "answer": 0.21808557001661782
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,182,438=？",
        "answer": 7.209043951774661
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 1,004=？",
        "answer": 4.28048731376183
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 56,335=？",
        "answer": 6.3070807994203975
    },
    {
        "question": "410,873 ÷ 833=？",
        "answer": 2.6930626016796615
    },
    {
        "question": "261 × 1,478,864=？",
        "answer": 8.58656874437419
    },
    {
        "question": "589,674,688 ÷ 4,287,842=？",
        "answer": 2.13837371199502
    },
    {
        "question": "11,465 × 249=？",
        "answer": 6.455573406161694
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 400,686=？",
        "answer": 6.301774172750837
    },
    {
        "question": "1,264 × 3,021=？",
        "answer": 6.581897799219647
    },
    {
        "question": "160,241,669 ÷ 305,312=？",
        "answer": 2.720031585542267
    },
    {
        "question": "60,556 × 4,097=？",
        "answer": 8.3946231442612
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 22,071=？",
        "answer": 4.343822010762161
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 200=？",
        "answer": 2.3010299956639813
    },
    {
        "question": "33,736 × 627=？",
        "answer": 7.325361128837524
    },
    {
        "question": "7,120 × 1,687=？",
        "answer": 7.079595076225981
    },
    {
        "question": "21,161,919 ÷ 8,286,861=？",
        "answer": 0.4071649934870054
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 543=？",
        "answer": 3.5129510799724906
    },
    {
        "question": "507,408 × 825=？",
        "answer": 8.621811258752283
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 34,761=？",
        "answer": 5.143152253012387
    },
    {
        "question": "772,572 ÷ 6,913=？",
        "answer": 2.0482724072605
    },
    {
        "question": "593 × 4,896=？",
        "answer": 6.462896102501768
    },
    {
        "question": "303,706,230 ÷ 181,484,770=？",
        "answer": 0.223613515406813
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 313,429=？",
        "answer": 5.973260431783002
    },
    {
        "question": "236,637 ÷ 2,626=？",
        "answer": 1.9547879291027694
    },
    {
        "question": "438,537 × 1,412=？",
        "answer": 8.791840938016325
    },
    {
        "question": "183,688 ÷ 88,303=？",
        "answer": 0.3181053270520345
    },
    {
        "question": "12,995 × 36,591=？",
        "answer": 8.677150562373855
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 1,801,476=？",
        "answer": 8.068541837291287
    },
    {
        "question": "388,976 ÷ 604=？",
        "answer": 2.808885867359812
    },
    {
        "question": "3,760,847 ÷ 309=？",
        "answer": 4.085327186247678
    },
    {
        "question": "80,073,664 ÷ 8,760=？",
        "answer": 3.960985595182538
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 21,894,813=？",
        "answer": 8.340341240306179
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 24,650=？",
        "answer": 4.69284691927723
    },
    {
        "question": "28,407,148 ÷ 9,951=？",
        "answer": 3.4555609076936915
    },
    {
        "question": "1,044 × 2,428=？",
        "answer": 6.403949181069463
    },
    {
        "question": "28,785,637 ÷ 2,139=？",
        "answer": 4.128965059868365
    },
    {
        "question": "9,311 × 11,168=？",
        "answer": 8.016971731927399
    },
    {
        "question": "21,866 ÷ 4,989=？",
        "answer": 0.6417558398295484
    },
    {
        "question": "82,699,759 ÷ 74,293,387=？",
        "answer": 0.04655408587465457
    },
    {
        "question": "3,629,159 ÷ 32,234=？",
        "answer": 2.051491794265583
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,793=？",
        "answer": 3.253580289562183
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 1,633,319=？",
        "answer": 7.574798850154064
    },
    {
        "question": "11,949,477 ÷ 442=？",
        "answer": 4.4319266283212935
    },
    {
        "question": "11,542,557 ÷ 421=？",
        "answer": 4.438019932046323
    },
    {
        "question": "113 × 1,598=？",
        "answer": 5.256655218461392
    },
    {
        "question": "79,914 ÷ 55,678=？",
        "answer": 0.15693924263891285
    },
    {
        "question": "3,019 × 2,598=？",
        "answer": 6.894502259760107
    },
    {
        "question": "592 × 102,802=？",
        "answer": 7.784323270608972
    },
    {
        "question": "1,434 × 161,146=？",
        "answer": 8.363768681164697
    },
    {
        "question": "594,935,834 ÷ 785=？",
        "answer": 5.879600471264898
    },
    {
        "question": "10,296 ÷ 6,132=？",
        "answer": 0.2250663877139927
    },
    {
        "question": "742,448 ÷ 1,879=？",
        "answer": 2.596739261587186
    },
    {
        "question": "5,006 × 30,361=？",
        "answer": 8.181806917084899
    },
    {
        "question": "640,201,584 ÷ 26,865,487=？",
        "answer": 1.3771220267670738
    },
    {
        "question": "839 × 845=？",
        "answer": 5.850618669778393
    },
    {
        "question": "147 × 12,139=？",
        "answer": 6.25150024616865
    },
    {
        "question": "766,776,390 ÷ 311,801=？",
        "answer": 3.3907912282309822
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 1,775,901=？",
        "answer": 8.163232604168586
    },
    {
        "question": "409 × 440=？",
        "answer": 5.255175984493529
    },
    {
        "question": "249,748,725 ÷ 2,861,264=？",
        "answer": 1.9409453491076927
    },
    {
        "question": "596,668,331 ÷ 16,737,333=？",
        "answer": 1.55204673088936
    },
    {
        "question": "3,810 ÷ 428=？",
        "answer": 0.9494812066624473
    },
    {
        "question": "87,047,148 ÷ 518,154=？",
        "answer": 2.2252956913936583
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 49,783=？",
        "answer": 4.6970810643133145
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 4,829=？",
        "answer": 4.382827209736365
    },
    {
        "question": "340,635,696 ÷ 121,642=？",
        "answer": 3.4472066046656225
    },
    {
        "question": "160 × 89,802=？",
        "answer": 7.157405991698413
    },
    {
        "question": "89,069 × 5,794=？",
        "answer": 8.71270506727776
    },
    {
        "question": "234 × 639,140=？",
        "answer": 8.174811855737397
    },
    {
        "question": "34,866,372 ÷ 8,079=？",
        "answer": 3.6350491513367844
    },
    {
        "question": "23,051,631 ÷ 1,107=？",
        "answer": 4.318554038098162
    },
    {
        "question": "3,942,141 ÷ 589=？",
        "answer": 3.825616859003816
    },
    {
        "question": "48,229,078 ÷ 10,623,172=？",
        "answer": 0.6570547463454275
    },
    {
        "question": "38,455 × 8,450=？",
        "answer": 8.511809524640684
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 3,577,657=？",
        "answer": 7.951538709870464
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 532,200=？",
        "answer": 6.930194852871295
    },
    {
        "question": "115 × 40,369=？",
        "answer": 6.666745831778766
    },
    {
        "question": "552 × 167,546=？",
        "answer": 7.9660731416601775
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 461,445=？",
        "answer": 6.840211203594307
    },
    {
        "question": "6,354,536 ÷ 211=？",
        "answer": 4.47880138912868
    },
    {
        "question": "124,373,737 ÷ 1,568=？",
        "answer": 4.8993826252207135
    },
    {
        "question": "931,317,912 ÷ 12,207,000=？",
        "answer": 1.8824890112306283
    },
    {
        "question": "459,870 ÷ 14,843=？",
        "answer": 1.4911133914877543
    },
    {
        "question": "1,982,739 × 443=？",
        "answer": 8.943669275365346
    },
    {
        "question": "826,084 × 232=？",
        "answer": 8.28251219550626
    },
    {
        "question": "8,292 × 40,918=？",
        "answer": 8.53057369142893
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 415,820=？",
        "answer": 6.765033409756779
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 3,895,532=？",
        "answer": 7.435664816242904
    },
    {
        "question": "378,973,258 ÷ 18,046,952=？",
        "answer": 1.3222047021131864
    },
    {
        "question": "151,668,680 ÷ 8,852,047=？",
        "answer": 1.2338521958884572
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 103,356=？",
        "answer": 5.85943373327805
    },
    {
        "question": "1,214,429 ÷ 12,442=？",
        "answer": 1.9894819324189292
    },
    {
        "question": "113,585,462 ÷ 1,349,812=？",
        "answer": 1.9250494640734863
    },
    {
        "question": "308 × 1,130,852=？",
        "answer": 8.54195648695272
    },
    {
        "question": "79,627 ÷ 26,087=？",
        "answer": 0.48463621551244745
    },
    {
        "question": "217 × 23,481=？",
        "answer": 6.707176322388075
    },
    {
        "question": "890,855,622 ÷ 360,757=？",
        "answer": 3.392592558338956
    },
    {
        "question": "9,749,501 ÷ 103,777=？",
        "answer": 1.9728812762659924
    },
    {
        "question": "9,767 × 4,348=？",
        "answer": 7.628050723133035
    },
    {
        "question": "30,456 ÷ 578=？",
        "answer": 1.7217450253857818
    },
    {
        "question": "2,226 × 522=？",
        "answer": 6.065195663000952
    },
    {
        "question": "2,763,424 ÷ 260=？",
        "answer": 4.02647417709516
    },
    {
        "question": "109,058 ÷ 20,337=？",
        "answer": 0.7293706403266101
    },
    {
        "question": "12,470,111 ÷ 941=？",
        "answer": 4.122280695847031
    },
    {
        "question": "23,697,086 ÷ 6,343,602=？",
        "answer": 0.5723590172994896
    },
    {
        "question": "10,908,226 ÷ 516=？",
        "answer": 4.325104425582988
    },
    {
        "question": "371,799 ÷ 2,115=？",
        "answer": 2.2449978456369597
    },
    {
        "question": "138,950 ÷ 57,961=？",
        "answer": 0.379722681375409
    },
    {
        "question": "339 × 429,207=？",
        "answer": 8.162866494527245
    },
    {
        "question": "1,188 × 10,433=？",
        "answer": 7.093225648027243
    },
    {
        "question": "69,097 × 9,714=？",
        "answer": 8.826857291059275
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 155,867=？",
        "answer": 6.03785221655689
    },
    {
        "question": "203,700 ÷ 155,507=？",
        "answer": 0.11724108584341997
    },
    {
        "question": "28,482,433 ÷ 4,554=？",
        "answer": 3.7961840581710735
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,162,850=？",
        "answer": 6.910621737224486
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 18,934=？",
        "answer": 5.277242372781358
    },
    {
        "question": "6,219,600 ÷ 6,716=？",
        "answer": 2.966651767421145
    },
    {
        "question": "262 × 1,063,344=？",
        "answer": 8.44497507619448
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,142,468=？",
        "answer": 6.330914344001441
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 544=？",
        "answer": 3.9116901587538613
    },
    {
        "question": "890 × 180,143=？",
        "answer": 8.205007397608425
    },
    {
        "question": "730,069 ÷ 283=？",
        "answer": 3.4115774724086645
    },
    {
        "question": "378,572 × 977=？",
        "answer": 8.56804305317967
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 114,003=？",
        "answer": 5.658976271316214
    },
    {
        "question": "4,306,979 ÷ 159,542=？",
        "answer": 1.4312977222169536
    },
    {
        "question": "3,234,478 ÷ 28,988=？",
        "answer": 2.0475859488926886
    },
    {
        "question": "25,078 × 739=？",
        "answer": 7.267937336438736
    },
    {
        "question": "38,087,372 ÷ 4,241=？",
        "answer": 3.9533127352426427
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 528,014=？",
        "answer": 7.065068118587345
    },
    {
        "question": "33,459 ÷ 9,546=？",
        "answer": 0.5446915268898808
    },
    {
        "question": "109,673 × 2,235=？",
        "answer": 8.389377250810417
    },
    {
        "question": "619,678 ÷ 48,654=？",
        "answer": 1.105047527164328
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,007=？",
        "answer": 4.116972822860455
    },
    {
        "question": "202,471,055 ÷ 32,758=？",
        "answer": 3.7910455672366603
    },
    {
        "question": "43,448,142 ÷ 57,986=？",
        "answer": 2.8746480579694156
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,497,496=？",
        "answer": 6.175365671007762
    },
    {
        "question": "1,710,287 ÷ 419=？",
        "answer": 3.610854971670133
    },
    {
        "question": "5,181,630 ÷ 2,789=？",
        "answer": 3.2690178842148536
    },
    {
        "question": "122,705 ÷ 729=？",
        "answer": 2.2261347314601068
    },
    {
        "question": "681,820 ÷ 92,630=？",
        "answer": 0.8669180722991713
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 219,983,115=？",
        "answer": 8.342389347441536
    },
    {
        "question": "971 × 664=？",
        "answer": 5.809387309276023
    },
    {
        "question": "154,718 ÷ 139,927=？",
        "answer": 0.04363931969480955
    },
    {
        "question": "731 × 96,704=？",
        "answer": 7.849361815280773
    },
    {
        "question": "1,004 × 16,571=？",
        "answer": 7.221082430122579
    },
    {
        "question": "207,018 ÷ 25,815=？",
        "answer": 0.904135979169383
    },
    {
        "question": "1,129 × 32,474=？",
        "answer": 7.564229728269921
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,118=？",
        "answer": 3.525563058270067
    },
    {
        "question": "1,303 × 246=？",
        "answer": 5.505879522815964
    },
    {
        "question": "761,403 × 832=？",
        "answer": 8.801737909933873
    },
    {
        "question": "6,793,680 ÷ 2,807,219=？",
        "answer": 0.38382879197885345
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 11,726=？",
        "answer": 4.546271144568441
    },
    {
        "question": "606,830 × 499=？",
        "answer": 8.4811675885891
    },
    {
        "question": "5,431,406 ÷ 138,363=？",
        "answer": 1.5938922978510395
    },
    {
        "question": "180 × 1,482,136=？",
        "answer": 8.426160561202495
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 97,886=？",
        "answer": 4.990720581920337
    },
    {
        "question": "6,250,290 ÷ 265=？",
        "answer": 4.372654294203733
    },
    {
        "question": "102,477,202 ÷ 277=？",
        "answer": 5.568147490016548
    },
    {
        "question": "98 × 3,154=？",
        "answer": 5.490087764685379
    },
    {
        "question": "37,908,006 ÷ 1,235=？",
        "answer": 4.487063983096318
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 236,831,516=？",
        "answer": 8.374439494985628
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 29,498,893=？",
        "answer": 8.946926973307583
    },
    {
        "question": "462 × 3,597=？",
        "answer": 6.220582413374637
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 169,940=？",
        "answer": 6.008446864300691
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 382=？",
        "answer": 2.582063362911709
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,875=？",
        "answer": 3.7501225267834
    },
    {
        "question": "36,809 ÷ 1,755=？",
        "answer": 1.3216768982101281
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 238,900=？",
        "answer": 5.85533740446954
    },
    {
        "question": "123 × 629=？",
        "answer": 4.888555756884667
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,815=？",
        "answer": 3.258876629372131
    },
    {
        "question": "60,080,721 ÷ 527,848=？",
        "answer": 2.0562262554223447
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 7,283=？",
        "answer": 5.5250681416358445
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 680=？",
        "answer": 4.849542252005016
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 825=？",
        "answer": 3.5185139398778875
    },
    {
        "question": "163,975,082 ÷ 10,878,752=？",
        "answer": 1.1781987803812728
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 1,883,000=？",
        "answer": 7.597069614750584
    },
    {
        "question": "1,522,178 ÷ 90,739=？",
        "answer": 1.2246714520415085
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 109,677=？",
        "answer": 5.88521360268134
    },
    {
        "question": "46,408,602 ÷ 35,970=？",
        "answer": 3.110658048229687
    },
    {
        "question": "927,026 ÷ 627=？",
        "answer": 3.169824374002218
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 346=？",
        "answer": 4.070555015835032
    },
    {
        "question": "245,582 ÷ 1,417=？",
        "answer": 2.238826681655086
    },
    {
        "question": "1,945 × 64,733=？",
        "answer": 8.100045340182433
    },
    {
        "question": "530,519,693 ÷ 283=？",
        "answer": 6.272915074112681
    },
    {
        "question": "942 × 10,142=？",
        "answer": 6.980174509004732
    },
    {
        "question": "1,161 × 2,120=？",
        "answer": 6.391168080667326
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,524=？",
        "answer": 3.9788193867328423
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 478=？",
        "answer": 3.883547879268044
    },
    {
        "question": "15,428 × 2,236=？",
        "answer": 7.53778142940839
    },
    {
        "question": "1,606 × 4,229=？",
        "answer": 6.831983226089562
    },
    {
        "question": "19,226,475 ÷ 669=？",
        "answer": 4.458473549810368
    },
    {
        "question": "17,562 ÷ 780=？",
        "answer": 1.352479370126955
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,564=？",
        "answer": 4.261405627074139
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 494,410=？",
        "answer": 6.5971772332573675
    },
    {
        "question": "231 × 38,144=？",
        "answer": 6.945038213616268
    },
    {
        "question": "37,457,449 ÷ 643=？",
        "answer": 4.765327223955142
    },
    {
        "question": "1,564,965 × 359=？",
        "answer": 8.749599077696033
    },
    {
        "question": "868,291,011 ÷ 1,236=？",
        "answer": 5.8466468342508735
    },
    {
        "question": "12,499,368 ÷ 5,889,902=？",
        "answer": 0.32677998574927974
    },
    {
        "question": "2,224 × 26,980=？",
        "answer": 7.778176728245906
    },
    {
        "question": "111,484,455 ÷ 812,903=？",
        "answer": 2.1371755888018624
    },
    {
        "question": "222,002,666 ÷ 11,148,923=？",
        "answer": 1.299125273849039
    },
    {
        "question": "8,210,790 ÷ 6,883,127=？",
        "answer": 0.07659916195321081
    },
    {
        "question": "24,836,752 ÷ 17,589=？",
        "answer": 3.149853651911383
    },
    {
        "question": "3,196 × 8,343=？",
        "answer": 7.425929014225776
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 21,547=？",
        "answer": 5.731326820331569
    },
    {
        "question": "2,728,025 ÷ 316,926=？",
        "answer": 0.9348904766010878
    },
    {
        "question": "259 × 367,625=？",
        "answer": 7.978704801596377
    },
    {
        "question": "48,798 × 249=？",
        "answer": 7.084601369779528
    },
    {
        "question": "51,006 × 16,572=？",
        "answer": 8.926996191187389
    },
    {
        "question": "678,611 × 1,123=？",
        "answer": 8.882000651359213
    },
    {
        "question": "1,533 × 68,129=？",
        "answer": 8.01887416924997
    },
    {
        "question": "13,848,195 ÷ 3,552=？",
        "answer": 3.5909202132162705
    },
    {
        "question": "10,022 ÷ 3,471=？",
        "answer": 0.4604997847350459
    },
    {
        "question": "8,086,303 ÷ 6,479=？",
        "answer": 3.096242030705875
    },
    {
        "question": "1,796,346 ÷ 4,621=？",
        "answer": 2.589654022731406
    },
    {
        "question": "3,148 × 1,325=？",
        "answer": 6.620250601959854
    },
    {
        "question": "440 × 2,328=？",
        "answer": 6.0104356524640385
    },
    {
        "question": "1,759,904 ÷ 318,763=？",
        "answer": 0.7420210728949199
    },
    {
        "question": "98 × 84,211=？",
        "answer": 6.9165949002951805
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 14,549,038=？",
        "answer": 7.463864273858504
    },
    {
        "question": "305,855,056 ÷ 2,254=？",
        "answer": 5.132561752377457
    },
    {
        "question": "449 × 37,219=？",
        "answer": 7.223011041331759
    },
    {
        "question": "523,787,803 ÷ 946=？",
        "answer": 5.7432642447598345
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 13,865=？",
        "answer": 5.372368795292155
    },
    {
        "question": "1,552 × 579=？",
        "answer": 5.953570280649606
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 45,528,409=？",
        "answer": 8.772225826366542
    },
    {
        "question": "282,361,349 ÷ 2,774,535=？",
        "answer": 2.0076150404083632
    },
    {
        "question": "27,585,059 ÷ 150,407=？",
        "answer": 2.263405868221451
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 102,169=？",
        "answer": 5.009319142655681
    },
    {
        "question": "2,497,552 ÷ 26,136=？",
        "answer": 1.9802754177040967
    },
    {
        "question": "181,638 ÷ 15,105=？",
        "answer": 1.080085981667715
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,991,766=？",
        "answer": 6.475927622319783
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 503,978=？",
        "answer": 7.5889023039054315
    },
    {
        "question": "4,567,959 ÷ 486,950=？",
        "answer": 0.9722378270484773
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 145,484=？",
        "answer": 5.940966483610737
    },
    {
        "question": "914 × 4,337=？",
        "answer": 6.598135617882593
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 467=？",
        "answer": 4.200795797608367
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 6,809,864=？",
        "answer": 7.7362284256830955
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,698,153=？",
        "answer": 6.832036808014619
    },
    {
        "question": "13,354 ÷ 1,792=？",
        "answer": 0.8722733665713575
    },
    {
        "question": "31,315,156 ÷ 97,392=？",
        "answer": 2.5072312951209823
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,314,012=？",
        "answer": 7.236941340144218
    },
    {
        "question": "140,286,300 ÷ 942,101=？",
        "answer": 2.1729177962352764
    },
    {
        "question": "697,901 × 549=？",
        "answer": 8.58336616506311
    },
    {
        "question": "43,697 × 5,724=？",
        "answer": 8.398151246768249
    },
    {
        "question": "750 ÷ 207=？",
        "answer": 0.5590909179347823
    },
    {
        "question": "2,241 × 204,285=？",
        "answer": 8.660678335471037
    },
    {
        "question": "663 × 29,702=？",
        "answer": 7.294299222156992
    },
    {
        "question": "1,080,179 ÷ 2,022=？",
        "answer": 2.7277145785567236
    },
    {
        "question": "63,127 × 10,815=？",
        "answer": 8.834241674509025
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 872,871=？",
        "answer": 6.982342750023242
    },
    {
        "question": "259,205,901 ÷ 17,771=？",
        "answer": 4.163933017447993
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 26,669,541=？",
        "answer": 7.7270455369300635
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 87,192=？",
        "answer": 6.496779140341608
    },
    {
        "question": "56,229,368 ÷ 5,558=？",
        "answer": 4.005044659765274
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 74,955,492=？",
        "answer": 8.829045968610448
    },
    {
        "question": "78 × 171,904=？",
        "answer": 7.127380585007064
    },
    {
        "question": "615,197 ÷ 227=？",
        "answer": 3.4329883517741426
    },
    {
        "question": "115 × 71,132=？",
        "answer": 6.91276286016847
    },
    {
        "question": "11,534 ÷ 220=？",
        "answer": 1.7195572662526724
    },
    {
        "question": "1,205,673 ÷ 630=？",
        "answer": 3.28188898591917
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 8,758,476=？",
        "answer": 6.942428544253667
    },
    {
        "question": "57,553 ÷ 7,110=？",
        "answer": 0.9081983658023025
    },
    {
        "question": "11,406 × 407=？",
        "answer": 6.666727776474307
    },
    {
        "question": "257,921,352 ÷ 225,384=？",
        "answer": 3.0585642144040124
    },
    {
        "question": "1,481,612 ÷ 619,922=？",
        "answer": 0.3783974378141218
    },
    {
        "question": "54,649 × 4,653=？",
        "answer": 8.405315271912212
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 9,783,480=？",
        "answer": 8.481855055367399
    },
    {
        "question": "114,648 × 1,470=？",
        "answer": 8.226683817743137
    },
    {
        "question": "190,723,456 ÷ 161,990,833=？",
        "answer": 0.07091366907717463
    },
    {
        "question": "7,549,973 ÷ 134,142=？",
        "answer": 1.7503806213219417
    },
    {
        "question": "9,388 ÷ 1,894=？",
        "answer": 0.6951931062593003
    },
    {
        "question": "1,792 × 3,146=？",
        "answer": 6.751096723613374
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 2,607=？",
        "answer": 4.972443531935617
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 2,258=？",
        "answer": 4.933507534205759
    },
    {
        "question": "53,327,484 ÷ 17,049=？",
        "answer": 3.4952521833123975
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 168,451,223=？",
        "answer": 8.226474168420275
    },
    {
        "question": "11,787,489 ÷ 8,296=？",
        "answer": 3.1525525570841006
    },
    {
        "question": "135,557 ÷ 298=？",
        "answer": 2.657905684862598
    },
    {
        "question": "131 × 224,078=？",
        "answer": 7.467670515209048
    },
    {
        "question": "183 × 3,599,837=？",
        "answer": 8.818733926163492
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 529=？",
        "answer": 3.5685537120494426
    },
    {
        "question": "38,823,153 ÷ 1,103=？",
        "answer": 4.546515291020583
    },
    {
        "question": "52,695,770 ÷ 3,132=？",
        "answer": 4.225954001496678
    },
    {
        "question": "1,796,058 ÷ 146,307=？",
        "answer": 1.0890552519365337
    },
    {
        "question": "527,200,397 ÷ 289,934,653=？",
        "answer": 0.2596756032756655
    },
    {
        "question": "2,625,856 × 351=？",
        "answer": 8.964578022484272
    },
    {
        "question": "481 × 458,815=？",
        "answer": 8.343782684187936
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 119,295=？",
        "answer": 5.7755922458444555
    },
    {
        "question": "88,974 ÷ 21,398=？",
        "answer": 0.618889932380995
    },
    {
        "question": "4,023 × 510=？",
        "answer": 6.312120208669198
    },
    {
        "question": "197 × 29,480=？",
        "answer": 6.763993705348607
    },
    {
        "question": "18,331 × 4,266=？",
        "answer": 7.893207008527115
    },
    {
        "question": "824 × 524,881=？",
        "answer": 8.635988063862278
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 7,331=？",
        "answer": 4.76825320649803
    },
    {
        "question": "32,008 × 15,945=？",
        "answer": 8.707883061949918
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 2,429,310=？",
        "answer": 8.299296790284357
    },
    {
        "question": "95,359,454 ÷ 1,293=？",
        "answer": 4.8677652308812664
    },
    {
        "question": "823,727,100 ÷ 408,792=？",
        "answer": 3.3042809660494985
    },
    {
        "question": "1,766,082 ÷ 1,232=？",
        "answer": 3.1564001563739352
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,282,119=？",
        "answer": 6.9530263761525015
    },
    {
        "question": "4,847 × 769=？",
        "answer": 6.57139935952419
    },
    {
        "question": "49,510 ÷ 339=？",
        "answer": 2.1644932281284017
    },
    {
        "question": "4,443 × 49,022=？",
        "answer": 8.338067338868584
    },
    {
        "question": "184,522,064 ÷ 1,220,176=？",
        "answer": 2.1796258253565934
    },
    {
        "question": "187,999 × 248=？",
        "answer": 7.668607220006721
    },
    {
        "question": "225 × 8,245=？",
        "answer": 6.2683731780919
    },
    {
        "question": "1,712 × 1,415=？",
        "answer": 6.384260200201443
    },
    {
        "question": "13,006,800 ÷ 74,059=？",
        "answer": 2.244592618751159
    },
    {
        "question": "48 × 16,741=？",
        "answer": 5.905022633775401
    },
    {
        "question": "82,674 ÷ 6,127=？",
        "answer": 1.1301210701892757
    },
    {
        "question": "136,066 ÷ 1,371=？",
        "answer": 1.996712163014209
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 147,022=？",
        "answer": 5.167382326338055
    },
    {
        "question": "169 × 86,218=？",
        "answer": 7.1634846489139825
    },
    {
        "question": "10,133 × 86,864=？",
        "answer": 8.94457786696303
    },
    {
        "question": "330,219,292 ÷ 4,050,707=？",
        "answer": 1.9112716114518395
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 27,711=？",
        "answer": 4.919773453062185
    },
    {
        "question": "151,005,849 ÷ 376,610=？",
        "answer": 2.603101921896668
    },
    {
        "question": "34,651,220 ÷ 9,157=？",
        "answer": 3.5779653156684175
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,314=？",
        "answer": 3.665393350279712
    },
    {
        "question": "11,843,379 ÷ 858,767=？",
        "answer": 1.1396002799913436
    },
    {
        "question": "2,072,480 ÷ 825=？",
        "answer": 3.4000363996318317
    },
    {
        "question": "144,876 × 259=？",
        "answer": 7.5742962107611564
    },
    {
        "question": "627,126,950 ÷ 4,122,856=？",
        "answer": 2.1821572980844555
    },
    {
        "question": "329 × 76,104=？",
        "answer": 7.398603381688669
    },
    {
        "question": "247 × 4,696=？",
        "answer": 6.064425041499224
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 11,527=？",
        "answer": 5.618018793927185
    },
    {
        "question": "107,583 × 8,154=？",
        "answer": 8.9431143577264
    },
    {
        "question": "53,731 × 263=？",
        "answer": 7.150180671888165
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 15,196=？",
        "answer": 5.8538271428184006
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 122,330,430=？",
        "answer": 8.786504506648212
    },
    {
        "question": "259,136,799 ÷ 671=？",
        "answer": 5.5868065696514275
    },
    {
        "question": "2,354,032 ÷ 2,706=？",
        "answer": 2.939484569953952
    },
    {
        "question": "6,214,515 ÷ 2,167,141=？",
        "answer": 0.4575200720118914
    },
    {
        "question": "4,934,319 ÷ 26,043=？",
        "answer": 2.277536211931149
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 62,130=？",
        "answer": 6.492271357949134
    },
    {
        "question": "174,789 ÷ 1,582=？",
        "answer": 2.0433076185324883
    },
    {
        "question": "98,663 ÷ 1,389=？",
        "answer": 1.8514520709798044
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 46,770,249=？",
        "answer": 8.749150928101482
    },
    {
        "question": "9,529 ÷ 436=？",
        "answer": 1.3395608376793786
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 20,717=？",
        "answer": 5.357719551203644
    },
    {
        "question": "43,352,867 ÷ 50,672=？",
        "answer": 2.9322497773785714
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 88,488,098=？",
        "answer": 8.645854864632357
    },
    {
        "question": "1,367 ÷ 282=？",
        "answer": 0.6855194062484612
    },
    {
        "question": "31,849 ÷ 30,492=？",
        "answer": 0.018909889739784583
    },
    {
        "question": "48 × 352=？",
        "answer": 4.227783900853718
    },
    {
        "question": "536,218,121 ÷ 110,121=？",
        "answer": 3.6874713399461982
    },
    {
        "question": "3,507,311 ÷ 3,026,203=？",
        "answer": 0.06407621984581925
    },
    {
        "question": "62,164 ÷ 23,785=？",
        "answer": 0.4172357960156416
    },
    {
        "question": "29,078,534 ÷ 14,905,462=？",
        "answer": 0.29022706601094045
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 142,306=？",
        "answer": 6.056313198474384
    },
    {
        "question": "110,563,534 ÷ 2,509,827=？",
        "answer": 1.6439681248283482
    },
    {
        "question": "1,366,076 ÷ 404=？",
        "answer": 3.5290934963597054
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 754=？",
        "answer": 3.6555225962534177
    },
    {
        "question": "214,877,112 ÷ 8,124=？",
        "answer": 4.422420243608939
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 304=？",
        "answer": 3.3279716236230104
    },
    {
        "question": "162,100 × 903=？",
        "answer": 8.16547076516202
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 858=？",
        "answer": 3.6324572921847245
    },
    {
        "question": "1,262 × 346=？",
        "answer": 5.640135453700892
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 9,170=？",
        "answer": 5.55343394269652
    },
    {
        "question": "300,311 ÷ 24,991=？",
        "answer": 1.079787605620895
    },
    {
        "question": "401 × 391,215=？",
        "answer": 8.195559870812277
    },
    {
        "question": "12,796,974 ÷ 290=？",
        "answer": 4.64470928968123
    },
    {
        "question": "12,238,719 ÷ 268=？",
        "answer": 4.659601169504177
    },
    {
        "question": "2,021 × 2,061=？",
        "answer": 6.619644305294517
    },
    {
        "question": "25,297,907 ÷ 8,862,721=？",
        "answer": 0.45551751383796085
    },
    {
        "question": "108 × 5,860=？",
        "answer": 5.801321371505041
    },
    {
        "question": "339,344,363 ÷ 468=？",
        "answer": 5.860394786254664
    },
    {
        "question": "1,381 × 670=？",
        "answer": 5.9662684812794575
    },
    {
        "question": "85,157 ÷ 79,692=？",
        "answer": 0.028805626968365684
    },
    {
        "question": "7,692,098 ÷ 837=？",
        "answer": 3.9633193506709596
    },
    {
        "question": "13,237,841 ÷ 3,045=？",
        "answer": 3.6382298634940238
    },
    {
        "question": "12,732 × 1,044=？",
        "answer": 7.123597128615208
    },
    {
        "question": "126,077,259 ÷ 94,283=？",
        "answer": 3.126203365478417
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,070,883=？",
        "answer": 6.61718555863771
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 100,875=？",
        "answer": 6.045176232888352
    },
    {
        "question": "576,578 ÷ 15,543=？",
        "answer": 1.569323220353625
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 22,566,420=？",
        "answer": 8.198560706864923
    },
    {
        "question": "604,061,477 ÷ 72,419=？",
        "answer": 3.921228616662208
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 27,402=？",
        "answer": 4.738812257654625
    },
    {
        "question": "116 × 458,621=？",
        "answer": 7.725911926178433
    },
    {
        "question": "1,768,082 ÷ 21,772=？",
        "answer": 1.9096040771822977
    },
    {
        "question": "12,256 × 619=？",
        "answer": 6.880039401308647
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 418,384=？",
        "answer": 6.399726318105729
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 167,924=？",
        "answer": 5.225112770722256
    },
    {
        "question": "40,800,469 ÷ 52,730=？",
        "answer": 2.8886073839873703
    },
    {
        "question": "236,102 ÷ 2,509=？",
        "answer": 1.9735990046513885
    },
    {
        "question": "101 × 10,944=？",
        "answer": 6.043497458158684
    },
    {
        "question": "977,865 × 925=？",
        "answer": 8.956420634763893
    },
    {
        "question": "10,112 ÷ 591=？",
        "answer": 1.2332495800570544
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 5,004,435=？",
        "answer": 7.978108653750537
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 146,798,960=？",
        "answer": 8.643844233543167
    },
    {
        "question": "705,958,150 ÷ 13,779,569=？",
        "answer": 1.7095433225073082
    },
    {
        "question": "806,130 ÷ 675,902=？",
        "answer": 0.07652135212717727
    },
    {
        "question": "11,807,480 ÷ 49,577=？",
        "answer": 2.376876975394128
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 23,797=？",
        "answer": 4.677552206268094
    },
    {
        "question": "13,821,579 ÷ 11,168=？",
        "answer": 3.092582255111827
    },
    {
        "question": "1,204 × 344,855=？",
        "answer": 8.618263014061808
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 427=？",
        "answer": 2.630427875025024
    },
    {
        "question": "136,648 × 367=？",
        "answer": 7.70026934393009
    },
    {
        "question": "1,254 × 73,395=？",
        "answer": 7.963964011310317
    },
    {
        "question": "5,204 × 386=？",
        "answer": 6.302924592561304
    },
    {
        "question": "1,913,604 ÷ 32,516=？",
        "answer": 1.7697549552325462
    },
    {
        "question": "264,962,647 ÷ 200=？",
        "answer": 6.122154658102306
    },
    {
        "question": "274,738,694 ÷ 9,803=？",
        "answer": 4.4475608268126585
    },
    {
        "question": "135,457 ÷ 50,158=？",
        "answer": 0.4314612418379999
    },
    {
        "question": "105,505 ÷ 16,348=？",
        "answer": 0.8098084127832973
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 47,190=？",
        "answer": 6.4062437371659176
    },
    {
        "question": "25,235,909 ÷ 31,911=？",
        "answer": 2.898078538721816
    },
    {
        "question": "34,589,596 ÷ 34,174=？",
        "answer": 3.0052496744703854
    },
    {
        "question": "80,665,324 ÷ 3,265=？",
        "answer": 4.39280369691938
    },
    {
        "question": "159 × 7,374=？",
        "answer": 6.0691002575905495
    },
    {
        "question": "2,305,381 ÷ 540=？",
        "answer": 3.6303489497395414
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 160,525,139=？",
        "answer": 8.205543054647755
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,420=？",
        "answer": 3.645422269349092
    },
    {
        "question": "12,670 × 224=？",
        "answer": 6.453024633217604
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 78,264,519=？",
        "answer": 8.796654907480997
    },
    {
        "question": "392,975 ÷ 657=？",
        "answer": 2.776799553061452
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 950,054=？",
        "answer": 5.977748290799922
    },
    {
        "question": "130,849 ÷ 230=？",
        "answer": 2.7550425719201606
    },
    {
        "question": "150,239,466 ÷ 234=？",
        "answer": 5.8075681738905836
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 613=？",
        "answer": 3.0884904701823963
    },
    {
        "question": "4,382 × 8,556=？",
        "answer": 7.573943149124177
    },
    {
        "question": "18,535,824 ÷ 11,204,583=？",
        "answer": 0.2186161990487705
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,008,562=？",
        "answer": 6.302885242013568
    },
    {
        "question": "2,517,090 ÷ 35,428=？",
        "answer": 1.8515521082690949
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 20,002=？",
        "answer": 5.204163409932788
    },
    {
        "question": "345,075,068 ÷ 2,851,960=？",
        "answer": 2.0827701521875444
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 351=？",
        "answer": 2.545307116465824
    },
    {
        "question": "73,666,993 ÷ 3,004=？",
        "answer": 4.389573014494657
    },
    {
        "question": "2,407,368 ÷ 485,172=？",
        "answer": 0.6956467542238659
    },
    {
        "question": "154,946,186 ÷ 74,361,156=？",
        "answer": 0.3188347579631024
    },
    {
        "question": "12,742,562 ÷ 8,057,982=？",
        "answer": 0.19903046243984415
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 2,990,663=？",
        "answer": 8.35082874112173
    },
    {
        "question": "5,867,400 ÷ 1,556,089=？",
        "answer": 0.5764112638175909
    },
    {
        "question": "2,295,193 ÷ 373=？",
        "answer": 3.7891103788971834
    },
    {
        "question": "15,891 × 470=？",
        "answer": 6.873249085590977
    },
    {
        "question": "68,377 ÷ 912=？",
        "answer": 1.8749152041393706
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 13,024,401=？",
        "answer": 7.892909009351243
    },
    {
        "question": "62,921,356 ÷ 725=？",
        "answer": 4.938460066836259
    },
    {
        "question": "19,433 ÷ 6,051=？",
        "answer": 0.5067126977380284
    },
    {
        "question": "390 × 13,046=？",
        "answer": 6.706541981212968
    },
    {
        "question": "126,496 ÷ 3,818=？",
        "answer": 1.5202408686052287
    },
    {
        "question": "1,681 × 1,218=？",
        "answer": 6.311215001736327
    },
    {
        "question": "2,716 × 305,579=？",
        "answer": 8.919053270952261
    },
    {
        "question": "70,905,789 ÷ 3,854,529=？",
        "answer": 1.2647103764870398
    },
    {
        "question": "948,071,668 ÷ 251,285,851=？",
        "answer": 0.5766731326684048
    },
    {
        "question": "13,298,399 ÷ 2,594,528=？",
        "answer": 0.7097409972760425
    },
    {
        "question": "841 × 432=？",
        "answer": 5.560279742612824
    },
    {
        "question": "59,137 ÷ 1,286=？",
        "answer": 1.6626183205485887
    },
    {
        "question": "1,507 × 168,904=？",
        "answer": 8.40575318700913
    },
    {
        "question": "96,742 ÷ 17,613=？",
        "answer": 0.7397817264540285
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 214,939,236=？",
        "answer": 8.633345696511029
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,657=？",
        "answer": 3.8641549560020256
    },
    {
        "question": "10,312 × 239=？",
        "answer": 6.391740805293484
    },
    {
        "question": "169,594,319 ÷ 146,926,517=？",
        "answer": 0.06231111689635729
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 585=？",
        "answer": 2.7671558660821804
    },
    {
        "question": "972,178,079 ÷ 42,569,287=？",
        "answer": 1.3586494480618823
    },
    {
        "question": "31,012,305 ÷ 7,000,931=？",
        "answer": 0.6463782491808305
    },
    {
        "question": "45,734,551 ÷ 5,043,740=？",
        "answer": 0.9574917287354294
    },
    {
        "question": "8,561 ÷ 4,173=？",
        "answer": 0.3120761123388335
    },
    {
        "question": "583,528,331 ÷ 3,804=？",
        "answer": 5.185821438145618
    },
    {
        "question": "35,837,158 ÷ 6,095=？",
        "answer": 3.7693598514749493
    },
    {
        "question": "16,934 × 1,208=？",
        "answer": 7.310826489720749
    },
    {
        "question": "769,321 ÷ 86,856=？",
        "answer": 0.9473077626285269
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 100,002,567=？",
        "answer": 8.301041143860246
    },
    {
        "question": "3,132,688 ÷ 175,530=？",
        "answer": 1.251565790654681
    },
    {
        "question": "119,256,524 ÷ 613,150=？",
        "answer": 2.2889154141045718
    },
    {
        "question": "7,182 ÷ 842=？",
        "answer": 0.9309333092904049
    },
    {
        "question": "25,308,488 ÷ 53,501=？",
        "answer": 2.6749043003645787
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 35,111=？",
        "answer": 5.749563181483203
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 202=？",
        "answer": 3.0835026198302673
    },
    {
        "question": "6,950 × 482=？",
        "answer": 6.525031842828963
    },
    {
        "question": "46,364 × 628=？",
        "answer": 7.46414054089478
    },
    {
        "question": "29,356 × 3,001=？",
        "answer": 7.944962874452444
    },
    {
        "question": "227,792,549 ÷ 26,648=？",
        "answer": 3.9318748946995266
    },
    {
        "question": "1,177,571 ÷ 750=？",
        "answer": 3.19592583837834
    },
    {
        "question": "1,221,929 ÷ 15,972=？",
        "answer": 1.8836866705020532
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 39,697,557=？",
        "answer": 8.297733785304041
    },
    {
        "question": "92,645,450 ÷ 535=？",
        "answer": 5.23847031310249
    },
    {
        "question": "205,367 ÷ 745=？",
        "answer": 2.4403743862339584
    },
    {
        "question": "710,539,287 ÷ 5,884,991=？",
        "answer": 2.081842292846095
    },
    {
        "question": "4,371,923 ÷ 47,467=？",
        "answer": 1.9642807199912502
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 299,320=？",
        "answer": 6.379225723542941
    },
    {
        "question": "903,605 ÷ 15,414=？",
        "answer": 1.7680632707262702
    },
    {
        "question": "596,754,905 ÷ 9,531,585=？",
        "answer": 1.7966308722156146
    },
    {
        "question": "48 × 294=？",
        "answer": 4.149588567787744
    },
    {
        "question": "7,702 × 78,476=？",
        "answer": 8.781340372799791
    },
    {
        "question": "6,144,925 ÷ 676=？",
        "answer": 3.9585698906649025
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 271=？",
        "answer": 3.9243309847086785
    },
    {
        "question": "1,048 × 110,803=？",
        "answer": 8.064912801756796
    },
    {
        "question": "8,302 × 293=？",
        "answer": 6.38605034939661
    },
    {
        "question": "3,527,994 ÷ 20,371=？",
        "answer": 2.2385154890876695
    },
    {
        "question": "6,158,575 ÷ 18,022=？",
        "answer": 2.533677249338378
    },
    {
        "question": "585,139,285 ÷ 128,401,546=？",
        "answer": 0.6586890038687371
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 50,058=？",
        "answer": 6.407043670065402
    },
    {
        "question": "42,752,693 ÷ 2,654,165=？",
        "answer": 1.207035558303888
    },
    {
        "question": "1,913,607 ÷ 569=？",
        "answer": 3.5267404845711745
    },
    {
        "question": "9,662 × 19,110=？",
        "answer": 8.266327720205513
    },
    {
        "question": "688,317 ÷ 20,671=？",
        "answer": 1.5224270088783631
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 4,432=？",
        "answer": 4.549689738712317
    },
    {
        "question": "231 × 3,468=？",
        "answer": 5.903691068696317
    },
    {
        "question": "251 × 718=？",
        "answer": 5.255798165723339
    },
    {
        "question": "389,978,238 ÷ 70,789,001=？",
        "answer": 0.7410745892670648
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,163=？",
        "answer": 3.0655797147284485
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 5,649,163=？",
        "answer": 7.793376791135349
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 55,732=？",
        "answer": 5.348164619766874
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 251=？",
        "answer": 3.098643725817057
    },
    {
        "question": "128,865 ÷ 1,756=？",
        "answer": 1.8656104665211228
    },
    {
        "question": "730,678,950 ÷ 5,816=？",
        "answer": 5.099102198161916
    },
    {
        "question": "480 × 39,877=？",
        "answer": 7.281963715689897
    },
    {
        "question": "716,593,105 ÷ 3,193,471=？",
        "answer": 2.351009648432859
    },
    {
        "question": "148,813,999 ÷ 68,854=？",
        "answer": 3.334714612206864
    },
    {
        "question": "66,140 × 3,871=？",
        "answer": 8.408287361896639
    },
    {
        "question": "166,827,529 ÷ 542=？",
        "answer": 5.488268430664444
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,323=？",
        "answer": 3.1215598441875008
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,041,547=？",
        "answer": 6.017678872344349
    },
    {
        "question": "2,690 × 1,842=？",
        "answer": 6.695041905863238
    },
    {
        "question": "612,759,236 ÷ 3,738=？",
        "answer": 5.214650568966337
    },
    {
        "question": "7,083,862 ÷ 99,727=？",
        "answer": 1.8514573374172731
    },
    {
        "question": "78 × 475=？",
        "answer": 4.568788212315347
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,610,414=？",
        "answer": 6.808997528727883
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 166,678=？",
        "answer": 5.221878280637083
    },
    {
        "question": "235,249,273 ÷ 127,290=？",
        "answer": 3.2667340034979206
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 217,302=？",
        "answer": 6.240153710482126
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,361=？",
        "answer": 3.434888120867316
    },
    {
        "question": "583 × 1,995=？",
        "answer": 6.065611454781781
    },
    {
        "question": "2,298,818 ÷ 108,358=？",
        "answer": 1.3266436085329651
    },
    {
        "question": "153,738,157 ÷ 200,496=？",
        "answer": 2.8846759578382946
    },
    {
        "question": "5,636,841 ÷ 4,872,914=？",
        "answer": 0.06324703795409625
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 637,224=？",
        "answer": 5.804292124428653
    },
    {
        "question": "23,363,234 ÷ 5,243,864=？",
        "answer": 0.6488815390756993
    },
    {
        "question": "114 × 43,583=？",
        "answer": 6.6962219725795045
    },
    {
        "question": "167,589,923 ÷ 327=？",
        "answer": 5.7097001487636545
    },
    {
        "question": "291 × 26,770=？",
        "answer": 6.89154136017284
    },
    {
        "question": "935,757,379 ÷ 19,816=？",
        "answer": 4.674147266890856
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 17,687=？",
        "answer": 4.247654175819024
    },
    {
        "question": "167 × 16,186=？",
        "answer": 6.431856007204116
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 1,101,879=？",
        "answer": 7.297406411309176
    },
    {
        "question": "623 × 399,233=？",
        "answer": 8.395714478887648
    },
    {
        "question": "17,772,369 ÷ 796,601=？",
        "answer": 1.3485044744725638
    },
    {
        "question": "39,993,196 ÷ 1,727,958=？",
        "answer": 1.3644529293070045
    },
    {
        "question": "5,291 × 63,261=？",
        "answer": 8.524673814288008
    },
    {
        "question": "68,834 × 6,362=？",
        "answer": 8.641396672265689
    },
    {
        "question": "308,808,369 ÷ 299,911,562=？",
        "answer": 0.012695852888776935
    },
    {
        "question": "40,905 ÷ 27,966=？",
        "answer": 0.16514604368108185
    },
    {
        "question": "39,533,035 ÷ 570,997=？",
        "answer": 1.840326330464963
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 118,747=？",
        "answer": 6.830497502180735
    },
    {
        "question": "750 × 42,439=？",
        "answer": 7.502826405359963
    },
    {
        "question": "89,639,848 ÷ 50,299=？",
        "answer": 3.2509417605566178
    },
    {
        "question": "740 ÷ 212=？",
        "answer": 0.5428958588022248
    },
    {
        "question": "305,916,942 ÷ 1,938,270=？",
        "answer": 2.198189255409511
    },
    {
        "question": "68,116,358 ÷ 785,112=？",
        "answer": 1.9383198039838614
    },
    {
        "question": "11,940,570 ÷ 8,551=？",
        "answer": 3.145008152515436
    },
    {
        "question": "76,030,417 ÷ 1,310=？",
        "answer": 4.763716076789457
    },
    {
        "question": "67,663,381 ÷ 3,412,681=？",
        "answer": 1.2972580002517682
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 1,131=？",
        "answer": 4.530583859645118
    },
    {
        "question": "285,485,417 ÷ 860,652=？",
        "answer": 2.5207563464581617
    },
    {
        "question": "136,661 ÷ 3,154=？",
        "answer": 1.6367829053016796
    },
    {
        "question": "17,981,746 ÷ 15,663=？",
        "answer": 3.059956910843383
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 2,670,575=？",
        "answer": 8.116800859161517
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,158,683=？",
        "answer": 6.84211588550034
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,620=？",
        "answer": 3.90848501887865
    },
    {
        "question": "1,303 ÷ 1,033=？",
        "answer": 0.10084409419296408
    },
    {
        "question": "714 × 31,365=？",
        "answer": 7.3501435036495275
    },
    {
        "question": "16,515,535 ÷ 546,695=？",
        "answer": 1.4801475447692733
    },
    {
        "question": "52,681 ÷ 5,337=？",
        "answer": 0.99435680741858
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 3,612,420=？",
        "answer": 8.15985822939201
    },
    {
        "question": "2,104,512 ÷ 1,233,299=？",
        "answer": 0.23208302709352305
    },
    {
        "question": "133 × 2,532,264=？",
        "answer": 8.527360621841009
    },
    {
        "question": "2,136,863 ÷ 772,862=？",
        "answer": 0.44167472480020215
    },
    {
        "question": "394 × 51,038=？",
        "answer": 7.303389869396399
    },
    {
        "question": "932,720,369 ÷ 172,484=？",
        "answer": 3.733002645952637
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,319=？",
        "answer": 4.0268599859845615
    },
    {
        "question": "162,342 ÷ 26,132=？",
        "answer": 0.7932582425113247
    },
    {
        "question": "399 × 30,501=？",
        "answer": 7.085286973963451
    },
    {
        "question": "81,440,175 ÷ 26,743,144=？",
        "answer": 0.483626235392129
    },
    {
        "question": "791 × 6,120=？",
        "answer": 6.684927905643238
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 3,156,515=？",
        "answer": 8.402297844460717
    },
    {
        "question": "6,973 × 2,342=？",
        "answer": 7.213006555941263
    },
    {
        "question": "33,562,536 ÷ 9,756,772=？",
        "answer": 0.5365486125307315
    },
    {
        "question": "8,043 ÷ 860=？",
        "answer": 0.9709196174589743
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 50,255=？",
        "answer": 6.581992869604825
    },
    {
        "question": "95,210 ÷ 56,924=？",
        "answer": 0.22338715517668672
    },
    {
        "question": "123 × 9,517=？",
        "answer": 6.068405180750857
    },
    {
        "question": "7,096,448 ÷ 46,250=？",
        "answer": 2.18592928770047
    },
    {
        "question": "281,236,083 ÷ 3,915,145=？",
        "answer": 1.856323189461715
    },
    {
        "question": "646,508,761 ÷ 81,859,381=？",
        "answer": 0.8975059581918529
    },
    {
        "question": "2,120 ÷ 427=？",
        "answer": 0.6959079859037276
    },
    {
        "question": "1,834,035 ÷ 14,104=？",
        "answer": 2.114065320026285
    },
    {
        "question": "4,297,192 ÷ 916=？",
        "answer": 3.671289284874715
    },
    {
        "question": "143,042,920 ÷ 3,751=？",
        "answer": 4.581319302841832
    },
    {
        "question": "837,276 × 272=？",
        "answer": 8.357437546637513
    },
    {
        "question": "14,968 × 3,327=？",
        "answer": 7.697216575360776
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 8,075,628=？",
        "answer": 6.907176305161616
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 293=？",
        "answer": 2.4668676203541096
    },
    {
        "question": "1,365 × 5,349=？",
        "answer": 6.863405249271792
    },
    {
        "question": "4,795,140 ÷ 108,684=？",
        "answer": 1.644635677662048
    },
    {
        "question": "8,978 × 1,621=？",
        "answer": 7.162962615914149
    },
    {
        "question": "11,515,323 ÷ 1,006=？",
        "answer": 4.058678143529996
    },
    {
        "question": "8,535,306 ÷ 92,200=？",
        "answer": 1.9664881746055864
    },
    {
        "question": "18,033,647 ÷ 12,575,831=？",
        "answer": 0.1565468718371229
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 1,344=？",
        "answer": 4.470821949540013
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 80,366=？",
        "answer": 5.946465038192348
    },
    {
        "question": "229,111,509 ÷ 2,909,857=？",
        "answer": 1.8961752588882173
    },
    {
        "question": "11,254 × 21,571=？",
        "answer": 8.385177189643983
    },
    {
        "question": "2,717 × 605=？",
        "answer": 6.21584501307036
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 14,156=？",
        "answer": 4.929091804349121
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 24,593,027=？",
        "answer": 8.432204671745252
    },
    {
        "question": "1,246 × 617=？",
        "answer": 5.8858032063563925
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 566=？",
        "answer": 2.7528164311882715
    },
    {
        "question": "59,452 ÷ 394=？",
        "answer": 2.1786702472948845
    },
    {
        "question": "436,770 × 362=？",
        "answer": 8.198961371287776
    },
    {
        "question": "6,950,836 ÷ 1,426,064=？",
        "answer": 0.6878980252071759
    },
    {
        "question": "4,492,243 ÷ 13,524=？",
        "answer": 2.5213580785287975
    },
    {
        "question": "1,380 × 110,158=？",
        "answer": 8.181895128784012
    },
    {
        "question": "63,368 ÷ 52,515=？",
        "answer": 0.08158663046105526
    },
    {
        "question": "318,655,082 ÷ 204,993=？",
        "answer": 3.191581817885588
    },
    {
        "question": "36,182 × 368=？",
        "answer": 7.124340387967829
    },
    {
        "question": "34,487,754 ÷ 4,833,133=？",
        "answer": 0.8534361656640524
    },
    {
        "question": "8,677,127 ÷ 347=？",
        "answer": 4.398046479120028
    },
    {
        "question": "277,576 ÷ 69,037=？",
        "answer": 0.6043000022179772
    },
    {
        "question": "27,603 × 7,225=？",
        "answer": 8.299794136850396
    },
    {
        "question": "13,134 ÷ 2,140=？",
        "answer": 0.7879832386023845
    },
    {
        "question": "1,634 × 26,282=？",
        "answer": 7.632910463156977
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,752,372=？",
        "answer": 6.243626305255599
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 48,224=？",
        "answer": 5.7624444766821625
    },
    {
        "question": "7,027 ÷ 827=？",
        "answer": 0.9292644439846721
    },
    {
        "question": "138,458 × 4,727=？",
        "answer": 8.815903656320804
    },
    {
        "question": "442 × 141,846=？",
        "answer": 7.797239362724381
    },
    {
        "question": "15,178 × 52,029=？",
        "answer": 8.897460027304854
    },
    {
        "question": "6,065,940 ÷ 3,296=？",
        "answer": 3.264910907236117
    },
    {
        "question": "145,225,334 ÷ 120,674,441=？",
        "answer": 0.08042708825826513
    },
    {
        "question": "328,247,163 ÷ 91,552,456=？",
        "answer": 0.5545309819804641
    },
    {
        "question": "83 × 6,780=？",
        "answer": 5.7503077862431375
    },
    {
        "question": "24,908,544 ÷ 1,364,638=？",
        "answer": 1.2613308815302902
    },
    {
        "question": "14,154,229 ÷ 2,550,532=？",
        "answer": 0.744255441002924
    },
    {
        "question": "4,074,158 ÷ 68,084=？",
        "answer": 1.776992804331901
    },
    {
        "question": "9,301 × 1,004=？",
        "answer": 6.97026335718384
    },
    {
        "question": "6,019 ÷ 341=？",
        "answer": 1.2467699643322923
    },
    {
        "question": "2,281,513 ÷ 213=？",
        "answer": 4.029843344275324
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 35,937=？",
        "answer": 6.189010275213249
    },
    {
        "question": "15,629,807 ÷ 1,586=？",
        "answer": 3.9936504323151123
    },
    {
        "question": "41,085 ÷ 820=？",
        "answer": 1.699869438925926
    },
    {
        "question": "20,672,156 ÷ 4,104,726=？",
        "answer": 0.7021016014226953
    },
    {
        "question": "38,355,221 ÷ 14,629=？",
        "answer": 3.418609849552185
    },
    {
        "question": "133,785,342 ÷ 529,766=？",
        "answer": 2.4023244510345805
    },
    {
        "question": "83,171 ÷ 9,667=？",
        "answer": 0.9346802046275561
    },
    {
        "question": "8,751 ÷ 319=？",
        "answer": 1.438267000784214
    },
    {
        "question": "1,926 × 42,689=？",
        "answer": 7.914972264259865
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 245=？",
        "answer": 3.5352941200427703
    },
    {
        "question": "34,190 × 583=？",
        "answer": 7.299567655555609
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,878=？",
        "answer": 4.158060793936605
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,180=？",
        "answer": 4.092018470752797
    },
    {
        "question": "21,969,734 ÷ 776=？",
        "answer": 4.4519630774451375
    },
    {
        "question": "5,450,720 ÷ 1,536,416=？",
        "answer": 0.5499450519782869
    },
    {
        "question": "33,333,784 ÷ 6,914,619=？",
        "answer": 0.6831163617056152
    },
    {
        "question": "307,817,608 ÷ 12,118,018=？",
        "answer": 1.4048618657671161
    },
    {
        "question": "195,904 ÷ 8,740=？",
        "answer": 1.3505318709468188
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 685,466=？",
        "answer": 6.614137168475499
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 12,885=？",
        "answer": 4.110084422886923
    },
    {
        "question": "4,743 ÷ 366=？",
        "answer": 1.1125720392574607
    },
    {
        "question": "9,926 ÷ 1,056=？",
        "answer": 0.9731103526635112
    },
    {
        "question": "935 × 13,458=？",
        "answer": 7.099792134839129
    },
    {
        "question": "1,701 × 533,097=？",
        "answer": 8.957510552154956
    },
    {
        "question": "391,431 ÷ 1,132=？",
        "answer": 2.538808790473327
    },
    {
        "question": "10,715 × 1,249=？",
        "answer": 7.126554613751983
    },
    {
        "question": "14,469,353 ÷ 549=？",
        "answer": 4.420876767538888
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 17,834=？",
        "answer": 6.0963468023201015
    },
    {
        "question": "171 × 110,326=？",
        "answer": 7.2756739829946255
    },
    {
        "question": "11,406 × 77,631=？",
        "answer": 8.947168547792057
    },
    {
        "question": "815 × 536=？",
        "answer": 5.640322398432747
    },
    {
        "question": "953,358,915 ÷ 25,463=？",
        "answer": 4.57334686203079
    },
    {
        "question": "248 × 1,989=？",
        "answer": 5.693086463950652
    },
    {
        "question": "387,318,018 ÷ 32,557=？",
        "answer": 4.075423321271206
    },
    {
        "question": "6,739 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 1.4842031826865916
    },
    {
        "question": "250,423 ÷ 203=？",
        "answer": 3.0911781760595334
    },
    {
        "question": "283,034 ÷ 4,869=？",
        "answer": 1.7643988345665638
    },
    {
        "question": "5,488 × 1,545=？",
        "answer": 6.928342586459549
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 17,320,311=？",
        "answer": 8.493828190958494
    },
    {
        "question": "658,375 ÷ 866=？",
        "answer": 2.8809554393481904
    },
    {
        "question": "1,183 ÷ 798=？",
        "answer": 0.17098185327720092
    },
    {
        "question": "1,919,555 × 299=？",
        "answer": 8.75887174856754
    },
    {
        "question": "7,569,717 ÷ 58,047=？",
        "answer": 2.1152998640173255
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 40,209,771=？",
        "answer": 8.081452854464713
    },
    {
        "question": "40,132 ÷ 37,232=？",
        "answer": 0.03257443763170596
    },
    {
        "question": "674,026,360 ÷ 172,592=？",
        "answer": 3.5916562199815623
    },
    {
        "question": "6,632,630 ÷ 6,064=？",
        "answer": 3.038926578315232
    },
    {
        "question": "78,608,785 ÷ 281,995=？",
        "answer": 2.4452296757527887
    },
    {
        "question": "2,284,774 ÷ 16,616=？",
        "answer": 2.138316764464356
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,012=？",
        "answer": 3.604657972047871
    },
    {
        "question": "726,621 ÷ 253,239=？",
        "answer": 0.4577773553150532
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 968=？",
        "answer": 4.433033388650613
    },
    {
        "question": "26,625 × 17,967=？",
        "answer": 8.679765184250666
    },
    {
        "question": "211,201,005 ÷ 158,539,241=？",
        "answer": 0.12455920576137035
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 14,434,279=？",
        "answer": 8.159395095515546
    },
    {
        "question": "945,378,951 ÷ 29,960,020=？",
        "answer": 1.499063829501123
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 784,112=？",
        "answer": 6.973559346369752
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 2,412=？",
        "answer": 4.336619812907439
    },
    {
        "question": "270,446,045 ÷ 4,208,163=？",
        "answer": 1.8079880811681426
    },
    {
        "question": "46,069 × 5,194=？",
        "answer": 8.378910730604453
    },
    {
        "question": "259 × 7,245=？",
        "answer": 6.273338153888445
    },
    {
        "question": "88,353,034 ÷ 174,868=？",
        "answer": 2.703511124603689
    },
    {
        "question": "122,598 ÷ 22,054=？",
        "answer": 0.7449960151476127
    },
    {
        "question": "546 × 6,465=？",
        "answer": 6.54776117192115
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 43,307,474=？",
        "answer": 8.113684108044197
    },
    {
        "question": "571,975 × 481=？",
        "answer": 8.43952212334986
    },
    {
        "question": "751 ÷ 322=？",
        "answer": 0.3677840653083375
    },
    {
        "question": "41,615 ÷ 1,498=？",
        "answer": 1.4437380856055195
    },
    {
        "question": "852,305,925 ÷ 4,428,921=？",
        "answer": 2.2842975738385753
    },
    {
        "question": "210 × 5,396=？",
        "answer": 6.0542912357337855
    },
    {
        "question": "7,190,004 ÷ 199,754=？",
        "answer": 1.556233647333555
    },
    {
        "question": "14,350 × 36,799=？",
        "answer": 8.722687918102693
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 17,092=？",
        "answer": 5.232792884145159
    },
    {
        "question": "152,450,996 ÷ 34,290=？",
        "answer": 3.6479627809488098
    },
    {
        "question": "1,014 × 407,429=？",
        "answer": 8.61608989299415
    },
    {
        "question": "22,683 ÷ 5,683=？",
        "answer": 0.6011228367371513
    },
    {
        "question": "3,163,884 ÷ 655,912=？",
        "answer": 0.6833749757810741
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 257=？",
        "answer": 2.4099331233312946
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 518,697=？",
        "answer": 6.714913736161671
    },
    {
        "question": "48,892,078 ÷ 386=？",
        "answer": 5.102651191269826
    },
    {
        "question": "11,665,296 ÷ 2,901,325=？",
        "answer": 0.604299383002183
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 2,583,870=？",
        "answer": 8.287331922984524
    },
    {
        "question": "373,304,561 ÷ 9,273,248=？",
        "answer": 1.6048314215932993
    },
    {
        "question": "219 × 1,154,933=？",
        "answer": 8.403000905497477
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 45,019=？",
        "answer": 5.25545583518426
    },
    {
        "question": "60,239 × 399=？",
        "answer": 7.380850649415803
    },
    {
        "question": "994,102,925 ÷ 38,229=？",
        "answer": 4.415038413819814
    },
    {
        "question": "182,920,962 ÷ 2,553=？",
        "answer": 4.855212661909385
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,857=？",
        "answer": 4.26881190373978
    },
    {
        "question": "177,347,409 ÷ 4,592=？",
        "answer": 4.586822968533791
    },
    {
        "question": "134,876 ÷ 1,938=？",
        "answer": 1.8425809049419066
    },
    {
        "question": "837,059,657 ÷ 25,503,672=？",
        "answer": 1.5161536968015628
    },
    {
        "question": "99,126,867 ÷ 5,808=？",
        "answer": 4.23216477240827
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 27,347,505=？",
        "answer": 8.215068960791324
    },
    {
        "question": "299,454 ÷ 5,350=？",
        "answer": 1.7479763365889316
    },
    {
        "question": "43,660,260 ÷ 8,258=？",
        "answer": 3.723211439097128
    },
    {
        "question": "3,613 × 28,845=？",
        "answer": 8.017938504862183
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,053=？",
        "answer": 3.624488362513449
    },
    {
        "question": "39,408 ÷ 2,167=？",
        "answer": 1.25972548317521
    },
    {
        "question": "1,755 × 975=？",
        "answer": 6.23328173650038
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 723,202=？",
        "answer": 7.549455698529784
    },
    {
        "question": "135 × 89,010=？",
        "answer": 7.07977256953151
    },
    {
        "question": "151,757 ÷ 25,776=？",
        "answer": 0.7699332095634785
    },
    {
        "question": "9,556,025 ÷ 765,445=？",
        "answer": 1.09636328673771
    },
    {
        "question": "757,923,860 ÷ 6,561=？",
        "answer": 5.062655541433147
    },
    {
        "question": "156,597 × 5,925=？",
        "answer": 8.967471792506712
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 758,632=？",
        "answer": 7.135303662914201
    },
    {
        "question": "3,094 × 13,778=？",
        "answer": 7.629706489779478
    },
    {
        "question": "2,139 ÷ 228=？",
        "answer": 0.9722759375710742
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 65,092=？",
        "answer": 5.716617602759048
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 24,587,704=？",
        "answer": 7.867839230929486
    },
    {
        "question": "20,017,851 ÷ 15,320,941=？",
        "answer": 0.1161320121801706
    },
    {
        "question": "2,090 × 50,749=？",
        "answer": 8.025573775085256
    },
    {
        "question": "18,973,437 ÷ 38,911=？",
        "answer": 2.688073617414535
    },
    {
        "question": "32 × 23,577,741=？",
        "answer": 8.877652171011475
    },
    {
        "question": "34,364 × 401=？",
        "answer": 7.13924808298367
    },
    {
        "question": "251,795 ÷ 2,478=？",
        "answer": 2.006945799847886
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 5,776,044=？",
        "answer": 7.36369048421441
    },
    {
        "question": "1,529 × 13,044=？",
        "answer": 7.299818275546239
    },
    {
        "question": "188,747 × 5,142=？",
        "answer": 8.987012129859458
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 271,322=？",
        "answer": 7.173847699220571
    },
    {
        "question": "2,847 × 16,691=？",
        "answer": 7.676869824285866
    },
    {
        "question": "2,627,699 ÷ 164,366=？",
        "answer": 1.2037636294651264
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 523=？",
        "answer": 3.97377419397058
    },
    {
        "question": "55,968 × 2,101=？",
        "answer": 8.070365840204536
    },
    {
        "question": "256,828,318 ÷ 2,801,272=？",
        "answer": 1.9622876272111156
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 5,909=？",
        "answer": 5.026786495082972
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 102,569=？",
        "answer": 6.718586297465817
    },
    {
        "question": "97,922 × 725=？",
        "answer": 7.851218281675722
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 86,208=？",
        "answer": 5.889790079146198
    },
    {
        "question": "31,186 × 20,045=？",
        "answer": 8.795965735140722
    },
    {
        "question": "15,810 ÷ 10,022=？",
        "answer": 0.19797747152575113
    },
    {
        "question": "157,071,110 ÷ 1,102=？",
        "answer": 5.153914718332155
    },
    {
        "question": "368,741 ÷ 1,769=？",
        "answer": 2.3189935962174135
    },
    {
        "question": "7,689,533 ÷ 239=？",
        "answer": 4.5075020641222645
    },
    {
        "question": "1,278,883 ÷ 575=？",
        "answer": 3.347162969704091
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 275,000,100=？",
        "answer": 8.740362847419481
    },
    {
        "question": "29,241 ÷ 739=？",
        "answer": 1.597347782389482
    },
    {
        "question": "14,188 × 2,257=？",
        "answer": 7.5054527388776675
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 13,461,643=？",
        "answer": 8.708881665590035
    },
    {
        "question": "604,334 ÷ 4,606=？",
        "answer": 2.1179530948367042
    },
    {
        "question": "885,201 ÷ 11,572=？",
        "answer": 1.883633470896352
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 62,198,456=？",
        "answer": 8.094809599663437
    },
    {
        "question": "2,873,729 ÷ 3,684=？",
        "answer": 2.89212618912314
    },
    {
        "question": "785 × 7,266=？",
        "answer": 6.756165050271949
    },
    {
        "question": "1,623 × 48,079=？",
        "answer": 7.892273945979851
    },
    {
        "question": "8,997,806 ÷ 1,761,898=？",
        "answer": 0.7081558626109054
    },
    {
        "question": "319,524,997 ÷ 109,573,833=？",
        "answer": 0.46479798548014495
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 77,942,576=？",
        "answer": 8.192804750778569
    },
    {
        "question": "7,871,008 ÷ 269=？",
        "answer": 4.466278073805849
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,828=？",
        "answer": 4.066549538761934
    },
    {
        "question": "18,655,098 ÷ 114,485=？",
        "answer": 2.212048946367548
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 55,514,753=？",
        "answer": 8.8905364475409
    },
    {
        "question": "343,746,174 ÷ 42,810,537=？",
        "answer": 0.9046871975323991
    },
    {
        "question": "97,061 ÷ 493=？",
        "answer": 2.2941978421739577
    },
    {
        "question": "8,155 × 410=？",
        "answer": 6.52420782209603
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 4,305,609=？",
        "answer": 7.588277097664247
    },
    {
        "question": "318,736 ÷ 4,424=？",
        "answer": 1.8576159998315664
    },
    {
        "question": "75,372,260 ÷ 54,531,710=？",
        "answer": 0.14056242110861605
    },
    {
        "question": "3,956 ÷ 410=？",
        "answer": 0.9844724262054063
    },
    {
        "question": "601 × 514,469=？",
        "answer": 8.490233682909645
    },
    {
        "question": "18,069,517 ÷ 2,485,218=？",
        "answer": 0.8615820535094986
    },
    {
        "question": "756,593 ÷ 716,061=？",
        "answer": 0.02391229820116133
    },
    {
        "question": "21,681,076 ÷ 4,342,963=？",
        "answer": 0.6982947024058315
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 54,360=？",
        "answer": 5.337339439388419
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 5,901=？",
        "answer": 4.469895618975018
    },
    {
        "question": "12,992,663 ÷ 34,597=？",
        "answer": 2.574659732419461
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 31,200=？",
        "answer": 6.467282447618142
    },
    {
        "question": "847 × 34,764=？",
        "answer": 7.469013151582094
    },
    {
        "question": "104,905,097 ÷ 3,623,725=？",
        "answer": 1.4616413574878395
    },
    {
        "question": "147,658 ÷ 82,159=？",
        "answer": 0.25460183709178197
    },
    {
        "question": "297,657,468 ÷ 6,886=？",
        "answer": 4.635749764774801
    },
    {
        "question": "603,745,502 ÷ 5,877,809=？",
        "answer": 2.011638438686053
    },
    {
        "question": "181 × 728,458=？",
        "answer": 8.120083091999128
    },
    {
        "question": "8,999 × 255=？",
        "answer": 6.360734432249818
    },
    {
        "question": "3,092,725 ÷ 2,398=？",
        "answer": 3.1104921262089333
    },
    {
        "question": "383 × 2,055,605=？",
        "answer": 8.896138439349617
    },
    {
        "question": "2,739 × 254,216=？",
        "answer": 8.842794913220317
    },
    {
        "question": "733,527 ÷ 613=？",
        "answer": 3.0779556296666146
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 347,028=？",
        "answer": 7.2563678609470115
    },
    {
        "question": "47,230 ÷ 7,885=？",
        "answer": 0.7774162479117783
    },
    {
        "question": "37,742,677 ÷ 149,039=？",
        "answer": 2.4035327724828566
    },
    {
        "question": "141,766 × 2,274=？",
        "answer": 8.508362546044157
    },
    {
        "question": "2,319,775 ÷ 69,020=？",
        "answer": 1.5264709088159787
    },
    {
        "question": "682 × 1,195=？",
        "answer": 5.9111522799406355
    },
    {
        "question": "71,673 × 8,535=？",
        "answer": 8.78655910846331
    },
    {
        "question": "2,437,419 ÷ 2,129=？",
        "answer": 3.058754530752748
    },
    {
        "question": "1,674,305 ÷ 1,063=？",
        "answer": 3.1973013096545344
    },
    {
        "question": "78,827,781 ÷ 1,004,710=？",
        "answer": 1.894638576490017
    },
    {
        "question": "79,714 ÷ 1,291=？",
        "answer": 1.7906083600430658
    },
    {
        "question": "692,998,440 ÷ 294=？",
        "answer": 6.372384926565949
    },
    {
        "question": "306 × 294,586=？",
        "answer": 7.9549335299276995
    },
    {
        "question": "296,007 × 763=？",
        "answer": 8.353826519369992
    },
    {
        "question": "911 × 82,330=？",
        "answer": 7.875076492384519
    },
    {
        "question": "26,936 × 32,733=？",
        "answer": 8.945318913874068
    },
    {
        "question": "14,095,006 ÷ 4,611=？",
        "answer": 3.485270142859894
    },
    {
        "question": "890,065 ÷ 3,312=？",
        "answer": 2.4293313955101987
    },
    {
        "question": "1,883 × 1,096=？",
        "answer": 6.314660874165015
    },
    {
        "question": "65,753 ÷ 1,406=？",
        "answer": 1.66993025174374
    },
    {
        "question": "319,924,553 ÷ 137,850,599=？",
        "answer": 0.36563891424409606
    },
    {
        "question": "1,089 × 39,759=？",
        "answer": 7.636463332444244
    },
    {
        "question": "48 × 10,045,154=？",
        "answer": 8.683197836582059
    },
    {
        "question": "9,606 ÷ 3,684=？",
        "answer": 0.41622296077813203
    },
    {
        "question": "270,540,839 ÷ 7,184,387=？",
        "answer": 1.5758431141772244
    },
    {
        "question": "188,447 × 1,911=？",
        "answer": 8.556449915103219
    },
    {
        "question": "68,538,096 ÷ 259,785=？",
        "answer": 2.42131796421265
    },
    {
        "question": "678,406,017 ÷ 2,087,677=？",
        "answer": 2.5118263845567124
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 41,355=？",
        "answer": 5.57077053460078
    },
    {
        "question": "343,703,731 ÷ 2,066=？",
        "answer": 5.221053929367116
    },
    {
        "question": "552 × 847,764=？",
        "answer": 8.67021404819058
    },
    {
        "question": "4,464,393 ÷ 23,976=？",
        "answer": 2.2699856885678296
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 114,031,597=？",
        "answer": 8.05702520661191
    },
    {
        "question": "786,497 ÷ 17,315=？",
        "answer": 1.6572745745119308
    },
    {
        "question": "19,877,997 ÷ 2,485,227=？",
        "answer": 0.9030065574933446
    },
    {
        "question": "25,634 ÷ 15,390=？",
        "answer": 0.2215777601484558
    },
    {
        "question": "139,087,442 ÷ 15,908,159=？",
        "answer": 0.9416679969008536
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 17,199,490=？",
        "answer": 8.826580176406749
    },
    {
        "question": "986,268,349 ÷ 142,017,020=？",
        "answer": 0.8416547006780242
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,848,080=？",
        "answer": 6.894763421408267
    },
    {
        "question": "240,522 ÷ 29,145=？",
        "answer": 0.9165907467991907
    },
    {
        "question": "2,245,342 ÷ 991,574=？",
        "answer": 0.35495736944694173
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,981=？",
        "answer": 4.410827827845384
    },
    {
        "question": "12,371 × 54,876=？",
        "answer": 8.831787254327315
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 5,787=？",
        "answer": 4.607551522377804
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 243=？",
        "answer": 3.499549625905149
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,795=？",
        "answer": 3.9818186071706636
    },
    {
        "question": "203,169,582 ÷ 88,813=？",
        "answer": 3.359382146811964
    },
    {
        "question": "1,243,777 ÷ 711=？",
        "answer": 3.242872920821995
    },
    {
        "question": "1,139,765 × 325=？",
        "answer": 8.568698677469774
    },
    {
        "question": "599,933,310 ÷ 120,328=？",
        "answer": 3.6977362776185445
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 3,381=？",
        "answer": 5.047559110643657
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 489,871=？",
        "answer": 7.31333102070387
    },
    {
        "question": "1,294 × 227,980=？",
        "answer": 8.469831025654976
    },
    {
        "question": "2,251,500 ÷ 287=？",
        "answer": 3.894590054564959
    },
    {
        "question": "459,329,973 ÷ 391,975,575=？",
        "answer": 0.06886577981877273
    },
    {
        "question": "107,478,191 ÷ 315,586=？",
        "answer": 2.5322026192436766
    },
    {
        "question": "188 × 81,469=？",
        "answer": 7.185150234812726
    },
    {
        "question": "619 × 362,870=？",
        "answer": 8.35144171374033
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 664=？",
        "answer": 3.9682961150462557
    },
    {
        "question": "286,821 × 1,181=？",
        "answer": 8.529860843250276
    },
    {
        "question": "195 × 240=？",
        "answer": 4.670245853074124
    },
    {
        "question": "173,469 ÷ 986=？",
        "answer": 2.245344959967582
    },
    {
        "question": "5,394,959 ÷ 2,958,915=？",
        "answer": 0.2608556590568231
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 453,105=？",
        "answer": 6.434350105015772
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 693=？",
        "answer": 3.5397032389478253
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,229,788=？",
        "answer": 6.089830250979561
    },
    {
        "question": "191,427,889 ÷ 136,263=？",
        "answer": 3.1476272638767235
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,016,405=？",
        "answer": 7.001422587714066
    },
    {
        "question": "105,037 ÷ 5,371=？",
        "answer": 1.2912871568402378
    },
    {
        "question": "2,551,124 ÷ 1,300=？",
        "answer": 3.292788216144959
    },
    {
        "question": "152,629 ÷ 6,965=？",
        "answer": 1.3407159380449731
    },
    {
        "question": "346,003 × 1,656=？",
        "answer": 8.758140196784405
    },
    {
        "question": "256 × 45,702=？",
        "answer": 7.068175171288878
    },
    {
        "question": "150,190,068 ÷ 186,859=？",
        "answer": 2.905127193588714
    },
    {
        "question": "129,520,034 ÷ 65,733=？",
        "answer": 3.294553496175686
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 1,851=？",
        "answer": 4.568436414416885
    },
    {
        "question": "48,858,319 ÷ 17,263=？",
        "answer": 3.4518222501952214
    },
    {
        "question": "4,677,179 ÷ 830,262=？",
        "answer": 0.750768829790452
    },
    {
        "question": "190 × 2,125,460=？",
        "answer": 8.606206537147179
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,938=？",
        "answer": 3.5883837683787276
    },
    {
        "question": "42,394 × 3,153=？",
        "answer": 8.126028366225563
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 282=？",
        "answer": 2.450249108319361
    },
    {
        "question": "123 × 228=？",
        "answer": 4.447839958439852
    },
    {
        "question": "3,858,987 ÷ 1,676,993=？",
        "answer": 0.36194206573527715
    },
    {
        "question": "92,405,653 ÷ 283=？",
        "answer": 5.5139121048690765
    },
    {
        "question": "498,642 ÷ 11,576=？",
        "answer": 1.6342303376854068
    },
    {
        "question": "142,664,945 ÷ 6,177=？",
        "answer": 4.363539671963914
    },
    {
        "question": "579,487,502 ÷ 15,619,859=？",
        "answer": 1.5693669646311743
    },
    {
        "question": "3,642,309 ÷ 16,712=？",
        "answer": 2.3383483599842765
    },
    {
        "question": "163,415,932 ÷ 109,714=？",
        "answer": 3.173032346132492
    },
    {
        "question": "126,116,533 ÷ 198,288=？",
        "answer": 2.8034755909378966
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 6,060,822=？",
        "answer": 8.42598420590901
    },
    {
        "question": "11,271,338 ÷ 329,910=？",
        "answer": 1.5335799936391696
    },
    {
        "question": "229 × 457=？",
        "answer": 5.019751682409738
    },
    {
        "question": "357,722 ÷ 259=？",
        "answer": 3.1402458861174645
    },
    {
        "question": "366 ÷ 302=？",
        "answer": 0.08347414243726002
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 5,600,931=？",
        "answer": 7.827441468510361
    },
    {
        "question": "41,281,973 ÷ 85,872=？",
        "answer": 2.6819088675205824
    },
    {
        "question": "5,903,306 ÷ 473,286=？",
        "answer": 1.0959716375725084
    },
    {
        "question": "368,395 ÷ 213,409=？",
        "answer": 0.23710099637454232
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 330,853=？",
        "answer": 6.519635076950111
    },
    {
        "question": "1,699,141 ÷ 66,368=？",
        "answer": 1.4082706890971306
    },
    {
        "question": "39,793,203 ÷ 3,856,149=？",
        "answer": 1.0136550908943929
    },
    {
        "question": "211 × 28,177=？",
        "answer": 6.774177207278903
    },
    {
        "question": "13,109,065 ÷ 1,948=？",
        "answer": 3.8279827643327295
    },
    {
        "question": "18,603 × 8,332=？",
        "answer": 8.19033224734232
    },
    {
        "question": "181,424 × 593=？",
        "answer": 8.03174943131501
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 52,875=？",
        "answer": 6.084978216400692
    },
    {
        "question": "2,998 × 2,902=？",
        "answer": 6.939529036613978
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 5,429=？",
        "answer": 4.336779832983642
    },
    {
        "question": "11,500 ÷ 2,068=？",
        "answer": 0.7451473059317067
    },
    {
        "question": "40,388 × 8,675=？",
        "answer": 8.544521831050588
    },
    {
        "question": "35,237,290 ÷ 486,310=？",
        "answer": 1.8600893006037693
    },
    {
        "question": "199 × 2,582,516=？",
        "answer": 8.710896097284882
    },
    {
        "question": "64 × 843,837=？",
        "answer": 7.732438538101017
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,413,760=？",
        "answer": 7.3113842357213885
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 3,819,526=？",
        "answer": 7.962220712383224
    },
    {
        "question": "10,760 × 2,231=？",
        "answer": 7.380311841614208
    },
    {
        "question": "170,085,746 ÷ 999=？",
        "answer": 5.231102430954301
    },
    {
        "question": "10,424,412 ÷ 772,136=？",
        "answer": 1.1303577660627289
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 1,012=？",
        "answer": 4.084361758551405
    },
    {
        "question": "170 × 6,639=？",
        "answer": 6.052551590025194
    },
    {
        "question": "175 × 53,868=？",
        "answer": 6.974368900135572
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 295,158=？",
        "answer": 7.482891783594828
    },
    {
        "question": "106,026,798 ÷ 1,416=？",
        "answer": 4.874352392596271
    },
    {
        "question": "601,437 × 532=？",
        "answer": 8.505101774386029
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 206=？",
        "answer": 3.012837224705172
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 9,622,285=？",
        "answer": 7.983278216014302
    },
    {
        "question": "20,449,844 ÷ 857=？",
        "answer": 4.377709177452065
    },
    {
        "question": "194,386 ÷ 2,957=？",
        "answer": 1.8178136585863005
    },
    {
        "question": "128,472 × 6,244=？",
        "answer": 8.904271379485417
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 14,944,705=？",
        "answer": 8.605851110892157
    },
    {
        "question": "721,322,676 ÷ 18,435=？",
        "answer": 4.592486443245123
    },
    {
        "question": "2,373,804 ÷ 5,856=？",
        "answer": 2.607843789267261
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 600,361,965=？",
        "answer": 8.778413170390259
    },
    {
        "question": "2,655,163 ÷ 328,563=？",
        "answer": 0.9074725322365872
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 8,469,288=？",
        "answer": 6.927846901397002
    },
    {
        "question": "577,039,340 ÷ 7,118=？",
        "answer": 4.908847438781683
    },
    {
        "question": "1,299 × 906=？",
        "answer": 6.070737348749841
    },
    {
        "question": "49,695,837 ÷ 1,130,108=？",
        "answer": 1.6432000602942174
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,101,628=？",
        "answer": 6.785445726336209
    },
    {
        "question": "606 × 33,666=？",
        "answer": 7.309664143253387
    },
    {
        "question": "119 × 196,093=？",
        "answer": 7.3680090521759
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 77,640=？",
        "answer": 6.367206781435987
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 142,381,222=？",
        "answer": 8.153452715989516
    },
    {
        "question": "292,499,993 ÷ 81,937=？",
        "answer": 3.552645801155775
    },
    {
        "question": "4,064 ÷ 444=？",
        "answer": 0.9615707291612431
    },
    {
        "question": "18,945,990 ÷ 59,878=？",
        "answer": 2.50025001780653
    },
    {
        "question": "2,690 × 304,805=？",
        "answer": 8.91377436686485
    },
    {
        "question": "45,151,344 ÷ 16,669=？",
        "answer": 3.4327611357047205
    },
    {
        "question": "10,898,837 ÷ 14,045=？",
        "answer": 2.889858413904868
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 2,141,570=？",
        "answer": 7.409913520492044
    },
    {
        "question": "400,146,036 ÷ 813=？",
        "answer": 5.692127973369626
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 46,488=？",
        "answer": 6.235542586497711
    },
    {
        "question": "958 ÷ 214=？",
        "answer": 0.6509517357293536
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 4,217,460=？",
        "answer": 7.855499893644379
    },
    {
        "question": "483 × 831,907=？",
        "answer": 8.604021909392808
    },
    {
        "question": "15,650 × 11,937=？",
        "answer": 8.271409535748518
    },
    {
        "question": "27,753 ÷ 1,643=？",
        "answer": 1.2276723722407379
    },
    {
        "question": "12,764,105 ÷ 42,428=？",
        "answer": 2.4783378079470575
    },
    {
        "question": "282,148,240 ÷ 36,774=？",
        "answer": 3.8849364738124574
    },
    {
        "question": "98 × 306=？",
        "answer": 4.476947502174075
    },
    {
        "question": "41,737 × 2,024=？",
        "answer": 7.926731737509814
    },
    {
        "question": "7,934,609 ÷ 226,457=？",
        "answer": 1.5445397808661028
    },
    {
        "question": "2,474,457 ÷ 2,241,513=？",
        "answer": 0.04293864927184093
    },
    {
        "question": "99,796,095 ÷ 1,883=？",
        "answer": 4.724263227752351
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 427=？",
        "answer": 3.329397879361043
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 364=？",
        "answer": 2.561101383649056
    },
    {
        "question": "33,251,447 ÷ 357,737=？",
        "answer": 1.9682466885468122
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 2,282=？",
        "answer": 3.8354368948018585
    },
    {
        "question": "477,738,138 ÷ 144,614,997=？",
        "answer": 0.5189765796377946
    },
    {
        "question": "519,725,569 ÷ 1,869,050=？",
        "answer": 2.4441531637968237
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 80,290=？",
        "answer": 6.396023151749797
    },
    {
        "question": "83,155 ÷ 355=？",
        "answer": 2.3696600148374776
    },
    {
        "question": "175,604 ÷ 1,352=？",
        "answer": 2.1135577126645937
    },
    {
        "question": "318 × 616=？",
        "answer": 5.292007832148858
    },
    {
        "question": "182 × 261=？",
        "answer": 4.676711895323356
    },
    {
        "question": "4,113,140 ÷ 9,585=？",
        "answer": 2.6325813747392224
    },
    {
        "question": "14,285,410 ÷ 825=？",
        "answer": 4.238438760864835
    },
    {
        "question": "1,646,507 ÷ 39,456=？",
        "answer": 1.6204505265063618
    },
    {
        "question": "658 × 752=？",
        "answer": 5.694443734205597
    },
    {
        "question": "666,685 ÷ 15,962=？",
        "answer": 1.6208333774059087
    },
    {
        "question": "3,286,761 ÷ 142,047=？",
        "answer": 1.3643360591309812
    },
    {
        "question": "63,525,630 ÷ 882=？",
        "answer": 4.857480395621943
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,811=？",
        "answer": 4.371861802620895
    },
    {
        "question": "2,725,929 ÷ 18,473=？",
        "answer": 2.168977109705369
    },
    {
        "question": "782,457,889 ÷ 2,050,307=？",
        "answer": 2.5816420791757273
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 1,676=？",
        "answer": 4.622214022966295
    },
    {
        "question": "285,580,740 ÷ 3,446=？",
        "answer": 4.918413641498525
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 20,695,926=？",
        "answer": 8.491976121911003
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 4,373=？",
        "answer": 4.339749481680876
    },
    {
        "question": "24,836 × 3,295=？",
        "answer": 7.9129370701039745
    },
    {
        "question": "5,604,046 ÷ 203,883=？",
        "answer": 1.439120676159431
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 4,593=？",
        "answer": 4.50719448543218
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 535=？",
        "answer": 4.427323786357247
    },
    {
        "question": "103,048 ÷ 1,671=？",
        "answer": 1.7900631173291404
    },
    {
        "question": "620,422,198 ÷ 173,992=？",
        "answer": 3.552158047720568
    },
    {
        "question": "74,953 ÷ 217=？",
        "answer": 2.538329286356067
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 17,377,657=？",
        "answer": 7.842051212199792
    },
    {
        "question": "33,620 × 2,661=？",
        "answer": 7.9516425836548414
    },
    {
        "question": "3,173 × 1,081=？",
        "answer": 6.535295766053722
    },
    {
        "question": "102,317 ÷ 5,201=？",
        "answer": 1.293860944089958
    },
    {
        "question": "680,446 ÷ 515=？",
        "answer": 3.12098643637977
    },
    {
        "question": "53,203 ÷ 1,529=？",
        "answer": 1.541528636482571
    },
    {
        "question": "86,677,467 ÷ 17,560=？",
        "answer": 3.6933816997533278
    },
    {
        "question": "449 × 148,256=？",
        "answer": 7.823258619526384
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,531,865=？",
        "answer": 6.963371743918846
    },
    {
        "question": "1,930,938 ÷ 45,397=？",
        "answer": 1.6287411753159144
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 323=？",
        "answer": 3.5883837683787276
    },
    {
        "question": "2,279 × 2,891=？",
        "answer": 6.818792416851033
    },
    {
        "question": "26,191,337 ÷ 5,797,327=？",
        "answer": 0.6549298710263813
    },
    {
        "question": "8,018,163 ÷ 625=？",
        "answer": 4.108194863365764
    },
    {
        "question": "252 × 2,813,090=？",
        "answer": 8.850584167677678
    },
    {
        "question": "10,228,379 ÷ 1,598=？",
        "answer": 3.8062300369221918
    },
    {
        "question": "20,437,517 ÷ 435=？",
        "answer": 4.671938874297583
    },
    {
        "question": "110,317 ÷ 1,082=？",
        "answer": 2.0084151821981755
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,445,914=？",
        "answer": 7.0052405027956235
    },
    {
        "question": "2,393 × 742=？",
        "answer": 6.249346603892464
    },
    {
        "question": "14,145,166 ÷ 209=？",
        "answer": 4.830461762356467
    },
    {
        "question": "1,359 ÷ 1,132=？",
        "answer": 0.07937302988024172
    },
    {
        "question": "53,805,002 ÷ 102,852=？",
        "answer": 2.718609910724893
    },
    {
        "question": "9,550 ÷ 3,079=？",
        "answer": 0.49159368268054826
    },
    {
        "question": "12,229,395 ÷ 1,756,680=？",
        "answer": 0.8427123157664231
    },
    {
        "question": "250 × 69,933=？",
        "answer": 7.242622167764552
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 45,401=？",
        "answer": 6.50832376742858
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 74,233,938=？",
        "answer": 8.648753750223756
    },
    {
        "question": "735,566,260 ÷ 5,663,772=？",
        "answer": 2.1135160380488536
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 85,030=？",
        "answer": 6.5630406346561365
    },
    {
        "question": "82,810 × 3,422=？",
        "answer": 8.45236278984727
    },
    {
        "question": "838,898,588 ÷ 27,776=？",
        "answer": 4.480039759913963
    },
    {
        "question": "304,099 × 229=？",
        "answer": 7.842850474351183
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,144,963=？",
        "answer": 7.012412251545016
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 232,598,668=？",
        "answer": 8.366607223367897
    },
    {
        "question": "14,518 ÷ 342=？",
        "answer": 1.6278806860111439
    },
    {
        "question": "237,396 ÷ 222=？",
        "answer": 3.029120422591848
    },
    {
        "question": "12,462,509 ÷ 5,340=？",
        "answer": 3.368064227923968
    },
    {
        "question": "760,397,732 ÷ 43,443,900=？",
        "answer": 1.2431120074897495
    },
    {
        "question": "208 × 178,829=？",
        "answer": 7.570501282972528
    },
    {
        "question": "424,448,545 ÷ 493=？",
        "answer": 5.9349781298916024
    },
    {
        "question": "8,869 × 3,933=？",
        "answer": 7.542598601307445
    },
    {
        "question": "466,787,931 ÷ 382,255=？",
        "answer": 3.0867664438382323
    },
    {
        "question": "87,105 ÷ 29,253=？",
        "answer": 0.4738726739311227
    },
    {
        "question": "1,625,145 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 3.8664998423316237
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 982=？",
        "answer": 3.594171479114912
    },
    {
        "question": "89 × 4,197=？",
        "answer": 5.5723289758564025
    },
    {
        "question": "4,364,093 ÷ 9,019=？",
        "answer": 2.68473561002178
    },
    {
        "question": "778,760,226 ÷ 13,786,075=？",
        "answer": 1.75196312563621
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 17,119=？",
        "answer": 5.801680115998887
    },
    {
        "question": "81,690 ÷ 2,132=？",
        "answer": 1.5833816957050924
    },
    {
        "question": "386,887 × 386=？",
        "answer": 8.174171441673646
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 3,967,703=？",
        "answer": 7.996479164520971
    },
    {
        "question": "296,869 ÷ 462=？",
        "answer": 2.8079228740040625
    },
    {
        "question": "348,332,453 ÷ 20,893,495=？",
        "answer": 1.2219828446344427
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 214,999=？",
        "answer": 5.332436439936573
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 2,625,240=？",
        "answer": 7.998952609467782
    },
    {
        "question": "147,634 ÷ 32,466=？",
        "answer": 0.6577576023845735
    },
    {
        "question": "70 × 32,983=？",
        "answer": 6.363388194785201
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 3,340=？",
        "answer": 4.523746466811565
    },
    {
        "question": "680 × 38,252=？",
        "answer": 7.415163059810419
    },
    {
        "question": "778,618,931 ÷ 213,947,911=？",
        "answer": 0.5610169083927555
    },
    {
        "question": "502 × 17,411=？",
        "answer": 6.941527432662685
    },
    {
        "question": "626,446 ÷ 2,342=？",
        "answer": 2.427296749776941
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,128,952=？",
        "answer": 6.853025690571411
    },
    {
        "question": "6,815,745 ÷ 57,957=？",
        "answer": 2.07040743643487
    },
    {
        "question": "4,848,661 ÷ 29,884=？",
        "answer": 2.210183093215711
    },
    {
        "question": "13,211 × 3,396=？",
        "answer": 7.651903374133046
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 217=？",
        "answer": 2.637489729512511
    },
    {
        "question": "19,672,201 ÷ 5,178,485=？",
        "answer": 0.5796502305343192
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 603=？",
        "answer": 4.413785767719737
    },
    {
        "question": "35,185,100 ÷ 425=？",
        "answer": 4.917969859628478
    },
    {
        "question": "2,427 ÷ 555=？",
        "answer": 0.6407767932092585
    },
    {
        "question": "179,195 × 2,659=？",
        "answer": 8.678044224897048
    },
    {
        "question": "57,131,753 ÷ 723=？",
        "answer": 4.897739252628905
    },
    {
        "question": "806,262,960 ÷ 31,726,461=？",
        "answer": 1.405055078178696
    },
    {
        "question": "806,918,794 ÷ 82,480=？",
        "answer": 3.9904811784909238
    },
    {
        "question": "559,171 ÷ 1,192=？",
        "answer": 2.671268384324535
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 7,958,845=？",
        "answer": 8.243272727640019
    },
    {
        "question": "25,193 ÷ 1,013=？",
        "answer": 1.3956704413068877
    },
    {
        "question": "7,309,383 ÷ 453,371=？",
        "answer": 1.2074269819040782
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 74,109=？",
        "answer": 6.618058980100089
    },
    {
        "question": "4,978 × 72,197=？",
        "answer": 8.55557404399021
    },
    {
        "question": "132 × 2,474=？",
        "answer": 5.513973626498951
    },
    {
        "question": "188,726,485 ÷ 14,649,462=？",
        "answer": 1.1100111757537314
    },
    {
        "question": "5,007,833 ÷ 3,765,500=？",
        "answer": 0.1238271857594651
    },
    {
        "question": "91,044,126 ÷ 54,171,985=？",
        "answer": 0.2254771816127942
    },
    {
        "question": "1,764 × 38,997=？",
        "answer": 7.8375297792695005
    },
    {
        "question": "2,558,564 ÷ 356,494=？",
        "answer": 0.8559440600774435
    },
    {
        "question": "958,242 ÷ 517,007=？",
        "answer": 0.2679787789309537
    },
    {
        "question": "88,967,412 ÷ 249,586=？",
        "answer": 2.5520107365671865
    },
    {
        "question": "164,069,215 ÷ 552,527=？",
        "answer": 2.4726735949092995
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,845=？",
        "answer": 4.13640344813399
    },
    {
        "question": "8,495,192 ÷ 8,581=？",
        "answer": 2.9956352968423334
    },
    {
        "question": "4,040,364 ÷ 2,271=？",
        "answer": 3.250203358631036
    },
    {
        "question": "68 × 34,618=？",
        "answer": 6.3718108862960445
    },
    {
        "question": "963 × 204=？",
        "answer": 5.293256454550433
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 382,990=？",
        "answer": 6.537429943978401
    },
    {
        "question": "75,550,739 ÷ 651=？",
        "answer": 5.06465772818167
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 526,782=？",
        "answer": 6.8677589624952615
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 45,156=？",
        "answer": 6.131836719087151
    },
    {
        "question": "1,705 × 99,528=？",
        "answer": 8.22966966040414
    },
    {
        "question": "11,611,989 ÷ 383,251=？",
        "answer": 1.4814233190406523
    },
    {
        "question": "455,240 ÷ 6,706=？",
        "answer": 1.8317768655773015
    },
    {
        "question": "25,409,882 ÷ 10,366=？",
        "answer": 3.3893914437476496
    },
    {
        "question": "314,652 × 3,065=？",
        "answer": 8.98426097542166
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 358,956=？",
        "answer": 6.032162471742767
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,776,345=？",
        "answer": 6.890775519957383
    },
    {
        "question": "64,161 × 247=？",
        "answer": 7.19996807741198
    },
    {
        "question": "6,058,380 ÷ 258=？",
        "answer": 4.370736804157305
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,022=？",
        "answer": 3.8464608251293324
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 693,649=？",
        "answer": 7.464389054909251
    },
    {
        "question": "251,359,354 ÷ 1,050=？",
        "answer": 5.379105752479414
    },
    {
        "question": "10,884 × 294=？",
        "answer": 6.505135863519877
    },
    {
        "question": "596 × 1,303=？",
        "answer": 5.890190675452821
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,872=？",
        "answer": 3.587935348636356
    },
    {
        "question": "710 × 1,535=？",
        "answer": 6.03736672853228
    },
    {
        "question": "2,888,847 ÷ 504=？",
        "answer": 3.7582940047703244
    },
    {
        "question": "67,632,994 ÷ 492=？",
        "answer": 5.138193510576921
    },
    {
        "question": "91 × 604,963=？",
        "answer": 7.740770206002962
    },
    {
        "question": "29,524,265 ÷ 5,998,402=？",
        "answer": 0.6921435268748559
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 82,332=？",
        "answer": 5.760666705388292
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 5,885,104=？",
        "answer": 7.2468753967040485
    },
    {
        "question": "120,821 ÷ 6,191=？",
        "answer": 1.2903816219235376
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 77,135=？",
        "answer": 5.7323495238729425
    },
    {
        "question": "19,414,451 ÷ 16,803,843=？",
        "answer": 0.06271649888986193
    },
    {
        "question": "184 × 7,331=？",
        "answer": 6.129981042515623
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 43,337=？",
        "answer": 6.193161344794449
    },
    {
        "question": "49,947,257 ÷ 281,824=？",
        "answer": 2.2485336679994936
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 422,784=？",
        "answer": 7.651424408604053
    },
    {
        "question": "49,079 ÷ 3,825=？",
        "answer": 1.108264265769358
    },
    {
        "question": "12,171,510 ÷ 1,861,788=？",
        "answer": 0.8154142334661768
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 6,825,445=？",
        "answer": 8.737220958418183
    },
    {
        "question": "85,545,628 ÷ 50,568,914=？",
        "answer": 0.22831419187777732
    },
    {
        "question": "4,822 ÷ 580=？",
        "answer": 0.9197992124784976
    },
    {
        "question": "217,673 ÷ 13,140=？",
        "answer": 1.2192091975875643
    },
    {
        "question": "2,587 ÷ 596=？",
        "answer": 0.637550168976307
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 463=？",
        "answer": 2.6655809910179533
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 83,813=？",
        "answer": 6.742855321599207
    },
    {
        "question": "28,780,298 ÷ 897=？",
        "answer": 4.50630284339755
    },
    {
        "question": "1,140,198 ÷ 14,345=？",
        "answer": 1.900279722298931
    },
    {
        "question": "360,976 ÷ 53,708=？",
        "answer": 0.8274393479376445
    },
    {
        "question": "1,301 × 190,127=？",
        "answer": 8.393321092113872
    },
    {
        "question": "4,312,284 ÷ 235,221=？",
        "answer": 1.2632312630815752
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 11,214,436=？",
        "answer": 8.429988678502903
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 486,535,863=？",
        "answer": 8.687114858024644
    },
    {
        "question": "336 × 103,226=？",
        "answer": 7.540128376176868
    },
    {
        "question": "101,243,234 ÷ 249,109=？",
        "answer": 2.6089765909799487
    },
    {
        "question": "47,170,965 ÷ 1,959=？",
        "answer": 4.381640324921056
    },
    {
        "question": "123,280,271 ÷ 164,447=？",
        "answer": 2.8748676253220498
    },
    {
        "question": "94,778 ÷ 5,279=？",
        "answer": 1.2541558780015019
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 1,735,660=？",
        "answer": 8.12595538000746
    },
    {
        "question": "349,346,091 ÷ 120,112,835=？",
        "answer": 0.4636664704297809
    },
    {
        "question": "1,235 × 2,535=？",
        "answer": 6.495644921265039
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 13,850=？",
        "answer": 4.141449773400467
    },
    {
        "question": "163,244,458 ÷ 697=？",
        "answer": 5.369605668199034
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 9,305=？",
        "answer": 5.290935672200705
    },
    {
        "question": "142,466,426 ÷ 41,064=？",
        "answer": 3.540251278208324
    },
    {
        "question": "8,747,744 ÷ 477,540=？",
        "answer": 1.262886309973361
    },
    {
        "question": "1,090 × 3,651=？",
        "answer": 6.599838330890351
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 183,939=？",
        "answer": 7.077587177719252
    },
    {
        "question": "25,498,821 ÷ 315=？",
        "answer": 4.90820954644704
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,536,487=？",
        "answer": 6.186528890103527
    },
    {
        "question": "239,927 ÷ 3,347=？",
        "answer": 1.8554234113549521
    },
    {
        "question": "1,508 ÷ 1,383=？",
        "answer": 0.037579161424444674
    },
    {
        "question": "1,612 × 430=？",
        "answer": 5.840833493048659
    },
    {
        "question": "3,912 × 37,089=？",
        "answer": 8.161643970079478
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 30,506=？",
        "answer": 4.785415261588475
    },
    {
        "question": "4,474 ÷ 1,562=？",
        "answer": 0.4570149502193293
    },
    {
        "question": "3,585,532 ÷ 200,961=？",
        "answer": 1.2514418196766715
    },
    {
        "question": "25,070,775 ÷ 55,957=？",
        "answer": 2.6513133364985606
    },
    {
        "question": "870,481,609 ÷ 4,738,194=？",
        "answer": 2.264146761595931
    },
    {
        "question": "37,670 × 10,742=？",
        "answer": 8.60708076824275
    },
    {
        "question": "191,413,388 ÷ 44,815,791=？",
        "answer": 0.6305412441649673
    },
    {
        "question": "26,089 × 16,545=？",
        "answer": 8.635124204263969
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 418,953=？",
        "answer": 7.49722656801539
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,210=？",
        "answer": 3.6848453616444123
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 263,616=？",
        "answer": 6.883369763839261
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 404=？",
        "answer": 4.5094713521025485
    },
    {
        "question": "23,641 × 268=？",
        "answer": 6.801800637020434
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 37,047,865=？",
        "answer": 8.04588444016766
    },
    {
        "question": "2,729 ÷ 650=？",
        "answer": 0.623090179027041
    },
    {
        "question": "1,696 ÷ 547=？",
        "answer": 0.4914385215872642
    },
    {
        "question": "125,296 ÷ 13,113=？",
        "answer": 0.9802351454140728
    },
    {
        "question": "7,513 × 275=？",
        "answer": 6.3151460826700205
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 316,499=？",
        "answer": 7.207942518270685
    },
    {
        "question": "32,630,305 ÷ 5,487,503=？",
        "answer": 0.7742463625401634
    },
    {
        "question": "26,728,345 ÷ 31,835=？",
        "answer": 2.9240672141855746
    },
    {
        "question": "267,881 ÷ 167,567=？",
        "answer": 0.20375341705750788
    },
    {
        "question": "8,608,239 ÷ 646,384=？",
        "answer": 1.1244237185146329
    },
    {
        "question": "287,586 × 3,392=？",
        "answer": 8.989223583881273
    },
    {
        "question": "42,930,938 ÷ 2,488,308=？",
        "answer": 1.2368662416682876
    },
    {
        "question": "101 × 1,264,234=？",
        "answer": 8.106148839741026
    },
    {
        "question": "37,387,392 ÷ 723,662=？",
        "answer": 1.713189403389412
    },
    {
        "question": "219 × 318,387=？",
        "answer": 7.84339944167106
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,600,661=？",
        "answer": 6.662820233427064
    },
    {
        "question": "139 × 11,420=？",
        "answer": 6.200680904163924
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 423=？",
        "answer": 3.103461622094705
    },
    {
        "question": "6,004 × 1,526=？",
        "answer": 6.961995217190094
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 818,609=？",
        "answer": 7.059204550760089
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,923=？",
        "answer": 3.9966429913554724
    },
    {
        "question": "5,582,584 ÷ 71,823=？",
        "answer": 1.890571725165927
    },
    {
        "question": "5,207 ÷ 309=？",
        "answer": 1.2266290982508576
    },
    {
        "question": "53,359 × 883=？",
        "answer": 7.673168385457736
    },
    {
        "question": "5,455 × 644=？",
        "answer": 6.545680622284173
    },
    {
        "question": "5,739 × 806=？",
        "answer": 6.665171266552049
    },
    {
        "question": "12,123,258 ÷ 98,790=？",
        "answer": 2.0889063622271564
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,176=？",
        "answer": 4.280031744138702
    },
    {
        "question": "880,518 × 1,028=？",
        "answer": 8.956731353123565
    },
    {
        "question": "36,761 × 652=？",
        "answer": 7.379634912607442
    },
    {
        "question": "1,280,090 ÷ 233=？",
        "answer": 3.7398845838791157
    },
    {
        "question": "399,667 ÷ 82,225=？",
        "answer": 0.6866944084382561
    },
    {
        "question": "241 × 9,782=？",
        "answer": 6.3724447010601315
    },
    {
        "question": "125,236,797 ÷ 227=？",
        "answer": 5.741706094573427
    },
    {
        "question": "74,024 ÷ 8,166=？",
        "answer": 0.9573631735724285
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 323=？",
        "answer": 4.384263785722803
    },
    {
        "question": "75,111 × 230=？",
        "answer": 7.23743138007197
    },
    {
        "question": "907,081,666 ÷ 1,432,014=？",
        "answer": 2.8016991251939816
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 19,955,171=？",
        "answer": 7.601085449359479
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 309,157=？",
        "answer": 5.4901790843362885
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 1,515=？",
        "answer": 4.88798280893626
    },
    {
        "question": "667 × 1,803=？",
        "answer": 6.0801215606389505
    },
    {
        "question": "14,717,255 ÷ 18,744=？",
        "answer": 2.8949645392004673
    },
    {
        "question": "610,440,291 ÷ 9,156=？",
        "answer": 4.823937406706918
    },
    {
        "question": "352 ÷ 347=？",
        "answer": 0.0062131886872573115
    },
    {
        "question": "566,543,774 ÷ 72,578,962=？",
        "answer": 0.8924227184806044
    },
    {
        "question": "715 × 1,218=？",
        "answer": 5.9399533300979375
    },
    {
        "question": "413,229 ÷ 47,277=？",
        "answer": 0.9415408820292268
    },
    {
        "question": "22,329 × 5,282=？",
        "answer": 8.071667670582439
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 1,835=？",
        "answer": 4.467756051244033
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 413,605=？",
        "answer": 7.031559128200041
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 28,966=？",
        "answer": 4.461888526343973
    },
    {
        "question": "6,527,072 ÷ 9,293=？",
        "answer": 2.8465624662661275
    },
    {
        "question": "17,293 ÷ 5,130=？",
        "answer": 0.5277529763649214
    },
    {
        "question": "4,034,295 ÷ 656,578=？",
        "answer": 0.788481325275027
    },
    {
        "question": "55,675,603 ÷ 5,227,629=？",
        "answer": 1.027360170875882
    },
    {
        "question": "2,700 × 2,018=？",
        "answer": 6.736284926059879
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 14,658,090=？",
        "answer": 8.245258629961082
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 34,867=？",
        "answer": 5.54241458174664
    },
    {
        "question": "192,043 ÷ 5,232=？",
        "answer": 1.5647307463657807
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 4,868,244=？",
        "answer": 8.231440381615359
    },
    {
        "question": "198 × 46,867=？",
        "answer": 6.967532345080136
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 11,026,108=？",
        "answer": 8.042422242049865
    },
    {
        "question": "31,509,197 ÷ 11,926=？",
        "answer": 3.421942530474255
    },
    {
        "question": "8,785 × 62,060=？",
        "answer": 8.73655353707946
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 5,087=？",
        "answer": 4.405431741967374
    },
    {
        "question": "1,380,523 ÷ 2,614=？",
        "answer": 2.722738063290246
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 9,282=？",
        "answer": 5.009034249241236
    },
    {
        "question": "163,991,821 ÷ 1,216,538=？",
        "answer": 2.129696509215031
    },
    {
        "question": "843 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 0.5814353009396317
    },
    {
        "question": "1,297 × 10,760=？",
        "answer": 7.14475224741445
    },
    {
        "question": "318 × 1,569=？",
        "answer": 5.69805006357137
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 2,565,105=？",
        "answer": 8.021889003940387
    },
    {
        "question": "2,489,327 ÷ 15,044=？",
        "answer": 2.2187186248785684
    },
    {
        "question": "193 × 8,155=？",
        "answer": 6.196981274384068
    },
    {
        "question": "1,110 × 16,706=？",
        "answer": 7.268195455856497
    },
    {
        "question": "432 × 241=？",
        "answer": 5.01750078938978
    },
    {
        "question": "48,317,108 ÷ 175,063=？",
        "answer": 2.4409065653147826
    },
    {
        "question": "2,559,870 ÷ 1,108,030=？",
        "answer": 0.3636663916261191
    },
    {
        "question": "423 × 320,697=？",
        "answer": 8.132435264660703
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 497,600=？",
        "answer": 7.21539431156065
    },
    {
        "question": "466,469 ÷ 139,017=？",
        "answer": 0.5257548750956916
    },
    {
        "question": "84,664,819 ÷ 1,743,663=？",
        "answer": 1.6862404322088393
    },
    {
        "question": "47,318,013 ÷ 425,930=？",
        "answer": 2.0456882689471168
    },
    {
        "question": "62 × 357=？",
        "answer": 4.345059905610447
    },
    {
        "question": "6,407 × 84,120=？",
        "answer": 8.731553988006144
    },
    {
        "question": "1,612,237 ÷ 322,548=？",
        "answer": 0.6988345304233871
    },
    {
        "question": "81,084 ÷ 8,433=？",
        "answer": 0.9829530646454968
    },
    {
        "question": "30,152 × 10,963=？",
        "answer": 8.51924553855011
    },
    {
        "question": "515,866 ÷ 237=？",
        "answer": 3.337788559070071
    },
    {
        "question": "286,281 ÷ 1,334=？",
        "answer": 2.331636695985698
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 9,235,608=？",
        "answer": 8.396829255419089
    },
    {
        "question": "62,735 ÷ 613=？",
        "answer": 2.0100494278104653
    },
    {
        "question": "49,379,555 ÷ 4,483=？",
        "answer": 4.041978432961081
    },
    {
        "question": "9,643 × 763=？",
        "answer": 6.866736704716314
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,215,397=？",
        "answer": 6.808264597890001
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 244,013=？",
        "answer": 5.688442960026763
    },
    {
        "question": "52,207,727 ÷ 2,458,858=？",
        "answer": 1.3270013366869937
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,846,329=？",
        "answer": 7.062167684069224
    },
    {
        "question": "5,480 × 35,769=？",
        "answer": 8.292287357158564
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 1,438,680=？",
        "answer": 7.921392199807525
    },
    {
        "question": "772,997,412 ÷ 269,768=？",
        "answer": 3.457187607713503
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 437,134,415=？",
        "answer": 8.64061499925156
    },
    {
        "question": "81,350 ÷ 308=？",
        "answer": 2.421806840772433
    },
    {
        "question": "287,394 ÷ 74,650=？",
        "answer": 0.5854478849518743
    },
    {
        "question": "197 × 125,585=？",
        "answer": 7.393403996086199
    },
    {
        "question": "104,616 ÷ 63,799=？",
        "answer": 0.21478423918501638
    },
    {
        "question": "33,357 × 2,913=？",
        "answer": 7.987527469578017
    },
    {
        "question": "355 × 927,714=？",
        "answer": 8.517642463578264
    },
    {
        "question": "17,387,423 ÷ 2,868=？",
        "answer": 3.7826560727405503
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 654,134=？",
        "answer": 6.116696718758079
    },
    {
        "question": "63,165 × 4,997=？",
        "answer": 8.499185849918533
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 19,178=？",
        "answer": 5.060954564675372
    },
    {
        "question": "5,056 × 50,242=？",
        "answer": 8.404873984452422
    },
    {
        "question": "56 × 8,677=？",
        "answer": 5.686557624458007
    },
    {
        "question": "86 × 458=？",
        "answer": 4.595363929247437
    },
    {
        "question": "28,872 ÷ 12,442=？",
        "answer": 0.36558667204479994
    },
    {
        "question": "1,065,702 ÷ 1,756=？",
        "answer": 2.7831112692474798
    },
    {
        "question": "6,921 × 1,483=？",
        "answer": 7.0113100002691375
    },
    {
        "question": "167,268,982 ÷ 1,072=？",
        "answer": 5.193220628437836
    },
    {
        "question": "64,013 ÷ 18,071=？",
        "answer": 0.5492859951907219
    },
    {
        "question": "54,134,042 ÷ 6,075,466=？",
        "answer": 0.9498908607799246
    },
    {
        "question": "32,105,356 ÷ 1,720,192=？",
        "answer": 1.2710005663643782
    },
    {
        "question": "38,588,020 ÷ 251,303=？",
        "answer": 2.1862548218095665
    },
    {
        "question": "19,339,306 ÷ 198,946=？",
        "answer": 1.9877056735035241
    },
    {
        "question": "722 × 703,536=？",
        "answer": 8.705823522796452
    },
    {
        "question": "115,974,238 ÷ 584,744=？",
        "answer": 2.2973957534493845
    },
    {
        "question": "142,155,878 ÷ 392=？",
        "answer": 5.559478755009425
    },
    {
        "question": "4,048,654 ÷ 4,596=？",
        "answer": 2.9449306433139206
    },
    {
        "question": "947,422 × 290=？",
        "answer": 8.438941463120607
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,321,702=？",
        "answer": 6.6356548171012415
    },
    {
        "question": "443,689,735 ÷ 2,395=？",
        "answer": 5.267773863446419
    },
    {
        "question": "336,148,411 ÷ 6,949,543=？",
        "answer": 1.6845748162057148
    },
    {
        "question": "46,429,544 ÷ 291,470=？",
        "answer": 2.2022005573716346
    },
    {
        "question": "657,508,324 ÷ 3,868=？",
        "answer": 5.230414789917195
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 6,934,307=？",
        "answer": 7.539973069440432
    },
    {
        "question": "627,514,643 ÷ 72,709,526=？",
        "answer": 0.9360325510476019
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 279=？",
        "answer": 3.144574207609616
    },
    {
        "question": "350,383,180 ÷ 65,964,219=？",
        "answer": 0.7252348250035194
    },
    {
        "question": "132,109 ÷ 128,329=？",
        "answer": 0.012607595126201996
    },
    {
        "question": "1,341,270 ÷ 1,161,939=？",
        "answer": 0.062332882027590165
    },
    {
        "question": "69,192,066 ÷ 209,690=？",
        "answer": 2.5184785786632093
    },
    {
        "question": "155,637 ÷ 107,560=？",
        "answer": 0.16046205736479854
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 30,549,227=？",
        "answer": 8.08706021690877
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 79,085=？",
        "answer": 5.597064123295363
    },
    {
        "question": "44,655,499 ÷ 5,778=？",
        "answer": 3.888097409217084
    },
    {
        "question": "536,506 ÷ 85,452=？",
        "answer": 0.7978523514320217
    },
    {
        "question": "79 × 286,191=？",
        "answer": 7.354283063440281
    },
    {
        "question": "111,137,325 ÷ 71,711,514=？",
        "answer": 0.19027104781747414
    },
    {
        "question": "352,174 × 326=？",
        "answer": 8.059974890162188
    },
    {
        "question": "507,856 ÷ 39,544=？",
        "answer": 1.1086599902824186
    },
    {
        "question": "1,162 ÷ 969=？",
        "answer": 0.07888235100354661
    },
    {
        "question": "40,419,554 ÷ 17,318=？",
        "answer": 3.368093781778716
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 425=？",
        "answer": 4.105510184769974
    },
    {
        "question": "155,303,167 ÷ 2,186,329=？",
        "answer": 1.8514647967078695
    },
    {
        "question": "534,035,382 ÷ 21,542=？",
        "answer": 4.39428401019006
    },
    {
        "question": "335,724,968 ÷ 1,524,220=？",
        "answer": 2.3429359851951865
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 14,473,699=？",
        "answer": 8.97349289329006
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 497,621=？",
        "answer": 5.696898699640314
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 125,834,061=？",
        "answer": 8.798768217004378
    },
    {
        "question": "390,080,387 ÷ 223,953,350=？",
        "answer": 0.24099655159213992
    },
    {
        "question": "918 × 407=？",
        "answer": 5.572437090426463
    },
    {
        "question": "262,181,898 ÷ 44,776,854=？",
        "answer": 0.7675491261093513
    },
    {
        "question": "76,278 ÷ 49,572=？",
        "answer": 0.18716285634987692
    },
    {
        "question": "14,700 × 292=？",
        "answer": 6.632700186196594
    },
    {
        "question": "498,523,906 ÷ 211,477=？",
        "answer": 3.3724228482155993
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 3,857=？",
        "answer": 4.364400889249685
    },
    {
        "question": "93,124 ÷ 438=？",
        "answer": 2.327587511662304
    },
    {
        "question": "4,529,057 ÷ 158,769=？",
        "answer": 1.4552420770818042
    },
    {
        "question": "19,096,505 ÷ 60,100=？",
        "answer": 2.502079418904496
    },
    {
        "question": "656,060 ÷ 10,229=？",
        "answer": 1.8071103810069225
    },
    {
        "question": "194,239 × 2,036=？",
        "answer": 8.597114207188799
    },
    {
        "question": "838,431,264 ÷ 2,453,263=？",
        "answer": 2.533723355334637
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 4,516=？",
        "answer": 4.8852028546312045
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 71,058=？",
        "answer": 6.550582983999497
    },
    {
        "question": "15,763 × 25,148=？",
        "answer": 8.598142327233719
    },
    {
        "question": "6,521 × 4,038=？",
        "answer": 7.42048051481508
    },
    {
        "question": "54,992,686 ÷ 9,019=？",
        "answer": 3.7851465454582125
    },
    {
        "question": "528,900,639 ÷ 119,223=？",
        "answer": 3.64701404596673
    },
    {
        "question": "3,726,821 ÷ 10,364=？",
        "answer": 2.555811129685254
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 537,499=？",
        "answer": 6.20749891531682
    },
    {
        "question": "3,538,607 ÷ 26,582=？",
        "answer": 2.1242446786195344
    },
    {
        "question": "278,286 ÷ 1,666=？",
        "answer": 2.2228163613449006
    },
    {
        "question": "2,084 × 373,998=？",
        "answer": 8.891766994391373
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 401=？",
        "answer": 2.9041743682841634
    },
    {
        "question": "1,950,941 ÷ 535=？",
        "answer": 3.5618903537177915
    },
    {
        "question": "24,604,639 ÷ 637=？",
        "answer": 4.5868775650998534
    },
    {
        "question": "673 × 21,675=？",
        "answer": 7.163974170372224
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 358,051=？",
        "answer": 5.553944891004415
    },
    {
        "question": "347,123,117 ÷ 22,090,352=？",
        "answer": 1.1962809006786603
    },
    {
        "question": "186,139 ÷ 236=？",
        "answer": 2.8969253734400384
    },
    {
        "question": "1,243,477 ÷ 40,213=？",
        "answer": 1.4902712828726834
    },
    {
        "question": "28,712 ÷ 14,368=？",
        "answer": 0.3006671260019543
    },
    {
        "question": "1,780,082 ÷ 40,064=？",
        "answer": 1.6476857014782071
    },
    {
        "question": "7,785 × 49,909=？",
        "answer": 8.589437485130656
    },
    {
        "question": "89,483 ÷ 54,430=？",
        "answer": 0.2159022014741397
    },
    {
        "question": "5,135 × 29,373=？",
        "answer": 8.178488753220439
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 1,481,798=？",
        "answer": 7.833546835956047
    },
    {
        "question": "609,513,598 ÷ 803,744=？",
        "answer": 2.8798656550869075
    },
    {
        "question": "506,558,953 ÷ 70,802=？",
        "answer": 3.854584469823473
    },
    {
        "question": "10,505,546 ÷ 260,862=？",
        "answer": 1.605007809076152
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 509,225=？",
        "answer": 7.462784572522779
    },
    {
        "question": "188 × 628,963=？",
        "answer": 8.072782947223315
    },
    {
        "question": "74 × 146,330=？",
        "answer": 7.034565092327959
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 23,448,836=？",
        "answer": 8.273211276204082
    },
    {
        "question": "3,712 ÷ 369=？",
        "answer": 1.002581601387764
    },
    {
        "question": "108 × 257,697=？",
        "answer": 7.4445331181937355
    },
    {
        "question": "2,632,565 ÷ 35,022=？",
        "answer": 1.876038159351877
    },
    {
        "question": "12,803 × 208=？",
        "answer": 6.425375080453435
    },
    {
        "question": "174,185 ÷ 9,872=？",
        "answer": 1.2466056061769892
    },
    {
        "question": "173,376,971 ÷ 1,867=？",
        "answer": 4.96784709334673
    },
    {
        "question": "1,114,385 ÷ 15,270=？",
        "answer": 1.863196220647828
    },
    {
        "question": "120,807,494 ÷ 56,821=？",
        "answer": 3.3275850028680503
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 490=？",
        "answer": 2.690196080028514
    },
    {
        "question": "619 × 18,057=？",
        "answer": 7.0483362470645705
    },
    {
        "question": "44,789 × 1,664=？",
        "answer": 7.8723246880535545
    },
    {
        "question": "120 × 21,804=？",
        "answer": 6.417717419403284
    },
    {
        "question": "43,303 ÷ 4,875=？",
        "answer": 0.9485433649634579
    },
    {
        "question": "332 × 8,587=？",
        "answer": 6.4549795466027575
    },
    {
        "question": "4,706,374 ÷ 1,559=？",
        "answer": 3.479840320970822
    },
    {
        "question": "2,529,389 ÷ 69,567=？",
        "answer": 1.560612350241541
    },
    {
        "question": "7,882 ÷ 331=？",
        "answer": 1.3768084367538655
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,612=？",
        "answer": 3.4169731726030363
    },
    {
        "question": "156,398 ÷ 373=？",
        "answer": 2.6225223632417562
    },
    {
        "question": "18,016,650 ÷ 1,444=？",
        "answer": 4.096106848583333
    },
    {
        "question": "25,243,801 ÷ 1,058,051=？",
        "answer": 1.3776481459244332
    },
    {
        "question": "199,917,671 ÷ 12,728=？",
        "answer": 4.1960910170674035
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 116,995=？",
        "answer": 5.0681673017563345
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 20,613,488=？",
        "answer": 8.092302735175213
    },
    {
        "question": "188,846 ÷ 2,518=？",
        "answer": 1.875052064576104
    },
    {
        "question": "380,627 ÷ 4,420=？",
        "answer": 1.9350773226289932
    },
    {
        "question": "4,941 ÷ 1,723=？",
        "answer": 0.4575295764413883
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 15,220=？",
        "answer": 4.659535907154217
    },
    {
        "question": "16,685 ÷ 1,266=？",
        "answer": 1.1198925053094753
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 59,179=？",
        "answer": 4.77216762222794
    },
    {
        "question": "437,202 × 520=？",
        "answer": 8.356685483616438
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 100,185,311=？",
        "answer": 8.000804050680063
    },
    {
        "question": "5,660 × 429=？",
        "answer": 6.385273723372996
    },
    {
        "question": "84,733 ÷ 74,000=？",
        "answer": 0.058820863288451694
    },
    {
        "question": "72 × 339,336=？",
        "answer": 7.387962432622173
    },
    {
        "question": "20,099 × 366=？",
        "answer": 6.86665553558676
    },
    {
        "question": "1,378,288 × 252=？",
        "answer": 8.540740515785787
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 826=？",
        "answer": 3.9169800473203824
    },
    {
        "question": "149,837,331 ÷ 2,725=？",
        "answer": 4.740253521887624
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 9,397,384=？",
        "answer": 8.01439965870653
    },
    {
        "question": "49,112 ÷ 1,445=？",
        "answer": 1.5313197732796742
    },
    {
        "question": "73 × 1,596=？",
        "answer": 5.066355747135167
    },
    {
        "question": "831 × 643,997=？",
        "answer": 8.72848486802827
    },
    {
        "question": "33,995,657 ÷ 30,445=？",
        "answer": 3.047907460374992
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 669=？",
        "answer": 4.147645412501743
    },
    {
        "question": "199,298,173 ÷ 1,150,436=？",
        "answer": 2.2386408540633704
    },
    {
        "question": "172,225,833 ÷ 1,307=？",
        "answer": 5.119822706389024
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 9,814=？",
        "answer": 4.690816057980915
    },
    {
        "question": "1,426 × 25,680=？",
        "answer": 7.563714544912663
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 755,127=？",
        "answer": 5.878019998994518
    },
    {
        "question": "179 × 435=？",
        "answer": 4.89134228793453
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 458,415,987=？",
        "answer": 8.661259754999502
    },
    {
        "question": "1,815 × 116,760=？",
        "answer": 8.326170715688107
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 65,075,382=？",
        "answer": 8.591567976531111
    },
    {
        "question": "2,594 × 5,371=？",
        "answer": 7.144025124123561
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 122,088=？",
        "answer": 6.720141434922548
    },
    {
        "question": "92,031,582 ÷ 14,054,636=？",
        "answer": 0.8161172851770565
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 10,636=？",
        "answer": 4.32780832432351
    },
    {
        "question": "153,470 ÷ 9,714=？",
        "answer": 1.1986253939804288
    },
    {
        "question": "1,935 × 37,062=？",
        "answer": 7.855609821076268
    },
    {
        "question": "22,640 × 9,126=？",
        "answer": 8.315156886952876
    },
    {
        "question": "785,843,327 ÷ 5,268,627=？",
        "answer": 2.173638516540611
    },
    {
        "question": "35,229 × 326=？",
        "answer": 7.060117915669116
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 333,089=？",
        "answer": 6.98495828859619
    },
    {
        "question": "10,323 × 3,064=？",
        "answer": 7.500094688301159
    },
    {
        "question": "33,140,798 ÷ 381,901=？",
        "answer": 1.9384121660556881
    },
    {
        "question": "56,111,757 ÷ 209=？",
        "answer": 5.428907581655992
    },
    {
        "question": "438 × 16,091=？",
        "answer": 6.84805714534189
    },
    {
        "question": "669,513 × 256=？",
        "answer": 8.233998979480567
    },
    {
        "question": "811 × 170,226=？",
        "answer": 8.14004674835075
    },
    {
        "question": "4,755 × 14,628=？",
        "answer": 7.84233547293944
    },
    {
        "question": "826,921 ÷ 760,118=？",
        "answer": 0.03658300417791937
    },
    {
        "question": "347,922 ÷ 11,244=？",
        "answer": 1.4905610542339116
    },
    {
        "question": "10,527 × 413=？",
        "answer": 6.63825467459147
    },
    {
        "question": "11,621 × 22,591=？",
        "answer": 8.419178956757984
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 751=？",
        "answer": 4.218062617826375
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,960,706=？",
        "answer": 6.842653290810909
    },
    {
        "question": "298 × 181,385=？",
        "answer": 7.732817633423361
    },
    {
        "question": "1,179 × 991=？",
        "answer": 6.0675874595803645
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,055=？",
        "answer": 3.500373714353374
    },
    {
        "question": "170,466,576 ÷ 2,412=？",
        "answer": 4.849261934512844
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 515=？",
        "answer": 3.41077723337721
    },
    {
        "question": "156 × 35,278=？",
        "answer": 6.740628554247786
    },
    {
        "question": "25,025,891 ÷ 13,020=？",
        "answer": 3.2837785644364605
    },
    {
        "question": "6,884,808 ÷ 966,189=？",
        "answer": 0.8528297446159622
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 93,570=？",
        "answer": 6.71149931897105
    },
    {
        "question": "1,549 × 4,872=？",
        "answer": 6.877758697384025
    },
    {
        "question": "69,378,870 ÷ 22,426,486=？",
        "answer": 0.4904659926151799
    },
    {
        "question": "1,894 ÷ 246=？",
        "answer": 0.8864448675638755
    },
    {
        "question": "6,747 ÷ 5,091=？",
        "answer": 0.1223076131179564
    },
    {
        "question": "151 × 172,967=？",
        "answer": 7.416940200219799
    },
    {
        "question": "93,105,814 ÷ 2,140,098=？",
        "answer": 1.6385431402359736
    },
    {
        "question": "102,492 × 2,193=？",
        "answer": 8.351728599591766
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,709,558=？",
        "answer": 6.23288383964718
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 11,119=？",
        "answer": 5.250185712886612
    },
    {
        "question": "220,905 ÷ 355=？",
        "answer": 2.793977192820119
    },
    {
        "question": "523 × 14,478=？",
        "answer": 6.879210261159704
    },
    {
        "question": "231,802,083 ÷ 241,189=？",
        "answer": 2.982759837381563
    },
    {
        "question": "210 × 116,888=？",
        "answer": 7.389989222480123
    },
    {
        "question": "60,370,849 ÷ 1,077=？",
        "answer": 4.74861158011591
    },
    {
        "question": "6,866 ÷ 3,834=？",
        "answer": 0.25305169054768756
    },
    {
        "question": "860,215 ÷ 90,379=？",
        "answer": 0.9785394795316006
    },
    {
        "question": "123,102,739 ÷ 1,081,065=？",
        "answer": 2.056415908881735
    },
    {
        "question": "86,155,891 ÷ 2,609=？",
        "answer": 4.518810899042773
    },
    {
        "question": "658,212,840 ÷ 44,848,237=？",
        "answer": 1.1666209745366654
    },
    {
        "question": "243,714 × 895=？",
        "answer": 8.338703512995133
    },
    {
        "question": "558,604,625 ÷ 942=？",
        "answer": 5.773053624353819
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 320=？",
        "answer": 3.709269960975831
    },
    {
        "question": "123,489,983 ÷ 9,407,518=？",
        "answer": 1.1181566728847017
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 299=？",
        "answer": 2.4756711883244296
    },
    {
        "question": "30,430 ÷ 361=？",
        "answer": 1.9257947504525093
    },
    {
        "question": "14,800,225 ÷ 664=？",
        "answer": 4.348100238426647
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 706,372=？",
        "answer": 6.548003480173791
    },
    {
        "question": "302,069 ÷ 1,823=？",
        "answer": 2.219319489191141
    },
    {
        "question": "1,047,220 ÷ 113,121=？",
        "answer": 0.9664946921849374
    },
    {
        "question": "724,109,379 ÷ 567=？",
        "answer": 6.106221113807334
    },
    {
        "question": "83 × 234=？",
        "answer": 4.288293949786217
    },
    {
        "question": "153,431,634 ÷ 374,456=？",
        "answer": 2.6125141163839247
    },
    {
        "question": "21,441 ÷ 5,193=？",
        "answer": 0.6158267142257732
    },
    {
        "question": "23,364,708 ÷ 58,524=？",
        "answer": 2.6012263561679143
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 548,251=？",
        "answer": 5.738979432495636
    },
    {
        "question": "402 × 1,393=？",
        "answer": 5.748177169508433
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 8,815=？",
        "answer": 5.4365840104696135
    },
    {
        "question": "2,719,358 × 286=？",
        "answer": 8.890832418792995
    },
    {
        "question": "569,310,992 ÷ 20,978,715=？",
        "answer": 1.4335706860311932
    },
    {
        "question": "13,987 ÷ 2,281=？",
        "answer": 0.7875992896040197
    },
    {
        "question": "24,553,504 ÷ 7,808=？",
        "answer": 3.497573673848198
    },
    {
        "question": "318,133,107 ÷ 343=？",
        "answer": 5.96731474692452
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 55,274=？",
        "answer": 4.742520894201264
    },
    {
        "question": "20,131,854 ÷ 2,428=？",
        "answer": 3.9186350897478563
    },
    {
        "question": "9,001 ÷ 1,002=？",
        "answer": 0.9534230401699001
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 13,251=？",
        "answer": 5.973507002697129
    },
    {
        "question": "26,869,118 ÷ 23,710=？",
        "answer": 3.0543218566299006
    },
    {
        "question": "418 × 315=？",
        "answer": 5.1194868355646355
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,183=？",
        "answer": 3.550105999347593
    },
    {
        "question": "73,110 ÷ 2,554=？",
        "answer": 1.4567558909769902
    },
    {
        "question": "776 × 33,295=？",
        "answer": 7.412240740486752
    },
    {
        "question": "124,160,830 ÷ 85,983=？",
        "answer": 3.159572013281272
    },
    {
        "question": "310,595 ÷ 40,657=？",
        "answer": 0.8830591303686381
    },
    {
        "question": "228 × 37,678=？",
        "answer": 6.9340226887854035
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,326,945=？",
        "answer": 7.212904929760363
    },
    {
        "question": "28,094,977 ÷ 833,673=？",
        "answer": 1.527632944578516
    },
    {
        "question": "38,565 ÷ 4,678=？",
        "answer": 0.9161331182254076
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 100,674=？",
        "answer": 6.5711190484985496
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 221,395,368=？",
        "answer": 8.947228521723043
    },
    {
        "question": "676,057,662 ÷ 47,590=？",
        "answer": 4.152468034368377
    },
    {
        "question": "12,225,549 ÷ 3,162=？",
        "answer": 3.58730650504749
    },
    {
        "question": "8,017,906 ÷ 193,769=？",
        "answer": 1.6167766624118984
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 87,602=？",
        "answer": 5.419635276173685
    },
    {
        "question": "20,052,417 ÷ 200=？",
        "answer": 5.001136731741024
    },
    {
        "question": "122,449 ÷ 12,087=？",
        "answer": 1.0056367206294974
    },
    {
        "question": "62,301,359 ÷ 44,159,456=？",
        "answer": 0.14947380548692304
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 644=？",
        "answer": 4.891671237676262
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 78,180,566=？",
        "answer": 8.592068814584037
    },
    {
        "question": "514,836,599 ÷ 266,702,725=？",
        "answer": 0.28564195964619987
    },
    {
        "question": "155,518 ÷ 31,833=？",
        "answer": 0.6889030932294288
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 33,187=？",
        "answer": 4.9980892500528755
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 13,788,238=？",
        "answer": 8.218690017243835
    },
    {
        "question": "575,847 × 348=？",
        "answer": 8.301886352574144
    },
    {
        "question": "2,473,674 ÷ 5,593=？",
        "answer": 2.6456976450311642
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 2,950,639=？",
        "answer": 7.932314076291384
    },
    {
        "question": "228,486,540 ÷ 1,049,766=？",
        "answer": 2.3377681184852657
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 1,833=？",
        "answer": 4.740283719681879
    },
    {
        "question": "880,303 × 895=？",
        "answer": 8.896455217214477
    },
    {
        "question": "143,650 × 580=？",
        "answer": 7.920733623890904
    },
    {
        "question": "3,065,430 ÷ 567=？",
        "answer": 3.7329083444407316
    },
    {
        "question": "90,988 × 1,894=？",
        "answer": 8.23636409360999
    },
    {
        "question": "119,960,743 ÷ 800,098=？",
        "answer": 2.175895962174784
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 18,762=？",
        "answer": 4.9722491359625955
    },
    {
        "question": "376,238,708 ÷ 1,007=？",
        "answer": 5.5724340038240125
    },
    {
        "question": "1,582,095 ÷ 23,689=？",
        "answer": 1.82468583007039
    },
    {
        "question": "214 × 11,746=？",
        "answer": 6.400303769856129
    },
    {
        "question": "4,281 × 9,184=？",
        "answer": 7.594577102888207
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 21,569=？",
        "answer": 4.333830010445646
    },
    {
        "question": "234 × 120,275=？",
        "answer": 7.449391222984745
    },
    {
        "question": "6,082,820 ÷ 2,856,459=？",
        "answer": 0.32827697038787074
    },
    {
        "question": "201,022 ÷ 210=？",
        "answer": 2.981024294804769
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 2,257=？",
        "answer": 4.307774068517087
    },
    {
        "question": "66,393,397 ÷ 30,305=？",
        "answer": 3.3406106014277595
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,608,605=？",
        "answer": 7.051547454293147
    },
    {
        "question": "42,529 × 454=？",
        "answer": 7.285741023965491
    },
    {
        "question": "15,027 × 49,513=？",
        "answer": 8.87159152750483
    },
    {
        "question": "419,109 ÷ 327,016=？",
        "answer": 0.1077579850056167
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 20,243=？",
        "answer": 4.607304870773328
    },
    {
        "question": "508,379,467 ÷ 316=？",
        "answer": 6.206500918845241
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 17,914=？",
        "answer": 5.36713592218528
    },
    {
        "question": "103,169,151 ÷ 20,754,863=？",
        "answer": 0.696429985652677
    },
    {
        "question": "2,700,656 ÷ 300=？",
        "answer": 3.9543480140971035
    },
    {
        "question": "1,004,558 ÷ 6,778=？",
        "answer": 2.1708734520958677
    },
    {
        "question": "280,491,381 ÷ 2,096=？",
        "answer": 5.126528242390474
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 28,527=？",
        "answer": 5.1542261064539705
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 5,374=？",
        "answer": 4.6333876490890935
    },
    {
        "question": "10,165 × 576=？",
        "answer": 6.767529866397269
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 514,479=？",
        "answer": 6.825311004738134
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,474=？",
        "answer": 3.393399695293102
    },
    {
        "question": "49,470 ÷ 13,622=？",
        "answer": 0.5601010344175913
    },
    {
        "question": "235,031 ÷ 374=？",
        "answer": 2.798253546203271
    },
    {
        "question": "1,031,098 ÷ 190,905=？",
        "answer": 0.7324826412997992
    },
    {
        "question": "95,453 ÷ 50,517=？",
        "answer": 0.27635203076132514
    },
    {
        "question": "65,765 × 10,545=？",
        "answer": 8.841041408526307
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,951,055=？",
        "answer": 6.7710072993604555
    },
    {
        "question": "116,371 ÷ 108,407=？",
        "answer": 0.030787440174275794
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 154,768=？",
        "answer": 5.888651174765289
    },
    {
        "question": "534,572,290 ÷ 205=？",
        "answer": 6.416252581931932
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 10,621,990=？",
        "answer": 7.026205888219734
    },
    {
        "question": "9,221,732 ÷ 411=？",
        "answer": 4.350970674817513
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 469,523=？",
        "answer": 6.847748130478738
    },
    {
        "question": "25,091 ÷ 1,843=？",
        "answer": 1.1339926352157998
    },
    {
        "question": "398,755,883 ÷ 24,104=？",
        "answer": 4.218617984761917
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,062,871=？",
        "answer": 7.043867848275471
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 201=？",
        "answer": 3.9159799141402245
    },
    {
        "question": "8,325 ÷ 785=？",
        "answer": 1.025514585433105
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 154,746,451=？",
        "answer": 8.18962069757073
    },
    {
        "question": "4,563,182 ÷ 1,820,411=？",
        "answer": 0.39909833960781826
    },
    {
        "question": "8,106 × 9,505=？",
        "answer": 7.886758720607136
    },
    {
        "question": "87,273,290 ÷ 1,062,616=？",
        "answer": 1.9145049972939627
    },
    {
        "question": "16,635 × 28,065=？",
        "answer": 8.669187851760533
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 78,926,712=？",
        "answer": 8.198254006615809
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 243,119=？",
        "answer": 6.340061410169589
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 6,105,804=？",
        "answer": 7.0867728547349325
    },
    {
        "question": "49,883,628 ÷ 8,944,159=？",
        "answer": 0.7464185208284126
    },
    {
        "question": "200,867,910 ÷ 177,042=？",
        "answer": 3.054834253759422
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 134,947=？",
        "answer": 5.13016323422097
    },
    {
        "question": "30,480,317 ÷ 1,105=？",
        "answer": 4.440657201399546
    },
    {
        "question": "61,983,051 ÷ 1,008=？",
        "answer": 4.788812417655207
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 1,775,499=？",
        "answer": 8.203562941472846
    },
    {
        "question": "821,594,172 ÷ 23,505=？",
        "answer": 4.543497094396477
    },
    {
        "question": "82,929 × 3,390=？",
        "answer": 8.448906126673545
    },
    {
        "question": "146,315,476 ÷ 189,806=？",
        "answer": 2.8869803276233
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 378=？",
        "answer": 3.0546130545568877
    },
    {
        "question": "562,644 ÷ 127,247=？",
        "answer": 0.6455861398238432
    },
    {
        "question": "8,070 ÷ 525=？",
        "answer": 1.1867142313161136
    },
    {
        "question": "44,562 ÷ 1,147=？",
        "answer": 1.5894012563979734
    },
    {
        "question": "5,329 × 37,547=？",
        "answer": 8.30122096289949
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 9,850,642=？",
        "answer": 8.034857221033649
    },
    {
        "question": "279,777,864 ÷ 16,858,860=？",
        "answer": 1.2199851459852569
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 6,387,317=？",
        "answer": 8.252476501897327
    },
    {
        "question": "3,498 ÷ 475=？",
        "answer": 0.8671261955177911
    },
    {
        "question": "586,321,960 ÷ 4,206=？",
        "answer": 5.144266892128576
    },
    {
        "question": "116 × 2,542,360=？",
        "answer": 8.469695036209506
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,608=？",
        "answer": 3.683407299132095
    },
    {
        "question": "78 × 1,686,731=？",
        "answer": 8.119140429481867
    },
    {
        "question": "423,272,466 ÷ 10,125=？",
        "answer": 4.621224986520714
    },
    {
        "question": "26,511 × 37,597=？",
        "answer": 8.998579302102893
    },
    {
        "question": "1,179,663 ÷ 66,958=？",
        "answer": 1.245955484999047
    },
    {
        "question": "94,448,044 ÷ 20,215,594=？",
        "answer": 0.6695064613559079
    },
    {
        "question": "16,808,941 ÷ 815,393=？",
        "answer": 1.3141733740070067
    },
    {
        "question": "34,703 ÷ 26,502=？",
        "answer": 0.11708837059922353
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,223,445=？",
        "answer": 6.648056386704644
    },
    {
        "question": "772,781,822 ÷ 9,679,457=？",
        "answer": 1.9022059028428164
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 367=？",
        "answer": 2.5646660642520893
    },
    {
        "question": "10,887,584 ÷ 228,755=？",
        "answer": 1.6775609232915947
    },
    {
        "question": "33,106,447 ÷ 4,259,261=？",
        "answer": 0.8905783208689647
    },
    {
        "question": "470,939,279 ÷ 26,690,072=？",
        "answer": 1.2466151692141076
    },
    {
        "question": "1,139 ÷ 1,054=？",
        "answer": 0.03368311320257253
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 3,236=？",
        "answer": 4.355106552954491
    },
    {
        "question": "102,505 ÷ 4,503=？",
        "answer": 1.3572431030088257
    },
    {
        "question": "11,325 × 9,113=？",
        "answer": 8.013699580958365
    },
    {
        "question": "492 × 333,863=？",
        "answer": 8.215533394279934
    },
    {
        "question": "294 × 121,443=？",
        "answer": 7.552719817449671
    },
    {
        "question": "14,326,247 ÷ 392,547=？",
        "answer": 1.5622407719365323
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 217,465=？",
        "answer": 6.752362717169469
    },
    {
        "question": "546,216,714 ÷ 1,172=？",
        "answer": 5.668437373552091
    },
    {
        "question": "18,436 ÷ 1,613=？",
        "answer": 1.0580323320635212
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 101,471=？",
        "answer": 5.483463195101525
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 305,087=？",
        "answer": 6.598367054709815
    },
    {
        "question": "57,307,373 ÷ 15,244,695=？",
        "answer": 0.5750917607513962
    },
    {
        "question": "39,681 ÷ 8,719=？",
        "answer": 0.6581159306021185
    },
    {
        "question": "31,856 ÷ 2,794=？",
        "answer": 1.0569648409051713
    },
    {
        "question": "7,677,677 ÷ 1,424=？",
        "answer": 3.7317198480887352
    },
    {
        "question": "240 × 523,688=？",
        "answer": 8.09928386412657
    },
    {
        "question": "78,765 × 390=？",
        "answer": 7.487397884369237
    },
    {
        "question": "253 × 1,127=？",
        "answer": 5.4550444372219244
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 196,162=？",
        "answer": 5.7697361354970935
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 108,418=？",
        "answer": 6.526463085369742
    },
    {
        "question": "317,487 ÷ 1,853=？",
        "answer": 2.233850527808776
    },
    {
        "question": "608 × 8,439=？",
        "answer": 6.710194566157599
    },
    {
        "question": "7,876,823 ÷ 4,264=？",
        "answer": 3.2665338905340855
    },
    {
        "question": "3,204,093 ÷ 5,134=？",
        "answer": 2.795249248819801
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 77,301=？",
        "answer": 6.092305094836511
    },
    {
        "question": "3,238 × 68,984=？",
        "answer": 8.349025217509933
    },
    {
        "question": "392 × 281,791=？",
        "answer": 8.043213185273018
    },
    {
        "question": "1,280 × 2,576=？",
        "answer": 6.518155828335643
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 10,239=？",
        "answer": 4.70922754733432
    },
    {
        "question": "696,104,434 ÷ 2,105=？",
        "answer": 5.519422299938189
    },
    {
        "question": "19,845,545 ÷ 1,429,614=？",
        "answer": 1.1424442375374633
    },
    {
        "question": "236 × 19,233=？",
        "answer": 6.656959034573501
    },
    {
        "question": "88 × 1,291,892=？",
        "answer": 8.055708881037926
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 16,406=？",
        "answer": 4.913972711550971
    },
    {
        "question": "197 × 68,364=？",
        "answer": 7.1292936916658975
    },
    {
        "question": "226,201,109 ÷ 600,409=？",
        "answer": 2.576047536217935
    },
    {
        "question": "268,950,021 ÷ 2,241,663=？",
        "answer": 2.07910125894415
    },
    {
        "question": "150,292 ÷ 20,535=？",
        "answer": 0.8644411566419271
    },
    {
        "question": "348,296,607 ÷ 253,551,529=？",
        "answer": 0.1378830098817332
    },
    {
        "question": "183,060 ÷ 491=？",
        "answer": 2.571511965903082
    },
    {
        "question": "497,391 ÷ 8,114=？",
        "answer": 1.7874629193313933
    },
    {
        "question": "414,946 ÷ 1,746=？",
        "answer": 2.3759473430583453
    },
    {
        "question": "2,812 × 243=？",
        "answer": 5.8346215899460985
    },
    {
        "question": "206,582,405 ÷ 282,464=？",
        "answer": 2.864130224198834
    },
    {
        "question": "12,495 ÷ 1,516=？",
        "answer": 0.9160370591664342
    },
    {
        "question": "836,963 ÷ 33,193=？",
        "answer": 1.4016597534302508
    },
    {
        "question": "94,139 × 8,033=？",
        "answer": 8.878647347626266
    },
    {
        "question": "1,522,804 ÷ 1,216,857=？",
        "answer": 0.0974044641816412
    },
    {
        "question": "7,552 ÷ 995=？",
        "answer": 0.8802389005442871
    },
    {
        "question": "226 × 754=？",
        "answer": 5.231479785017175
    },
    {
        "question": "436,745,701 ÷ 4,619=？",
        "answer": 4.97568067655744
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 1,553,407=？",
        "answer": 8.38161695602146
    },
    {
        "question": "2,218,442 ÷ 26,870=？",
        "answer": 1.916780412366881
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 16,492=？",
        "answer": 5.66443135747154
    },
    {
        "question": "851,405 ÷ 297,776=？",
        "answer": 0.4562465045274259
    },
    {
        "question": "43,647 ÷ 14,901=？",
        "answer": 0.46673898388293666
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 603,058=？",
        "answer": 6.625457123080798
    },
    {
        "question": "90,386,858 ÷ 1,122=？",
        "answer": 4.906112432924819
    },
    {
        "question": "6,752,256 ÷ 3,628=？",
        "answer": 3.2697816210588884
    },
    {
        "question": "508,938,282 ÷ 2,128=？",
        "answer": 5.37869349582182
    },
    {
        "question": "149,709 ÷ 970=？",
        "answer": 2.1884761751806643
    },
    {
        "question": "35,788 ÷ 1,012=？",
        "answer": 1.5485569161674828
    },
    {
        "question": "1,421 × 24,759=？",
        "answer": 7.546327177756478
    },
    {
        "question": "733 × 1,870=？",
        "answer": 6.136945581177627
    },
    {
        "question": "117 × 336=？",
        "answer": 4.594525139136006
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 33,626,782=？",
        "answer": 8.304836558777312
    },
    {
        "question": "3,510 × 116,236=？",
        "answer": 8.610647772747033
    },
    {
        "question": "1,784,305 ÷ 257,849=？",
        "answer": 0.8401036410219401
    },
    {
        "question": "701,897 ÷ 802=？",
        "answer": 2.9420990179003392
    },
    {
        "question": "12,810,900 ÷ 1,119,594=？",
        "answer": 1.0585190787866534
    },
    {
        "question": "10,284,338 ÷ 243,697=？",
        "answer": 1.6253261586221563
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 569,526,698=？",
        "answer": 8.755514087541206
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 906=？",
        "answer": 3.8602181846687564
    },
    {
        "question": "675 × 18,181=？",
        "answer": 7.088921539645359
    },
    {
        "question": "1,606 × 9,324=？",
        "answer": 7.175347805791201
    },
    {
        "question": "9,799,887 ÷ 2,183,188=？",
        "answer": 0.6521299324348887
    },
    {
        "question": "1,558 ÷ 1,018=？",
        "answer": 0.1848196753358057
    },
    {
        "question": "98,525 × 1,334=？",
        "answer": 8.11870227311817
    },
    {
        "question": "127,054,575 ÷ 100,468=？",
        "answer": 3.1019625508915785
    },
    {
        "question": "537,333 ÷ 19,910=？",
        "answer": 1.4311722533084659
    },
    {
        "question": "576,370,761 ÷ 253,421,780=？",
        "answer": 0.3568580041424446
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 3,965,355=？",
        "answer": 7.20034206511011
    },
    {
        "question": "5,320 × 6,512=？",
        "answer": 7.539626024176193
    },
    {
        "question": "107,451,532 ÷ 2,166,215=？",
        "answer": 1.6955110530750765
    },
    {
        "question": "11,518,459 ÷ 1,070=？",
        "answer": 4.032010603089279
    },
    {
        "question": "361,333 × 1,964=？",
        "answer": 8.851049110292786
    },
    {
        "question": "265,680,172 ÷ 3,185,757=？",
        "answer": 1.9211464977040318
    },
    {
        "question": "997,350,766 ÷ 405,671=？",
        "answer": 3.3906739629390117
    },
    {
        "question": "22,292 ÷ 6,405=？",
        "answer": 0.5416299003034575
    },
    {
        "question": "30,221,436 ÷ 2,804=？",
        "answer": 4.03253708711008
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 17,667,291=？",
        "answer": 8.361113314719884
    },
    {
        "question": "204,704,523 ÷ 456,021=？",
        "answer": 2.652142596011051
    },
    {
        "question": "329 × 979,822=？",
        "answer": 8.508343084418865
    },
    {
        "question": "17,328,173 ÷ 27,731=？",
        "answer": 2.7957872443520633
    },
    {
        "question": "829 × 19,906=？",
        "answer": 7.217538530283658
    },
    {
        "question": "267,267,308 ÷ 28,478,555=？",
        "answer": 0.9724278898764959
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 911=？",
        "answer": 5.00873639964318
    },
    {
        "question": "4,498 ÷ 266=？",
        "answer": 1.2281378144685464
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 445,422=？",
        "answer": 6.551861650616419
    },
    {
        "question": "28,942 ÷ 1,068=？",
        "answer": 1.4329572864937896
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 5,266=？",
        "answer": 5.043700149503969
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 91,094=？",
        "answer": 6.51579227342958
    },
    {
        "question": "28,833,739 ÷ 251=？",
        "answer": 5.06022724146835
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 4,749,554=？",
        "answer": 7.375622834080257
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 1,071,056=？",
        "answer": 7.642596035166137
    },
    {
        "question": "2,766,624 ÷ 1,693=？",
        "answer": 3.213293181942376
    },
    {
        "question": "11,285,148 ÷ 307=？",
        "answer": 4.565368883564583
    },
    {
        "question": "826,988,657 ÷ 585,307=？",
        "answer": 3.1501158346922726
    },
    {
        "question": "11,698,254 ÷ 4,441=？",
        "answer": 3.420640273636567
    },
    {
        "question": "8,257,112 ÷ 11,054=？",
        "answer": 2.873308715188485
    },
    {
        "question": "777,440,599 ÷ 57,189=？",
        "answer": 4.133354713741109
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,264,636=？",
        "answer": 6.354998406836593
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 13,620=？",
        "answer": 4.979275147591023
    },
    {
        "question": "44,350,065 ÷ 215,496=？",
        "answer": 2.3134550474040787
    },
    {
        "question": "2,730,067 ÷ 1,908,530=？",
        "answer": 0.1554743144471554
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,763,844=？",
        "answer": 6.246460172102434
    },
    {
        "question": "115 × 6,737,213=？",
        "answer": 8.889178118337481
    },
    {
        "question": "171,414,706 ÷ 497,096=？",
        "answer": 2.537607809650967
    },
    {
        "question": "4,389,427 ÷ 8,769=？",
        "answer": 2.699457760647931
    },
    {
        "question": "410,790 ÷ 193,875=？",
        "answer": 0.3260980520547002
    },
    {
        "question": "41,519,274 ÷ 1,091,590=？",
        "answer": 1.580190202429898
    },
    {
        "question": "48 × 93,385=？",
        "answer": 6.651518360496571
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 188,251=？",
        "answer": 6.937495123557385
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 2,606=？",
        "answer": 4.457367096534791
    },
    {
        "question": "155,089,568 ÷ 504=？",
        "answer": 5.488152049811636
    },
    {
        "question": "463,080,377 ÷ 2,162,890=？",
        "answer": 2.3306219454800803
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,403,630=？",
        "answer": 7.050342628877306
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,039,889=？",
        "answer": 6.715956988576873
    },
    {
        "question": "77,748 ÷ 7,614=？",
        "answer": 1.0090763535146032
    },
    {
        "question": "11,817,080 ÷ 100,696=？",
        "answer": 2.06949795646357
    },
    {
        "question": "196 × 414,006=？",
        "answer": 7.909262706554692
    },
    {
        "question": "839,238,240 ÷ 341,977,224=？",
        "answer": 0.38988808171676403
    },
    {
        "question": "285,891,468 ÷ 23,190,708=？",
        "answer": 1.0908871870668024
    },
    {
        "question": "248 ÷ 228=？",
        "answer": 0.0365168338257625
    },
    {
        "question": "787,798,274 ÷ 189,029=？",
        "answer": 3.6198865881323585
    },
    {
        "question": "17,463 ÷ 13,625=？",
        "answer": 0.10778234305586294
    },
    {
        "question": "116,638 × 480=？",
        "answer": 7.748081301535266
    },
    {
        "question": "148,355 ÷ 3,721=？",
        "answer": 1.6006425178798376
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 1,400,095=？",
        "answer": 7.818255362596827
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 36,187=？",
        "answer": 4.8595825760794344
    },
    {
        "question": "7,519 × 2,646=？",
        "answer": 7.29874992467711
    },
    {
        "question": "829,918,743 ÷ 567,785=？",
        "answer": 3.164851657910877
    },
    {
        "question": "1,033 × 82,824=？",
        "answer": 7.932256522522714
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 10,098=？",
        "answer": 5.004235366359468
    },
    {
        "question": "4,155 ÷ 1,164=？",
        "answer": 0.5526180478062601
    },
    {
        "question": "160,002,732 ÷ 10,389=？",
        "answer": 4.18755365190177
    },
    {
        "question": "96,806,013 ÷ 2,474,919=？",
        "answer": 1.5923413441116208
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 394=？",
        "answer": 4.285692301854088
    },
    {
        "question": "221,862,864 ÷ 126,125=？",
        "answer": 3.2452834356973828
    },
    {
        "question": "39,962,649 ÷ 286=？",
        "answer": 5.145288235412688
    },
    {
        "question": "598,519 × 1,382=？",
        "answer": 8.91758598468818
    },
    {
        "question": "73,866,034 ÷ 14,022=？",
        "answer": 3.7216348188205313
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 1,385,844=？",
        "answer": 7.503442181912263
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 57,020=？",
        "answer": 5.534178463357085
    },
    {
        "question": "300,482 × 2,542=？",
        "answer": 8.882994007465857
    },
    {
        "question": "123,670,325 ÷ 553=？",
        "answer": 5.349540370791333
    },
    {
        "question": "263 × 111,489=？",
        "answer": 7.467187768564834
    },
    {
        "question": "2,341 × 4,940=？",
        "answer": 7.063128362620271
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,026=？",
        "answer": 3.607669436688243
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 12,146=？",
        "answer": 4.385463272450526
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 686,926=？",
        "answer": 6.137939950303384
    },
    {
        "question": "461,995,849 ÷ 296=？",
        "answer": 6.19334636240954
    },
    {
        "question": "3,185,421 ÷ 287,457=？",
        "answer": 1.044593950016851
    },
    {
        "question": "10,871,167 ÷ 552,735=？",
        "answer": 1.293759201688123
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 1,780,416=？",
        "answer": 7.5727407832204365
    },
    {
        "question": "3,936 ÷ 287=？",
        "answer": 1.1371731930253115
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 193,796,880=？",
        "answer": 8.287346780920677
    },
    {
        "question": "84,101,268 ÷ 345=？",
        "answer": 5.386983448658665
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 24,974,937=？",
        "answer": 7.3975044013790265
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 11,543=？",
        "answer": 4.965408682650719
    },
    {
        "question": "1,584,606 ÷ 414=？",
        "answer": 3.5829209548985204
    },
    {
        "question": "8,431,821 ÷ 1,728=？",
        "answer": 3.6883776401409887
    },
    {
        "question": "850,442,054 ÷ 181,762=？",
        "answer": 3.670141634951608
    },
    {
        "question": "1,940 × 460=？",
        "answer": 5.9505595616118
    },
    {
        "question": "2,582 × 565=？",
        "answer": 6.16400468574984
    },
    {
        "question": "435,653,574 ÷ 48,967=？",
        "answer": 3.949237783779119
    },
    {
        "question": "147,857,904 ÷ 132,087=？",
        "answer": 3.048984468982162
    },
    {
        "question": "890,336,990 ÷ 1,889,641=？",
        "answer": 2.6731751136139077
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 316,057=？",
        "answer": 5.499765413482663
    },
    {
        "question": "1,153,407 ÷ 5,000=？",
        "answer": 2.363012578469871
    },
    {
        "question": "245,159,512 ÷ 485,431=？",
        "answer": 2.7033212409362344
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 470=？",
        "answer": 2.6720978579357175
    },
    {
        "question": "220,269 ÷ 3,807=？",
        "answer": 1.7623705033310677
    },
    {
        "question": "753 × 436,195=？",
        "answer": 8.516475659257102
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 26,752,547=？",
        "answer": 7.42736513571754
    },
    {
        "question": "1,504 ÷ 1,104=？",
        "answer": 0.13427876286244336
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 4,848=？",
        "answer": 3.986592606822211
    },
    {
        "question": "609,799 × 591=？",
        "answer": 8.55677418871836
    },
    {
        "question": "532,907 ÷ 402=？",
        "answer": 3.122425371869159
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 87,458=？",
        "answer": 5.418920796343922
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 904,515=？",
        "answer": 7.132507032422009
    },
    {
        "question": "5,475,038 ÷ 4,082=？",
        "answer": 3.1275141374029793
    },
    {
        "question": "6,951 × 7,010=？",
        "answer": 7.6877653064762965
    },
    {
        "question": "443,243,111 ÷ 245=？",
        "answer": 6.257475910042803
    },
    {
        "question": "197 × 52,622=？",
        "answer": 7.0156335764193996
    },
    {
        "question": "981,298,113 ÷ 1,406,860=？",
        "answer": 2.8435500818098114
    },
    {
        "question": "215,135 × 625=？",
        "answer": 8.128591088216622
    },
    {
        "question": "117 × 4,043,408=？",
        "answer": 8.674933427766586
    },
    {
        "question": "36,589,310 ÷ 719=？",
        "answer": 4.7066253292699445
    },
    {
        "question": "230 × 3,690,482=？",
        "answer": 8.928810927453018
    },
    {
        "question": "285,386,258 ÷ 1,398=？",
        "answer": 5.309925885601425
    },
    {
        "question": "880 × 18,725=？",
        "answer": 7.216904498521672
    },
    {
        "question": "606 × 202,542=？",
        "answer": 8.088987718269605
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 5,651=？",
        "answer": 4.6552152942898415
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 11,331,402=？",
        "answer": 7.957373634118764
    },
    {
        "question": "1,028 ÷ 255=？",
        "answer": 0.6054529342253018
    },
    {
        "question": "60,207,107 ÷ 28,744=？",
        "answer": 3.3211005553121407
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 52,963,510=？",
        "answer": 7.723976758967873
    },
    {
        "question": "4,502,718 ÷ 1,455,088=？",
        "answer": 0.49058548932002805
    },
    {
        "question": "615 × 1,485=？",
        "answer": 5.960601569428648
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 17,906,450=？",
        "answer": 7.9519794987150245
    },
    {
        "question": "88,891 ÷ 2,830=？",
        "answer": 1.497071356399791
    },
    {
        "question": "934,094,790 ÷ 5,155,569=？",
        "answer": 2.258114346119496
    },
    {
        "question": "97,289,349 ÷ 8,637=？",
        "answer": 4.0517023777752215
    },
    {
        "question": "33,826,878 ÷ 231,013=？",
        "answer": 2.165625497072725
    },
    {
        "question": "187,912 × 329=？",
        "answer": 7.791150412842282
    },
    {
        "question": "62,670 × 687=？",
        "answer": 7.634016431759521
    },
    {
        "question": "314,671,946 ÷ 9,109,097=？",
        "answer": 1.5383826991419411
    },
    {
        "question": "140,888,497 ÷ 2,910=？",
        "answer": 4.684982547108835
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 6,924=？",
        "answer": 3.8403570592033565
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 1,659=？",
        "answer": 4.333789738331197
    },
    {
        "question": "1,051 × 487=？",
        "answer": 5.709131677242876
    },
    {
        "question": "503 × 1,169=？",
        "answer": 5.7693824962177676
    },
    {
        "question": "4,645 ÷ 342=？",
        "answer": 1.1329596122735255
    },
    {
        "question": "8,580,855 ÷ 85,008=？",
        "answer": 2.0040707647238456
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 52,830=？",
        "answer": 6.603694202967731
    },
    {
        "question": "90 × 4,981,762=？",
        "answer": 8.651625485037307
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 70,173,145=？",
        "answer": 8.147200936715212
    },
    {
        "question": "63 × 678=？",
        "answer": 4.630570243320645
    },
    {
        "question": "6,349 ÷ 236=？",
        "answer": 1.4297933241042455
    },
    {
        "question": "4,396 ÷ 4,330=？",
        "answer": 0.006569787398087471
    },
    {
        "question": "612,013,466 ÷ 99,014,313=？",
        "answer": 0.7910629994254218
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,094=？",
        "answer": 3.3209766773428235
    },
    {
        "question": "58,841 ÷ 3,933=？",
        "answer": 1.1749560985225553
    },
    {
        "question": "3,286,507 ÷ 473=？",
        "answer": 3.841873420892461
    },
    {
        "question": "1,104,989 × 316=？",
        "answer": 8.54304503732453
    },
    {
        "question": "155,533 × 1,572=？",
        "answer": 8.388275090676464
    },
    {
        "question": "6,199,220 ÷ 38,470=？",
        "answer": 2.2072148627065804
    },
    {
        "question": "565,307 ÷ 448=？",
        "answer": 3.1010063492128173
    },
    {
        "question": "751,936,986 ÷ 1,746,836=？",
        "answer": 2.6339293136868362
    },
    {
        "question": "6,517,605 ÷ 284=？",
        "answer": 4.360769696425976
    },
    {
        "question": "295,468,263 ÷ 147,646,249=？",
        "answer": 0.3012884209924843
    },
    {
        "question": "2,476,804 ÷ 21,592=？",
        "answer": 2.0595987688337494
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 1,009=？",
        "answer": 4.694087246265425
    },
    {
        "question": "1,144,152 ÷ 373=？",
        "answer": 3.486774892277841
    },
    {
        "question": "1,494,896 ÷ 6,452=？",
        "answer": 2.3649166211025854
    },
    {
        "question": "967,246,758 ÷ 303,439=？",
        "answer": 3.5034658842798
    },
    {
        "question": "946,240,987 ÷ 17,393=？",
        "answer": 4.735627258889598
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,860,224=？",
        "answer": 6.993886781154085
    },
    {
        "question": "39,580,817 ÷ 1,643,192=？",
        "answer": 1.3817964425068605
    },
    {
        "question": "196,870 × 272=？",
        "answer": 7.728748445326684
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 202,617=？",
        "answer": 5.306675880789606
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 5,032=？",
        "answer": 4.479891882820856
    },
    {
        "question": "187,078,881 ÷ 605,477=？",
        "answer": 2.489927113109728
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 191,399=？",
        "answer": 5.281939664393717
    },
    {
        "question": "222,584,874 ÷ 26,791=？",
        "answer": 3.919506723669564
    },
    {
        "question": "230,043 × 1,468=？",
        "answer": 8.528535078194446
    },
    {
        "question": "336,015 × 2,294=？",
        "answer": 8.886952078668848
    },
    {
        "question": "563 × 83,425=？",
        "answer": 7.671804610178176
    },
    {
        "question": "3,585 ÷ 1,504=？",
        "answer": 0.37724132374819547
    },
    {
        "question": "8,520 × 2,239=？",
        "answer": 7.2804936883457305
    },
    {
        "question": "123 × 731=？",
        "answer": 4.953822488397258
    },
    {
        "question": "959 × 13,289=？",
        "answer": 7.1053109085933155
    },
    {
        "question": "206,223,719 ÷ 134,434,921=？",
        "answer": 0.18582651827242053
    },
    {
        "question": "78,302 ÷ 1,442=？",
        "answer": 1.734807594623076
    },
    {
        "question": "82,925 ÷ 2,712=？",
        "answer": 1.4853957949964942
    },
    {
        "question": "4,269,205 ÷ 638,339=？",
        "answer": 0.8252956304672042
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 17,519=？",
        "answer": 5.8667586030246754
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,343,777=？",
        "answer": 6.727848326396718
    },
    {
        "question": "661 × 256,062=？",
        "answer": 8.228546592757658
    },
    {
        "question": "54,684,467 ÷ 9,744=？",
        "answer": 3.7491267081895114
    },
    {
        "question": "929,129,100 ÷ 139,224=？",
        "answer": 3.8243619550622583
    },
    {
        "question": "178 × 7,803=？",
        "answer": 6.142681609224429
    },
    {
        "question": "14,644,196 ÷ 439=？",
        "answer": 4.523201012665324
    },
    {
        "question": "468,544 ÷ 4,854=？",
        "answer": 1.9846506088414015
    },
    {
        "question": "2,177 × 36,710=？",
        "answer": 7.902642813545081
    },
    {
        "question": "5,328,483 ÷ 93,130=？",
        "answer": 1.7575139815870977
    },
    {
        "question": "33,452 ÷ 18,248=？",
        "answer": 0.2632068158441602
    },
    {
        "question": "35,639,467 ÷ 60,732=？",
        "answer": 2.768513617039576
    },
    {
        "question": "173,026,656 ÷ 116,440,719=？",
        "answer": 0.17200813600596518
    },
    {
        "question": "66,784 × 1,737=？",
        "answer": 8.064472245832459
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 26,714,431=？",
        "answer": 8.125715932763539
    },
    {
        "question": "22,219,934 ÷ 3,749,858=？",
        "answer": 0.7727279424873579
    },
    {
        "question": "176,914 ÷ 238=？",
        "answer": 2.871185244887505
    },
    {
        "question": "7,842,134 ÷ 5,226,329=？",
        "answer": 0.17623751359339468
    },
    {
        "question": "139,174 ÷ 286=？",
        "answer": 2.6871920763466663
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 1,260,392=？",
        "answer": 7.5154789859138456
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 6,629=？",
        "answer": 5.2838460169164865
    },
    {
        "question": "77,275 ÷ 40,978=？",
        "answer": 0.2754882556233126
    },
    {
        "question": "7,804,355 ÷ 3,654,336=？",
        "answer": 0.3295285398034529
    },
    {
        "question": "302,844,083 ÷ 385,916=？",
        "answer": 2.8947263080834698
    },
    {
        "question": "4,755,897 ÷ 1,115=？",
        "answer": 3.6299575730082223
    },
    {
        "question": "595,212 × 563=？",
        "answer": 8.525180073238039
    },
    {
        "question": "49,596,206 ÷ 391=？",
        "answer": 5.103271697798243
    },
    {
        "question": "4,929,573 ÷ 842=？",
        "answer": 3.767497210784656
    },
    {
        "question": "4,337 ÷ 708=？",
        "answer": 0.787156164458993
    },
    {
        "question": "2,667,532 ÷ 611,784=？",
        "answer": 0.6395115232866114
    },
    {
        "question": "14,663,655 ÷ 108,504=？",
        "answer": 2.130796485439655
    },
    {
        "question": "404 × 668=？",
        "answer": 5.4311578275861505
    },
    {
        "question": "1,847 × 26,587=？",
        "answer": 7.691136231006117
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 25,327=？",
        "answer": 4.403583750366688
    },
    {
        "question": "157,139 ÷ 478=？",
        "answer": 2.5168560884455555
    },
    {
        "question": "19,151 × 32,068=？",
        "answer": 8.788263331200907
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,113=？",
        "answer": 3.3248994970523134
    },
    {
        "question": "5,239,103 ÷ 590,383=？",
        "answer": 0.9481230931548218
    },
    {
        "question": "399,504,028 ÷ 9,780=？",
        "answer": 4.61118230765929
    },
    {
        "question": "4,470,670 ÷ 206=？",
        "answer": 4.336505393478226
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 641=？",
        "answer": 3.585009279902461
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 38,611=？",
        "answer": 5.948438885734309
    },
    {
        "question": "62,307,078 ÷ 8,733,213=？",
        "answer": 0.8533633321511761
    },
    {
        "question": "71,212,369 ÷ 58,685,650=？",
        "answer": 0.08402351437689644
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,509=？",
        "answer": 3.17868923977559
    },
    {
        "question": "788,262 ÷ 13,899=？",
        "answer": 1.7536870359707866
    },
    {
        "question": "1,417 × 662,524=？",
        "answer": 8.972571465503513
    },
    {
        "question": "130,833,931 ÷ 252=？",
        "answer": 5.7153198494991155
    },
    {
        "question": "6,119 × 402=？",
        "answer": 6.390906506281119
    },
    {
        "question": "189,333,546 ÷ 1,752,745=？",
        "answer": 2.0335088319201544
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 95,250,884=？",
        "answer": 8.279899010610489
    },
    {
        "question": "315,682,842 ÷ 2,955=？",
        "answer": 5.028693492534233
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 830,849,911=？",
        "answer": 8.919522577681079
    },
    {
        "question": "96 × 293=？",
        "answer": 4.449138853393678
    },
    {
        "question": "509,472,805 ÷ 1,809=？",
        "answer": 5.449682440023067
    },
    {
        "question": "152,533,639 ÷ 20,946=？",
        "answer": 3.862264532163901
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 7,498=？",
        "answer": 5.838733263431087
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 87,577,431=？",
        "answer": 8.84548218842252
    },
    {
        "question": "25,807 × 4,671=？",
        "answer": 8.08114738910514
    },
    {
        "question": "17,732,122 ÷ 714,084=？",
        "answer": 1.3950114084177319
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 6,914,734=？",
        "answer": 8.564051347675308
    },
    {
        "question": "91,779 ÷ 2,347=？",
        "answer": 1.5922302318266432
    },
    {
        "question": "227 × 6,691=？",
        "answer": 6.181516887072553
    },
    {
        "question": "53,917,302 ÷ 14,929,685=？",
        "answer": 0.5576775074667962
    },
    {
        "question": "1,765,609 ÷ 26,759=？",
        "answer": 1.8194246543763533
    },
    {
        "question": "500,676,556 ÷ 1,031=？",
        "answer": 5.686298590908272
    },
    {
        "question": "274,247 ÷ 29,222=？",
        "answer": 0.9724319490880451
    },
    {
        "question": "12,882 ÷ 3,143=？",
        "answer": 0.6126389138023123
    },
    {
        "question": "182,175,674 ÷ 148,310=？",
        "answer": 3.089319950068583
    },
    {
        "question": "28,772,905 ÷ 2,213,885=？",
        "answer": 1.1138286540437226
    },
    {
        "question": "950,479,129 ÷ 3,751,359=？",
        "answer": 2.40375395735854
    },
    {
        "question": "1,312,311 × 216=？",
        "answer": 8.452490520320334
    },
    {
        "question": "174 × 12,234=？",
        "answer": 6.328117724444383
    },
    {
        "question": "60,176 × 374=？",
        "answer": 7.352294918278804
    },
    {
        "question": "198 × 469=？",
        "answer": 4.967838032976615
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,189,098=？",
        "answer": 6.552338903371443
    },
    {
        "question": "1,971 × 66,495=？",
        "answer": 8.11747561463446
    },
    {
        "question": "681,558 ÷ 3,797=？",
        "answer": 2.2540622226906684
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 17,839=？",
        "answer": 4.251370505496703
    },
    {
        "question": "870,096,074 ÷ 193,168=？",
        "answer": 3.653632025772268
    },
    {
        "question": "18,105,476 ÷ 872=？",
        "answer": 4.317293462141255
    },
    {
        "question": "994 × 1,366=？",
        "answer": 6.132837083742827
    },
    {
        "question": "25 × 813,588=？",
        "answer": 7.308344543016155
    },
    {
        "question": "24,995 ÷ 2,046=？",
        "answer": 1.0869475117124676
    },
    {
        "question": "2,630,731 ÷ 397=？",
        "answer": 3.8212859357018014
    },
    {
        "question": "35,978 ÷ 5,089=？",
        "answer": 0.8494045665824418
    },
    {
        "question": "3,907,177 ÷ 360=？",
        "answer": 4.035560584985809
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 8,948=？",
        "answer": 4.993118660582817
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 180,842=？",
        "answer": 5.257299301415568
    },
    {
        "question": "1,327 × 7,435=？",
        "answer": 6.994151895722409
    },
    {
        "question": "130 × 951,434=？",
        "answer": 8.092322019412315
    },
    {
        "question": "364,194 ÷ 2,792=？",
        "answer": 2.115417372679782
    },
    {
        "question": "305,615,969 ÷ 261,420=？",
        "answer": 3.0678372328675945
    },
    {
        "question": "3,372 × 73,035=？",
        "answer": 8.39141859955428
    },
    {
        "question": "2,294,462 ÷ 734,753=？",
        "answer": 0.49453950149681825
    },
    {
        "question": "18,707,089 ÷ 667,880=？",
        "answer": 1.4473077739337323
    },
    {
        "question": "1,360,728 ÷ 276,671=？",
        "answer": 0.6918076816467067
    },
    {
        "question": "342,912,698 ÷ 23,296=？",
        "answer": 4.1679022096319756
    },
    {
        "question": "4,084,034 ÷ 469,695=？",
        "answer": 0.9392734119221616
    },
    {
        "question": "534,789 ÷ 3,183=？",
        "answer": 2.2253458271184727
    },
    {
        "question": "6,811 × 7,629=？",
        "answer": 7.71567849517798
    },
    {
        "question": "9,175 × 17,440=？",
        "answer": 8.204152553520675
    },
    {
        "question": "3,460 × 153,629=？",
        "answer": 8.725549302451729
    },
    {
        "question": "20,431,573 ÷ 46,907=？",
        "answer": 2.6390641457318176
    },
    {
        "question": "464 × 24,052=？",
        "answer": 7.047669175728342
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 2,329=？",
        "answer": 4.622441993637986
    },
    {
        "question": "17,890,651 ÷ 5,576,152=？",
        "answer": 0.5062915401818291
    },
    {
        "question": "163,486 ÷ 31,557=？",
        "answer": 0.7143848582792882
    },
    {
        "question": "53,473,555 ÷ 2,332=？",
        "answer": 4.360410511504314
    },
    {
        "question": "14,313 × 27,358=？",
        "answer": 8.592815016493626
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 14,149,247=？",
        "answer": 8.451763323690612
    },
    {
        "question": "13,701,791 ÷ 1,255=？",
        "answer": 4.038133612914478
    },
    {
        "question": "86,464 × 4,514=？",
        "answer": 8.59139687774766
    },
    {
        "question": "2,266 × 37,442=？",
        "answer": 7.928618944465378
    },
    {
        "question": "368 × 1,022,719=？",
        "answer": 8.575604142988656
    },
    {
        "question": "26 × 1,708,125=？",
        "answer": 7.647492997007554
    },
    {
        "question": "4,520,648 ÷ 46,894=？",
        "answer": 1.984083412936408
    },
    {
        "question": "42,773,107 ÷ 451=？",
        "answer": 4.976994256285004
    },
    {
        "question": "122,510 × 502=？",
        "answer": 7.788875257009372
    },
    {
        "question": "123,482,903 ÷ 29,864=？",
        "answer": 3.616458853983007
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 19,467,511=？",
        "answer": 7.590340424427721
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 1,307,353=？",
        "answer": 6.961490907819043
    },
    {
        "question": "964,013 ÷ 842=？",
        "answer": 3.058770799032016
    },
    {
        "question": "1,044 × 292,488=？",
        "answer": 8.484808551509438
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 55,373=？",
        "answer": 4.743298053368377
    },
    {
        "question": "78,601,157 ÷ 30,322,414=？",
        "answer": 0.41366516586405466
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 129,488=？",
        "answer": 6.60359121688275
    },
    {
        "question": "232,070,419 ÷ 8,457=？",
        "answer": 4.438403455776754
    },
    {
        "question": "189 × 206=？",
        "answer": 4.590329024542397
    },
    {
        "question": "142,108 × 1,926=？",
        "answer": 8.437274810104153
    },
    {
        "question": "213,693 ÷ 14,836=？",
        "answer": 1.1584734714374696
    },
    {
        "question": "191,554 ÷ 18,857=？",
        "answer": 1.006818624212297
    },
    {
        "question": "212 × 61,486=？",
        "answer": 7.115112101665173
    },
    {
        "question": "80,021,459 ÷ 109,006=？",
        "answer": 2.8657560620358367
    },
    {
        "question": "285,893 ÷ 6,930=？",
        "answer": 1.615470287312847
    },
    {
        "question": "89,525 × 1,376=？",
        "answer": 8.090562763583433
    },
    {
        "question": "121 × 4,950=？",
        "answer": 5.777390569250019
    },
    {
        "question": "217,562,028 ÷ 153,310,808=？",
        "answer": 0.1520103259015495
    },
    {
        "question": "488,065 ÷ 126,601=？",
        "answer": 0.5860405286377045
    },
    {
        "question": "21,542,279 ÷ 9,020,682=？",
        "answer": 0.37805227305807776
    },
    {
        "question": "182 × 671,899=？",
        "answer": 8.087375382706593
    },
    {
        "question": "148,774 ÷ 3,620=？",
        "answer": 1.6138184692576978
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 3,079=？",
        "answer": 3.488409688903198
    },
    {
        "question": "33,820,058 ÷ 49,717=？",
        "answer": 2.8326694332940416
    },
    {
        "question": "173,476,639 ÷ 40,881=？",
        "answer": 3.627719488739083
    },
    {
        "question": "1,443 × 4,213=？",
        "answer": 6.783857790220342
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 5,903,713=？",
        "answer": 8.0015741581428
    },
    {
        "question": "994 × 12,079=？",
        "answer": 7.079417365664325
    },
    {
        "question": "709,722,511 ÷ 530,506=？",
        "answer": 3.1263982802958066
    },
    {
        "question": "1,864 × 378=？",
        "answer": 5.847937707855188
    },
    {
        "question": "38,002,462 ÷ 32,452,012=？",
        "answer": 0.06857010551838898
    },
    {
        "question": "1,168 × 480,926=？",
        "answer": 8.749521099474428
    },
    {
        "question": "50,667,118 ÷ 1,180=？",
        "answer": 4.632844194551284
    },
    {
        "question": "415 × 262,607=？",
        "answer": 8.037354395087242
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 3,526,409=？",
        "answer": 7.802605186334325
    },
    {
        "question": "644,157,575 ÷ 12,600=？",
        "answer": 4.7086215731461065
    },
    {
        "question": "198,803,410 ÷ 20,561=？",
        "answer": 3.985379596332804
    },
    {
        "question": "2,474 × 3,543=？",
        "answer": 6.942770847626279
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 59,406=？",
        "answer": 4.773830310895266
    },
    {
        "question": "577 × 1,000=？",
        "answer": 5.761175813155732
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 409,444=？",
        "answer": 5.612194511336785
    },
    {
        "question": "94,434 ÷ 613=？",
        "answer": 2.187667911240347
    },
    {
        "question": "172,065,244 ÷ 3,035,599=？",
        "answer": 1.7534487535901584
    },
    {
        "question": "1,840 × 16,755=？",
        "answer": 7.488962255180827
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 3,840,894=？",
        "answer": 8.29200249788162
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 17,805=？",
        "answer": 5.364485330317109
    },
    {
        "question": "151,931 ÷ 298=？",
        "answer": 2.707430132270647
    },
    {
        "question": "1,357,868 ÷ 35,378=？",
        "answer": 1.5841242761033785
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,740=？",
        "answer": 3.9395192526186187
    },
    {
        "question": "367,373 × 1,729=？",
        "answer": 8.802902228036583
    },
    {
        "question": "576,564 ÷ 914=？",
        "answer": 2.7999013263116947
    },
    {
        "question": "6,560,999 ÷ 1,038=？",
        "answer": 3.8007726180515187
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 57,178=？",
        "answer": 6.473232303958018
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 145,540=？",
        "answer": 5.162982370585433
    },
    {
        "question": "126,581,127 ÷ 16,762,711=？",
        "answer": 0.878024700485309
    },
    {
        "question": "9,138 × 9,918=？",
        "answer": 7.957275257674778
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 72,776,963=？",
        "answer": 7.861993928416179
    },
    {
        "question": "54,864,881 ÷ 8,192=？",
        "answer": 3.82590449793553
    },
    {
        "question": "48,249 ÷ 1,155=？",
        "answer": 1.6209063324364685
    },
    {
        "question": "33,029,251 ÷ 235,922=？",
        "answer": 2.1461302841260954
    },
    {
        "question": "6,951,370 ÷ 14,625=？",
        "answer": 2.6769745305273576
    },
    {
        "question": "4,195,875 ÷ 591=？",
        "answer": 3.851235060694873
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 39,370,948=？",
        "answer": 8.294145876484949
    },
    {
        "question": "124,871,956 ÷ 1,019,850=？",
        "answer": 2.087928614349465
    },
    {
        "question": "263,149 × 2,682=？",
        "answer": 8.848660497497198
    },
    {
        "question": "7,146 ÷ 1,757=？",
        "answer": 0.6092912503711261
    },
    {
        "question": "11,553,671 ÷ 371=？",
        "answer": 4.493346086884542
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 12,580,962=？",
        "answer": 7.09971385059399
    },
    {
        "question": "144,353,158 ÷ 33,756,170=？",
        "answer": 0.6310731239629364
    },
    {
        "question": "53,040,260 ÷ 7,369=？",
        "answer": 3.8571970877632267
    },
    {
        "question": "186,931 × 3,254=？",
        "answer": 8.784098877869118
    },
    {
        "question": "1,901,548 ÷ 280,022=？",
        "answer": 0.8319151394647045
    },
    {
        "question": "2,657 × 633=？",
        "answer": 6.225795264427632
    },
    {
        "question": "279 × 63,354=？",
        "answer": 7.247378243536248
    },
    {
        "question": "155,348 × 2,775=？",
        "answer": 8.634568653839164
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 745,242,319=？",
        "answer": 8.872297508578393
    },
    {
        "question": "30,644 × 20,659=？",
        "answer": 8.801454749312384
    },
    {
        "question": "861,262,203 ÷ 1,728=？",
        "answer": 5.697591650221884
    },
    {
        "question": "29,330,803 ÷ 11,365=？",
        "answer": 3.4117545129193974
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 15,638,638=？",
        "answer": 7.4952289224670015
    },
    {
        "question": "582,455,429 ÷ 25,900=？",
        "answer": 4.3519629335482115
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 406=？",
        "answer": 3.5116160205691376
    },
    {
        "question": "3,256 × 1,720=？",
        "answer": 6.748212843124713
    },
    {
        "question": "760,896 ÷ 19,049=？",
        "answer": 1.6014531192350832
    },
    {
        "question": "8,946 × 1,922=？",
        "answer": 7.2353822771691645
    },
    {
        "question": "334 × 557,124=？",
        "answer": 8.269698334377196
    },
    {
        "question": "831,560,343 ÷ 2,626,921=？",
        "answer": 2.500446757363809
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,676,765=？",
        "answer": 7.0673225399298225
    },
    {
        "question": "30,823 × 507=？",
        "answer": 7.193882865618361
    },
    {
        "question": "260,946,159 ÷ 420=？",
        "answer": 5.793301618237986
    },
    {
        "question": "45 × 9,420,919=？",
        "answer": 8.627305783570508
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 8,672,604=？",
        "answer": 6.93814951651125
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 62,805=？",
        "answer": 4.797994219946911
    },
    {
        "question": "2,896 ÷ 417=？",
        "answer": 0.8416625025513518
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 100,266=？",
        "answer": 6.5196676294719405
    },
    {
        "question": "625,765,242 ÷ 33,956,761=？",
        "answer": 1.265485178754582
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 23,398=？",
        "answer": 4.971238727965237
    },
    {
        "question": "3,852,582 ÷ 804,940=？",
        "answer": 0.6799883818115572
    },
    {
        "question": "16,098,349 ÷ 6,814=？",
        "answer": 3.373379209100853
    },
    {
        "question": "2,582 ÷ 202=？",
        "answer": 1.1066048684837777
    },
    {
        "question": "7,277 × 302=？",
        "answer": 6.341959317878603
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 6,017=？",
        "answer": 5.141107847509248
    },
    {
        "question": "259,705 × 1,035=？",
        "answer": 8.429420660806553
    },
    {
        "question": "823,325,564 ÷ 481,555=？",
        "answer": 3.232925703815792
    },
    {
        "question": "134 × 15,116=？",
        "answer": 6.306541681609785
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 3,862=？",
        "answer": 4.967023511154982
    },
    {
        "question": "5,515,632 ÷ 14,061=？",
        "answer": 2.593579074336313
    },
    {
        "question": "1,192 × 1,314=？",
        "answer": 6.194871620627979
    },
    {
        "question": "62,590,677 ÷ 12,081=？",
        "answer": 3.714406764714206
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 10,222=？",
        "answer": 4.854633916633475
    },
    {
        "question": "43,122 ÷ 9,762=？",
        "answer": 0.645160091919889
    },
    {
        "question": "504,084,665 ÷ 91,015,645=？",
        "answer": 0.7433874346124435
    },
    {
        "question": "55 × 6,941,416=？",
        "answer": 8.581810762003602
    },
    {
        "question": "943,277,620 ÷ 55,939,997=？",
        "answer": 1.2269170918395975
    },
    {
        "question": "139,757,192 ÷ 64,534=？",
        "answer": 3.335585581479688
    },
    {
        "question": "5,384,178 ÷ 3,574=？",
        "answer": 3.1779648609846176
    },
    {
        "question": "12,854,126 ÷ 3,343=？",
        "answer": 3.584906176087501
    },
    {
        "question": "66,730,802 ÷ 277,711=？",
        "answer": 2.3807332621355553
    },
    {
        "question": "299 × 4,687=？",
        "answer": 6.14656614184464
    },
    {
        "question": "385,778 × 1,489=？",
        "answer": 8.759232154986867
    },
    {
        "question": "1,003,298 ÷ 7,582=？",
        "answer": 2.1216461664230715
    },
    {
        "question": "358,684 ÷ 72,775=？",
        "answer": 0.6927297902018885
    },
    {
        "question": "8,865,734 ÷ 916=？",
        "answer": 3.985819223285857
    },
    {
        "question": "13,162,799 ÷ 11,116=？",
        "answer": 3.0733997114310556
    },
    {
        "question": "22,224,147 ÷ 31,552=？",
        "answer": 2.84779820775111
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 219=？",
        "answer": 3.185542154854375
    },
    {
        "question": "9,660,326 ÷ 432,832=？",
        "answer": 1.3486724210737764
    },
    {
        "question": "827 × 276,906=？",
        "answer": 8.359837875694149
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 919,705=？",
        "answer": 6.866738534536379
    },
    {
        "question": "9,023 × 1,177=？",
        "answer": 7.026127420211094
    },
    {
        "question": "16,264,744 ÷ 358=？",
        "answer": 4.657364205421442
    },
    {
        "question": "6,443,601 ÷ 47,656=？",
        "answer": 2.131011053150621
    },
    {
        "question": "833,483 ÷ 65,316=？",
        "answer": 1.1058771658731288
    },
    {
        "question": "129 × 983,354=？",
        "answer": 8.103299599006878
    },
    {
        "question": "23,003 × 609=？",
        "answer": 7.146401772062748
    },
    {
        "question": "403,559,279 ÷ 12,664,562=？",
        "answer": 1.5033171630067876
    },
    {
        "question": "5,292,552 ÷ 1,533=？",
        "answer": 3.5381229788568413
    },
    {
        "question": "167,827 ÷ 550=？",
        "answer": 2.484499141895491
    },
    {
        "question": "382,275,443 ÷ 63,702=？",
        "answer": 3.778223332522156
    },
    {
        "question": "26,802 × 25,451=？",
        "answer": 8.833872053809195
    },
    {
        "question": "5,776 × 40,729=？",
        "answer": 8.371530931750124
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 8,645=？",
        "answer": 4.413886252329604
    },
    {
        "question": "8,115,476 ÷ 2,767,844=？",
        "answer": 0.46717238878248285
    },
    {
        "question": "55,591 × 15,884=？",
        "answer": 8.945964364817089
    },
    {
        "question": "201,130 ÷ 629=？",
        "answer": 2.5048262081586143
    },
    {
        "question": "5,381,880 ÷ 1,268,534=？",
        "answer": 0.6276318981219294
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 160,216,850=？",
        "answer": 8.50573818454826
    },
    {
        "question": "169,317,349 ÷ 47,641=？",
        "answer": 3.550720591222879
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 92,842=？",
        "answer": 6.569804478773284
    },
    {
        "question": "1,245 × 23,942=？",
        "answer": 7.4743297778983
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,124,301=？",
        "answer": 7.026186057883553
    },
    {
        "question": "72,735,118 ÷ 8,941,039=？",
        "answer": 0.9103561585010634
    },
    {
        "question": "8,527 × 2,601=？",
        "answer": 7.3459366151791725
    },
    {
        "question": "5,347 ÷ 732=？",
        "answer": 0.8635991030419488
    },
    {
        "question": "2,134 × 1,011=？",
        "answer": 6.333945570679452
    },
    {
        "question": "11,914,385 ÷ 392=？",
        "answer": 4.482785562708628
    },
    {
        "question": "88,473,572 ÷ 42,999=？",
        "answer": 3.313355206083307
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 58,108=？",
        "answer": 5.241357182577787
    },
    {
        "question": "16,456 ÷ 1,691=？",
        "answer": 0.9881806710889258
    },
    {
        "question": "65,248,441 ÷ 581=？",
        "answer": 5.050394007019438
    },
    {
        "question": "31,045,280 ÷ 582,707=？",
        "answer": 1.7265453458812623
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,131,532=？",
        "answer": 6.530788095137593
    },
    {
        "question": "413 × 686=？",
        "answer": 5.452274167363153
    },
    {
        "question": "3,950,530 × 208=？",
        "answer": 8.91471869910431
    },
    {
        "question": "348,704,604 ÷ 178,613=？",
        "answer": 3.2905446164874896
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 236,799,281=？",
        "answer": 8.374380379392916
    },
    {
        "question": "81,187,073 ÷ 225=？",
        "answer": 5.557304366158164
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 247=？",
        "answer": 4.015946243657567
    },
    {
        "question": "2,153 × 12,338=？",
        "answer": 7.424288795731448
    },
    {
        "question": "650,946,634 ÷ 13,012=？",
        "answer": 4.699201331025462
    },
    {
        "question": "22,346,030 ÷ 251=？",
        "answer": 4.949526655998532
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 766=？",
        "answer": 2.884228769632604
    },
    {
        "question": "9,663 × 3,938=？",
        "answer": 7.580387691341453
    },
    {
        "question": "284,615,545 ÷ 185,613=？",
        "answer": 3.185650226340015
    },
    {
        "question": "1,892,085 ÷ 687,835=？",
        "answer": 0.43945637192585224
    },
    {
        "question": "46,327,315 ÷ 5,570,538=？",
        "answer": 0.9199399892932826
    },
    {
        "question": "27,027 ÷ 220=？",
        "answer": 2.0893751608160995
    },
    {
        "question": "14,249,488 ÷ 3,671=？",
        "answer": 3.589014875435666
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,438=？",
        "answer": 3.458788881710845
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 253,975=？",
        "answer": 5.404790968996309
    },
    {
        "question": "5,162 × 1,822=？",
        "answer": 6.973366372844829
    },
    {
        "question": "435,753 × 1,317=？",
        "answer": 8.758826160712744
    },
    {
        "question": "6,364 × 70,479=？",
        "answer": 8.651789904381332
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 105,417=？",
        "answer": 5.97715316216455
    },
    {
        "question": "11,580,604 ÷ 186,800=？",
        "answer": 1.7923543392267303
    },
    {
        "question": "2,243 × 20,806=？",
        "answer": 7.669017867734763
    },
    {
        "question": "506 × 1,745=？",
        "answer": 5.945945948134998
    },
    {
        "question": "444,551 ÷ 10,878=？",
        "answer": 1.6113725370318792
    },
    {
        "question": "1,715,614 ÷ 1,687,009=？",
        "answer": 0.007302182067083622
    },
    {
        "question": "875,127,097 ÷ 403,552=？",
        "answer": 3.3361716273180697
    },
    {
        "question": "73 × 4,945=？",
        "answer": 5.557489156053654
    },
    {
        "question": "11,122 × 2,059=？",
        "answer": 7.359839237358913
    },
    {
        "question": "96,189 ÷ 258=？",
        "answer": 2.5715057037830156
    },
    {
        "question": "153 × 260,920=？",
        "answer": 7.601198800668048
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 948,634=？",
        "answer": 5.977098686147359
    },
    {
        "question": "25,550,243 ÷ 2,371=？",
        "answer": 4.032463480944882
    },
    {
        "question": "43,730 × 1,875=？",
        "answer": 7.913780749408595
    },
    {
        "question": "3,390 × 399=？",
        "answer": 6.13117259388983
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 92,111=？",
        "answer": 6.28653079196701
    },
    {
        "question": "724,222,820 ÷ 11,338,289=？",
        "answer": 1.8053246826942264
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 296=？",
        "answer": 2.77232170672292
    },
    {
        "question": "354 × 556,528=？",
        "answer": 8.294490281441503
    },
    {
        "question": "126,641 ÷ 419=？",
        "answer": 2.480360308237082
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 13,234=？",
        "answer": 4.966789170321833
    },
    {
        "question": "11,280,382 ÷ 109,037=？",
        "answer": 2.014749912900783
    },
    {
        "question": "921,804,108 ÷ 15,304=？",
        "answer": 4.779833682197507
    },
    {
        "question": "57 × 1,837,424=？",
        "answer": 8.020084240401118
    },
    {
        "question": "168 × 233=？",
        "answer": 4.592665202751882
    },
    {
        "question": "327,415,482 ÷ 109,234=？",
        "answer": 3.476741374170849
    },
    {
        "question": "8,040 × 361=？",
        "answer": 6.462763250654109
    },
    {
        "question": "270,386,215 ÷ 288,267=？",
        "answer": 2.972189617943725
    },
    {
        "question": "2,498 × 2,748=？",
        "answer": 6.8366091624256295
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 9,451,164=？",
        "answer": 7.6744553036014675
    },
    {
        "question": "671,158,737 ÷ 830=？",
        "answer": 5.907747155736484
    },
    {
        "question": "161 × 9,246=？",
        "answer": 6.172779765133913
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 75,795=？",
        "answer": 6.110089478672186
    },
    {
        "question": "3,205,203 ÷ 467=？",
        "answer": 3.836538659993225
    },
    {
        "question": "9,472 ÷ 549=？",
        "answer": 1.2368693449287527
    },
    {
        "question": "72,267,390 ÷ 353,738=？",
        "answer": 2.3102606540446686
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 311=？",
        "answer": 3.98412208286111
    },
    {
        "question": "8,493 ÷ 1,779=？",
        "answer": 0.6788851760008404
    },
    {
        "question": "3,285 × 290,008=？",
        "answer": 8.978945352166942
    },
    {
        "question": "661,461 × 220=？",
        "answer": 8.162926923927579
    },
    {
        "question": "3,532,314 ÷ 1,604=？",
        "answer": 3.342854938660104
    },
    {
        "question": "4,072 × 9,045=？",
        "answer": 7.566216340524535
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 199,595=？",
        "answer": 7.032543417517769
    },
    {
        "question": "58 × 1,842=？",
        "answer": 5.028717619423768
    },
    {
        "question": "11,649 ÷ 722=？",
        "answer": 1.207751447696071
    },
    {
        "question": "396,556 ÷ 972=？",
        "answer": 2.6106382603305915
    },
    {
        "question": "2,714,722 ÷ 22,521=？",
        "answer": 2.081137691866402
    },
    {
        "question": "233,778 ÷ 4,492=？",
        "answer": 1.7163638912802144
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 766,723=？",
        "answer": 5.884638491328833
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 396,785=？",
        "answer": 5.598555245789696
    },
    {
        "question": "141,057 ÷ 13,249=？",
        "answer": 1.0272115429387438
    },
    {
        "question": "377,934,541 ÷ 68,022=？",
        "answer": 3.7447671886785896
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 107,984,249=？",
        "answer": 8.033360412234575
    },
    {
        "question": "2,638,914 ÷ 180,838=？",
        "answer": 1.1641355419009314
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,341,975=？",
        "answer": 6.8267144296599165
    },
    {
        "question": "22,842 × 3,098=？",
        "answer": 7.849815540621198
    },
    {
        "question": "72,720,461 ÷ 31,346,706=？",
        "answer": 0.36546471268546266
    },
    {
        "question": "504,706,212 ÷ 1,178=？",
        "answer": 5.63189335967733
    },
    {
        "question": "11,999 ÷ 10,456=？",
        "answer": 0.05977947876026096
    },
    {
        "question": "78,950 × 280=？",
        "answer": 7.344510165686533
    },
    {
        "question": "569,492 ÷ 24,856=？",
        "answer": 1.3600563874126992
    },
    {
        "question": "483 × 1,999=？",
        "answer": 5.984759924869629
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 4,410,799=？",
        "answer": 8.547607254432602
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 8,410,972=？",
        "answer": 7.623816191554127
    },
    {
        "question": "2,980 ÷ 1,223=？",
        "answer": 0.3867898070399698
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 207=？",
        "answer": 2.79309160017658
    },
    {
        "question": "258,353,722 ÷ 3,708,053=？",
        "answer": 1.843068789654395
    },
    {
        "question": "650,979,534 ÷ 4,505,431=？",
        "answer": 2.1598309921738985
    },
    {
        "question": "8,061,056 ÷ 219,640=？",
        "answer": 1.564680503161331
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 13,670=？",
        "answer": 5.391041019671128
    },
    {
        "question": "1,001 × 24,753=？",
        "answer": 7.394061919314137
    },
    {
        "question": "377,385,869 ÷ 480,966=？",
        "answer": 2.89467125750425
    },
    {
        "question": "3,032 ÷ 1,708=？",
        "answer": 0.24924133060702966
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 2,055,538=？",
        "answer": 7.655348190660427
    },
    {
        "question": "261 × 148,904=？",
        "answer": 7.589546871676048
    },
    {
        "question": "119 × 188,569=？",
        "answer": 7.351017259361598
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 5,444,228=？",
        "answer": 8.660215590886423
    },
    {
        "question": "26,566,669 ÷ 35,087=？",
        "answer": 2.8791908679569014
    },
    {
        "question": "178 × 1,733=？",
        "answer": 5.489218565022811
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 551,769=？",
        "answer": 5.741757296891389
    },
    {
        "question": "7,168,545 ÷ 7,480=？",
        "answer": 2.981529417971391
    },
    {
        "question": "584 × 12,180=？",
        "answer": 6.852060135409256
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 84,426=？",
        "answer": 5.2275062090864415
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 453,895=？",
        "answer": 5.6569553986838725
    },
    {
        "question": "13,307,110 ÷ 4,189=？",
        "answer": 3.501973386523407
    },
    {
        "question": "317,938 × 2,214=？",
        "answer": 8.847520054504791
    },
    {
        "question": "22,296,295 ÷ 12,590,477=？",
        "answer": 0.24819051784585083
    },
    {
        "question": "243,467 ÷ 224,013=？",
        "answer": 0.0361668822110382
    },
    {
        "question": "6,691 × 340=？",
        "answer": 6.356969946921686
    },
    {
        "question": "453 × 1,000=？",
        "answer": 5.656098202012832
    },
    {
        "question": "532,190,616 ÷ 2,230,951=？",
        "answer": 2.377577180800969
    },
    {
        "question": "744,561,607 ÷ 95,655=？",
        "answer": 3.8911929622080557
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 43,398,331=？",
        "answer": 7.637473027866706
    },
    {
        "question": "437,090 ÷ 30,638=？",
        "answer": 1.1543104587292619
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 2,296=？",
        "answer": 4.703394564548142
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 242=？",
        "answer": 4.270306091152913
    },
    {
        "question": "564,303,364 ÷ 51,531,823=？",
        "answer": 1.0394371328309413
    },
    {
        "question": "1,858,707 ÷ 666,543=？",
        "answer": 0.445382762675694
    },
    {
        "question": "6,370,611 ÷ 95,839=？",
        "answer": 1.822638813586983
    },
    {
        "question": "551,181,233 ÷ 7,039,856=？",
        "answer": 1.8937306462372459
    },
    {
        "question": "1,396 × 215,483=？",
        "answer": 8.47829843154298
    },
    {
        "question": "43,352 ÷ 31,438=？",
        "answer": 0.139554228391158
    },
    {
        "question": "3,709 × 246=？",
        "answer": 5.960191940431989
    },
    {
        "question": "798 × 871,185=？",
        "answer": 8.842113280512002
    },
    {
        "question": "666 × 36,632=？",
        "answer": 7.387334859689942
    },
    {
        "question": "29,522,641 ÷ 173,146=？",
        "answer": 2.231742742491222
    },
    {
        "question": "116,061,265 ÷ 81,244,308=？",
        "answer": 0.15489435589231015
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 51,432=？",
        "answer": 6.496563247764202
    },
    {
        "question": "49,392,484 ÷ 26,491=？",
        "answer": 3.2705625151918434
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 4,564,805=？",
        "answer": 8.021150066029687
    },
    {
        "question": "5,369,804 ÷ 128,044=？",
        "answer": 1.6225992013431494
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,748,276=？",
        "answer": 6.740090340957598
    },
    {
        "question": "173,697,981 ÷ 678,148=？",
        "answer": 2.4084702851339377
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 36,178,283=？",
        "answer": 7.558447951652595
    },
    {
        "question": "2,089 × 113,811=？",
        "answer": 8.376122679266338
    },
    {
        "question": "4,967,598 ÷ 50,180=？",
        "answer": 1.9956157865817021
    },
    {
        "question": "23,257,434 ÷ 4,525=？",
        "answer": 3.710943213647668
    },
    {
        "question": "11,922,609 ÷ 369,194=？",
        "answer": 1.5091166671489729
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 54,228,020=？",
        "answer": 8.21134500227198
    },
    {
        "question": "91,722,846 ÷ 1,273=？",
        "answer": 4.857649118013925
    },
    {
        "question": "318 × 9,865=？",
        "answer": 6.496524209572643
    },
    {
        "question": "10,608,752 ÷ 1,229=？",
        "answer": 3.9361124141730177
    },
    {
        "question": "43,892 ÷ 8,017=？",
        "answer": 0.7383734869302981
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 2,500=？",
        "answer": 4.778151250383644
    },
    {
        "question": "1,752 × 912=？",
        "answer": 6.203528940160478
    },
    {
        "question": "990 × 2,100=？",
        "answer": 6.317854489331469
    },
    {
        "question": "11,111,534 ÷ 1,982,185=？",
        "answer": 0.7486298341633698
    },
    {
        "question": "106,517,468 ÷ 1,666,657=？",
        "answer": 1.805574603683406
    },
    {
        "question": "1,123,440 ÷ 881,443=？",
        "answer": 0.10535564968170642
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,332=？",
        "answer": 3.8237349883987313
    },
    {
        "question": "1,001,805 ÷ 797=？",
        "answer": 3.099324873522756
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 51,127,842=？",
        "answer": 8.553755502459737
    },
    {
        "question": "593,638,985 ÷ 194,412,730=？",
        "answer": 0.48479771505978264
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,455,553=？",
        "answer": 7.015638813124642
    },
    {
        "question": "451,231,280 ÷ 10,980=？",
        "answer": 4.613796857821599
    },
    {
        "question": "76,916,192 ÷ 447,232=？",
        "answer": 2.2354849045654115
    },
    {
        "question": "21,608,364 ÷ 15,816=？",
        "answer": 3.135525230768814
    },
    {
        "question": "13,733 ÷ 3,485=？",
        "answer": 0.595562637623314
    },
    {
        "question": "11,116,916 ÷ 138,488=？",
        "answer": 1.9045721807539981
    },
    {
        "question": "670,856,182 ÷ 7,236,175=？",
        "answer": 1.9671203648791769
    },
    {
        "question": "4,039 × 3,110=？",
        "answer": 7.099034242196826
    },
    {
        "question": "184,459,815 ÷ 86,157=？",
        "answer": 3.330611200383177
    },
    {
        "question": "3,153 ÷ 361=？",
        "answer": 0.9412167688422468
    },
    {
        "question": "125 × 15,960=？",
        "answer": 6.299942900022767
    },
    {
        "question": "8,610,278 ÷ 201,644=？",
        "answer": 1.6304318698183582
    },
    {
        "question": "36 × 8,946,843=？",
        "answer": 8.5079723171391
    },
    {
        "question": "4,629,533 ÷ 2,329,183=？",
        "answer": 0.2983335724961386
    },
    {
        "question": "26,121 ÷ 9,501=？",
        "answer": 0.43922048108759776
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 4,967=？",
        "answer": 3.6960941599952233
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 406,305=？",
        "answer": 6.387003417182239
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 3,460,546=？",
        "answer": 7.840174622225408
    },
    {
        "question": "10,200 × 534=？",
        "answer": 6.736141428790474
    },
    {
        "question": "265,403 × 1,369=？",
        "answer": 8.560309275765956
    },
    {
        "question": "77 × 2,098,427=？",
        "answer": 8.208384590762583
    },
    {
        "question": "21,175 ÷ 4,433=？",
        "answer": 0.6791256877034101
    },
    {
        "question": "78,729 × 208=？",
        "answer": 7.214198070118232
    },
    {
        "question": "945 × 648,991=？",
        "answer": 8.787670482694164
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,010=？",
        "answer": 4.002166061756507
    },
    {
        "question": "10,831,520 ÷ 998=？",
        "answer": 4.0355588646723985
    },
    {
        "question": "1,344 × 357,453=？",
        "answer": 8.681618215043649
    },
    {
        "question": "1,397,588 ÷ 2,250=？",
        "answer": 2.793196644930944
    },
    {
        "question": "624,486,206 ÷ 11,670,796=？",
        "answer": 1.7284223720135379
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 7,207=？",
        "answer": 4.760844509051386
    },
    {
        "question": "2,309,379 ÷ 12,580=？",
        "answer": 2.26381457119362
    },
    {
        "question": "14,696,100 ÷ 7,837,992=？",
        "answer": 0.27299728260491735
    },
    {
        "question": "8,154,223 ÷ 789,870=？",
        "answer": 1.013826965044894
    },
    {
        "question": "386,159,481 ÷ 11,373,692=？",
        "answer": 1.5308652387526256
    },
    {
        "question": "126,756,366 ÷ 159,766=？",
        "answer": 2.899485417768532
    },
    {
        "question": "719,940,199 ÷ 455,327=？",
        "answer": 3.1989730198759445
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 48,611,826=？",
        "answer": 7.6867419347307795
    },
    {
        "question": "15,447 ÷ 6,000=？",
        "answer": 0.4106928961632535
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 4,053,341=？",
        "answer": 8.576296090215367
    },
    {
        "question": "18,242 × 7,748=？",
        "answer": 8.150262063437896
    },
    {
        "question": "67 × 1,942,991=？",
        "answer": 8.114545591638546
    },
    {
        "question": "842,266 ÷ 70,377=？",
        "answer": 1.0780185197735908
    },
    {
        "question": "1,842 × 104,765=？",
        "answer": 8.28550584318744
    },
    {
        "question": "348 × 495,616=？",
        "answer": 8.236724562230805
    },
    {
        "question": "2,636,983 ÷ 90,155=？",
        "answer": 1.4661175122934522
    },
    {
        "question": "1,832 ÷ 250=？",
        "answer": 0.864985460659794
    },
    {
        "question": "76,668 ÷ 793=？",
        "answer": 1.985340946862161
    },
    {
        "question": "161 × 56,124=？",
        "answer": 6.955974491987979
    },
    {
        "question": "758,757,745 ÷ 222,402=？",
        "answer": 3.5329644487372223
    },
    {
        "question": "411 × 142,905=？",
        "answer": 7.768889246149342
    },
    {
        "question": "1,633,546 ÷ 2,770=？",
        "answer": 2.770651599477577
    },
    {
        "question": "47,268 ÷ 308=？",
        "answer": 2.1860165103563225
    },
    {
        "question": "578 × 20,280=？",
        "answer": 7.068995789081828
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 21,979,402=？",
        "answer": 7.944075863599551
    },
    {
        "question": "21,369 × 3,082=？",
        "answer": 7.818616833446632
    },
    {
        "question": "164,960 × 479=？",
        "answer": 7.8977141613540045
    },
    {
        "question": "5,870,344 ÷ 544=？",
        "answer": 4.033064651792088
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 124,020,160=？",
        "answer": 8.57061354201984
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 55,180,874=？",
        "answer": 7.741788574910314
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 3,543,505=？",
        "answer": 7.452523036893452
    },
    {
        "question": "189 × 476,593=？",
        "answer": 7.954609463493587
    },
    {
        "question": "109,677 × 285=？",
        "answer": 7.494960422675593
    },
    {
        "question": "950 × 3,957=？",
        "answer": 6.5750896555548755
    },
    {
        "question": "826,368,062 ÷ 3,489,977=？",
        "answer": 2.374350959108622
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,105,797=？",
        "answer": 6.793203061782547
    },
    {
        "question": "15,680,520 ÷ 810,552=？",
        "answer": 1.2865795790082326
    },
    {
        "question": "84,508 ÷ 60,509=？",
        "answer": 0.14507784800255305
    },
    {
        "question": "11,023,308 ÷ 5,496=？",
        "answer": 3.3022652180651786
    },
    {
        "question": "608 × 170,153=？",
        "answer": 8.01474318990092
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 188,360=？",
        "answer": 7.178078668762629
    },
    {
        "question": "84 × 39,044=？",
        "answer": 6.515833590162553
    },
    {
        "question": "368,018 ÷ 492=？",
        "answer": 2.873903958051528
    },
    {
        "question": "119,086 × 1,876=？",
        "answer": 8.349093541956313
    },
    {
        "question": "47,085 ÷ 429=？",
        "answer": 2.0404252825709994
    },
    {
        "question": "454,951 ÷ 380,348=？",
        "answer": 0.07778348703559217
    },
    {
        "question": "333,322,866 ÷ 75,597=？",
        "answer": 3.644360546099644
    },
    {
        "question": "199,597 ÷ 20,427=？",
        "answer": 0.9899494205321193
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,015,025=？",
        "answer": 6.9095667260178635
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 3,376=？",
        "answer": 5.379660786672693
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 3,947=？",
        "answer": 4.5962671263955155
    },
    {
        "question": "8,318,431 ÷ 2,884=？",
        "answer": 3.460046162514878
    },
    {
        "question": "1,425,223 ÷ 642,735=？",
        "answer": 0.34585087233455586
    },
    {
        "question": "1,327,178 ÷ 291=？",
        "answer": 3.6590361849964976
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 51,245,166=？",
        "answer": 7.709652904292855
    },
    {
        "question": "68,677 × 1,155=？",
        "answer": 7.899393299955509
    },
    {
        "question": "4,783,904 ÷ 3,492,514=？",
        "answer": 0.13664430026230026
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 306,282=？",
        "answer": 5.96324272906336
    },
    {
        "question": "995 ÷ 349=？",
        "answer": 0.45499765378654555
    },
    {
        "question": "4,693 ÷ 1,280=？",
        "answer": 0.5642405845646263
    },
    {
        "question": "2,434 × 3,432=？",
        "answer": 6.921867853070714
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 572=？",
        "answer": 3.456366033129043
    },
    {
        "question": "1,705 × 91,577=？",
        "answer": 8.193510795562494
    },
    {
        "question": "116 × 115,348=？",
        "answer": 7.126468057988721
    },
    {
        "question": "171,249 × 2,478=？",
        "answer": 8.627729346170932
    },
    {
        "question": "20,273 × 11,645=？",
        "answer": 8.373057513247998
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 7,289=？",
        "answer": 4.163697945892569
    },
    {
        "question": "280 × 274,578=？",
        "answer": 7.885823768680836
    },
    {
        "question": "470,090 ÷ 82,346=？",
        "answer": 0.7565385048108428
    },
    {
        "question": "28,053,720 ÷ 2,125=？",
        "answer": 4.120631523660506
    },
    {
        "question": "1,710 × 416,059=？",
        "answer": 8.852151031301497
    },
    {
        "question": "897 × 30,151=？",
        "answer": 7.432094163741816
    },
    {
        "question": "628 × 382,337=？",
        "answer": 8.380405971885143
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 3,555=？",
        "answer": 3.851869600729766
    },
    {
        "question": "303,411,971 ÷ 1,556,361=？",
        "answer": 2.2899223721868402
    },
    {
        "question": "12,112 × 710=？",
        "answer": 6.934474210875073
    },
    {
        "question": "877,791,313 ÷ 247=？",
        "answer": 6.550694325305757
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,963,846=？",
        "answer": 7.2931074284751265
    },
    {
        "question": "1,261,890 ÷ 785=？",
        "answer": 3.2061518420019053
    },
    {
        "question": "12,199 × 2,911=？",
        "answer": 7.550366436746196
    },
    {
        "question": "416,859,631 ÷ 2,985,877=？",
        "answer": 2.1449179262963574
    },
    {
        "question": "77,235,498 ÷ 278=？",
        "answer": 5.443772155223203
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 34,460=？",
        "answer": 6.055829212989897
    },
    {
        "question": "59,671,467 ÷ 241,209=？",
        "answer": 2.393373206753898
    },
    {
        "question": "102 × 2,417=？",
        "answer": 5.391876822169568
    },
    {
        "question": "4,640,768 ÷ 130,662=？",
        "answer": 1.5504405563245678
    },
    {
        "question": "11,422 ÷ 1,952=？",
        "answer": 0.7672623424980798
    },
    {
        "question": "1,527,888 ÷ 398=？",
        "answer": 3.5842084478958824
    },
    {
        "question": "59,889 ÷ 546=？",
        "answer": 2.040154418783083
    },
    {
        "question": "16,932,534 ÷ 11,232=？",
        "answer": 3.1782648615433144
    },
    {
        "question": "554,068,695 ÷ 740=？",
        "answer": 5.874331893390802
    },
    {
        "question": "508,139 ÷ 21,438=？",
        "answer": 1.3747982619884438
    },
    {
        "question": "5,759 × 75,974=？",
        "answer": 8.641012070962834
    },
    {
        "question": "6,724,089 ÷ 1,546=？",
        "answer": 3.6384239635422193
    },
    {
        "question": "224 × 19,981=？",
        "answer": 6.650865238140745
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 241=？",
        "answer": 2.3820170425748683
    },
    {
        "question": "383 × 11,375=？",
        "answer": 6.639150179297773
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 1,650,109=？",
        "answer": 8.24281849828777
    },
    {
        "question": "103,108 × 1,661=？",
        "answer": 8.233661995320427
    },
    {
        "question": "10,814 × 50,075=？",
        "answer": 8.73360732320522
    },
    {
        "question": "706 × 1,532=？",
        "answer": 6.034063466348389
    },
    {
        "question": "4,979,302 ÷ 840,438=？",
        "answer": 0.7726627869058126
    },
    {
        "question": "8,200 × 23,239=？",
        "answer": 8.280031288329813
    },
    {
        "question": "846 × 619=？",
        "answer": 5.719061012059141
    },
    {
        "question": "138,231 × 214=？",
        "answer": 7.471019223183247
    },
    {
        "question": "269,341,969 ÷ 919=？",
        "answer": 5.466988519281153
    },
    {
        "question": "5,738,168 ÷ 1,541,772=？",
        "answer": 0.5707531049935495
    },
    {
        "question": "8,623,416 ÷ 674=？",
        "answer": 4.107019440759407
    },
    {
        "question": "88,544,472 ÷ 10,306=？",
        "answer": 3.934071314415865
    },
    {
        "question": "138 × 5,962=？",
        "answer": 5.915271058097848
    },
    {
        "question": "3,720 × 33,071=？",
        "answer": 8.089990267178901
    },
    {
        "question": "52,337,574 ÷ 774,943=？",
        "answer": 1.8295438282749383
    },
    {
        "question": "6,739 × 2,132=？",
        "answer": 7.157382656726237
    },
    {
        "question": "668,127,243 ÷ 562,839,863=？",
        "answer": 0.07447433188899828
    },
    {
        "question": "6,084,068 ÷ 381=？",
        "answer": 4.2032690837256785
    },
    {
        "question": "614,624,252 ÷ 141,954=？",
        "answer": 3.63646205811457
    },
    {
        "question": "719,054 × 221=？",
        "answer": 8.201153780231271
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 351,902=？",
        "answer": 7.209179566793252
    },
    {
        "question": "136,455,714 ÷ 88,066=？",
        "answer": 3.1901834552765664
    },
    {
        "question": "2,131 ÷ 232=？",
        "answer": 0.9630954648233023
    },
    {
        "question": "635,279,169 ÷ 556=？",
        "answer": 6.057889823336591
    },
    {
        "question": "361 × 837,661=？",
        "answer": 8.480575497843368
    },
    {
        "question": "860 × 547,973=？",
        "answer": 8.673257611479963
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 16,168,062=？",
        "answer": 7.208657965908426
    },
    {
        "question": "205 × 1,019,775=？",
        "answer": 8.320258221996552
    },
    {
        "question": "10,814 × 2,404=？",
        "answer": 7.414920828570308
    },
    {
        "question": "28,482,662 ÷ 28,001,582=？",
        "answer": 0.007398007895397817
    },
    {
        "question": "123 × 923,256=？",
        "answer": 8.055227250138179
    },
    {
        "question": "134,340,863 ÷ 5,270,573=？",
        "answer": 1.4063503009613971
    },
    {
        "question": "17,211,272 ÷ 902,682=？",
        "answer": 1.28027818560765
    },
    {
        "question": "1,048,661 ÷ 6,994=？",
        "answer": 2.1759094887964965
    },
    {
        "question": "263,434,936 ÷ 18,947,680=？",
        "answer": 1.1431173278701616
    },
    {
        "question": "174,860,458 ÷ 608=？",
        "answer": 5.458788032298867
    },
    {
        "question": "128 × 2,288,057=？",
        "answer": 8.46667680903333
    },
    {
        "question": "194 × 5,126,026=？",
        "answer": 8.9975825345931
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 4,140=？",
        "answer": 5.048364105279886
    },
    {
        "question": "393,886,017 ÷ 479,255=？",
        "answer": 2.914803911070558
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 532=？",
        "answer": 3.2030328870147105
    },
    {
        "question": "1,197,563 ÷ 91,947=？",
        "answer": 1.1147608056804792
    },
    {
        "question": "53 × 2,870=？",
        "answer": 5.1821577663347815
    },
    {
        "question": "114,555,508 ÷ 5,175,619=？",
        "answer": 1.3450536770381354
    },
    {
        "question": "978,148,171 ÷ 86,737,331=？",
        "answer": 1.0521985928792161
    },
    {
        "question": "124 × 1,872,328=？",
        "answer": 8.365803617231016
    },
    {
        "question": "39,739,573 ÷ 910=？",
        "answer": 4.640181804002274
    },
    {
        "question": "5,903 × 85,397=？",
        "answer": 8.70251539739579
    },
    {
        "question": "218 × 58,520=？",
        "answer": 7.105760811057878
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 2,411,871=？",
        "answer": 6.3823540756545265
    },
    {
        "question": "378,910,259 ÷ 35,931,108=？",
        "answer": 1.0230657543042125
    },
    {
        "question": "216,808,958 ÷ 2,449=？",
        "answer": 4.947088437066344
    },
    {
        "question": "773 × 4,182=？",
        "answer": 6.509563522399978
    },
    {
        "question": "36,384 × 232=？",
        "answer": 6.92639842789854
    },
    {
        "question": "127,889,951 ÷ 6,078,992=？",
        "answer": 1.3230048491204547
    },
    {
        "question": "2,333 × 191,643=？",
        "answer": 8.6504076995253
    },
    {
        "question": "41,509 ÷ 1,994=？",
        "answer": 1.3184171168706447
    },
    {
        "question": "516 × 1,828=？",
        "answer": 5.974625893025024
    },
    {
        "question": "6,464,343 ÷ 148,614=？",
        "answer": 1.6384646686429158
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 2,124=？",
        "answer": 4.406335758457057
    },
    {
        "question": "166,944,162 ÷ 53,127=？",
        "answer": 3.4972559438145288
    },
    {
        "question": "393 × 444,896=？",
        "answer": 8.242651051457845
    },
    {
        "question": "50,979 × 339=？",
        "answer": 7.237591010333949
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 100,666=？",
        "answer": 5.002882812105568
    },
    {
        "question": "95,726,117 ÷ 91,465,247=？",
        "answer": 0.019774331185725007
    },
    {
        "question": "14,937,645 ÷ 13,040,853=？",
        "answer": 0.05897613456338432
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 454,335=？",
        "answer": 6.657376194268663
    },
    {
        "question": "10,385 × 12,641=？",
        "answer": 8.118187932199085
    },
    {
        "question": "94 × 525,271=？",
        "answer": 7.693511277841531
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 303=？",
        "answer": 3.180412632838324
    },
    {
        "question": "1,726,897 ÷ 202,735=？",
        "answer": 0.9303377036395907
    },
    {
        "question": "254,130,651 ÷ 2,543,826=？",
        "answer": 1.9995696471265618
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,076,920=？",
        "answer": 6.509304697247914
    },
    {
        "question": "11,163 × 953=？",
        "answer": 7.026873825379523
    },
    {
        "question": "428,768,124 ÷ 746=？",
        "answer": 5.759483663564936
    },
    {
        "question": "370,228 ÷ 150,258=？",
        "answer": 0.3916316570557015
    },
    {
        "question": "187,766,493 ÷ 169,293=？",
        "answer": 3.0449790937490033
    },
    {
        "question": "543,934 ÷ 125,142=？",
        "answer": 0.6381431148383983
    },
    {
        "question": "546,236 ÷ 207=？",
        "answer": 3.4214099737194323
    },
    {
        "question": "55,959 × 1,170=？",
        "answer": 7.816055806694573
    },
    {
        "question": "15,074,777 ÷ 961,225=？",
        "answer": 1.1954258387577583
    },
    {
        "question": "138,802,689 ÷ 73,366=？",
        "answer": 3.2769030382328017
    },
    {
        "question": "7,573 ÷ 2,686=？",
        "answer": 0.45016194849191626
    },
    {
        "question": "4,412,379 ÷ 1,514=？",
        "answer": 3.4645469338034207
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 59,036=？",
        "answer": 4.771116924072814
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 192,457,073=？",
        "answer": 8.886393867831186
    },
    {
        "question": "2,390 × 77,670=？",
        "answer": 8.268651206102673
    },
    {
        "question": "56,003 ÷ 210=？",
        "answer": 2.425991997424929
    },
    {
        "question": "97 × 2,996,080=？",
        "answer": 8.46332513978723
    },
    {
        "question": "121,248 × 2,564=？",
        "answer": 8.492592604441679
    },
    {
        "question": "49 × 3,115,584=？",
        "answer": 8.183735544893791
    },
    {
        "question": "738 × 1,428=？",
        "answer": 6.022784569263197
    },
    {
        "question": "891 × 11,665=？",
        "answer": 7.016762447166646
    },
    {
        "question": "79,635,723 ÷ 10,685,460=？",
        "answer": 0.8723147043928957
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 909=？",
        "answer": 3.43568513794163
    },
    {
        "question": "400,701,915 ÷ 30,033,442=？",
        "answer": 1.1252163103586352
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 144,080=？",
        "answer": 5.857573704147495
    },
    {
        "question": "284,152,424 ÷ 188,811=？",
        "answer": 3.1775240728040948
    },
    {
        "question": "61 × 2,755,578=？",
        "answer": 8.225542543781854
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 20,707,440=？",
        "answer": 8.928910268380221
    },
    {
        "question": "171,901,200 ÷ 30,046=？",
        "answer": 3.757492245491363
    },
    {
        "question": "2,443,800 ÷ 827,453=？",
        "answer": 0.4703223255993388
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 19,336,480=？",
        "answer": 8.240619927701761
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 1,024,925=？",
        "answer": 7.3117220822480835
    },
    {
        "question": "1,016 × 502,891=？",
        "answer": 8.708367571277492
    },
    {
        "question": "3,039,023 ÷ 6,262=？",
        "answer": 2.686020923648433
    },
    {
        "question": "169 × 44,869=？",
        "answer": 6.879833095088993
    },
    {
        "question": "4,373 × 10,515=？",
        "answer": 7.662588754367197
    },
    {
        "question": "817,887 × 386=？",
        "answer": 8.499280609973345
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,302,076=？",
        "answer": 7.061089661525442
    },
    {
        "question": "54,486 × 780=？",
        "answer": 7.62837952875036
    },
    {
        "question": "165,406 × 290=？",
        "answer": 7.6809492571640305
    },
    {
        "question": "196,908,809 ÷ 136,580,461=？",
        "answer": 0.15887657110476364
    },
    {
        "question": "129,699,560 ÷ 24,316,625=？",
        "answer": 0.7270352054172936
    },
    {
        "question": "1,214 × 7,363=？",
        "answer": 6.95127348721594
    },
    {
        "question": "3,473,940 ÷ 467,648=？",
        "answer": 0.8709032319489474
    },
    {
        "question": "336,906 × 575=？",
        "answer": 8.287176590142963
    },
    {
        "question": "18,068,818 ÷ 2,592,554=？",
        "answer": 0.843201932413524
    },
    {
        "question": "11,175 ÷ 5,916=？",
        "answer": 0.27621936647911927
    },
    {
        "question": "307,748,110 ÷ 337,029=？",
        "answer": 2.9605281226558042
    },
    {
        "question": "19,509,020 ÷ 620,155=？",
        "answer": 1.4977352044027936
    },
    {
        "question": "374,752 ÷ 206,705=？",
        "answer": 0.2583929773661904
    },
    {
        "question": "106,596,648 ÷ 8,673,747=？",
        "answer": 1.0895367979482231
    },
    {
        "question": "210,803,654 ÷ 570,651=？",
        "answer": 2.5675075518672887
    },
    {
        "question": "1,502,480 × 233=？",
        "answer": 8.544164620704159
    },
    {
        "question": "5,086,099 ÷ 600,527=？",
        "answer": 0.9278522711066
    },
    {
        "question": "44,380,785 ÷ 3,679,015=？",
        "answer": 1.0814634211622827
    },
    {
        "question": "11,942 ÷ 4,801=？",
        "answer": 0.39574536087659534
    },
    {
        "question": "125,870 ÷ 3,425=？",
        "answer": 1.5652616563684776
    },
    {
        "question": "671,857,257 ÷ 564=？",
        "answer": 6.07599790853144
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 4,121,107=？",
        "answer": 8.106375584482688
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 114,644,997=？",
        "answer": 8.758325111612171
    },
    {
        "question": "103 × 10,422=？",
        "answer": 6.030788293535914
    },
    {
        "question": "246,282,393 ÷ 796=？",
        "answer": 5.490520297019546
    },
    {
        "question": "691,672 × 873=？",
        "answer": 8.780914438797836
    },
    {
        "question": "25,400 ÷ 359=？",
        "answer": 1.849739268041619
    },
    {
        "question": "324,434,765 ÷ 126,631=？",
        "answer": 3.4085873486219227
    },
    {
        "question": "123 × 3,315,297=？",
        "answer": 8.610427552078647
    },
    {
        "question": "15,849,563 ÷ 476=？",
        "answer": 4.522410339744638
    },
    {
        "question": "1,097 × 5,485=？",
        "answer": 6.779383259485441
    },
    {
        "question": "965,152 × 428=？",
        "answer": 8.616039483976511
    },
    {
        "question": "13,790,343 ÷ 4,568,217=？",
        "answer": 0.47982834265291074
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 1,383,897=？",
        "answer": 7.84007377220513
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 5,109=？",
        "answer": 4.854463938360501
    },
    {
        "question": "1,621 ÷ 667=？",
        "answer": 0.385657180931966
    },
    {
        "question": "1,474 × 45,090=？",
        "answer": 7.822577718829603
    },
    {
        "question": "338,446,830 ÷ 121,000=？",
        "answer": 3.4467050803964696
    },
    {
        "question": "92,454,441 ÷ 6,851=？",
        "answer": 4.1301738095817715
    },
    {
        "question": "2,577 × 1,428=？",
        "answer": 6.565842625991061
    },
    {
        "question": "308,796,487 ÷ 630,354=？",
        "answer": 2.690087837918011
    },
    {
        "question": "345 × 12,684=？",
        "answer": 6.641075328428325
    },
    {
        "question": "46 × 20,288,924=？",
        "answer": 8.970016847011928
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 1,526,067=？",
        "answer": 7.827026277661752
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 1,699=？",
        "answer": 4.3763214145472835
    },
    {
        "question": "71 × 265=？",
        "answer": 4.274504222655883
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 15,188=？",
        "answer": 5.0265986284820166
    },
    {
        "question": "63,461,583 ÷ 2,669=？",
        "answer": 4.3761623272512375
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 424=？",
        "answer": 3.104487111312395
    },
    {
        "question": "499 × 10,676=？",
        "answer": 6.72650911073886
    },
    {
        "question": "99 × 2,068=？",
        "answer": 5.311185729019455
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 12,662,069=？",
        "answer": 7.947602715827225
    },
    {
        "question": "3,971 × 1,292=？",
        "answer": 6.710162400722949
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 22,129=？",
        "answer": 5.123113039173326
    },
    {
        "question": "13,547 × 234=？",
        "answer": 6.5010589882148375
    },
    {
        "question": "50,683,844 ÷ 13,361,950=？",
        "answer": 0.5789997032259432
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 587,026=？",
        "answer": 6.546808587417401
    },
    {
        "question": "416,545,513 ÷ 402,824,943=？",
        "answer": 0.01454610632620331
    },
    {
        "question": "8,213 ÷ 4,271=？",
        "answer": 0.28397225140049004
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 305=？",
        "answer": 4.107549129744687
    },
    {
        "question": "420 × 1,841=？",
        "answer": 5.888303078901915
    },
    {
        "question": "54,112,299 ÷ 772,422=？",
        "answer": 1.8454413508488734
    },
    {
        "question": "10,532,320 ÷ 3,851=？",
        "answer": 3.4369505270375607
    },
    {
        "question": "25,319,792 ÷ 1,736,394=？",
        "answer": 1.1638118571746212
    },
    {
        "question": "64,637 ÷ 13,492=？",
        "answer": 0.6804048587877224
    },
    {
        "question": "4,914,090 ÷ 47,267=？",
        "answer": 2.016885067340485
    },
    {
        "question": "15,013 × 2,620=？",
        "answer": 7.5947687759188796
    },
    {
        "question": "11,145,036 ÷ 40,395=？",
        "answer": 2.4407538631822723
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 40,847=？",
        "answer": 5.933379460099549
    },
    {
        "question": "135,887 ÷ 3,120=？",
        "answer": 1.6390233167367307
    },
    {
        "question": "189 × 85,496=？",
        "answer": 7.208407600555632
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 33,131,169=？",
        "answer": 7.520236759796616
    },
    {
        "question": "76 × 4,309=？",
        "answer": 5.515190086369159
    },
    {
        "question": "806,846,447 ÷ 155,765,249=？",
        "answer": 0.714320317221036
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 451,873=？",
        "answer": 7.0167442284633665
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 253,498=？",
        "answer": 6.922488477147281
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 8,865,980=？",
        "answer": 8.026907993324562
    },
    {
        "question": "395 × 140,216=？",
        "answer": 7.743394669280194
    },
    {
        "question": "107,296,694 ÷ 93,374,027=？",
        "answer": 0.06036025149447464
    },
    {
        "question": "1,116,392 ÷ 539=？",
        "answer": 3.316227950512062
    },
    {
        "question": "830,412,847 ÷ 421=？",
        "answer": 6.295011963524749
    },
    {
        "question": "190,267,655 ÷ 377,480=？",
        "answer": 2.702471019267598
    },
    {
        "question": "261,667 ÷ 2,842=？",
        "answer": 1.964124881675165
    },
    {
        "question": "264,478,647 ÷ 4,101=？",
        "answer": 4.809500845214475
    },
    {
        "question": "1,329 × 18,251=？",
        "answer": 7.38481164604119
    },
    {
        "question": "2,204,085 ÷ 136,967=？",
        "answer": 1.2066123954877317
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 1,959,592=？",
        "answer": 7.672376899499906
    },
    {
        "question": "879,930 ÷ 3,106=？",
        "answer": 2.452246673231592
    },
    {
        "question": "771,002 ÷ 374=？",
        "answer": 3.3141839024235473
    },
    {
        "question": "1,720 × 129,162=？",
        "answer": 8.346663208107419
    },
    {
        "question": "4,869 × 22,218=？",
        "answer": 8.03414473697898
    },
    {
        "question": "109,044,386 ÷ 43,788=？",
        "answer": 3.396248202024847
    },
    {
        "question": "119 × 210,211=？",
        "answer": 7.398202399603813
    },
    {
        "question": "54,151,034 ÷ 872=？",
        "answer": 4.793090268848844
    },
    {
        "question": "4,959 × 65,985=？",
        "answer": 8.514839329323655
    },
    {
        "question": "14,485,740 ÷ 375,791=？",
        "answer": 1.58599431115839
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 700,972=？",
        "answer": 5.845700670622354
    },
    {
        "question": "148,118,588 ÷ 6,815,553=？",
        "answer": 1.3371084639459747
    },
    {
        "question": "183 × 3,857,210=？",
        "answer": 8.848724373750343
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 1,946,839=？",
        "answer": 6.766451292370823
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 4,144,161=？",
        "answer": 7.316406623672942
    },
    {
        "question": "76,341 ÷ 26,662=？",
        "answer": 0.4568651204392914
    },
    {
        "question": "652,204 ÷ 71,428=？",
        "answer": 0.9605149680760408
    },
    {
        "question": "167,494,172 ÷ 1,168,655=？",
        "answer": 2.1563133787508457
    },
    {
        "question": "3,390 × 4,056=？",
        "answer": 7.138297644528362
    },
    {
        "question": "127 × 218,581=？",
        "answer": 7.443416129467272
    },
    {
        "question": "56,983,718 ÷ 18,671,595=？",
        "answer": 0.48456936346175916
    },
    {
        "question": "89,230,425 ÷ 599=？",
        "answer": 5.1730861391242575
    },
    {
        "question": "5,668 × 1,376=？",
        "answer": 6.892048275474916
    },
    {
        "question": "23,346 × 1,923=？",
        "answer": 7.652191765425866
    },
    {
        "question": "4,739,007 ÷ 6,202=？",
        "answer": 2.8831555882961157
    },
    {
        "question": "578,852,975 ÷ 13,213=？",
        "answer": 4.64156683468851
    },
    {
        "question": "717,256 ÷ 377,623=？",
        "answer": 0.2786157517605893
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 10,211=？",
        "answer": 4.486189530911881
    },
    {
        "question": "27 × 9,011,479=？",
        "answer": 8.38615983913646
    },
    {
        "question": "9,624 ÷ 2,074=？",
        "answer": 0.6665468622787661
    },
    {
        "question": "26,523 ÷ 644=？",
        "answer": 1.614736777929438
    },
    {
        "question": "850,667 × 239=？",
        "answer": 8.308157486455656
    },
    {
        "question": "111 × 6,756=？",
        "answer": 5.875012619685629
    },
    {
        "question": "5,824,926 ÷ 220=？",
        "answer": 4.422867731623352
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 27,840=？",
        "answer": 4.921790485658187
    },
    {
        "question": "4,170,903 ÷ 677,628=？",
        "answer": 0.7892387468518713
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 5,250,350=？",
        "answer": 7.761580940564587
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 10,024,363=？",
        "answer": 7.001056784845883
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 18,548=？",
        "answer": 4.745418341943429
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 44,865=？",
        "answer": 5.606150181526324
    },
    {
        "question": "136,274,506 ÷ 668=？",
        "answer": 5.3096381538938795
    },
    {
        "question": "2,741,574 ÷ 5,500=？",
        "answer": 2.6976372832705517
    },
    {
        "question": "444 × 3,886=？",
        "answer": 6.236885766378384
    },
    {
        "question": "153,344 × 3,113=？",
        "answer": 8.678845908383677
    },
    {
        "question": "17,808,806 ÷ 640,237=？",
        "answer": 1.44429403406712
    },
    {
        "question": "6,197,124 ÷ 328=？",
        "answer": 4.276316342445581
    },
    {
        "question": "740,891,901 ÷ 338,796,922=？",
        "answer": 0.33981539128047755
    },
    {
        "question": "1,418 ÷ 873=？",
        "answer": 0.21066198714147802
    },
    {
        "question": "2,823 × 791=？",
        "answer": 6.3488873616445956
    },
    {
        "question": "14,795 ÷ 3,063=？",
        "answer": 0.6839679726900791
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 169,645=？",
        "answer": 5.229541064073035
    },
    {
        "question": "65 × 2,294,314=？",
        "answer": 8.173566211853785
    },
    {
        "question": "8,828,081 ÷ 2,548=？",
        "answer": 3.5396668856124003
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,562,828=？",
        "answer": 7.046325627633265
    },
    {
        "question": "394,327 ÷ 2,494=？",
        "answer": 2.198960065565896
    },
    {
        "question": "112,908 ÷ 42,121=？",
        "answer": 0.4282260413039272
    },
    {
        "question": "495,217 ÷ 253,726=？",
        "answer": 0.29043057204599243
    },
    {
        "question": "244,472 ÷ 17,564=？",
        "answer": 1.1436056970238588
    },
    {
        "question": "72,125,334 ÷ 169,707=？",
        "answer": 2.6283880810357045
    },
    {
        "question": "499,573 × 974=？",
        "answer": 8.687157915267909
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 789,017=？",
        "answer": 7.175839961483739
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 1,775,309=？",
        "answer": 6.249273954751932
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 328,748,502=？",
        "answer": 8.51686378256362
    },
    {
        "question": "75 × 2,783,966=？",
        "answer": 8.319725190414077
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 232=？",
        "answer": 4.279301837274616
    },
    {
        "question": "48,671 × 730=？",
        "answer": 7.550593129520329
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,170,441=？",
        "answer": 6.93860797605569
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,075=？",
        "answer": 3.6180480967120925
    },
    {
        "question": "2,838 × 16,941=？",
        "answer": 7.681951433577997
    },
    {
        "question": "20,501,146 ÷ 46,703=？",
        "answer": 2.6424333598248126
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,111,100=？",
        "answer": 6.74472315193016
    },
    {
        "question": "56,632 × 1,617=？",
        "answer": 7.9617719192271945
    },
    {
        "question": "33 × 196,587=？",
        "answer": 6.812068735088472
    },
    {
        "question": "166,391,265 ÷ 97,089=？",
        "answer": 3.233960495553836
    },
    {
        "question": "33,157,081 ÷ 5,846,195=？",
        "answer": 0.7537029930641269
    },
    {
        "question": "47 × 2,440,640=？",
        "answer": 8.059601582644337
    },
    {
        "question": "316,007 ÷ 20,267=？",
        "answer": 1.1929072354635553
    },
    {
        "question": "706,917,875 ÷ 58,307,915=？",
        "answer": 1.0836414512872579
    },
    {
        "question": "36,610 × 398=？",
        "answer": 7.163482800955219
    },
    {
        "question": "180 × 351=？",
        "answer": 4.80057962156913
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 86,985=？",
        "answer": 5.893686877243222
    },
    {
        "question": "288 × 1,521=？",
        "answer": 5.64152170181223
    },
    {
        "question": "700,675,862 ÷ 610=？",
        "answer": 6.060187321471292
    },
    {
        "question": "3,908,661 ÷ 1,518,425=？",
        "answer": 0.4106346599490891
    },
    {
        "question": "644 ÷ 221=？",
        "answer": 0.4644935936747014
    },
    {
        "question": "2,346,208 ÷ 7,909=？",
        "answer": 2.4722449357541443
    },
    {
        "question": "302,576,792 ÷ 12,272=？",
        "answer": 4.391920267456135
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 5,375,731=？",
        "answer": 7.031467524285172
    },
    {
        "question": "46,700 × 20,009=？",
        "answer": 8.97054226478782
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 585,155=？",
        "answer": 7.681084772702453
    },
    {
        "question": "15,718 × 1,724=？",
        "answer": 7.432934545926037
    },
    {
        "question": "116,235,388 ÷ 3,765,865=？",
        "answer": 1.4894736224250296
    },
    {
        "question": "503,358,355 ÷ 1,135=？",
        "answer": 5.646881420120524
    },
    {
        "question": "5,937,794 ÷ 4,528=？",
        "answer": 3.1177187083544564
    },
    {
        "question": "501 × 248=？",
        "answer": 5.094289406693462
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 32,937,556=？",
        "answer": 8.663819406617261
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 51,767,025=？",
        "answer": 7.714053207222368
    },
    {
        "question": "682,815 ÷ 23,230=？",
        "answer": 1.4682538432776011
    },
    {
        "question": "2,048 ÷ 1,432=？",
        "answer": 0.1553869343319564
    },
    {
        "question": "27,718,592 ÷ 3,952=？",
        "answer": 3.8459542300616656
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 167,897=？",
        "answer": 5.526072931855123
    },
    {
        "question": "97,159 ÷ 2,662=？",
        "answer": 1.5622749850817477
    },
    {
        "question": "29,405,375 ÷ 9,831,460=？",
        "answer": 0.47580870563403993
    },
    {
        "question": "8,850,048 ÷ 588,715=？",
        "answer": 1.1770405247484061
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 2,979=？",
        "answer": 5.097319793612944
    },
    {
        "question": "22,131 ÷ 611=？",
        "answer": 1.5589598279354877
    },
    {
        "question": "593,981,853 ÷ 1,252,821=？",
        "answer": 2.6758841523694477
    },
    {
        "question": "224 × 749=？",
        "answer": 5.224729836033629
    },
    {
        "question": "1,679,705 ÷ 37,588=？",
        "answer": 1.6501837968033644
    },
    {
        "question": "149,226 × 2,759=？",
        "answer": 8.614596198366414
    },
    {
        "question": "28,801 ÷ 10,615=？",
        "answer": 0.43348756866493005
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 1,472,196=？",
        "answer": 7.5481768751179
    },
    {
        "question": "141,777,529 ÷ 5,502,283=？",
        "answer": 1.4110644791063391
    },
    {
        "question": "468,916,074 ÷ 42,834,924=？",
        "answer": 1.0392971195093625
    },
    {
        "question": "199,580,462 ÷ 3,454,284=？",
        "answer": 1.7617599826404726
    },
    {
        "question": "42,634,131 ÷ 91,257=？",
        "answer": 2.669491227710383
    },
    {
        "question": "2,781 × 246=？",
        "answer": 5.835136095967538
    },
    {
        "question": "5,319 × 776=？",
        "answer": 6.615691711578768
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 681,079=？",
        "answer": 6.134227485365586
    },
    {
        "question": "157,306 ÷ 40,583=？",
        "answer": 0.5884011398428239
    },
    {
        "question": "480,388 ÷ 7,473=？",
        "answer": 1.8080971680174267
    },
    {
        "question": "563,262,272 ÷ 5,474=？",
        "answer": 5.012405869556689
    },
    {
        "question": "108,274 ÷ 498=？",
        "answer": 2.337294838591713
    },
    {
        "question": "11,014,633 ÷ 21,998=？",
        "answer": 2.6995868336232984
    },
    {
        "question": "220,031 ÷ 208=？",
        "answer": 3.0244205375889424
    },
    {
        "question": "686,888 ÷ 115,572=？",
        "answer": 0.774033300368153
    },
    {
        "question": "26,033 × 623=？",
        "answer": 7.2100122650323994
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 1,066,501=？",
        "answer": 6.3289912626639415
    },
    {
        "question": "289,601 ÷ 545=？",
        "answer": 2.7254035548815194
    },
    {
        "question": "1,052,677 ÷ 70,342=？",
        "answer": 1.1750804218727204
    },
    {
        "question": "42 × 9,402=？",
        "answer": 5.596469537250134
    },
    {
        "question": "12,971,118 ÷ 186,339=？",
        "answer": 1.842673649695841
    },
    {
        "question": "69,671,659 ÷ 237=？",
        "answer": 5.468307805933498
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 2,212=？",
        "answer": 4.548905105288585
    },
    {
        "question": "157,785,490 ÷ 1,515,486=？",
        "answer": 2.017515134134687
    },
    {
        "question": "314 × 17,403=？",
        "answer": 6.737553768260474
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 5,675,263=？",
        "answer": 8.201144023516129
    },
    {
        "question": "1,669 × 2,281=？",
        "answer": 6.580581621955895
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 1,358=？",
        "answer": 3.7349597612724454
    },
    {
        "question": "3,177 × 196,265=？",
        "answer": 8.794860073458617
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 679=？",
        "answer": 3.5308397786165204
    },
    {
        "question": "291,954 × 227=？",
        "answer": 7.821340286998025
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 355=？",
        "answer": 4.518711301609029
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 10,484,080=？",
        "answer": 7.497651580941764
    },
    {
        "question": "66,439 × 5,216=？",
        "answer": 8.539760669812217
    },
    {
        "question": "1,643,513 ÷ 298,029=？",
        "answer": 0.7415146180740434
    },
    {
        "question": "358,377,493 ÷ 958=？",
        "answer": 5.572975217991804
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 186,328=？",
        "answer": 6.1153761623918275
    },
    {
        "question": "916,140,390 ÷ 488,988=？",
        "answer": 3.272663828900969
    },
    {
        "question": "19,134,013 ÷ 1,557=？",
        "answer": 4.089517452126233
    },
    {
        "question": "585,196,849 ÷ 721=？",
        "answer": 5.909366714275887
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 2,209,633=？",
        "answer": 6.645350142964288
    },
    {
        "question": "291,205,871 ÷ 13,115,185=？",
        "answer": 1.3464257055031439
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,000=？",
        "answer": 3.9542425094393248
    },
    {
        "question": "863,353 ÷ 1,249=？",
        "answer": 2.839625964069534
    },
    {
        "question": "488,574,525 ÷ 22,819,939=？",
        "answer": 1.330616339298908
    },
    {
        "question": "1,010,956 ÷ 186,105=？",
        "answer": 0.7349742128504052
    },
    {
        "question": "67,411,493 ÷ 14,916,614=？",
        "answer": 0.6550636942532181
    },
    {
        "question": "101 × 1,130,601=？",
        "answer": 8.05763073903401
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 25,255=？",
        "answer": 5.632796294226642
    },
    {
        "question": "1,685,282 ÷ 1,288,372=？",
        "answer": 0.11663130444621271
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 731=？",
        "answer": 2.8639173769578603
    },
    {
        "question": "59,595 ÷ 1,211=？",
        "answer": 1.692065680967992
    },
    {
        "question": "18,593,042 ÷ 5,418=？",
        "answer": 3.5355114496306284
    },
    {
        "question": "88 × 1,811=？",
        "answer": 5.202401122464227
    },
    {
        "question": "109,465,232 ÷ 15,465,891=？",
        "answer": 0.8499012567943235
    },
    {
        "question": "147 × 1,153,944=？",
        "answer": 8.22950206810766
    },
    {
        "question": "42,145,384 ÷ 40,362=？",
        "answer": 3.018777337119519
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,831,405=？",
        "answer": 6.7657732048847965
    },
    {
        "question": "29 × 16,031,234=？",
        "answer": 8.667364951242746
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 21,269=？",
        "answer": 4.9298070625804185
    },
    {
        "question": "44,434 ÷ 2,133=？",
        "answer": 1.318724555242126
    },
    {
        "question": "13,813,050 ÷ 4,379=？",
        "answer": 3.498914638666711
    },
    {
        "question": "2,531 × 34,592=？",
        "answer": 7.94226781743147
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 7,390=？",
        "answer": 4.345765693114489
    },
    {
        "question": "318,019,180 ÷ 17,264,922=？",
        "answer": 1.2652886928131972
    },
    {
        "question": "7,713 × 1,450=？",
        "answer": 7.048591333597498
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 587=？",
        "answer": 4.047391702200444
    },
    {
        "question": "999 × 891,314=？",
        "answer": 8.949596216330141
    },
    {
        "question": "117,650,222 ÷ 67,584,595=？",
        "answer": 0.24074503537227648
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 506,114=？",
        "answer": 7.0052783464852215
    },
    {
        "question": "567,942,660 ÷ 26,697=？",
        "answer": 4.327842029673963
    },
    {
        "question": "4,856 × 100,624=？",
        "answer": 8.688980255451673
    },
    {
        "question": "24,642 × 3,151=？",
        "answer": 7.890124356411295
    },
    {
        "question": "2,115 × 58,435=？",
        "answer": 8.091983420087146
    },
    {
        "question": "393 × 103,728=？",
        "answer": 7.610288554634256
    },
    {
        "question": "21,523 ÷ 8,035=？",
        "answer": 0.4279169245864279
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 8,687,200=？",
        "answer": 7.893122329559025
    },
    {
        "question": "745,324 ÷ 29,532=？",
        "answer": 1.402052246317806
    },
    {
        "question": "10,355,526 ÷ 1,253=？",
        "answer": 3.917221092408736
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 80,004=？",
        "answer": 4.903111701173189
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 1,603=？",
        "answer": 3.9830847727377883
    },
    {
        "question": "4,893 × 21,399=？",
        "answer": 8.019968694500283
    },
    {
        "question": "50 × 7,033,976=？",
        "answer": 8.546170886502136
    },
    {
        "question": "2,979,564 × 322=？",
        "answer": 8.982008590051477
    },
    {
        "question": "232,348,498 ÷ 6,851=？",
        "answer": 4.5303859018394235
    },
    {
        "question": "409,717,826 ÷ 20,570=？",
        "answer": 4.299250567950433
    },
    {
        "question": "1,173,196 ÷ 768,369=？",
        "answer": 0.18380073874243014
    },
    {
        "question": "44,952,583 ÷ 1,748,779=？",
        "answer": 1.4100197221201858
    },
    {
        "question": "104 × 836,955=？",
        "answer": 7.939735447498658
    },
    {
        "question": "2,200,696 ÷ 39,317=？",
        "answer": 1.7479796815667152
    },
    {
        "question": "3,791,969 ÷ 1,061=？",
        "answer": 3.553149394346974
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 255=？",
        "answer": 2.406540180433955
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 351=？",
        "answer": 3.1473671077937864
    },
    {
        "question": "195,416,826 ÷ 2,361,670=？",
        "answer": 1.9177427422653501
    },
    {
        "question": "148,033 ÷ 422=？",
        "answer": 2.545046089570766
    },
    {
        "question": "1,409 × 4,340=？",
        "answer": 6.786400722621867
    },
    {
        "question": "218,209 ÷ 200=？",
        "answer": 3.0378426633735396
    },
    {
        "question": "277 × 890,011=？",
        "answer": 8.391875143360798
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 662=？",
        "answer": 2.8208579894397
    },
    {
        "question": "408 × 22,091=？",
        "answer": 6.954875538746379
    },
    {
        "question": "9,380 ÷ 2,853=？",
        "answer": 0.5169010667219881
    },
    {
        "question": "1,826 × 335,644=？",
        "answer": 8.787379661304406
    },
    {
        "question": "44 × 7,077,310=？",
        "answer": 8.493320895454564
    },
    {
        "question": "250,122 × 437=？",
        "answer": 8.038633329654134
    },
    {
        "question": "83 × 67,215=？",
        "answer": 6.7465442953447985
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 6,918,271=？",
        "answer": 7.7942400794766495
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 4,617=？",
        "answer": 4.2664198658791035
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 613,146,547=？",
        "answer": 8.787564286830081
    },
    {
        "question": "130 × 3,373=？",
        "answer": 5.641959693496038
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 3,544=？",
        "answer": 4.151553704542976
    },
    {
        "question": "155 × 597=？",
        "answer": 4.966306029299661
    },
    {
        "question": "460,123 ÷ 7,551=？",
        "answer": 1.784869472458686
    },
    {
        "question": "74,776 ÷ 2,343=？",
        "answer": 1.5039899410847002
    },
    {
        "question": "43 × 321,754=？",
        "answer": 7.140992410276848
    },
    {
        "question": "15,145 ÷ 432=？",
        "answer": 1.5447855308539624
    },
    {
        "question": "3,615 × 1,851=？",
        "answer": 6.825514720383453
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 24,826=？",
        "answer": 5.985971358080525
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 24,248=？",
        "answer": 5.426068608517791
    },
    {
        "question": "6,987,905 ÷ 1,035=？",
        "answer": 3.8294066423599387
    },
    {
        "question": "537,728,018 ÷ 3,287=？",
        "answer": 5.213762961641884
    },
    {
        "question": "603,353,335 ÷ 157,489=？",
        "answer": 3.583321492224475
    },
    {
        "question": "1,591,910 ÷ 3,198=？",
        "answer": 2.6970400514736923
    },
    {
        "question": "252,316,311 ÷ 225,838=？",
        "answer": 3.0481483073276596
    },
    {
        "question": "36,255,427 ÷ 177,762=？",
        "answer": 2.3095340965463227
    },
    {
        "question": "406,852,522 ÷ 3,622=？",
        "answer": 5.050488566469332
    },
    {
        "question": "20 × 1,242=？",
        "answer": 4.3951515915045425
    },
    {
        "question": "1,228,614 ÷ 668,980=？",
        "answer": 0.26400232559621456
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 24,835=？",
        "answer": 5.173215414714885
    },
    {
        "question": "367,679,317 ÷ 86,555=？",
        "answer": 3.6281770395532362
    },
    {
        "question": "148,808 ÷ 312=？",
        "answer": 2.6784716857294675
    },
    {
        "question": "140 × 772,906=？",
        "answer": 8.034254714378369
    },
    {
        "question": "954,427,774 ÷ 259=？",
        "answer": 6.566443304803408
    },
    {
        "question": "26,103 ÷ 1,264=？",
        "answer": 1.3149433494291978
    },
    {
        "question": "8,215 × 12,424=？",
        "answer": 8.008869010491583
    },
    {
        "question": "736 × 26,420=？",
        "answer": 7.288810627616007
    },
    {
        "question": "714,459 ÷ 349,198=？",
        "answer": 0.3109055637267472
    },
    {
        "question": "1,596 × 53,281=？",
        "answer": 7.929605254273171
    },
    {
        "question": "2,736,220 ÷ 1,404,994=？",
        "answer": 0.28947654338529
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 404,945=？",
        "answer": 6.753524076624872
    },
    {
        "question": "727 × 381=？",
        "answer": 5.442459386534657
    },
    {
        "question": "149,316 × 3,691=？",
        "answer": 8.741250392367444
    },
    {
        "question": "23,943 × 1,101=？",
        "answer": 7.420965884499881
    },
    {
        "question": "7,247 ÷ 2,390=？",
        "answer": 0.4817603603701406
    },
    {
        "question": "255,611 ÷ 25,248=？",
        "answer": 1.0053525578494746
    },
    {
        "question": "431,425 ÷ 1,030=？",
        "answer": 2.622068083069845
    },
    {
        "question": "80 × 1,391=？",
        "answer": 5.04641711698399
    },
    {
        "question": "439 × 4,296=？",
        "answer": 6.2755287929336205
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,802,563=？",
        "answer": 7.0496153753941995
    },
    {
        "question": "452,537 × 1,010=？",
        "answer": 8.659975467244099
    },
    {
        "question": "13,981 × 332=？",
        "answer": 6.666676319416269
    },
    {
        "question": "137,770 ÷ 6,288=？",
        "answer": 1.3406421253755527
    },
    {
        "question": "441 × 32,167=？",
        "answer": 7.151849148529603
    },
    {
        "question": "5,973 ÷ 614=？",
        "answer": 0.9880241436059043
    },
    {
        "question": "87,448 ÷ 292=？",
        "answer": 2.4763670298460214
    },
    {
        "question": "2,704 × 223,897=？",
        "answer": 8.782054961767903
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 26,804=？",
        "answer": 4.428199609263877
    },
    {
        "question": "3,102 × 32,522=？",
        "answer": 8.00381903895606
    },
    {
        "question": "185,726,069 ÷ 182,320,876=？",
        "answer": 0.008036467896270709
    },
    {
        "question": "1,752 × 742=？",
        "answer": 6.113938007111089
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 4,919=？",
        "answer": 5.2600785466263265
    },
    {
        "question": "6,045,281 ÷ 513=？",
        "answer": 4.071299127663648
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 10,488=？",
        "answer": 5.275965183785334
    },
    {
        "question": "18,992,452 ÷ 682=？",
        "answer": 4.444796662820187
    },
    {
        "question": "106 × 53,342=？",
        "answer": 6.752375160320919
    },
    {
        "question": "1,894,007 ÷ 18,463=？",
        "answer": 2.0110793100749453
    },
    {
        "question": "2,653,645 ÷ 5,977=？",
        "answer": 2.6473595674222348
    },
    {
        "question": "31 × 5,873,926=？",
        "answer": 8.260290164792913
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 252,715=？",
        "answer": 5.402631020407813
    },
    {
        "question": "589,124,710 ÷ 441,220=？",
        "answer": 3.1255520486953143
    },
    {
        "question": "37,850 × 6,950=？",
        "answer": 8.420050688426205
    },
    {
        "question": "3,547,249 × 225=？",
        "answer": 8.902074193059333
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 15,181=？",
        "answer": 4.880270384602839
    },
    {
        "question": "59,528 ÷ 14,511=？",
        "answer": 0.6130239494213795
    },
    {
        "question": "232,455,893 ÷ 77,130,443=？",
        "answer": 0.47911473473061716
    },
    {
        "question": "1,232 × 654=？",
        "answer": 5.906188456152674
    },
    {
        "question": "357,948,663 ÷ 139,193,747=？",
        "answer": 0.4102010186881674
    },
    {
        "question": "63,693,683 ÷ 3,794,324=？",
        "answer": 1.2249619492475374
    },
    {
        "question": "420,490 × 323=？",
        "answer": 8.132958194292716
    },
    {
        "question": "146,755 ÷ 16,628=？",
        "answer": 0.9457528909196666
    },
    {
        "question": "766,830,009 ÷ 846=？",
        "answer": 5.957328737108699
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 89,612=？",
        "answer": 4.952366170207074
    },
    {
        "question": "1,955 × 38,785=？",
        "answer": 7.87981055751209
    },
    {
        "question": "10,304 ÷ 985=？",
        "answer": 1.0195696195181252
    },
    {
        "question": "10,013 × 641=？",
        "answer": 6.807422245684193
    },
    {
        "question": "7,861,863 ÷ 811,504=？",
        "answer": 0.9862348067230968
    },
    {
        "question": "952 × 301,445=？",
        "answer": 8.457845033101293
    },
    {
        "question": "246,228,878 ÷ 1,287,521=？",
        "answer": 2.281584664834488
    },
    {
        "question": "18,457,165 ÷ 4,385=？",
        "answer": 3.6241953969613583
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 49,326,111=？",
        "answer": 8.693076875895553
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 431,495=？",
        "answer": 6.112097022360715
    },
    {
        "question": "279,636,236 ÷ 47,013=？",
        "answer": 3.774375482411564
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 20,659=？",
        "answer": 5.160207335659003
    },
    {
        "question": "443,545,799 ÷ 944=？",
        "answer": 5.671966475926141
    },
    {
        "question": "8,164,810 ÷ 1,554=？",
        "answer": 3.720495068433676
    },
    {
        "question": "2,637,701 ÷ 305,945=？",
        "answer": 0.9355822039891916
    },
    {
        "question": "22,601 × 25,502=？",
        "answer": 8.760701896702818
    },
    {
        "question": "11,677,509 ÷ 57,143=？",
        "answer": 2.3103871736275017
    },
    {
        "question": "4,367,982 ÷ 116,221=？",
        "answer": 1.574996232100398
    },
    {
        "question": "11,023 × 27,818=？",
        "answer": 8.486625710201679
    },
    {
        "question": "66 × 482=？",
        "answer": 4.502590973780718
    },
    {
        "question": "2,317 × 133,810=？",
        "answer": 8.49141460449035
    },
    {
        "question": "60,811 × 826=？",
        "answer": 7.700962192501036
    },
    {
        "question": "1,442,155 ÷ 10,110=？",
        "answer": 2.154260784422845
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 59,620=？",
        "answer": 5.816784656854837
    },
    {
        "question": "18,603 × 10,745=？",
        "answer": 8.300789405894076
    },
    {
        "question": "90,462,307 ÷ 1,311,313=？",
        "answer": 1.8387612923663277
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 334=？",
        "answer": 3.2227164711475833
    },
    {
        "question": "3,233 × 5,149=？",
        "answer": 7.2213285964387905
    },
    {
        "question": "973,054 ÷ 759,586=？",
        "answer": 0.10755999065689459
    },
    {
        "question": "359,548 ÷ 11,501=？",
        "answer": 1.4950212738664674
    },
    {
        "question": "215,712 × 2,244=？",
        "answer": 8.684897158042821
    },
    {
        "question": "303,541,459 ÷ 693,859=？",
        "answer": 2.640946791405864
    },
    {
        "question": "599 × 3,882=？",
        "answer": 6.366482353441655
    },
    {
        "question": "983,499,733 ÷ 7,664=？",
        "answer": 5.108318750282842
    },
    {
        "question": "297 × 19,702=？",
        "answer": 6.76726676405119
    },
    {
        "question": "12,116 × 72,943=？",
        "answer": 8.946342885671113
    },
    {
        "question": "533,963,340 ÷ 427,812=？",
        "answer": 3.0962584787188834
    },
    {
        "question": "16 × 44,241=？",
        "answer": 5.849944917624664
    },
    {
        "question": "2,732,051 × 314=？",
        "answer": 8.933418450261277
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 23,660=？",
        "answer": 5.652768341244741
    },
    {
        "question": "82 × 8,131,534=？",
        "answer": 8.823986334618844
    },
    {
        "question": "674 × 5,666=？",
        "answer": 6.581936466719738
    },
    {
        "question": "93,045 ÷ 404=？",
        "answer": 2.3623116751100426
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 10,557=？",
        "answer": 4.023540521554854
    },
    {
        "question": "38 × 39,428=？",
        "answer": 6.175588344499235
    },
    {
        "question": "62,033 ÷ 13,858=？",
        "answer": 0.650922227745532
    },
    {
        "question": "33,660 ÷ 674=？",
        "answer": 1.6984542151044852
    },
    {
        "question": "8,903 ÷ 4,517=？",
        "answer": 0.29468628281474835
    },
    {
        "question": "14,855,448 ÷ 4,081=？",
        "answer": 3.5611191587069775
    },
    {
        "question": "122,761 ÷ 2,880=？",
        "answer": 1.6296679297385228
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 3,347=？",
        "answer": 4.12671570368574
    },
    {
        "question": "205 × 2,107=？",
        "answer": 5.635418396663854
    },
    {
        "question": "466,360,909 ÷ 21,738=？",
        "answer": 4.331502555709514
    },
    {
        "question": "495,150,783 ÷ 11,897,297=？",
        "answer": 1.6192891668543414
    },
    {
        "question": "3,507 ÷ 970=？",
        "answer": 0.5581640316152577
    },
    {
        "question": "28 × 610=？",
        "answer": 4.232487866352987
    },
    {
        "question": "1,894 × 291=？",
        "answer": 5.741272963653162
    },
    {
        "question": "1,037 ÷ 313=？",
        "answer": 0.5202344188425925
    },
    {
        "question": "300,282,830 ÷ 2,958,912=？",
        "answer": 2.0063984510519677
    },
    {
        "question": "895 × 2,203=？",
        "answer": 6.29483753246668
    },
    {
        "question": "252,905 ÷ 5,603=？",
        "answer": 1.6545367930806485
    },
    {
        "question": "467,510 ÷ 249=？",
        "answer": 3.2735915577349846
    },
    {
        "question": "56,611,833 ÷ 119,287=？",
        "answer": 2.6763141004058135
    },
    {
        "question": "46,704,085 ÷ 19,535=？",
        "answer": 3.378541452486471
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 13,178=？",
        "answer": 4.72190949453948
    },
    {
        "question": "86,104,302 ÷ 470=？",
        "answer": 5.262926992567727
    },
    {
        "question": "65,166,621 ÷ 48,801,501=？",
        "answer": 0.1255920227603725
    },
    {
        "question": "218,895,131 ÷ 12,604,815=？",
        "answer": 1.2396996254847552
    },
    {
        "question": "158 × 12,033=？",
        "answer": 6.2790310036557315
    },
    {
        "question": "48,310 × 259=？",
        "answer": 7.097336801567772
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 12,155,461=？",
        "answer": 7.385801429921871
    },
    {
        "question": "55,673,548 ÷ 1,507,272=？",
        "answer": 1.5674572676845293
    },
    {
        "question": "1,871,582 ÷ 225,657=？",
        "answer": 0.9187600495884662
    },
    {
        "question": "89,490,994 ÷ 2,889=？",
        "answer": 4.491031790087317
    },
    {
        "question": "802 × 206=？",
        "answer": 5.218041588653317
    },
    {
        "question": "18,381 × 18,908=？",
        "answer": 8.541014728682493
    },
    {
        "question": "37,457 ÷ 23,954=？",
        "answer": 0.19415494576917333
    },
    {
        "question": "1,833 × 12,715=？",
        "answer": 7.367478829473944
    },
    {
        "question": "7,741 × 1,926=？",
        "answer": 7.173453350245197
    },
    {
        "question": "841 × 18,014=？",
        "answer": 7.1804061542056505
    },
    {
        "question": "667,787,375 ÷ 88,054,693=？",
        "answer": 0.8798856968851032
    },
    {
        "question": "999,218,348 ÷ 7,593=？",
        "answer": 5.11924700022995
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 5,303,617=？",
        "answer": 6.724572154010528
    },
    {
        "question": "556 × 7,046=？",
        "answer": 6.593017430427281
    },
    {
        "question": "1,171 × 1,415=？",
        "answer": 6.219313334932672
    },
    {
        "question": "215 × 322=？",
        "answer": 4.840294331611436
    },
    {
        "question": "906,573,740 ÷ 6,231=？",
        "answer": 5.16284538378749
    },
    {
        "question": "101,737 ÷ 245=？",
        "answer": 2.61831284273211
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 58,144,490=？",
        "answer": 7.764508565565327
    },
    {
        "question": "7,896,305 ÷ 2,859,126=？",
        "answer": 0.44119062001506054
    },
    {
        "question": "17 × 562,772=？",
        "answer": 6.980781402912842
    },
    {
        "question": "116 × 439=？",
        "answer": 4.70692250946904
    },
    {
        "question": "9,577 × 969=？",
        "answer": 6.967553264470766
    },
    {
        "question": "5,664 × 4,547=？",
        "answer": 7.4108481988868204
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 1,714=？",
        "answer": 3.932980821923198
    },
    {
        "question": "1,460 ÷ 322=？",
        "answer": 0.6564969840886062
    },
    {
        "question": "991,516,307 ÷ 85,413,237=？",
        "answer": 1.0647746801188291
    },
    {
        "question": "598,482,524 ÷ 7,985,965=？",
        "answer": 1.8747240708186443
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 6,404,747=？",
        "answer": 7.408561970268299
    },
    {
        "question": "211,893,026 ÷ 96,627,447=？",
        "answer": 0.3410161579153449
    },
    {
        "question": "762,546,106 ÷ 221,324=？",
        "answer": 3.5372375970200296
    },
    {
        "question": "383,044,356 ÷ 187,496=？",
        "answer": 3.3102570605574884
    },
    {
        "question": "282 × 402,883=？",
        "answer": 8.055428050659447
    },
    {
        "question": "12,035 × 222=？",
        "answer": 6.426799069061688
    },
    {
        "question": "2,306,237 ÷ 2,146,874=？",
        "answer": 0.031097378992484142
    },
    {
        "question": "26,735 × 31,834=？",
        "answer": 8.929971400377603
    },
    {
        "question": "4,614,875 ÷ 1,811=？",
        "answer": 3.4062414917660857
    },
    {
        "question": "2,200,123 ÷ 55,435=？",
        "answer": 1.59866290928848
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 677,061=？",
        "answer": 6.131657793994561
    },
    {
        "question": "27,436 ÷ 405=？",
        "answer": 1.8308657709717806
    },
    {
        "question": "1,298 × 3,509=？",
        "answer": 6.658458060679757
    },
    {
        "question": "119,713,284 ÷ 6,489,662=？",
        "answer": 1.2659202665223794
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 995=？",
        "answer": 3.298853076409707
    },
    {
        "question": "2,393,406 ÷ 22,595=？",
        "answer": 2.025004029755111
    },
    {
        "question": "1,026 ÷ 456=？",
        "answer": 0.3521825181113625
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 12,546,092=？",
        "answer": 8.098508467877375
    },
    {
        "question": "281 × 754,592=？",
        "answer": 8.326418516510486
    },
    {
        "question": "47,271,321 ÷ 39,922,047=？",
        "answer": 0.07338493725513275
    },
    {
        "question": "52 × 81,940=？",
        "answer": 6.629499303251922
    },
    {
        "question": "119,141,364 ÷ 10,873,536=？",
        "answer": 1.0396917711801057
    },
    {
        "question": "46,181,793 ÷ 225,621=？",
        "answer": 2.311091270537524
    },
    {
        "question": "6,342,639 ÷ 690,624=？",
        "answer": 0.9630283271125832
    },
    {
        "question": "310,398,282 ÷ 196,551=？",
        "answer": 3.1984440511108003
    },
    {
        "question": "30,090 × 11,185=？",
        "answer": 8.527058176172728
    },
    {
        "question": "26,963,265 ÷ 391=？",
        "answer": 4.838595722664314
    },
    {
        "question": "362,356,866 ÷ 246,856,578=？",
        "answer": 0.1666917904412764
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 10,754=？",
        "answer": 4.934660019133044
    },
    {
        "question": "143,252 × 216=？",
        "answer": 7.490554445196295
    },
    {
        "question": "8,695,270 ÷ 288=？",
        "answer": 4.479890584225223
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 611=？",
        "answer": 2.786041210242554
    },
    {
        "question": "1,870 ÷ 590=？",
        "answer": 0.5009895948943548
    },
    {
        "question": "33,908,810 ÷ 9,570,341=？",
        "answer": 0.5493851364988998
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 3,240,587=？",
        "answer": 8.474411512789942
    },
    {
        "question": "42,319 ÷ 741=？",
        "answer": 1.7567171887696098
    },
    {
        "question": "204,819,319 ÷ 748,240=？",
        "answer": 2.437329996490818
    },
    {
        "question": "50,324 × 9,856=？",
        "answer": 8.695475848499337
    },
    {
        "question": "8,063,433 ÷ 2,191,946=？",
        "answer": 0.565690130876964
    },
    {
        "question": "12 × 30,339=？",
        "answer": 5.561182508007922
    },
    {
        "question": "67,238,608 ÷ 59,074=？",
        "answer": 3.0562223352620346
    },
    {
        "question": "2,211,336 ÷ 491,298=？",
        "answer": 0.6533097399919514
    },
    {
        "question": "509 × 43,126=？",
        "answer": 7.341456960898013
    },
    {
        "question": "37 × 1,801,599=？",
        "answer": 7.823859856177744
    },
    {
        "question": "19,683 × 17,376=？",
        "answer": 8.534041100385714
    },
    {
        "question": "3,062,016 ÷ 528=？",
        "answer": 3.7633735331600944
    },
    {
        "question": "1,749,283 × 342=？",
        "answer": 8.776886181627432
    },
    {
        "question": "3,307 ÷ 478=？",
        "answer": 0.840006298301584
    },
    {
        "question": "698 × 2,381=？",
        "answer": 6.220614818028041
    },
    {
        "question": "161 × 1,501=？",
        "answer": 5.38320656827512
    },
    {
        "question": "1,038,745 ÷ 670,071=？",
        "answer": 0.1903881238067423
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 3,674,150=？",
        "answer": 8.177940739457759
    },
    {
        "question": "785,573 ÷ 298,465=？",
        "answer": 0.4202931382349719
    },
    {
        "question": "369 × 230=？",
        "answer": 4.928754202176653
    },
    {
        "question": "990,032 ÷ 46,883=？",
        "answer": 1.3246338381689153
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 3,947,891=？",
        "answer": 7.073486408151908
    },
    {
        "question": "36,158 × 3,714=？",
        "answer": 8.12804629983028
    },
    {
        "question": "24,934 ÷ 1,933=？",
        "answer": 1.1105601011129285
    },
    {
        "question": "36,824 ÷ 436=？",
        "answer": 1.9266444726173317
    },
    {
        "question": "173,138,437 ÷ 8,220=？",
        "answer": 4.323521675083642
    },
    {
        "question": "43,841,723 ÷ 512,838=？",
        "answer": 1.9319074159589837
    },
    {
        "question": "779,908,981 ÷ 437=？",
        "answer": 6.251562484494455
    },
    {
        "question": "6,498 × 396=？",
        "answer": 6.410474892934476
    },
    {
        "question": "206 × 286,089=？",
        "answer": 7.770368380057879
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 128,297=？",
        "answer": 6.222159853586844
    },
    {
        "question": "1,709 × 262,344=？",
        "answer": 8.65161319873484
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 29,762=？",
        "answer": 5.0757221036782365
    },
    {
        "question": "214,722 ÷ 39,403=？",
        "answer": 0.7363472550124579
    },
    {
        "question": "48,813 × 4,070=？",
        "answer": 8.298129909022858
    },
    {
        "question": "54 × 1,445=？",
        "answer": 4.892261606915535
    },
    {
        "question": "857,008,876 ÷ 383,886,435=？",
        "answer": 0.3487825537424559
    },
    {
        "question": "257 × 1,840=？",
        "answer": 5.674750946340831
    },
    {
        "question": "16,825,092 ÷ 821=？",
        "answer": 4.311614290515539
    },
    {
        "question": "77,141 × 1,095=？",
        "answer": 7.926699383621469
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 70,270=？",
        "answer": 4.846769953537219
    },
    {
        "question": "60,442,079 ÷ 2,047=？",
        "answer": 4.470221551500502
    },
    {
        "question": "282,449 × 322=？",
        "answer": 7.958795913167714
    },
    {
        "question": "931,646,879 ÷ 419,403=？",
        "answer": 3.3466198007655272
    },
    {
        "question": "2,877 × 534=？",
        "answer": 6.186481118918882
    },
    {
        "question": "242 × 562=？",
        "answer": 5.133551681549492
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 613,437=？",
        "answer": 6.0887999629596425
    },
    {
        "question": "507,039,906 ÷ 347,251,074=？",
        "answer": 0.16439854370742205
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 423=？",
        "answer": 2.9273703630390235
    },
    {
        "question": "4,232,717 ÷ 1,204,198=？",
        "answer": 0.5459213308891251
    },
    {
        "question": "46,431,953 ÷ 14,526=？",
        "answer": 3.5046709113248613
    },
    {
        "question": "24,575 ÷ 1,170=？",
        "answer": 1.3223076647580116
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 11,739,980=？",
        "answer": 7.069667357056653
    },
    {
        "question": "1,262,457 ÷ 19,159=？",
        "answer": 1.8188437573023557
    },
    {
        "question": "50,909 ÷ 348=？",
        "answer": 2.1652153223748414
    },
    {
        "question": "67 × 1,908=？",
        "answer": 5.106653173068903
    },
    {
        "question": "495,725,813 ÷ 2,268,273=？",
        "answer": 2.3395462104330145
    },
    {
        "question": "743,292,390 ÷ 411=？",
        "answer": 6.257317864541941
    },
    {
        "question": "2,063 × 8,983=？",
        "answer": 7.267920627654187
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 395=？",
        "answer": 2.59659709562646
    },
    {
        "question": "13 × 27,478=？",
        "answer": 5.552928471503178
    },
    {
        "question": "40,895,007 ÷ 6,454,465=？",
        "answer": 0.8018100367269425
    },
    {
        "question": "14,788,635 ÷ 1,471=？",
        "answer": 4.002315417474541
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 904=？",
        "answer": 3.5582284218033258
    },
    {
        "question": "30,863,895 ÷ 93,974=？",
        "answer": 2.5164430198399055
    },
    {
        "question": "123,977,567 ÷ 50,318,738=？",
        "answer": 0.3916133688633201
    },
    {
        "question": "89 × 1,104,873=？",
        "answer": 7.992702367409021
    },
    {
        "question": "129,235,283 ÷ 1,153,217=？",
        "answer": 2.0494700623218693
    },
    {
        "question": "177 × 1,402,488=？",
        "answer": 8.394872420385493
    },
    {
        "question": "5,198,031 ÷ 543,481=？",
        "answer": 0.9806544993875682
    },
    {
        "question": "2,545,339 ÷ 34,259=？",
        "answer": 1.8709709498543976
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 5,117,094=？",
        "answer": 7.186144649668394
    },
    {
        "question": "7,973,985 ÷ 1,490=？",
        "answer": 3.7284891459560687
    },
    {
        "question": "715,254,025 ÷ 25,496,513=？",
        "answer": 1.4479795216889018
    },
    {
        "question": "134,924 × 1,107=？",
        "answer": 8.174236828819671
    },
    {
        "question": "396 × 2,050,601=？",
        "answer": 8.909576350752344
    },
    {
        "question": "13,619 × 11,890=？",
        "answer": 8.209327074498987
    },
    {
        "question": "92 × 3,821=？",
        "answer": 5.545964865033964
    },
    {
        "question": "259 × 401,296=？",
        "answer": 8.016764594917545
    },
    {
        "question": "170,998 ÷ 28,422=？",
        "answer": 0.7793363957832242
    },
    {
        "question": "1,896 × 501=？",
        "answer": 5.977676058869293
    },
    {
        "question": "712 × 4,555=？",
        "answer": 6.5109683749458735
    },
    {
        "question": "5 × 2,012,303=？",
        "answer": 7.002663378990499
    },
    {
        "question": "65,528 ÷ 4,609=？",
        "answer": 1.1528202048000464
    },
    {
        "question": "5,051,520 ÷ 643=？",
        "answer": 3.8952111038650306
    },
    {
        "question": "30 × 4,865,580=？",
        "answer": 8.164255872352939
    },
    {
        "question": "227 × 470,504=？",
        "answer": 8.028589177136087
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 17,171=？",
        "answer": 4.234795588220643
    },
    {
        "question": "468,302 ÷ 12,695=？",
        "answer": 1.5668933073387472
    },
    {
        "question": "4,439 ÷ 2,290=？",
        "answer": 0.28744966268547867
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 254=？",
        "answer": 3.249931756634195
    },
    {
        "question": "159,786 ÷ 8,151=？",
        "answer": 1.2923278318460483
    },
    {
        "question": "81,897 × 376=？",
        "answer": 7.488455838173933
    },
    {
        "question": "214,910,113 ÷ 46,141,238=？",
        "answer": 0.6681676097666166
    },
    {
        "question": "45,006 × 2,591=？",
        "answer": 8.066737828832037
    },
    {
        "question": "679,590 ÷ 18,162=？",
        "answer": 1.5730833083671334
    },
    {
        "question": "408,514,346 ÷ 2,405,306=？",
        "answer": 2.230036977848382
    },
    {
        "question": "623,232,694 ÷ 9,401,925=？",
        "answer": 1.8214334453421475
    },
    {
        "question": "6,722,320 ÷ 37,856=？",
        "answer": 2.2493844592300123
    },
    {
        "question": "294,740,871 ÷ 56,513=？",
        "answer": 3.717292000096458
    },
    {
        "question": "1,829 × 7,125=？",
        "answer": 7.114998574156965
    },
    {
        "question": "43,140,748 ÷ 479=？",
        "answer": 4.954552157473803
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 1,199,966=？",
        "answer": 6.982258927854923
    },
    {
        "question": "418,760,042 ÷ 31,519=？",
        "answer": 4.1233928044699075
    },
    {
        "question": "57,178 ÷ 6,064=？",
        "answer": 0.9744697676992217
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 5,360,141=？",
        "answer": 7.57427425409444
    },
    {
        "question": "45,587,991 ÷ 3,203=？",
        "answer": 4.153293515199936
    },
    {
        "question": "252,357 ÷ 290=？",
        "answer": 2.939617358007323
    },
    {
        "question": "2,695 × 48,021=？",
        "answer": 8.111989969182957
    },
    {
        "question": "17,216 ÷ 9,434=？",
        "answer": 0.2612363820766121
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 244=？",
        "answer": 2.864511081058392
    },
    {
        "question": "4,924 × 188,241=？",
        "answer": 8.967032265552872
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 454,044=？",
        "answer": 6.979317235765646
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 74,955,040=？",
        "answer": 8.35192209498065
    },
    {
        "question": "189 × 4,569,848=？",
        "answer": 8.936363559197344
    },
    {
        "question": "59 × 1,749,136=？",
        "answer": 8.013675589990624
    },
    {
        "question": "6,097,741 ÷ 163,484=？",
        "answer": 1.571693718722453
    },
    {
        "question": "1,319,994 × 284=？",
        "answer": 8.573890297182574
    },
    {
        "question": "1,938 × 4,031=？",
        "answer": 6.892766570867797
    },
    {
        "question": "115,010 ÷ 803=？",
        "answer": 2.1560200581706375
    },
    {
        "question": "1,129 ÷ 675=？",
        "answer": 0.22339016909394294
    },
    {
        "question": "1,245,204 ÷ 148,024=？",
        "answer": 0.9249083712902129
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 56,363=？",
        "answer": 4.750994100987553
    },
    {
        "question": "74 × 111,057=？",
        "answer": 6.914777657361644
    },
    {
        "question": "174,521 ÷ 2,630=？",
        "answer": 1.8218919443262718
    },
    {
        "question": "93 × 1,143=？",
        "answer": 5.026529178949217
    },
    {
        "question": "492,912 ÷ 43,227=？",
        "answer": 1.0570142951548398
    },
    {
        "question": "671,569,308 ÷ 268=？",
        "answer": 6.398956045803478
    },
    {
        "question": "355,811,660 ÷ 1,100=？",
        "answer": 5.509827490716399
    },
    {
        "question": "81,782 ÷ 8,779=？",
        "answer": 0.969212678107238
    },
    {
        "question": "12,297,070 ÷ 3,688=？",
        "answer": 3.5230107328451234
    },
    {
        "question": "7 × 3,937,253=？",
        "answer": 7.440291362595603
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 101,974=？",
        "answer": 5.00848945513538
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 302=？",
        "answer": 3.7352794480604565
    },
    {
        "question": "617,986 ÷ 83,731=？",
        "answer": 0.8680923585693311
    },
    {
        "question": "954,360,572 ÷ 296=？",
        "answer": 6.508420777737734
    },
    {
        "question": "310 × 986,578=？",
        "answer": 8.485493120604902
    },
    {
        "question": "51 × 1,057=？",
        "answer": 4.7316451634053625
    },
    {
        "question": "328 × 249,434=？",
        "answer": 7.912829494963152
    },
    {
        "question": "141,532,710 ÷ 132,593,548=？",
        "answer": 0.028334430590092344
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 173,169=？",
        "answer": 6.01662139941645
    },
    {
        "question": "36,208,825 ÷ 10,944=？",
        "answer": 3.519638347530287
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 4,155=？",
        "answer": 4.095692282839792
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 432,352=？",
        "answer": 5.93686746796592
    },
    {
        "question": "1,276 × 1,085=？",
        "answer": 6.141280412569692
    },
    {
        "question": "6 × 579=？",
        "answer": 3.54082981411108
    },
    {
        "question": "33,508,329 ÷ 1,350,465=？",
        "answer": 1.3946694378321707
    },
    {
        "question": "40 × 74,435=？",
        "answer": 6.473837184033068
    },
    {
        "question": "4,167,109 ÷ 1,242=？",
        "answer": 3.525713264702967
    },
    {
        "question": "31,660 ÷ 1,507=？",
        "answer": 1.3223976582117054
    },
    {
        "question": "5,013,360 ÷ 22,889=？",
        "answer": 2.3405020724564967
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 103,514=？",
        "answer": 6.337218385701423
    },
    {
        "question": "1,784,675 × 228=？",
        "answer": 8.609493987024253
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 204,912=？",
        "answer": 5.311567392179534
    },
    {
        "question": "79 × 3,723=？",
        "answer": 5.4685201275088335
    },
    {
        "question": "360,891 ÷ 1,998=？",
        "answer": 2.256780567748169
    },
    {
        "question": "15,714,965 ÷ 648,813=？",
        "answer": 1.3841938750335268
    },
    {
        "question": "3 × 7,251=？",
        "answer": 4.337519159846975
    },
    {
        "question": "10 × 1,974,306=？",
        "answer": 7.295414465361087
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 395=？",
        "answer": 3.550839605065785
    },
    {
        "question": "8 × 15,036,355=？",
        "answer": 8.080232557606548
    },
    {
        "question": "8,411 ÷ 937=？",
        "answer": 0.9531080420877589
    },
    {
        "question": "40,481,697 ÷ 81,201=？",
        "answer": 2.697697332253481
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 231=？",
        "answer": 2.3636119798921444
    },
    {
        "question": "40,341,628 ÷ 27,356=？",
        "answer": 3.168700825269649
    },
    {
        "question": "23 × 4,712,085=？",
        "answer": 8.03494095198552
    },
    {
        "question": "142,490 ÷ 18,859=？",
        "answer": 0.8782657259575591
    },
    {
        "question": "14,569 ÷ 3,048=？",
        "answer": 0.6794147806339093
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 550=？",
        "answer": 2.7403626894942437
    },
    {
        "question": "1,319,332 ÷ 59,419=？",
        "answer": 1.3464287577353948
    },
    {
        "question": "2,041 × 1,122=？",
        "answer": 6.359835861636213
    },
    {
        "question": "22 × 393,894=？",
        "answer": 6.937802046280402
    },
    {
        "question": "180 × 31,527=？",
        "answer": 6.753955151860323
    },
    {
        "question": "589 ÷ 458=？",
        "answer": 0.10924981678323246
    },
    {
        "question": "34 × 54,589=？",
        "answer": 6.268584055706895
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 212,476=？",
        "answer": 6.368702567044759
    },
    {
        "question": "15 × 1,784,758=？",
        "answer": 7.427670596372442
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 268=？",
        "answer": 3.683407299132095
    },
    {
        "question": "36,340,892 ÷ 7,899=？",
        "answer": 3.6628234691882082
    },
    {
        "question": "33,118 × 11,171=？",
        "answer": 8.568156153621157
    },
    {
        "question": "826,547 × 445=？",
        "answer": 8.565627564908118
    },
    {
        "question": "76,933 ÷ 59,721=？",
        "answer": 0.10998559689779276
    },
    {
        "question": "1,136 × 330=？",
        "answer": 5.5738922712528876
    },
    {
        "question": "4,028,206 ÷ 52,437=？",
        "answer": 1.8854738349193643
    },
    {
        "question": "88,347,476 ÷ 18,929,996=？",
        "answer": 0.6690436244609738
    },
    {
        "question": "252,098,897 ÷ 1,076,558=？",
        "answer": 2.3695335129446446
    },
    {
        "question": "151,791,022 ÷ 174,189=？",
        "answer": 2.9402253591272167
    },
    {
        "question": "2,271,941 ÷ 182,721=？",
        "answer": 1.0946085856090477
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 373,375,094=？",
        "answer": 8.572145344949114
    },
    {
        "question": "66,972 ÷ 4,492=？",
        "answer": 1.173453520974865
    },
    {
        "question": "588,033,022 ÷ 1,865=？",
        "answer": 5.498722879165607
    },
    {
        "question": "25,033,043 ÷ 707=？",
        "answer": 4.549094231567669
    },
    {
        "question": "141,853 ÷ 39,700=？",
        "answer": 0.5530480182095632
    },
    {
        "question": "9 × 15,494=？",
        "answer": 5.14440606107003
    },
    {
        "question": "5,258,110 ÷ 7,425=？",
        "answer": 2.850133209344674
    },
    {
        "question": "39,376,288 ÷ 18,434=？",
        "answer": 3.329615189666479
    },
    {
        "question": "320 × 265,578=？",
        "answer": 7.929342074338443
    },
    {
        "question": "1,194 × 250=？",
        "answer": 5.474944335465388
    },
    {
        "question": "337,672 ÷ 41,652=？",
        "answer": 0.9088591904051297
    },
    {
        "question": "250,887 ÷ 210,382=？",
        "answer": 0.07646957900544894
    },
    {
        "question": "258 × 242,476=？",
        "answer": 7.7962884650525215
    },
    {
        "question": "78,178,155 ÷ 14,410,700=？",
        "answer": 0.7344003397038712
    },
    {
        "question": "8,893 ÷ 855=？",
        "answer": 1.0170821775874912
    },
    {
        "question": "261 × 55,824=？",
        "answer": 7.163461459442317
    },
    {
        "question": "32,740 × 976=？",
        "answer": 7.504528492742614
    },
    {
        "question": "35,627,097 ÷ 10,134=？",
        "answer": 3.5459995362542176
    },
    {
        "question": "170 × 1,094=？",
        "answer": 5.269466243375686
    },
    {
        "question": "152,480 × 1,341=？",
        "answer": 8.31064166114585
    },
    {
        "question": "13,492,673 ÷ 830=？",
        "answer": 4.211019902822448
    },
    {
        "question": "326 × 642,006=？",
        "answer": 8.32075668694476
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 110,744,783=？",
        "answer": 8.044323276496206
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 26,412=？",
        "answer": 4.722831284264954
    },
    {
        "question": "4,320,611 ÷ 874=？",
        "answer": 3.694033734357597
    },
    {
        "question": "109,139 × 1,181=？",
        "answer": 8.11022986780032
    },
    {
        "question": "83,317,003 ÷ 1,361,643=？",
        "answer": 1.7866703817705405
    },
    {
        "question": "136,163,834 ÷ 29,541,693=？",
        "answer": 0.6636263908540041
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 150,163=？",
        "answer": 6.789346792880914
    },
    {
        "question": "913 × 687,559=？",
        "answer": 8.797780748800264
    },
    {
        "question": "5,097,547 ÷ 303,490=？",
        "answer": 1.2252168530788876
    },
    {
        "question": "124,152,309 ÷ 1,189=？",
        "answer": 5.018772946409497
    },
    {
        "question": "21,427 ÷ 720=？",
        "answer": 1.473628873180323
    },
    {
        "question": "19 × 6,675,236=？",
        "answer": 8.103220225549128
    },
    {
        "question": "926 × 311,584=？",
        "answer": 8.460186135008144
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 7,544,872=？",
        "answer": 6.877651876296469
    },
    {
        "question": "36,598,738 ÷ 23,919=？",
        "answer": 3.184723091469765
    },
    {
        "question": "139 × 522=？",
        "answer": 4.860685303256357
    },
    {
        "question": "505,053,142 ÷ 13,784=？",
        "answer": 4.563961812813554
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 566=？",
        "answer": 3.0538464268522527
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 66,448=？",
        "answer": 4.822481913765803
    },
    {
        "question": "2,936 × 25,142=？",
        "answer": 7.8681558732978525
    },
    {
        "question": "86,660,126 ÷ 294,152=？",
        "answer": 2.4692475105527447
    },
    {
        "question": "64,848 × 259=？",
        "answer": 7.225196350478869
    },
    {
        "question": "2 × 31,834=？",
        "answer": 4.803921207605225
    },
    {
        "question": "35 × 213=？",
        "answer": 3.8724476477890133
    },
    {
        "question": "152 × 26,287=？",
        "answer": 6.601584613085423
    },
    {
        "question": "8,018,805 ÷ 667,488=？",
        "answer": 1.079666190076621
    },
    {
        "question": "3,225 ÷ 770=？",
        "answer": 0.6220389937988047
    },
    {
        "question": "828 × 1,774=？",
        "answer": 6.166983952280588
    },
    {
        "question": "92,575 ÷ 14,800=？",
        "answer": 0.7962320053265228
    },
    {
        "question": "329 × 278,086=？",
        "answer": 7.9613750231830895
    },
    {
        "question": "10,419,463 ÷ 7,391=？",
        "answer": 3.1491421345212025
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 9,164,671=？",
        "answer": 6.9621168789600825
    },
    {
        "question": "13,584,620 ÷ 2,184,567=？",
        "answer": 0.7936821255581753
    },
    {
        "question": "257 × 2,572,593=？",
        "answer": 8.820304206923884
    },
    {
        "question": "7,305,348 ÷ 413=？",
        "answer": 4.247690857303839
    },
    {
        "question": "29,837 × 1,473=？",
        "answer": 7.642957901134429
    },
    {
        "question": "106,068,791 ÷ 1,282,475=？",
        "answer": 1.9175387107550965
    },
    {
        "question": "24 × 354=？",
        "answer": 3.929214503737394
    },
    {
        "question": "36,029,418 ÷ 8,893,762=？",
        "answer": 0.6075717434127659
    },
    {
        "question": "474,901,030 ÷ 18,709,807=？",
        "answer": 1.4045338039306683
    },
    {
        "question": "2,642,950 ÷ 16,324=？",
        "answer": 2.2092623610147766
    },
    {
        "question": "4,339 × 7,268=？",
        "answer": 7.498804568765209
    },
    {
        "question": "39 × 8,307,516=？",
        "answer": 8.510535793414807
    },
    {
        "question": "102 × 259=？",
        "answer": 4.421899935843169
    },
    {
        "question": "3,899 × 10,842=？",
        "answer": 7.626062638132561
    },
    {
        "question": "649,810,507 ÷ 23,358,713=？",
        "answer": 1.4443378186324916
    },
    {
        "question": "42,964 ÷ 26,375=？",
        "answer": 0.21191223960591832
    },
    {
        "question": "23,932,876 ÷ 69,535=？",
        "answer": 2.5367914316793794
    },
    {
        "question": "19,688 × 653=？",
        "answer": 7.10911478196982
    },
    {
        "question": "1,817,844 ÷ 11,454=？",
        "answer": 2.2005994323165003
    },
    {
        "question": "4,531,599 ÷ 15,213=？",
        "answer": 2.474036607019951
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 762,562=？",
        "answer": 5.882275159708306
    },
    {
        "question": "24,252,640 ÷ 116,497=？",
        "answer": 2.3184442785898445
    },
    {
        "question": "611 × 680=？",
        "answer": 5.618550122948791
    },
    {
        "question": "1,761 × 1,156=？",
        "answer": 6.308717190051787
    },
    {
        "question": "20,624 × 11,244=？",
        "answer": 8.36529373694473
    },
    {
        "question": "7,376,163 ÷ 57,876=？",
        "answer": 2.1053319973128306
    },
    {
        "question": "112 × 7,502,602=？",
        "answer": 8.924429931163743
    },
    {
        "question": "162,989,375 ÷ 11,644=？",
        "answer": 4.1460570976416715
    },
    {
        "question": "206 × 587=？",
        "answer": 5.082505321616768
    },
    {
        "question": "121,989 ÷ 905=？",
        "answer": 2.129672092004945
    },
    {
        "question": "11 × 29,990=？",
        "answer": 5.518369150917752
    },
    {
        "question": "18 × 28,620=？",
        "answer": 5.711942134527064
    },
    {
        "question": "4,673,113 ÷ 423=？",
        "answer": 4.043265915400418
    },
    {
        "question": "21,937 × 20,652=？",
        "answer": 8.65613935162255
    },
    {
        "question": "711,060 ÷ 323=？",
        "answer": 3.3427037261757326
    },
    {
        "question": "4,066,749 ÷ 32,635=？",
        "answer": 2.095563751517447
    },
    {
        "question": "164,647 ÷ 8,635=？",
        "answer": 1.2802914800237966
    },
    {
        "question": "821 × 1,015=？",
        "answer": 5.920809199368673
    },
    {
        "question": "140,422 × 1,787=？",
        "answer": 8.399559706810184
    },
    {
        "question": "2,285 × 423=？",
        "answer": 5.985226571780911
    },
    {
        "question": "130 × 210,755=？",
        "answer": 7.437721239027821
    },
    {
        "question": "64,857 × 653=？",
        "answer": 7.626870037521092
    },
    {
        "question": "283,226,172 ÷ 94,470=？",
        "answer": 3.476839467242035
    },
    {
        "question": "14 × 16,539=？",
        "answer": 5.36463728287717
    },
    {
        "question": "1 × 10,635,049=？",
        "answer": 7.026739495214826
    },
    {
        "question": "55,273 × 1,000=？",
        "answer": 7.742513037009627
    },
    {
        "question": "41 × 866=？",
        "answer": 4.550301748737082
    },
    {
        "question": "69 × 260,347=？",
        "answer": 7.2544016683665875
    },
    {
        "question": "1,625 × 1,899=？",
        "answer": 6.489378330051911
    },
    {
        "question": "5,555,218 ÷ 21,573=？",
        "answer": 2.410790562889303
    },
    {
        "question": "3,068 × 23,770=？",
        "answer": 7.862884537005123
    },
    {
        "question": "627,249,516 ÷ 669,761=？",
        "answer": 2.9715204797841706
    },
    {
        "question": "21 × 212=？",
        "answer": 3.6485551556626707
    },
    {
        "question": "233,148 ÷ 4,806=？",
        "answer": 1.6858479278553797
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 2,493,664=？",
        "answer": 6.998897926927417
    },
    {
        "question": "4 × 233,020=？",
        "answer": 5.969453189250438
    }
]